<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sign in and registration on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/sign-in-and-registration/</link><description>Recent content in sign in and registration on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/sign-in-and-registration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chroma-Hash Password Masking</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/chroma-hash-password-masking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/chroma-hash-password-masking/</guid><description>Chroma-Hash is a jQuery script that Mattt Thompson created to explore a visual method for confirmation password matches during confirmation on login and registration forms. The idea is similar to Identicon, but uses a small colored bars in the input to visually check your strings. He describes the project on Mattt.com and you can try the demo out on GitHub or download it. Versions supporting other libraries are also linked from this page.</description></item><item><title>Confirming Passwords Is Annoying: Is There a Better Way?</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/confirming-passwords-annoying-there-better-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/confirming-passwords-annoying-there-better-way/</guid><description>This an article from March 09 by Kevin Vigneault of Viget that explores some techniques using Javascript to create more usable password inputs in forms. The ideas range from using a checkbox or button to temporarily show the password or changing type from text to password when the input is not in focus. Great ideas.
If you're interested in this topic, you might also want to check out Chris Dary's experiments with password masking.</description></item><item><title>iPhone-like Passwords using jQuery</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-passwords-using-jquery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-passwords-using-jquery/</guid><description>Stefan Ullrich's jQuery plugin on the DECAF site provides a behavior for masking passwords that is familiar to mobile users. The plugin obscures previously entered characters at delayed intervals or when new characters are entered. It falls back on using the browser's password masking when JS is disabled.
http://blog.decaf.de/2009/07/iphone-like-password-fields-using-jquery/</description></item><item><title>Log in or sign up?</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</guid><description>Leah Culver discusses the design of hybrid sign up / login forms, showing a few examples and the final form as implemented for Leafy Chat. Uses the familiar I'm a customer/I'm new here radios that we know from Amazon, but positions it before the password field, which I find an improvement over the Amazon implementation. Lots of ideas in the comments.
http://blog.leahculver.com/2009/11/log-in-or-sign-up.html</description></item><item><title>Designing For Sign Up</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-sign/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-sign/</guid><description>View more presentations from Joshua Porter. Joshua Porter's "Designing for Sign Up" presentation from Webstock, 2009, does a great job of focusing the task of sign up on user motivation and anxiety, and thinking through scenarios that help remove barriers to entry. As he says, the form itself is the least of your concerns. Porter describes the entire experience leading up to the call to action, providing excellent examples that ease users into sign up.</description></item><item><title>12 Excellent Examples of Lazy Registration</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/12-excellent-examples-lazy-registration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/12-excellent-examples-lazy-registration/</guid><description>This is a short entry about sites that use "Lazy Registration," or registration/sign up processes that often don't require any information from the user while they try out a site, until they decide to commit to using it. In some cases, sites bypass signup altogether, and in others, users are permitted to register once they've decided to go beyond simply "testing out" a site or application. As noted, the process of "</description></item><item><title>Account Sign-in: 8 Design Mistakes to Avoid</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/account-sign-8-design-mistakes-avoid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/account-sign-8-design-mistakes-avoid/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I don't want to develop a relationship with these guys. I just want to buy something.&amp;quot; That's what some of your customers are saying when you ask them to register or sign in, and some of them will walk away with their dollars if you frustrate them enough. UIE rounds up the most common mistakes they observe from watching users in testing sessions try to sign in to user accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>