<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mobile devices on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/mobile-devices/</link><description>Recent content in mobile devices on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/mobile-devices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Principle for Mac: Animation and Prototyping</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</guid><description>Principle for Mac ($99) is a tool for designing animation, primarily for mobile devices. It provides an easy to use interface for prototyping interaction, transitions, or other animated elements in your interface.
You can design with text, rectangles (which can modified with border radius to make circles), or graphics created with other tools, and then hook up animations for actions like taps, scrolling, and drag, and use the drivers UI to connect those actions to drive other properties.</description></item><item><title>PAPERPROTO</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/paperproto/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/paperproto/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://paperproto.com/">PAPERPROTO&lt;/a> is a 3D printable model to use for paper prototyping mobile applications, in the style of a &lt;a href="http://lifestyle.howstuffworks.com/crafts/seasonal/winter/theatre-activities-for-kids7.htm" target="_blank">story scroll&lt;/a>. You can download the file or buy the model for printing on demand directly from Shapeways.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pinterest Mobile Radial Menus</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-mobile-radial-menus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-mobile-radial-menus/</guid><description>&lt;p>Pinterest's mobile app displays a radial menu if you tap on an image. The menu items are for functions that are also available using the icons and buttons in the top of the UI for allowing you to pin, like, or send the image.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Tumblr Fave Animation</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</guid><description>This is a small animation of the heart/broken heart that is shown when favoriting or unfaving a Tumblr post in the mobile app.
Screencast / Video https://www.tumblr.com/</description></item><item><title>Cloudwash: Washing machine prototype by Berg</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/cloudwash-washing-machine-prototype-berg/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cloudwash-washing-machine-prototype-berg/</guid><description>I love Berg's demo of their Cloudwash smart washing machine concept. The company created the prototype to demonstrate how a smart networked appliance might be better designed. The video provides an excellent walkthrough of their design process.
They simplify the face, which consisted of many controls for dedicated functions, reducing that to "high value functions" only. More functionality is accessible via a smart phone app, which also integrates the device with services such as warranty and supplies management and purchasing.</description></item><item><title>Origami: Design prototyping with Quartz Composer</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/origami-design-prototyping-quartz-composer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/origami-design-prototyping-quartz-composer/</guid><description>Origami is a free toolkit created by the Facebook Design team for Quartz Composer, the visual programming tool that's available with the Apple XCode development environment. Origami provides patches that can be added to your Quartz Composer library, to create interactive prototypes without programming. Quartz composer's UI allows you connect patches with wires (or tubes, if you're familiar with that metaphor) to perform tasks or set behaviors and properties.
Jay Thrash's video explains how to use it.</description></item><item><title>Precomposed Touch Gestures</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</guid><description>Aureus Wade's Precomposed Touch Gestures are a set of touch-device gestures available as QuickTime animations for use in product demos or presentations. They'll work in your video editor, and Photoshop.
http://areuswade.com/precomposed-touch-gestures/</description></item><item><title>Tapotype Transition Library</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/tapotype-transition-library/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/tapotype-transition-library/</guid><description>Tapotype is a reference library of transitions for mobile prototypes created by Gene Lu using Fireworks and the TAP platform, a framework for iOS prototyping developed by UNITiD. Gene provides tutorials on building prototypes with Tapotype and TAP, and shows how to integrate InDesign and its documenting capabilities into your Fireworks/Tap prototyping workflow.
http://tapotype.com/</description></item><item><title>Buxton Collection</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</guid><description>Bill Buxton has been collecting input and interactive devices whose design struck him as interesting, useful, or important. In the process, he has assembled a great collection spanning over 30 years of the history of pen computing, pointing devices, touch technologies, as well as an illustration of the nature of how new technologies emerge.
The collection can be browsed in HTML or via the PivotViewer Silverlight interface. PivotViewer provides a richer experience with faceted filtering, search, and hypertext links for metadata.</description></item><item><title>Adobe Shadow Mobile Device Testing</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/adobe-shadow-mobile-device-testing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/adobe-shadow-mobile-device-testing/</guid><description>Adobe Labs' Shadow is an application for Mac and Windows that allows you to preview and inspect your mobile website on iOS and Android devices.
After installing the software on your computer and any number of mobile devices, you can connect and pair them and all devices will be kept in sync with the web site you're previewing on your computer. This should help perform remote inspection and debugging so you can see HTML/CSS/JavaScript changes instantly on your devices.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Tappy: Video rig for tablets and mobile devices</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/mr-tappy-video-rig-tablets-and-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/mr-tappy-video-rig-tablets-and-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Mr Tappy is a kit for filming mobile phones, tablet computers and handheld devices from the user's point of view. Looks like a great alternative to setting up your own DIY rig, and costs $289.
Originally designed by Nick Bowmast as a filming rig for iPad usability testing, Mr Tappy lets you capture or share user interaction with mobile devices during user experience research, product demonstrations or classroom presentations. Attach your webcam and any type of mobile device, set the camera height and angle, and record.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Design Pattern Gallery</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</guid><description>Theresa Neil's forthcoming book, Mobile Design Pattern Gallery, is set to be released by O'Reilly in the Fall of 2011.
Theresa launched a site to go along with the book that includes a fantastic gallery of 70 user interface design patterns for mobile devices with 400+ supporting examples from iOS, Android, BlackBerry, WebOS, Windows Mobile, and Symbian applications. The gallery covers a broad range of problems from designing your application's navigation to choosing the right invitation technique.</description></item><item><title>Project Rimino, The Future of Mobile Experience</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/project-rimino-future-mobile-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/project-rimino-future-mobile-experience/</guid><description>Project Rimino is an interaction design project proposing a hypothetical e-paper mobile device. The project was created by Amid Moradganjeh, an interaction design student from Umea Institute of Design in Sweden, for his masters degree project on mobile experience design. The design is based on both observational and experimental design research methods. Watch the video below for the concept.
Some of the ideas are pretty exciting. I particularly like the emphasis on everyday tasks, utilizing the materials of the device to create minimal, task-focussed interfaces.</description></item><item><title>Read &amp;amp;quot;Mobile Design &amp; Development&amp;amp;quot; free online</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/read-mobile-design-development-free-online/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/read-mobile-design-development-free-online/</guid><description>Brian Fling's book, Mobile Design &amp; Development, published by O'Reilly in 2009, is available to read in its entirety online. Fling says he says 75-80% of the content of the book (which is some 68,000 words) is up to date and extremely relevant as of March 2011.
More from the author:
I wrote this book to have something for everyone interested in designing in developing for mobile devices, regardless of experience and regardless of the application.</description></item><item><title>Word Lens: Translation using Augmented Reality</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/word-lens-translation-using-augmented-reality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/word-lens-translation-using-augmented-reality/</guid><description>This is one of the most practical uses of augmented reality I've seen. Word Lens translates text you capture from an iPhone's camera to another language. I think it's only Spanish-English/English-Spanish at the moment, and $4.99 per language. If you're skeptical, as some YouTubers seem to be in the comments, you can see an example of the translation I did on my phone of an English magazine page to Spanish.</description></item></channel></rss>