<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>storytelling on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/storytelling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in storytelling on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/storytelling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Storytellers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-storytellers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-storytellers/</guid>
      <description>UX Storytellers is a blog that captures the stories that we share when we&#39;re talking UX with our peers at conferences and events. Jan Jursa&#39;s team are collecting these stories to publish as a free PDF, an online magazine and eventually a book.
http://uxstorytellers.blogspot.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hitotoki</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/hitotoki/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/hitotoki/</guid>
      <description>Hitotoki is a literary project collecting stories tied to geographic locations. Nice hand drawn details and minimalist sensibility. Uses the connection to locales using Google Maps to navigate the story spaces on the home page.
http://hitotoki.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>howies</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/howies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/howies/</guid>
      <description>My friend Carl told me about howies a while ago, but I only recently had a look back. They&#39;re a clothing and accessories company that aims at providing products with materials and construction that are meant to last and can be handed down to others for reuse. What I like most is how they use storytelling to provide a picture about materials in their products and their handmedown idea, which is communicated in its own mini site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twix.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/twixcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/twixcom/</guid>
      <description>Man, the candy advertising biz sure spends a lot on creative work. While not as unexpected as the Skittles site, the interactive storytelling on Twix.com takes you through a scenario where you get to play a guy trying and lying to pick up a girl at a party by helping him make strategic decisions at each Twix moment. Guess 18-30-ish guys are their target demographic. Clever use of interactive video and a humorous story to keep you engaged on the site for more than a few seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Shows How to Do Low Fi Concept Demos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</guid>
      <description>The Drawing Board: Commuter Buddy from Cooper Journal on Vimeo. Cooper Interactive&#39;s Commuter Buddy concept video is another great find via Dave Malouf&#39;s Engage blog. You might have already seen this one, but as Dave points out, it is a great example of using personas, narrative, and really low fidelity sketches to demonstrate a concept.
The video above uses still photography, super-imposed photos of whiteboard drawings, and voice over narrative to describe the idea for a mobile phone application that helps a commuter to get to his ride on time, and even to remember to get off if he becomes engrossed in an article, for instance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Tell Stories</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/we-tell-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/we-tell-stories/</guid>
      <description>http://www.wetellstories.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
