<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>code libraries on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/code-libraries/</link><description>Recent content in code libraries on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/code-libraries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AniJS: Declarative handling library for CSS animations</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</guid><description>AniJS is a library for CSS animations that allows you to write simple statements for handling animation as key/value pairs in html data attributes. It feels very close to writing natural language statements, in a format that is a bit more familiar in code than writing sentences. A simple example contains IF, ON, DO, and TO pairs and would look like this: &amp;lt;input id="name" type="text" data-anijs="if: focus, do: wobble, to: p"</description></item><item><title>uilang</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/uilang/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/uilang/</guid><description>uilang is a minimal, ui-focused programming language for web designers that handles click events, primarily for toggling classes and css display properties. I love the natural language approach to scripting in uilang. You just insert a statement in a code block like this and it works magically: &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;clicking on ".try-it" toggles class "hidden" on ".info-box"&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; You still have to write your CSS to handle things like effects, but that's a plus if you don't want or need someone else's implementation of those things.</description></item><item><title>Semantic UI Library</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/semantic-ui-library/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/semantic-ui-library/</guid><description>Semantic UI is a framework for building HTML sites that aims at creating a system based on semantic naming and sensible defaults.
The framework compares itself directly with Bootstrap. It uses simple, common language for parts of interface elements and familiar rules used in natural languages for describing elements. Interface definitions are tag ambivalent so you can use div, article, section, span without affecting the display of the element.
http://semantic-ui.com/</description></item><item><title>Making Infield Form Labels Suck Less</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/making-infield-form-labels-suck-less/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/making-infield-form-labels-suck-less/</guid><description>Jackson Fox and Jeremy Fields did an excellent 2-part write on the use of "infield" labels at Viget. There are several techniques for placing labels inside the input box. For varying reasons we may want to avoid the label on top or side positioning, but as Jackson points out, the infield placement can be problematic. Part 1 talks about the problems using infield labels. Part 2 shows how they deal with the problem by using a visible tooltip that doesn't obscure the input, with a jsFiddle snippet to play with the code.</description></item><item><title>MiniAjax: Rich UI Showcase</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/miniajax-rich-ui-showcase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/miniajax-rich-ui-showcase/</guid><description>MiniAjax is a nice showcase of javascript libraries for rich interaction behaviors.
http://miniajax.com/</description></item><item><title>Sencha Touch HTML5 Mobile App Framework</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</guid><description>Sencha Touch looks like an excellent toolkit for delivering HTML 5/CSS 3 mobile experiences. Check out these demos your mobile device to give it a test run: GeoCongress (makes use of geolocation), Solitaire (drag and drop and flip animations), Kiva (provides iPad popover controls).
Sencha Touch allows you to develop web apps that look and feel native on Apple iOS and Google Android touchscreen devices. It's built specifically to leverage HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript and makes use of HTML5 to deliver components like audio and video, as well as a localStorage proxy for saving data offline.</description></item><item><title>Drupal Coda Clips</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/drupal-coda-clips/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/drupal-coda-clips/</guid><description>Dezinerfolio's free Drupal snippet library for the Coda editor (Mac OS only) provides a very useful set of code clips for theming Drupal sites.
http://www.dezinerfolio.com/freebie/drupal-coda-clips</description></item><item><title>jQuery Slider Gallery</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/jquery-slider-gallery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/jquery-slider-gallery/</guid><description>The jQuery Slider Gallery article on jQuery for Designers provides a tutorial and demonstration for using jQuery plugins to create a scrolling gallery similar to the scrolling showcase on Apple's product pages.
http://jqueryfordesigners.com/slider-gallery/</description></item><item><title>Uni-Form</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/uni-form/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/uni-form/</guid><description>Uni-Form is a cool tool from Dragan Babić of Superawesome. The CSS library standardizes form markup (xhtml) and css, and "modularizes" it so even people with only basic knowledge of these technologies can get nice looking, well structured, highly customizable, semantic, accessible and usable forms. Download the plug and play XHTML and CSS and you're ready to go.
http://sprawsm.com/uni-form/</description></item><item><title>Yahoo! BrowserPlus</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-browserplus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-browserplus/</guid><description>Yahoo! BrowserPlus is software that extends the capabilities of web browsers to make rich web experiences possible. Websites can use the software to support behaviors like drag and drop from the desktop, easier file uploads, acquisition of feeds and information, and native desktop notifications. The site is showing very cool demos right now including dragging and dropping photos from the desktop to a web browser, live image manipulation, and live refreshing IRC chatrooms in the browser.</description></item><item><title>Timeframe: A Javascript Control For Date Ranges</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/timeframe-javascript-control-date-ranges/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/timeframe-javascript-control-date-ranges/</guid><description>Stephen Celis' Timeframe javascript library allows you to create a calendar that allows users to select date-ranges by first clicking a start or end date, and then clicking the other end of the range. The range is shown as you expect in desktop calendar applications with a filled bar between the dates. Hover over the range and click the X control to delete. Nice.
http://stephencelis.com/projects/timeframe#example_information</description></item></channel></rss>