<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Realizing Empathy: An Inquiry into the Meaning of Making</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/realizing-empathy-inquiry-meaning-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/realizing-empathy-inquiry-meaning-making/</guid>
      <description>Seung Chan Lim, better known as Slim, spent 10 years making software, working in computer science and interaction design at MAYA Design where he was the Assistant Director of Engineering. After some soul searching he began to ask why he was doing what he was doing, and at the suggestion of a mentor, he went out to do something different, something he didn&amp;rsquo;t understand. He went to art school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Design Pattern Gallery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil&amp;rsquo;s forthcoming book, Mobile Design Pattern Gallery, is set to be released by O&amp;rsquo;Reilly in the Fall of 2011.
Theresa launched a site to go along with the book that includes a fantastic gallery of 70 user interface design patterns for mobile devices with 400+ supporting examples from iOS, Android, BlackBerry, WebOS, Windows Mobile, and Symbian applications. The gallery covers a broad range of problems from designing your application&#39;s navigation to choosing the right invitation technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read &amp;amp;quot;Mobile Design &amp; Development&amp;amp;quot; free online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/read-mobile-design-development-free-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/read-mobile-design-development-free-online/</guid>
      <description>Brian Fling&amp;rsquo;s book, Mobile Design &amp;amp; Development, published by O&amp;rsquo;Reilly in 2009, is available to read in its entirety online. Fling says he says 75-80% of the content of the book (which is some 68,000 words) is up to date and extremely relevant as of March 2011.
More from the author:
I wrote this book to have something for everyone interested in designing in developing for mobile devices, regardless of experience and regardless of the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Them Click</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-makes-them-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-makes-them-click/</guid>
      <description>I just started reading What Makes Them Click, Susan Weinschenk&amp;rsquo;s blog for people who want to learn how to apply psychology to understand how people think, work, and relate.
&amp;quot;The blog focuses especially on applying the latest research in psychology to make you more effective, be more successful at your work and in your career, and get to know better why you and the people around you do what you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Good Ideas Come From, by Steven Johnson</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/where-good-ideas-come-steven-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/where-good-ideas-come-steven-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Chance favors the connected mind.
I just picked up Steven Berlin Johnson&#39;s Where Good Ideas Come From after watching this sketch-note summarization of the ideas in the book.
 I became a fan of Steven&#39;s after reading the New Yorker article &#34;Watching TV Makes you Smarter&#34; and his book, Everything Bad is Good for You. This one looks like it will be an interesting read. I&#39;m hoping it&#39;s full of stories of long drawn out infancy of ideas, and the collisions and connections that make ideas succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speak Human: The new book from Eric Karjaluoto</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/speak-human-new-book-eric-karjaluoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/speak-human-new-book-eric-karjaluoto/</guid>
      <description>smashLab&amp;rsquo;s Eric Karjaluoto writes about outmarketing the big guys by getting personal in his book Speak Human. He&amp;rsquo;s adding a sneak preview of a new chapter every few weeks, so you can read it online for free. Read the sample chapters on the book site and find the links to buy via Amazon.
Via swissmiss
http://speakhuman.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playful Design Book Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/playful-design-book-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/playful-design-book-site/</guid>
      <description>Rosenfeld Media have a book site and Ning community up for John Ferrara&amp;rsquo;s forthcoming book, Playful Design: Creating Game Expderiences in Everyday Interfaces.
Game design is a sibling discipline to software and Web design, but they&#39;re siblings that grew up in different houses. They have much more in common than their perceived distinction typically suggests, and user experience practitioners can realize enormous benefit by exploiting the solutions that games have found to the real problems of design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printed books on User Experience free to read online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/printed-books-user-experience-free-read-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/printed-books-user-experience-free-read-online/</guid>
      <description>UX Bookmark lists a few printed UX books that are available to read for free online, including the following.  Search User Interfaces- by Marti A. Hearst Designing Interfaces- by Jenifer Tidwell Thoughts on Interaction- by John Kolko. Contributions by Ellen Beldner, Uday Gajendar, Chris Connors and Justin Petro The Psychology of Menu Selection: Designing Cognitive Control at the Human/Computer Interface- by Kent L. Norman Just Ask: Integrating Accessibility Throughout Design- by Shawn Henry Building accessible websites- by Joe Clark  View the list with links on UX Bookmark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Prototyping Book Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dynamic-prototyping-book-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dynamic-prototyping-book-site/</guid>
      <description>Dynamic Prototyping with SketchFlow in Expression Blend is a book coming out in late 2009 through Que Publishing and is being written by Chris Bernard and Sara Summers. It will teach you everything you need to know to create rich and dynamic prototypes using SketchFlow in Expression Blend. The book site includes updates about the progress on the book and a preview chapter and the associated projects that go along with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read the &amp;amp;quot;Search User Interfaces&amp;amp;quot; book for free online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/read-search-user-interfaces-book-free-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/read-search-user-interfaces-book-free-online/</guid>
      <description>Marti Hearst and Cambridge University Press have made the Search User Interfaces book available for free online. About the book:
This book focuses on the human users of search engines and the tool they use to interact with them: the search user interface. The truly worldwide reach of the Web has brought with it a new realization among computer scientists and laypeople of the enormous importance of usability and user interface design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchbook: Conceptual Drawings from the World&#39;s Most Influential Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbook-conceptual-drawings-worlds-most-influential-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbook-conceptual-drawings-worlds-most-influential-designers/</guid>
      <description>Core77 reviews Timothy O&amp;rsquo;Donnell&amp;rsquo;s Sketchbook, which looks at the problem solving processes of influential designers on finished projects through the lens of their sketchbooks. It looks beautiful. Organized in three sections, &amp;ldquo;Rough,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Refined,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Random&amp;rdquo; (plus bonus section &amp;ldquo;Revealed,&amp;rdquo; where O&amp;rsquo;Donnell shows the thumbnail sketches he used to lay out the book), almost all sketches/sketchbook pages are pared with pictures of the finished product side by side. The &amp;ldquo;Rough&amp;rdquo; section features loose artwork and thick lines, but crisp final products, like the way Jason Munn turns simple sketches into iconic music posters, while the &amp;ldquo;Refined&amp;rdquo; section sees Stefan Bucher&amp;rsquo;s gorgeous pens turned into, well, equally iconic logos and business cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Project Guide to UX Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/project-guide-ux-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/project-guide-ux-design/</guid>
      <description>The companion site to the book, Project Guide to UX Design: For User Experience Designers in the Field or in the Making, by authors Russ Unger &amp;amp; Carolyn Chandler contains additional reference materials from the book and a bonus chapter, “A Brief Guide to Meetings”.
http://projectuxd.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handbook of Usability Testing: Templates and Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/handbook-usability-testing-templates-and-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/handbook-usability-testing-templates-and-forms/</guid>
      <description>The Handbook of Usability Testing, by Jeffrey Rubin and Dana Chisnell, describes how to plan, design, and conduct effective tests. The books site includes a downloads page with templates and examples of usability test plans, questionairres, test scripts, and consent forms.
http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/WileyTitle/productCd-0470185481,descCd-DOWNLOAD.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nick&#39;s Top User Experience Books</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/nicks-top-user-experience-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/nicks-top-user-experience-books/</guid>
      <description>Nick lists his list of recommended user experience books. http://www.nickfinck.com/blog/entry/nicks_top_user_experience_books</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Design Reading Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-reading-recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-reading-recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Requested Reading Recommendations from the School of Visual Arts, MFA in Interaction Design program.
Upon the request of readers, we asked faculty to recommend books for an interaction design reading list. These could be landmark texts, underdogs, or critical reads, or stepping stones to other fields. The following is what resulted from our request, comprising in part: a sneak preview of what will be assigned in courses; what some consider to be cornerstone interaction design texts; and what some consider important connections to other fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you design? Ebook</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-do-you-design-ebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-do-you-design-ebook/</guid>
      <description>Hugh Dubberly has released a free E Book on design and development models.
In this book, I have collected over one-hundred descriptions of design and development processes, from architecture, industrial design, mechanical engineering, quality management, and software development. They range from short mnemonic devices, such as the 4Ds (deﬁne, design, develop, deploy), to elaborate schemes, such as Archer’s 9-phase, 229-step “systematic method for designers.” Some are synonyms for the same process; others represent differing approaches to design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Book Club</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-book-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-book-club/</guid>
      <description>A UX (User Experience) Book Club is a get-together in which people interested in the area of user experience come to discuss a book relevant to the discipline. http://uxbookclub.org/doku.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working through Screens Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/working-through-screens-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/working-through-screens-book/</guid>
      <description>Flashbulb Interactions&amp;rsquo;s Working through Screens is an excellent, well-illustrated ebook on concept design for designers and product developers. The key point here is how to use design tools and methodologies to get the right design for the problem. Working through Screens is an online book for product teams creating new or iteratively improved applications for thinking work. Written for use during early, formative conversations, it provides teams with a broad range of considerations for setting the overall direction and priorities for their onscreen tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Designer&#39;s Review of Books</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designers-review-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designers-review-books/</guid>
      <description>Andy Polaine&amp;rsquo;s review of books for designers.
Although there are several good design websites that occasionally have book reviews, there didn’t seem to be a single place online where you could get constant updates and reviews of new (and sometimes old) design books.
Design books are often expensive and contrary – sometimes the book is worth having for the physical production values alone, sometimes for the images, sometimes for the words and, occasionally, for all three.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Interaction Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/thoughts-interaction-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/thoughts-interaction-design/</guid>
      <description>Just getting around to reading Jon Kolko&amp;rsquo;s Thoughts on Interaction Design, which is available online now that the printed book is no longer available.
http://thoughtsoninteraction.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back of the Napkin</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/back-napkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/back-napkin/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a more appropriate site for a cute hand drawn interface than for The Back of the Napkin book site. This is a great book for anyone who wants to expand their tools for business thinking. Dan Roam provides a friendly approach and simple formula to using drawing to collect, analyze, and communicate problems and ideas, and you don&amp;rsquo;t need to be good at drawing to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Form Design: Filling in the blanks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/web-form-design-filling-blanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/web-form-design-filling-blanks/</guid>
      <description>Luke Wroblewski&#39;s book on form design is finally out. From the author:
Forms make or break the most crucial online interactions: checkout (commerce), registration (community), data input (participation and sharing), and any task requiring information entry. In Web Form Design, Luke Wroblewski draws on original research, his considerable experience at Yahoo! and eBay, and the perspectives of many of the field&#39;s leading designers to show you everything you need to know about designing effective and engaging Web forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosenfeld Media - Mental Models</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/rosenfeld-media-mental-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rosenfeld-media-mental-models/</guid>
      <description>Rosenfeld Media publishes it&amp;rsquo;s first UX book, Mental Models by Indi Young. Congrats to Lou and Indi!
After two long years, Rosenfeld Media is a real, bona fide publisher. More importantly, as a loyal Bloug reader, you can purchase our first book, Mental Models: Aligning design strategy with human behavior, by Indi Young, with a 10% discount from the Rosenfeld Media site (use code BLOUG01MM). You&amp;rsquo;ll receive Indi&amp;rsquo;s excellent book, illustrated and beautifully printed in full color on high quality paper with a sewn binding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>