<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 14:45:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Raz Kids</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/raz-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 14:45:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/raz-kids/</guid>
      <description>K-5 site with 400+ eBooks that students can listen to, read, and even record themselves reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Author Read Alouds on YouTube</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/author-readalouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 22:12:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/author-readalouds/</guid>
      <description>The Children&amp;rsquo;s Book Council&amp;rsquo;s playlist of authors reading their books aloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookflix on Schoolastic</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/schoolastic-bookflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 21:56:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/schoolastic-bookflix/</guid>
      <description>Scholastic BookFlix is a literacy resource that pairs classic video storybooks from Weston Woods with related nonfiction eBooks from Scholastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity Read Alouds on Storyline</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 21:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/storyline/</guid>
      <description>Storyline Online, streams videos featuring celebrated actors reading children’s books alongside creatively produced illustrations. Readers include Viola Davis, Chris Pine, Lily Tomlin, Kevin Costner, Annette Bening, James Earl Jones, Betty White and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epic! Digital Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/epic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 22:09:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/epic/</guid>
      <description>Digital Library for kids 12 &amp;amp; under. Free access through your school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio Stories on Audible</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/audible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 23:36:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/kidstuff/audible/</guid>
      <description>Free audio stories for kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realizing Empathy: An Inquiry into the Meaning of Making</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/realizing-empathy-inquiry-meaning-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/realizing-empathy-inquiry-meaning-making/</guid>
      <description>Seung Chan Lim, better known as Slim, spent 10 years making software, working in computer science and interaction design at MAYA Design where he was the Assistant Director of Engineering. After some soul searching he began to ask why he was doing what he was doing, and at the suggestion of a mentor, he went out to do something different, something he didn&#39;t understand. He went to art school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Design Pattern Gallery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil&#39;s forthcoming book, Mobile Design Pattern Gallery, is set to be released by O&#39;Reilly in the Fall of 2011.
Theresa launched a site to go along with the book that includes a fantastic gallery of 70 user interface design patterns for mobile devices with 400+ supporting examples from iOS, Android, BlackBerry, WebOS, Windows Mobile, and Symbian applications. The gallery covers a broad range of problems from designing your application&#39;s navigation to choosing the right invitation technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read &amp;amp;quot;Mobile Design &amp; Development&amp;amp;quot; free online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/read-mobile-design-development-free-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/read-mobile-design-development-free-online/</guid>
      <description>Brian Fling&#39;s book, Mobile Design &amp; Development, published by O&#39;Reilly in 2009, is available to read in its entirety online. Fling says he says 75-80% of the content of the book (which is some 68,000 words) is up to date and extremely relevant as of March 2011.
More from the author:
I wrote this book to have something for everyone interested in designing in developing for mobile devices, regardless of experience and regardless of the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Them Click</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-makes-them-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-makes-them-click/</guid>
      <description>I just started reading What Makes Them Click, Susan Weinschenk&#39;s blog for people who want to learn how to apply psychology to understand how people think, work, and relate.
&amp;quot;The blog focuses especially on applying the latest research in psychology to make you more effective, be more successful at your work and in your career, and get to know better why you and the people around you do what you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Good Ideas Come From, by Steven Johnson</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/where-good-ideas-come-steven-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/where-good-ideas-come-steven-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Chance favors the connected mind.
I just picked up Steven Berlin Johnson&#39;s Where Good Ideas Come From after watching this sketch-note summarization of the ideas in the book.
 I became a fan of Steven&#39;s after reading the New Yorker article &#34;Watching TV Makes you Smarter&#34; and his book, Everything Bad is Good for You. This one looks like it will be an interesting read. I&#39;m hoping it&#39;s full of stories of long drawn out infancy of ideas, and the collisions and connections that make ideas succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speak Human: The new book from Eric Karjaluoto</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/speak-human-new-book-eric-karjaluoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/speak-human-new-book-eric-karjaluoto/</guid>
      <description>smashLab&#39;s Eric Karjaluoto writes about outmarketing the big guys by getting personal in his book Speak Human. He&#39;s adding a sneak preview of a new chapter every few weeks, so you can read it online for free. Read the sample chapters on the book site and find the links to buy via Amazon.
Via swissmiss
http://speakhuman.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playful Design Book Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/playful-design-book-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/playful-design-book-site/</guid>
      <description>Rosenfeld Media have a book site and Ning community up for John Ferrara&#39;s forthcoming book, Playful Design: Creating Game Expderiences in Everyday Interfaces.
Game design is a sibling discipline to software and Web design, but they&#39;re siblings that grew up in different houses. They have much more in common than their perceived distinction typically suggests, and user experience practitioners can realize enormous benefit by exploiting the solutions that games have found to the real problems of design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printed books on User Experience free to read online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/printed-books-user-experience-free-read-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/printed-books-user-experience-free-read-online/</guid>
      <description>UX Bookmark lists a few printed UX books that are available to read for free online, including the following.  Search User Interfaces- by Marti A. Hearst Designing Interfaces- by Jenifer Tidwell Thoughts on Interaction- by John Kolko. Contributions by Ellen Beldner, Uday Gajendar, Chris Connors and Justin Petro The Psychology of Menu Selection: Designing Cognitive Control at the Human/Computer Interface- by Kent L. Norman Just Ask: Integrating Accessibility Throughout Design- by Shawn Henry Building accessible websites- by Joe Clark  View the list with links on UX Bookmark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Prototyping Book Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dynamic-prototyping-book-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dynamic-prototyping-book-site/</guid>
      <description>Dynamic Prototyping with SketchFlow in Expression Blend is a book coming out in late 2009 through Que Publishing and is being written by Chris Bernard and Sara Summers. It will teach you everything you need to know to create rich and dynamic prototypes using SketchFlow in Expression Blend. The book site includes updates about the progress on the book and a preview chapter and the associated projects that go along with it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
