<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>typography on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/typography/</link><description>Recent content in typography on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/typography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colosseo Letterpress Poster Site</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/colosseo-letterpress-poster-site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/colosseo-letterpress-poster-site/</guid><description>Cameron Moll's gorgeous Colosseo poster reimagines the Roman Colloseum with type, and the elegant product site beautiful tells its story.
http://colosseotype.com/</description></item><item><title>Typograph</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/typograph/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typograph/</guid><description>Iain Lamb's Typograph is cool tool that allows you to explore the relationship between scale and rhythm by modifying the properties of typographic elements in a page of sample text.
It sets out to explore how two, intertwined concepts, often playful but sometimes cheeky, can be encouraged to dance in web pages. Drag the colored boxes along the scale to throw these words anew. For the most part, this text is just a libretto for the performance you are about to play upon it.</description></item><item><title>fontcapture.com: Create fonts from your handwriting</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/fontcapturecom-create-fonts-your-handwriting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/fontcapturecom-create-fonts-your-handwriting/</guid><description>fontcapture might be interesting to people who create sketch-style wireframes, but don't like using Apple's Casual or Comic Sans. Simply download and fill in the font template, scan and upload it to fontcatpure, and download your completed font, usable on both Windows and Mac computers.
http://www.fontcapture.com/</description></item><item><title>@font-face: The Potential of Web Typography</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/font-face-potential-web-typography/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/font-face-potential-web-typography/</guid><description>How can @font-face be used with currently implemented CSS selectors to create engaging, nuanced and more mature typography? Ian Lynam &amp;amp; Craig Mod discuss the potential of using @font-face now that Firefox 3.5 is out. http://craigmod.com/journal/font-face/</description></item><item><title>Typekit: Foundry-Approved Font Embedding</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/typekit-foundry-approved-font-embedding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typekit-foundry-approved-font-embedding/</guid><description>Jeff Veen announces Typekit, a solution for providing foundry-approved font embedding on the web. More info below from the Typkekit blog.
We’ve been working with foundries to develop a consistent web-only font linking license. We’ve built a technology platform that lets us to host both free and commercial fonts in a way that is incredibly fast, smoothes out differences in how browsers handle type, and offers the level of protection that type designers need without resorting to annoying and ineffective DRM.</description></item><item><title>Typography Is the UI on the Zune HD</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/typography-ui-zune-hd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typography-ui-zune-hd/</guid><description>Zune HD Video Hands On from Gizmodo on Vimeo.
http://fosat.tumblr.com/post/114567959/typography-is-the-user-interface-the-new-zune-hd</description></item><item><title>Striking Web Sites with Font Stacks that Inspire</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/striking-web-sites-font-stacks-inspire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/striking-web-sites-font-stacks-inspire/</guid><description>Inspiration Bit has a wonderful collection of sites whose style sheets utilize users' system-installed fonts.
http://www.inspirationbit.com/striking-web-sites-with-font-stacks-that-inspire/</description></item><item><title>Feltron 2008 Annual Report</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/feltron-2008-annual-report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/feltron-2008-annual-report/</guid><description>Nick Felton's annual report continues to take mundane data and meticulously render superb stastical diagrams and information graphics. If every corporate Power Point chart looked this good, fewer people would be bored out of their skulls in meetings.
http://feltron.com/index.php?/content/2008_annual_report/</description></item><item><title>TypeNeu</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/typeneu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/typeneu/</guid><description>TypeNeue is a typography blog that uses Suprb's Grid A Liciouis theme for WordPress to give it that dense multi-column layout. Entries are ordered reverse chronologically, but unlike typical columnar layouts, the entries are read from left to right first, then top to bottom, so the lines of demarcation are staggered. This creates a unexpectedness and less ordered feeling to the layout, but gives the design the ability to put more content into the screen above the fold.</description></item><item><title>20 Websites with Beautiful Typography</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/20-websites-beautiful-typography/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/20-websites-beautiful-typography/</guid><description>Six revisions showcases 20 sites that use typography exceptionally well.
http://sixrevisions.com/web_design/20-websites-with-beautiful-typography/</description></item><item><title>The 100% Easy-2-Read Standard</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/100-easy-2-read-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/100-easy-2-read-standard/</guid><description>I just stumbled onto ia.jp's web type manifesto for the first time and whole heartedly agree. http://informationarchitects.jp/100e2r/</description></item><item><title>typeface.js: Rendering text with Javascript, canvas, and VML</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/typefacejs-rendering-text-javascript-canvas-and-vml/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typefacejs-rendering-text-javascript-canvas-and-vml/</guid><description>I just came across typeface.js, a type face replacement method like SIFR and FLIR, that lets you embed custom fonts in your pages using CSS. On the backend, javscript is used with or VML to draw the glyphs for your fonts. Compared with SIFR, this suffers from some issues. Biggest one perhaps is that you can't select text since it's rendered as an image. Not so with SIFR. I wouldn't go using this method for body text, but if you're already considering doing image replacement for elements like headings, this would be a library to watch.</description></item><item><title>Typocalypse</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/typocalypse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typocalypse/</guid><description>Lars Willem Veldkampf's Typocalypse flickr set exposes the subliminal messages in type.
http://flickr.com/photos/larsveldkamp/sets/72157607710779069/</description></item><item><title>Lighthouse International - Making Text Legible</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/lighthouse-international-making-text-legible/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/lighthouse-international-making-text-legible/</guid><description>Lighthouse provides 10 basic guidelines for designing for people with partial sight. "Impaired vision often makes reading difficult by: Reducing the amount of light that enters the eye, Blurring the retinal image, Damaging the central portion of the retina best suited to reading."
http://www.lighthouse.org/accessibility/legible/</description></item><item><title>Typechart - Browse Web Type, Grab CSS</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/typechart-browse-web-type-grab-css/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typechart-browse-web-type-grab-css/</guid><description>TYPECHART is pretty neat. It lets you flip through, preview for Mac or Windows and compare web typography while retrieving the CSS.
http://www.typechart.com/</description></item></channel></rss>