<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Links on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/links/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Links on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 14:55:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tota11y: An Accessibility Visualization Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/tota11y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 14:55:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/tota11y/</guid>
      <description>Tota11y is a tool to find accessibility issues on websites. Install the bookmarklet and a small button will be displayed when the bookmarklet is toggled. It runs a single javascript file on checks the page against accessibility criteria. Select criteria from the menu, and tota11y will visually call out the areas you may need to review, providing a description of the issue and recommendations for making the element accessible. The free tool is provided by Khan Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 1 1 1 dns service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/1-1-1-1-dns-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 16:24:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/1-1-1-1-dns-service/</guid>
      <description>1.1.1.1 is a DNS service created by Cloudflare and APNIC to offer you a more private experience on the Internet. Here’s what they say:
Unfortunately, by default, DNS is usually slow and insecure. Your ISP, and anyone else listening in on the Internet, can see every site you visit and every app you use — even if their content is encrypted. Creepily, some DNS providers sell data about your Internet activity or use it target you with ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RGBA feColorMatrix</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/rgba-fecolormatrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 12:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/rgba-fecolormatrix/</guid>
      <description>feColorMatrix is an SVG filter that changes colors based on a transformation matrix. Every pixel’s color value (represented by an [R,G,B,A] vector) is matrix multiplied to create a new color.
This filter allows granular per channel color manipulation. Una Kravets wrote an excellent article explaining how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Microcopy</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/good-microcopy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 16:02:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/good-microcopy/</guid>
      <description>Good Micrcopy is a showcase of clear, concise and sometimes quirky copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storyboarder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/storyboarder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:11:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/storyboarder/</guid>
      <description>Wonderunit’s Storyboarder is a free storyboarding application for the Mac that lets you visualize a story quickly. Quickly sketch your stick figures, then create and show animatics to others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design Basics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/graphic-design-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 16:16:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/graphic-design-basics/</guid>
      <description>Designers Ellen Lupton and Jennifer Cole Phillips, authors of the book Graphic Design, The New Basics&amp;nbsp; and Directors of the MFA Program at Maryland Institute College of Art offer a free 35 minute Skillshare course walking through 5 basic principles of graphic design. The course is a quick primer on design principles suited to various visual design projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspect Ratio Calculators</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/aspect-ratio-calculators/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/aspect-ratio-calculators/</guid>
      <description>In my Skillshare course there&amp;rsquo;s a brief moment where I show a ratio calculator that I use for doing things like figuring out dimensions of containers while designing.
The idea is simple. You have a ratio like 16:9, 4:3, 9:6, etc. and want to see how to scale another object with that ratio using a fixed dimension, e.g. you know the width.
Here are a few that I like:
Aspect Ratio Calculator, a free web calculator by Andrew Hedges that I&amp;rsquo;ve used for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principle for Mac: Animation and Prototyping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</guid>
      <description>Principle for Mac ($99) is a tool for designing animation, primarily for mobile devices. It provides an easy to use interface for prototyping interaction, transitions, or other animated elements in your interface.
You can design with text, rectangles (which can modified with border radius to make circles), or graphics created with other tools, and then hook up animations for actions like taps, scrolling, and drag, and use the drivers UI to connect those actions to drive other properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots Static Site Builder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 15:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</guid>
      <description>Roots is an open source static site compiler that can help take some of the work out of setting up your own build tasks using taskrunners like gulp or grunt. It runs in your terminal and requires minimal setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relay.io Design Sharing via Slack</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/relay-io-design-sharing-via-slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/relay-io-design-sharing-via-slack/</guid>
      <description>Relay looks like it&amp;rsquo;ll be a nice design communication tool for teams using Slack. Capture screens directly from Adobe CC, Sketch, Chrome, or anything else on your screen and it&amp;rsquo;ll be ready for critique in Slack, with comments and annotation.
(Hatip Leon)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generator Directories</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/static-site-generator-directories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/static-site-generator-directories/</guid>
      <description>These are the 2 main directories listing generators that you can use to build a static site. Each offers a sortable lists to browse by user rating or language.
StaticGen - Lists the top Open Source static site generators only. Filter by language. Sort by rating, issues, forks, titles.
Static Site Generators - Lists Open Source and Commercial static site generators. Sort by rating, license, and language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astropad: Use iPad as Mac Graphics Tablet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;video&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&#34;853&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ouwCHT3rGRY&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://astropad.com/&#34;&gt;AstroPad&lt;/a&gt; turns your iPad into a Mac graphics tablet, mirroring a section of your Mac&amp;rsquo;s screen when connected via WiFi or USB. Once connected you can sketch/draw on the tablet with an iPad stylus or finger. It will operate pretty much like a Wacom graphics tablet when you&amp;rsquo;re using a Desktop graphics app with a drawing tool like Pixelmator, Photoshop, or Sketchbook Pro. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAPERPROTO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/paperproto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/paperproto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://paperproto.com/&#34;&gt;PAPERPROTO&lt;/a&gt; is a 3D printable model to use for paper prototyping mobile applications, in the style of a &lt;a href=&#34;http://lifestyle.howstuffworks.com/crafts/seasonal/winter/theatre-activities-for-kids7.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;story scroll&lt;/a&gt;. You can download the file or buy the model for printing on demand directly from Shapeways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Via &lt;a href=&#34;http://zekefranco.com/&#34;&gt;Zeke Franco&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Check</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-check/</guid>
      <description>UX Check is a Google Chrome extension for reviewing web sites and apps against Jakob Neilsen&amp;rsquo;s Usability Heuristics.
The tool opens the heuristics in a side panel next to the website you enter. You select a problem area on the screen, related to one of the usability heuristics and a callout appears for you to add notes and recommendations. When you&#39;re done a report is available with screenshots and your notes for each issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Accessibility Project</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/accessibility-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/accessibility-project/</guid>
      <description>The A11Y project is a community-driven effort to make web accessibility easier. They provide articles on best practices for doing front end development with accessibility in mind. The site includes an accessibility checklist, a pattern library for accessible widgets, and a list of resources for diving deeper into web accessibility.
http://a11yproject.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Project Checklist</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-project-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-project-checklist/</guid>
      <description>This UX Checklist by Andrea Soverini&#39;s is a nice overview of potential UX-related tools and techniques that you could use for product design. It provides a layered visualization of a design process, like an extension of JJG&#39;s layers, with links to articles on the technique. Would make a good poster for a workspace.
http://uxchecklist.github.io/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RemoteIE: Remote Testing for Internet Explorer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/remoteie-remote-testing-internet-explorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/remoteie-remote-testing-internet-explorer/</guid>
      <description>The Microsoft Remote Desktop app lets you use Azure RemoteApp to test your site on IE (on Windows 10 Technical Preview from anywhere). After you download the app for Mac, Windows iOS or Android, you can connect to their cloud-based version of IE.
https://remote.modern.ie/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sticker UI Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sticker-ui-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sticker-ui-book/</guid>
      <description>The Sticker UI Book is a UI design sketchbook that with templates (web, mobile, and storyboard) and UI element stickers, being produced by Jennifer Williams and Brandy Bora of Killer Inc. You can order one via their Kickstarter campaign which ends Oct 30 2014 7:44 AM PDT. http://stickerui.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AniJS: Declarative handling library for CSS animations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</guid>
      <description>AniJS is a library for CSS animations that allows you to write simple statements for handling animation as key/value pairs in html data attributes. It feels very close to writing natural language statements, in a format that is a bit more familiar in code than writing sentences. A simple example contains IF, ON, DO, and TO pairs and would look like this: &amp;lt;input id=&#34;name&#34; type=&#34;text&#34; data-anijs=&#34;if: focus, do: wobble, to: p&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>uilang</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/uilang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/uilang/</guid>
      <description>uilang is a minimal, ui-focused programming language for web designers that handles click events, primarily for toggling classes and css display properties. I love the natural language approach to scripting in uilang. You just insert a statement in a code block like this and it works magically: &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;clicking on &#34;.try-it&#34; toggles class &#34;hidden&#34; on &#34;.info-box&#34;&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; You still have to write your CSS to handle things like effects, but that&#39;s a plus if you don&#39;t want or need someone else&#39;s implementation of those things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Your Cache</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/refresh-your-cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/refresh-your-cache/</guid>
      <description>I used to do a lot of technical support, and still do some occasionally. Refresh Your Cache is a simple guide to clearing browser cache that you can send to your customers rather than sleuthing platform and browser, because Shift-Refresh doesn&amp;rsquo;t work all the time for all browsers.
Via Ben in a backchannel. ;)
http://www.refreshyourcache.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origami: Design prototyping with Quartz Composer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/origami-design-prototyping-quartz-composer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/origami-design-prototyping-quartz-composer/</guid>
      <description>Origami is a free toolkit created by the Facebook Design team for Quartz Composer, the visual programming tool that&amp;rsquo;s available with the Apple XCode development environment. Origami provides patches that can be added to your Quartz Composer library, to create interactive prototypes without programming. Quartz composer&amp;rsquo;s UI allows you connect patches with wires (or tubes, if you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with that metaphor) to perform tasks or set behaviors and properties.
Jay Thrash&amp;rsquo;s video explains how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precomposed Touch Gestures</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</guid>
      <description>Aureus Wade&amp;rsquo;s Precomposed Touch Gestures are a set of touch-device gestures available as QuickTime animations for use in product demos or presentations. They&amp;rsquo;ll work in your video editor, and Photoshop.
http://areuswade.com/precomposed-touch-gestures/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GluePrint: Floating guides for your mockups</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/glueprint-floating-guides-your-mockups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/glueprint-floating-guides-your-mockups/</guid>
      <description>I like the simple idea behind GluePrint. Drop your mockup or visual design comp onto the app and it provides a semi-opaque window of the design. I can see it being useful for overlaying on top of your browser, like an onionskin, while you&amp;rsquo;re working on front end implementation. And even in other reverse scenarios, like for creating new designs based on an existing version of your product.
http://glueprintapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>explainshell: Unix Manual pages explained visually</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/explainshell-unix-manual-pages-explained-visually/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/explainshell-unix-manual-pages-explained-visually/</guid>
      <description>Idan Kamara&amp;rsquo;s explainshell displays Ubuntu&amp;rsquo;s manpage repository visually like a schematic, allowing you to highlight parts of a commands parts (command, arguments, options) and view a callout that describes what the part does.
http://explainshell.com/explain?cmd=tar%20xzvf%20archive.tar.gz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghostlab Browser Testing Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ghostlab-browser-testing-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ghostlab-browser-testing-tool/</guid>
      <description>Ghostlab is a tool for synchronized browser testing. It synchronizes scrolls, clicks, reloads and form input across all connected clients so that you can test a full user experience.
http://vanamco.com/ghostlab/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shim Browser Testing Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/shim-browser-testing-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/shim-browser-testing-tool/</guid>
      <description>Shim is a node.js-based browser-compatibility tool that lets you synchronize several devices/browsers and surf the same pages simultaneously on all of them.
https://github.com/antistatique/shim</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Preview</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/remote-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/remote-preview/</guid>
      <description>Remote Preview is a JavaScript-based tool for previewing a web page on multiple devices, built by Viljami Salminen @viljamis for the Helsinki Device Lab. Just enter a URL, hit Enter, and the new URL gets automatically loaded on each device. Works on platforms like Android, Blackberry, iOS, Maemo, Meego, Symbian, Windows Phone and WebOS. I don&#39;t think the GameBoy pictured is supported. ;)

Source code is available on Github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mapsicon</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mapsicon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mapsicon/</guid>
      <description>Mapsicon is a free collection of maps for nearly every country in the world, available as PNG in 11 different sizes, ranging from 16x16 pixels to 1024x1024 pixels, as well as in .svg format. Useful for placeholders or for illustrative purposes, rather than for precise rendering of geography.
https://github.com/djaiss/mapsicon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pivot Mac for PivotalTracker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/pivot-mac-pivotaltracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/pivot-mac-pivotaltracker/</guid>
      <description>I was looking for a way to add stories to Pivotal Tracker without having to load their UI in the web browser. I wanted something as fast as using Alfred, and found Jelle Vandebeeck&amp;rsquo;s Pivot App for the Mac.
Pivot puts an icon in your menubar, and drops down a form to file chores, features, bugs, and releases with auto-completion for projects, owners, and tags. Simple. Only thing I could want more from this is a clipboard link to the story, or an optional description field, but is otherwise near perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Web Designer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/google-web-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/google-web-designer/</guid>
      <description>Google Web Designer is design and development tools for creating interactive HTML5-based motion graphics. The tool looks like it&amp;rsquo;s targeted at advertising creative. It provides templates for banner ads, which makes sense, but can be used for generating any canvas motion graphics. The default layouts are for DoubleClick and AdMob mobile ads.
Web Designer is a web application that&#39;s built with HTML5, and runs natively on your desktop. It provides support for text, images, videos, and even provides bezier drawing tools for creating shapes and 3d objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoSWS: HTML5 Video Player Comparison</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/videosws-html5-video-player-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/videosws-html5-video-player-comparison/</guid>
      <description>I like this &amp;quot;See What Sucks&amp;quot; table of HTML5 Video players, for comparing features of the video players like library dependencies, flash fallback, playlist and audio support. Starred products indicate the &amp;quot;Suck less than others&amp;quot; rating.
http://praegnanz.de/html5video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frontify: Design review, documentation, and specification app</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</guid>
      <description>Frontify looks like an interesting SaaS product for design teams. It provides collaborative features for getting design feedback, creating specifications, documentation and style guides, and linking pages together.
The commenting and linking features are what you&#39;d expect, but what I was really impressed with are the measures, colors, and typography tools for generating style guides. Very nicely done. There are additional capabilities for code export &amp;amp; integration with their API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Semantic UI Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/semantic-ui-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/semantic-ui-library/</guid>
      <description>Semantic UI is a framework for building HTML sites that aims at creating a system based on semantic naming and sensible defaults.
The framework compares itself directly with Bootstrap. It uses simple, common language for parts of interface elements and familiar rules used in natural languages for describing elements. Interface definitions are tag ambivalent so you can use div, article, section, span without affecting the display of the element.
http://semantic-ui.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basiliq by Cloud Castle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/basiliq-cloud-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/basiliq-cloud-castle/</guid>
      <description>Sketch-style controls and icons for Photoshop from the folks at Cloudcastle.
http://cloudcastlegroup.com/blog/basiliq/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random User Generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/random-user-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/random-user-generator/</guid>
      <description>RandomUser is an API that provides you with a randomly generated user. These users can be used as placeholders in web mockups, and will save you time from creating your own placeholder information.
http://randomuser.me/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macaw: Code-savvy web design tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/macaw-code-savvy-web-design-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/macaw-code-savvy-web-design-tool/</guid>
      <description>Macaw is a forthcoming Mac application for designing pages for web browsers that are ready to use as web-native code. The app runs natively in html and css, and provides excellent export to clean html and css.
There are some great optimizations for nudging/pudging on a grid, and for setting properties that make sense for css—thinking of positioning and dimensions.
The outline view is a nice way to browse through all the groups in the document and adding container tags and/or classes for semantic html publishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Inter Faces: Avatars for mockups</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/user-inter-faces-avatars-mockups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/user-inter-faces-avatars-mockups/</guid>
      <description>UI Faces is a useful little tool by Caleb Ogden for generating a grid of avatars that you can use in your designs.
http://uifaces.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starters Guide to iOS Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/starters-guide-ios-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/starters-guide-ios-design/</guid>
      <description>Ben Taylor&amp;rsquo;s Starters Guide to iOS describes an exhaustive range of topics as intro to iOS design. He covers the deliverables you&amp;rsquo;ll be expected to produce, outlines the constraints of the medium, and introduces fundamental iOS and UI design concepts.
http://taybenlor.com/2013/05/21/designing-for-ios.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchnote Typeface by Mike Rohde</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketchnote-typeface-mike-rohde/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketchnote-typeface-mike-rohde/</guid>
      <description>Mike Rohde&amp;rsquo;s Sketchnote font can be purchased on Delve for desktop and webfont use. Mike created the font for the Sketchnote handbook and writes about its design on his blog. The family has four fonts: Sketchnote Text in Reg­ular, Bold and Italic, plus Sketchnote Square.
Sketchnote Text is a friendly, casual script with a bouncy baseline and a warm texture. To emulate natural hand­writing, OpenType features auto­matically switch be­tween multiple versions of each letter or number, with over 240 alter­nates in each text font.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FontPrep: Web Font Generator for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/fontprep-web-font-generator-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/fontprep-web-font-generator-mac/</guid>
      <description>FontPrep is a web font generator for the Mac with a simple drag/drop interface for adding your TTF and OTF font files and generating all of the respective font-formats for the web: WOFF, EOT, and SVG. Each converted web-font is bundled with @font-face declarations, and a subsettings feature allows you to select which character sets to include.
http://fontprep.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screensiz.es</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/screensizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/screensizes/</guid>
      <description>screensiz.es displays a table of screen specifications including resolution and pixel density for popular devices and monitors currently on the market.
Via Swissmiss
http://screensiz.es/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SketchMine: Sketch app templates</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketchmine-sketch-app-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketchmine-sketch-app-templates/</guid>
      <description>Sketchmine provides .sketch files for use in Bohemian Coding&amp;rsquo;s Sketch app for Mac. The files are free to download and are contributed by the Sketch community.
http://sketchmine.co/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowWow</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/powwow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/powwow/</guid>
      <description>PowWow is a free simple service for scheduling user research using your Google Calendar. The fine folks at Pointless Corp (aka Viget) created this as a side project for handling scheduling of user interviews and testing, but could be used for any kind of event.
There are other apps like this that remove the fuss of coordinating schedules via email. PowWow does it simply, and provides a polished and pleasing experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Jots</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</guid>
      <description>Sticky Jots is a set of storytelling sticky note paper and paper prototyping kits for designing mobile and tablet interfaces. The product is designed by Rae Milne and Pamela Jue, two grad students in the SVA Interaction Design program. 
Pam writes about the thinking behind Sticky Jots. The idea came from our constant prototyping and ideation process in almost every project this semester. While it’s great to do, it’s still frustrating how time consuming it can be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protosketch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</guid>
      <description>Protosketch is a new free app for iOS from UI Stencils to convert sketches to interactive prototypes. The app is made to work with their sketch pads and stencils. Sketch your screens, add them to the app, define hot areas for links, select link destinations, and prototype.
https://protosketch.uistencils.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixture</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mixture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mixture/</guid>
      <description>Mixture is a rapid prototyping and static site generation tool for Mac and Windows. It works with the Liquid templating system, supports includes and smart paths, handles HAML and SASS comilation, CSS and JS minification, and provides a simple model system for global and custom data, and supports access to form and query data in their request model. It can produce static HTML that you can push to a hosting service, and allows use of your own domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hammer for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/hammer-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/hammer-mac/</guid>
      <description>Hammer is a static web site builder for the Mac that lets you build out sites quickly with no server side requirements.
Hammer does includes without PHP, compiles Coffeescript to JS, SASS/SCSS to CSS, has an auto-refresh feature for never having to reload the browser, and provides some simple to use helpers. Since it knows about all of the files in your projects, you just reference names and it knows how to build out paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawscript: Generate vector code from Illustrator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/drawscript-generate-vector-code-illustrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/drawscript-generate-vector-code-illustrator/</guid>
      <description>Drawscript is an extension for Adobe Illustrator that generates graphics code from vector shapes in realtime. Generates OBJ-C, C++, JavaScript for HTML5 Canvas, Processing, Actionscript 3, JSON, and Raw bezier points.
http://drawscri.pt/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redacted Font</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/redacted-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/redacted-font/</guid>
      <description>Christian Naths&amp;rsquo; Redacted is a set of fonts released under SIL Open Font license with block and scribbled font faces. Main difference between Redacted and BLOKK (which the font is copies/is inspired by) is that Redacted uses smaller widths so your text blocks won&amp;rsquo;t end up wider than your normal font setting.
Git it for free.
https://github.com/christiannaths/Redacted-Font/blob/master/README.md</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tapotype Transition Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/tapotype-transition-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/tapotype-transition-library/</guid>
      <description>Tapotype is a reference library of transitions for mobile prototypes created by Gene Lu using Fireworks and the TAP platform, a framework for iOS prototyping developed by UNITiD. Gene provides tutorials on building prototypes with Tapotype and TAP, and shows how to integrate InDesign and its documenting capabilities into your Fireworks/Tap prototyping workflow.
http://tapotype.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive Sketch Pad from UI Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</guid>
      <description>UI Stencils&amp;rsquo; responsive design sketchpad is made to help figure out breakpoints and how your product might translate to mobile and tablet versions. 2 device silhouettes on the front and 3 on the back. 50 pages on 70# paper in Letter or A4.
http://www.uistencils.com/products/responsive-sketch-pad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLOKK font</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/blokk-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/blokk-font/</guid>
      <description>BLOKK is a font for quick mock-ups and wireframing for clients who do not understand lorem ipsum. Awesome.
http://www.blokkfont.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AirServer: Airplay receiver for iOS devices</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/airserver-airplay-receiver-ios-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/airserver-airplay-receiver-ios-devices/</guid>
      <description>AirServer is an AirPlay receiver for Mac/PC that allows you to receive AirPlay feeds in up to full 1080p HD. It works similar to an Apple TV, so you can stream content or Mirror your display from your iOS devices or Mountain Lion to your desktop computer. The app was made for game and video streaming, but would work perfectly for application demos and presentation or usability testing, when coupled with a concurrent video recording of the user&amp;rsquo;s face and hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One div: Pure CSS icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/one-div-pure-css-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/one-div-pure-css-icons/</guid>
      <description>One Div is a library of icons that are realised in pure css with only one html div as an alternative to SVG. Icons allow precise borders even when resized—same as one would expect with vector icons.
http://one-div.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflector.app: iOS AirPlay mirroring to computer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/reflectorapp-ios-airplay-mirroring-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/reflectorapp-ios-airplay-mirroring-computer/</guid>
      <description>Reflector lets you AirPlay mirror your iPhone 4S, iPad 2 or the new iPad to any Mac or PC, wirelessly, for development, presentation, and testing.
@dakotareese tipped me that some users report problems using apps that hack into Airplay. More info here.
Via 90poe
https://www.reflectorapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jKit: jQuery based UI Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/jkit-jquery-based-ui-toolkit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/jkit-jquery-based-ui-toolkit/</guid>
      <description>jKit is a cross platform, jQuery based UI toolkit, that&amp;rsquo;s small in size and is simple enough for non-programmers to use. There is a technique using a special attribute that even allows you to inject behaviors without writing javascript. It has commonly used design patterns, and nice techniques for content templating and binding to cover the basics of UI prototypes.
http://jquery-jkit.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Recorder for Skype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</guid>
      <description>ecamm&amp;rsquo;s Call Recorder for Mac captures audio and video to save Skype calls as QuickTime movies. Useful for user interviews or screensharing sessions.
Thanks to Thomas @vanderwal for the tip
http://www.ecamm.com/mac/callrecorder/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POP: Prototyping on Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/pop-prototyping-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/pop-prototyping-paper/</guid>
      <description>POP is an iPhone app that lets you take pictures of your sketches, and map areas on each screen to create simple click-through prototypes.
http://popapp.in/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>responsivepx</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/responsivepx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/responsivepx/</guid>
      <description>Responsivepx allows you to enter the url to your site (local or online) and use the controls to adjust the width and height of your viewport to find exact breakpoint widths in pixels. Then you can use that information in your media queries to create a responsive design.
http://responsivepx.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ai to Canvas Plug-In</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ai-canvas-plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ai-canvas-plug/</guid>
      <description>The Ai-&amp;gt;Canvas plug-in enables Adobe Illustrator to export vector and bitmap artwork directly to an HTML5 canvas element that can be rendered in a canvas-enabled browser. The plug-in provides drawing, animation and coding options such as events so that you can build interactive, well-designed canvas-based web apps.
http://visitmix.com/labs/ai2canvas/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Printed Word and The Written Words fonts from LettError</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/printed-word-and-written-words-fonts-letterror/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/printed-word-and-written-words-fonts-letterror/</guid>
      <description>2 different fonts to turn text to obscure your copy in design documents so they don&amp;rsquo;t distract the audience. It&amp;rsquo;s an alternative to using real text or lorem ipsum. Download for free.
Thanks to Ryan Schroeder (@rschroed) for pointing me to this.
http://www.letterror.com/foundry/goodies/index.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPEVO Ziggi Review</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever done the dance of holding a sketch up to your computer&amp;rsquo;s webcam or taken pictures of them with your iPhone to email to yourself or to colleagues? I&amp;rsquo;ve done that sort of thing for all of the years that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked remotely on design and development teams, because scanners get tired real fast. Frustrated with this process, I had largely given up, until a few months ago when I was looking for tools to share work on paper between students and teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whitelines Link</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</guid>
      <description>Everyone&amp;rsquo;s getting in on on the physical paper capturing game using the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s camera. Whitelines is one of my favorite sketch paper makers. They make great graph paper that reverses the grid using white lines over pale a gray paper. The result is that the grid it more subtle and less distracting
The Whitelines Link product is a free iPhone app that let&amp;rsquo;s you capture sketches made on their new Whitelines Link papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Smart Notebook by Moleskine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried a lot of tools for transferring sketches from analog sketchbook to digital. I was an early Pen-It user, have used page cutters with a scanner, and have lately just resorted to taking photos with my iPhone. The Evernote/Moleskine Smart Notebook looks like it might provide the right mix I&amp;rsquo;m looking for.
I&#39;ve given up on the idea of converting paper sketches to vector drawings. What this seems to offer is the ability to use that dotted sheet tech to correctly line up your photos taken with Evernote app, and combines that with some neat stickers that will automatically route your sketches to tags and/or specific notebooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wirefy: Responsive Wireframe Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/wirefy-responsive-wireframe-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/wirefy-responsive-wireframe-library/</guid>
      <description>Wirefy is a collection of CSS and JS files for creating responsive HTML wireframes. It builds on tools including the Frameless grid system and Boostrap, and has CSS media queries for adapting to different device resolutions.
http://cjdsie.github.com/wirefy/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contrast-A: Find Accessible Color Combinations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/contrast-find-accessible-color-combinations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/contrast-find-accessible-color-combinations/</guid>
      <description>Contrast-A allows you to experiment with color combinations, examine them using accessibility guidelines and, create custom color palettes. The app checks color combinations for sufficient contrast and displays the results according to WCAG 2.0 (Luminance Ratio) as well as the results according to older accessibility guidelines, WCAG 1.0 (Difference in Brightness and Color).
http://www.dasplankton.de/ContrastA/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive Design Bookmarklet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-design-bookmarklet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-design-bookmarklet/</guid>
      <description>Victor Coulon&#39;s Responsive Design Bookmarklet is a simple browser-based tool for testing your web layout in desktop, tablet and mobile phone dimensions. Save the bookmarklet, go to the page you want to test, then select the bookmarklet. It puts your page in a frame at the dimensions you want to test. Found via Takashi Sakamoto
http://responsive.victorcoulon.fr/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buxton Collection</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton has been collecting input and interactive devices whose design struck him as interesting, useful, or important. In the process, he has assembled a great collection spanning over 30 years of the history of pen computing, pointing devices, touch technologies, as well as an illustration of the nature of how new technologies emerge.
The collection can be browsed in HTML or via the PivotViewer Silverlight interface. PivotViewer provides a richer experience with faceted filtering, search, and hypertext links for metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Shadow Mobile Device Testing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/adobe-shadow-mobile-device-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/adobe-shadow-mobile-device-testing/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Labs&#39; Shadow is an application for Mac and Windows that allows you to preview and inspect your mobile website on iOS and Android devices.
After installing the software on your computer and any number of mobile devices, you can connect and pair them and all devices will be kept in sync with the web site you&#39;re previewing on your computer. This should help perform remote inspection and debugging so you can see HTML/CSS/JavaScript changes instantly on your devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive.is: Display and present responsive web designs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/responsiveis-display-and-present-responsive-web-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/responsiveis-display-and-present-responsive-web-designs/</guid>
      <description>Responsive.is is a clever tool. Enter a URL or append one to http://responsive.is to view how the layout presents itself on the Desktop, and in tablets and mobile phones.
http://responsive.is/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenleap Screen Sharing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/screenleap-screen-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/screenleap-screen-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Screenleap is a free service that lets you share your screen from any device with a browser, including tablets and smartphones. No software downloads, installs, or sign ups are required. May come in handy for people doing customer support or testing sessions where participant software installation could be an issue.
http://www.screenleap.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usabilla Discover</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</guid>
      <description>Usabilla Discover is like a mashup of Pinterest and LittleBigDetails, or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a social LittleSnapper. Whatever the pitch, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty useful to share screenshots of interface and visual designs you like. Now to figure out how to get my over 2,000 screenshots into it.
Note: To get in during the beta, sign up here with code &amp;quot;KONIGI&amp;quot;, good for the first 200 who use the code.
http://discover.usabilla.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Tappy: Video rig for tablets and mobile devices</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mr-tappy-video-rig-tablets-and-mobile-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mr-tappy-video-rig-tablets-and-mobile-devices/</guid>
      <description>Mr Tappy is a kit for filming mobile phones, tablet computers and handheld devices from the user&amp;rsquo;s point of view. Looks like a great alternative to setting up your own DIY rig, and costs $289.
Originally designed by Nick Bowmast as a filming rig for iPad usability testing, Mr Tappy lets you capture or share user interaction with mobile devices during user experience research, product demonstrations or classroom presentations. Attach your webcam and any type of mobile device, set the camera height and angle, and record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnigraffle Stencil for Twitter Bootstrap 2</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-stencil-twitter-bootstrap-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-stencil-twitter-bootstrap-2/</guid>
      <description>The team at Viget have created a free OmniGraffle stencil for designing interfaces with Twitter Bootstrap.
http://www.viget.com/advance/an-omnigraffle-stencil-for-twitter-bootstrap-2/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Fireworks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/bootstrap-fireworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/bootstrap-fireworks/</guid>
      <description>Bootstrap Fireworks a UI Toolkit created Grady Kelly for Twitter Bootstrap, the HTML/CSS/JS framework. The entire UI recreated as vector images for Adobe Fireworks. (Fw PNG)
http://www.extendingfireworks.com/?p=133</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap, from Twitter</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/bootstrap-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/bootstrap-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Bootstrap is a free, simple, and flexible HTML, CSS (Less Framework), and Javascript (jQuery) for popular user interface components and interactions created by the devs at Twitter.
http://twitter.github.com/bootstrap/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InstaCSS: CSS Documentation Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/instacss-css-documentation-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/instacss-css-documentation-search/</guid>
      <description>Using InstaCSS is a much easier way to look up CSS docs than Googling. Enter a CSS property in the search box, and the panel below dynamically shows matching properties. Simple. If you&amp;rsquo;re a Mac user, it seems to me like it would be useful tucked into a Fluid menu item like this. Via Think Vitamin Newsletter
http://instacss.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reframer: Qualitative data analysis system</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/reframer-qualitative-data-analysis-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/reframer-qualitative-data-analysis-system/</guid>
      <description>Reframer is a collaborative web app for collecting and analyzing qualitative data. You start by capturing data into the app&amp;#8212;things like customer feedback, free text responses in surveys, emails, interviews, and usability test data. The system then uses the aggregated information and provides a view reframed with quantitative values based on a significance rating that team members apply. These values can also be used to prioritize issues to assess feasibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sauce Labs: Cloud-Based Cross-Browser Testing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/saucelabs-cloud-based-cross-browser-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/saucelabs-cloud-based-cross-browser-testing/</guid>
      <description>Sauce Labs provides browser testing services for front end development and quality assurance. Their Scout service lets you test your public or private web app in any browser via a VM that&amp;rsquo;s run in the cloud. Enter a URL to test, select an OS and browser, and a virtual machine runs in the web page so you can test in that configuration on demand. Scout can record and save screenshots and video of every session, and they can can be shared, embedded etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animate.css: Plug-and-play CSS animation stylesheet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/animatecss-plug-and-play-css-animation-stylesheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/animatecss-plug-and-play-css-animation-stylesheet/</guid>
      <description>animate.css is a stylesheet created by Dan Eden for doing common, cross-browser css3 animations for things like transitions for emphasis. To use them in your project, simply add add the stylesheet and link, add a class to an element, or call the animation yourself in your CSS file.
http://daneden.me/animate/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine Res Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/fine-res-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/fine-res-tool/</guid>
      <description>The folks at FINE Design created a browser-based tool for seeing how your web site measures up at different screen resolutions.
To use it, simply enter a full URL of your choosing. Up pops that location superimposed with a draggable set of rulers (x and y axis) configurable in center/left/and right alignment. These rulers allow you to view that site as it would be seen at different resolutions. So you can get a sense for what other eyeballs experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steedicons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/steedicons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/steedicons/</guid>
      <description>The Steedicons set by Kyle Steed contains 300+ hand drawn icons available as a font or in vector format (.ai, .eps, .csh) for Illustrator, Photoshop, or the wireframing tool of your choice. The bold, sketchy icons would would work perfectly in Balsamiq Mockups or alongside the Konigi Sketch stencils.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a small sample of the icons available in this set.  Buy them here.
http://steedicons.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vector Doodlekit Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/vector-doodlekit-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/vector-doodlekit-icons/</guid>
      <description>The Doodlekit Icons set contains 700+ hand-drawn icons for use in sketch-style wireframes. You can buy them in vector format to use in the design tool of your choice, or download the free set of 32 x 32 px PNGs. Here&amp;rsquo;s a screenshot of the icons in the new custom icon feature that&amp;rsquo;s available in the pre-release version of Mockups.  More info here.
http://doodlekit.imagiag.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Form design guidelines crib sheet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/form-design-guidelines-crib-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/form-design-guidelines-crib-sheet/</guid>
      <description>These form design crib sheets provide examples for laying out forms to get users through the process efficiently. Created by Joe Leech at cxpartners, and available for OmniGraffle, Photoshop, or in PDF vector format.
Via @theresaneil
http://www.cxpartners.co.uk/cxinsights/form_design_guidelines_crib_sheet_free.htm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BrowserStack: Cross-Browser Testing Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/browserstack-cross-browser-testing-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/browserstack-cross-browser-testing-tool/</guid>
      <description>Browserstack allows you to stop relying on screenshot web apps or using multiple virtual machines to do your testing. The service gives you remote, web-based, VNC screen sharing using the web browser you choose, so you can test your web sites and apps in real time rather than relying on static screen comparisons.
Enter a URL to test, and select a target browser in the version of your choosing and screen resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samuel L Ipsum Generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/samuel-l-ipsum-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/samuel-l-ipsum-generator/</guid>
      <description>Samuel L. Jackson wants to generate your placeholder text. Say &amp;quot;what&amp;quot; again. I dare you.
Thank Paul Maloney to bringing this to life.
http://slipsum.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X and iOS Icon Templates from Cohdoo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mac-os-x-and-ios-icon-templates-cohdoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mac-os-x-and-ios-icon-templates-cohdoo/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo have created downloadable iOS and OS X icon templates for Photoshop that lay out all the different sizes of assets for a given platform and state where they were to be used.
Download the PSD templates here.
http://blog.cohdoo.com/post/9293679992/icon-grids</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Stencils for OmniGraffle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ios-stencils-omnigraffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ios-stencils-omnigraffle/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been asked several times in the past to add iOS stencils to the wireframe stencil set I make. These are some that I know of, and have been recommended to me by @OmniGraffle and @jmk.
 iA&amp;rsquo;s OmniGraffle port of the Teehan+Lax iPad Stencils David Morford&amp;rsquo;s iOS Design Stencils iPad and iPhone Design  I prefer to link to these than to throw together something myself until I actually work on an iOS project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usaura: Free 5-second tests</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usaura-free-5-second-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usaura-free-5-second-tests/</guid>
      <description>Usaura is a free service for conducting 5-second tests. Upload a screenshot. Enter a question asking your respondents to respond by clicking somewhere on your screenshot. Copy the test url to give to participants or use Twitter to share the test. View the results as a heatmap or as click nodes with time-to-click data.
I set up a dummy test to try here.
http://www.usaura.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edistorm</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/edistorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/edistorm/</guid>
      <description>Edistorm looks like an interesting tool for collaborative brainstorming. Group brainstorming sticky note boards (storms) can be set up with a background template, e.g. 5 up, SWOT, venn diagrams, etc. You place colored sticky notes with text, organize however you want, you can add +1 votes using a voting system, and add comments to notes. There&amp;rsquo;s some kind of recomendations feature that will suggest new topics, which I guess might only work well with certain content types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Stickynotes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-stickynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-stickynotes/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had a UX Stickynotes pad near me for a few weeks to play with. I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a sticky notes nerd. I mostly like to place them in sketchbooks to mark and annotate, but also like them for brainstorming and doing info organization exercises. Sticky notes for UI sketches and sketchboards makes sense.
The sticky notes are A5 sized, with light non-photo blue dot grid, and the browser version has 960gs markers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flickholdr.com: Placeholder images from flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/flickholdrcom-placeholder-images-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/flickholdrcom-placeholder-images-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Best part of flickholdr, a placeholder image service that grabs images from flickr, is how you can string together an odd set of tags to get unusual placeholders.
http://flickholdr.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placehold.it: Simple image placeholders</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/placeholdit-simple-image-placeholders/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/placeholdit-simple-image-placeholders/</guid>
      <description>Placehold.it is a placeholder image service that let&amp;rsquo;s you place images using a url like this: http://placehold.it/350x150 which ends up like the box below when placed in an image tag.
Via @moddpodd
http://placehold.it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lorempixum: Placeholder images for every case</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/lorempixum-placeholder-images-every-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/lorempixum-placeholder-images-every-case/</guid>
      <description>lorempixum is a cool placeholder image service for html wireframers and prototypers. Set dimensions for a placeholder image, and optionally select a category and color or black and white, and the URL will provided will serve a random image for your html page.
Via @poornerd
http://lorempixum.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>{placekitten}</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/placekitten/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/placekitten/</guid>
      <description>{placekitten}. Kittens for placeholder images, inspired by placeholder.it. Use at your own risk.
See also: http://placedog.com/ and http://placesheen.com/
Via @nickf
http://placekitten.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cohdoo Highlight: Voice recording iPhone app</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/cohdoo-highlight-voice-recording-iphone-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/cohdoo-highlight-voice-recording-iphone-app/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo, the company that makes the iPhone whiteboard magnets that I&amp;rsquo;ve posted about have just released Highlight a nice iPhone app for voice recordings. It&amp;rsquo;s aimed at helping user researchers record interviews, and is just as useful for recording meetings and conference talks.
To start new sessions, press the New Recording button, and during the recording you can tap the huge green Mark Highlight button, which I could see being useful for marking new questions during interviews, or marking sections of conference talks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pear Note: Note taking utility for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/pear-note-note-taking-utility-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/pear-note-note-taking-utility-mac/</guid>
      <description>Pear Note from Useful Fruit Software is a powerful note-taking tool for Mac OS X. The application integrates text notes with audio and video you can record from interview sessions, meetings, etc.
The notes are time-marked to the video and slides that are being viewed during the recording, so you can click text from your notes, and the app will jump to that time in the recording so you can watch the video or see the slide that went with the note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouEye: User testing with webcam eye tracking</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/youeye-user-testing-webcam-eye-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/youeye-user-testing-webcam-eye-tracking/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.youeye.com/&amp;lsquo;&amp;gt;YouEye looks interesting. The usability testing service allows you to create remote, unmoderated usability test sessions with a small number of tasks, and using the test participant&amp;rsquo;s web browser and web cam, they record eye-tracking results during the test. The service allows you to use paid self-identified test participants from different demographics. Would hope that you could recruit your own testers as well.
http://youeye.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Interaction Design Patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Android Patterns is a community-contributed site with interaction patterns for Android app design. The site is created by the folks at Dutch interaction design firm, UNITiD, who also provide an mobile wireframe templates for Android and Blackberry devices.
http://www.androidpatterns.com/wiki</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phonedoo: Dry erase iPhone sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo makes a nice iPhone UI sketching product called Phone Doos. They are 6.8&amp;quot; by 3.5&amp;quot; dry erase iPhone surfaces with faint grid lines and magnetic backing. A pack contains 10 Phone Doos.
I like that these gives you a surface to work on that can be re-arranged easily on a table and presented on a metallic wall. They have some good screenshots using them arranged on a whiteboard with flow arrows pointing between them, which is another thing that&#39;s probably much easier with these as opposed to using paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Multitouch Gesture Library and Illustrations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/open-source-multitouch-gesture-library-and-illustrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/open-source-multitouch-gesture-library-and-illustrations/</guid>
      <description>GestureWorks, a multitouch framework for Flash, have published their our free gesture icon set, available to use and reuse under a CC license. You can download vector and raster versions, as well as a poster with all 200+ icons. They&amp;rsquo;re also available on flickr as part of their educational project, Open Exhibits.
http://gestureworks.com/features/open-source-gestures/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wirify: Create wireframes from web pages</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/wirify-create-wireframes-web-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/wirify-create-wireframes-web-pages/</guid>
      <description>Wirify is a bookmarklet that lets you turn any web page into a wireframe in one click. Similar to the Web Without Words, it converts all of the elements on a web page to gray boxes, so you can visualize the page as a schematic without content.  This reminds me of a a technique used in painting and design where one steps back a distance from the canvas or screen and blurs the eyes to get a view of the placement of parts of the design, the relationship of the parts to each other, the white space, and the hierarchy of elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clue: A 5 Second Test Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/clue-5-second-test-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/clue-5-second-test-service/</guid>
      <description>Zurb&amp;rsquo;s Clue is another great 5 second test service. They describe it as a fun and easy way to test what people remember on your website.
To use, enter a URL for a page you&#39;d like to test, they generate a screenshot, and provide you with URLs for the test and the test report. Here&#39;s an example using this site: test and report. Feel free to mock my home page at will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UXPin: Paper prototyping redesigned</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/uxpin-paper-prototyping-redesigned/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/uxpin-paper-prototyping-redesigned/</guid>
      <description>UXPin just made it a little easier for you to paper prototype. They&amp;rsquo;ve created a kit with sticky note interface elements (buttons, combo-boxes, check-boxes etc. – 50 each), universal elements (to easily make menus, lists, boxes – 50 each) and a 50 page paper browser notepad packaged in a hard cover case.
http://www.uxpin.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gangsta Lorem Ippzle Dummy Text Generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gangsta-lorem-ippzle-dummy-text-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gangsta-lorem-ippzle-dummy-text-generator/</guid>
      <description>And the lorem ipsum hits keep coming, this time in the form of Gangsta Lorem ippzle dummy text generator. Use at your own risk.
Via Swiss Miss
http://www.lorizzle.nl/?feed=1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fillerati Greeking Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/fillerati-greeking-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/fillerati-greeking-tool/</guid>
      <description>Fillerati is a fun greeking/dummy text alternative if you&amp;rsquo;re not into lorem ipsum, but would love some literary copy. Select an author (Edgar Rice Burroughs, Herman Melville, Jules Verne, and H. G. Wells) and title, and choose an excerpt rendered in html (h1, p, or li) or plain text. A slick slider UI lets you choose the number of words to include in your text. Grab some Fillerati.
Via The Letter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrity: Website link checker and xml sitemap generator for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/integrity-website-link-checker-and-xml-sitemap-generator-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/integrity-website-link-checker-and-xml-sitemap-generator-mac/</guid>
      <description>Doing a website relaunch often requires a good deal of cleanup and checking for link rot. I use a utility called Integrity, created by Shiela Dixon, to crawl a site and generate a report of invalid links, missing links, broken anchors, and broken images. Provides a filterable report and XML export options.
http://peacockmedia.co.uk/integrity/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop Android GUI Set</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/photoshop-android-gui-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/photoshop-android-gui-set/</guid>
      <description>Webdesignshock produced a set of high fidelity Photoshop assets for creating Android designs. Available for free.
http://www.webdesignshock.com/freebies/free-photoshop-android-interface-gui/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProCSSor: CSS Prettifier</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/procssor-css-prettifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/procssor-css-prettifier/</guid>
      <description>ProCSSor is a tool to format your CSS to be readable. Paste, specify URL, or upload file, and then select your options and ProCSSor outputs a cleaned up version of your stylesheet.
http://www.procssor.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review: Sync design comps to iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/review-sync-design-comps-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/review-sync-design-comps-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Review is a simple app to review your visual design comps on the iPhone. You install an app on your mac and an app on your iPhone and pair the two. On the Mac, drop images into Review, and they&amp;rsquo;re synced with the iPhone for previewing at full screen.
http://www.getreviewapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Sketching Notation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-sketching-notation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-sketching-notation/</guid>
      <description>Jakub Linowski created a sketch annotation system for interaction design and provides a free downloadable PDF describing how to use it.
&amp;quot;The interactive sketching notation is an emerging visual language which affords the representation of interface states and event-based user actions. Through a few simple and standardized rules, what the user sees (drawn in greys and blacks) and does (drawn in red) are unified into a coherent sketching system. This unification of both interface and use, intends to enable designers to tell more powerful stories of interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnigraffle Sitemap Generator from Sitemap XML</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-sitemap-generator-sitemap-xml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-sitemap-generator-sitemap-xml/</guid>
      <description>Wireframes Mag pointed to an XML to OmniGraffle Sitmap Generator created by Jason Kunesh at Fuzzy Math to generate a sitemap from an XML file. The script assumes that your XML file consists of url elements, and that parent child relationships are defined by the paths in the url. For instance, http://konigi.com/about-site/unicorns would be a child of http://konigi.com/about-site. Once you generate a list of your urls and pass it to the script, OmniGraffle generates the sitemap hierarchy for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draftboard: Design Review Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/draftboard-design-review-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/draftboard-design-review-tool/</guid>
      <description>Draftboard is a wireframe and visual design review web app for capturing design reviews of your work.
http://www.draftboardapp.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quplo: HTML Prototyping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/quplo-html-prototyping/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/quplo-html-prototyping/</guid>
      <description>Quplo may be the most promising HTML prototyping tools I&amp;rsquo;ve seen for UX designers who know a little HTML and would like to do HTML prototyping, but either don&amp;rsquo;t have the chops to build the interaction by hand, or are lazy like me.
The web-based tool allows you to build multiple prototypes using a combination of standard HTML/CSS. If you can do JS, the standard JS libraries are available to include in your pages (or sheets in Quplo lingo).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch Notation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/touch-notation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/touch-notation/</guid>
      <description>Touch Notation is a simple annotation system created by Matt Gemmell for documenting multi-touch gestures. It&amp;rsquo;s an incredibly simple system when compared to the more literal annotation symbols that use hands, because the symbology can be quickly rendered in sketches as well as being used in wireframing libraries.
The Touch Notation page provides PSD, AI, and OmniGraffle templates. I&#39;ve additionally created a Balsamiq Mockups version of the system on Mockups To Go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataTables (table plug-in for jQuery)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/datatables-table-plug-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/datatables-table-plug-jquery/</guid>
      <description>DataTables is a plug-in for the jQuery Javascript library. It is flexible tool, based upon the foundations of progressive enhancement, which will add advanced interaction controls to any HTML table. Key features:
  Variable length pagination  On-the-fly filtering  Multi-column sorting with data type detection  Smart handling of column widths  Display data from almost any data source  DOM, Javascript array, Ajax file and server-side processing (PHP, C#, Perl, Ruby, AIR, Gears etc)  Fully internationalisable  jQuery UI ThemeRoller support  Wide variety of plug-ins inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AddUse User research service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/adduse-user-research-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/adduse-user-research-service/</guid>
      <description>AddUse is a commercial user research service that allow you to run and analyze web surveys and allows usability test facilitators to manually capture and analyze the results of test sessions.
http://www.adduse.com/Default.aspx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bounce: Screenshot annotation service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/bounce-screenshot-annotation-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/bounce-screenshot-annotation-service/</guid>
      <description>Bounce is a new screen capture service from Zurb that lets you invite other collaborators to annotate screenshots.
Here&#39;s a test page of Konigi for you to defile, er, test.
http://www.bounceapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dapp: The App Design App</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/dapp-app-design-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/dapp-app-design-app/</guid>
      <description>Dapp is an Apple UI Standards professional rapid application development tool that runs in the iPhone. It lets you design iPhone app prototypes, publish a spec to PDF, and generate iPhone SDK code.
http://dapp.kerofrog.com.au/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Lists</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/elastic-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/elastic-lists/</guid>
      <description>Elastic Lists is an open source project from Moritz Stefaner that allows you to create a faceted browsing interface for navigating large, multi-dimensional info spaces with just a few clicks, never letting you run into situations with zero results. Elastic Lists is an Apache licensed, AS3 project for use in Flash CS4 or Flex.
http://moritz.stefaner.eu/projects/elastic-lists/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LiveView for iPhone &amp; iPad</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone-ipad/</guid>
      <description>LiveView is a free remote screen viewing application created by Nicholas Zambetti to help designers create graphics for mobile applications, and for quick and dirty simulations, demos, and prototypes.
Visual Designers may use it to view artboard while you work. LiveView is compatible with both standard and Retina displays. Interaction Designers can use with iPhone or iPad tethered via WiFi, to interact with software prototypes and demos running on your Mac to communicate and iterate your concepts quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sencha Touch HTML5 Mobile App Framework</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</guid>
      <description>Sencha Touch looks like an excellent toolkit for delivering HTML 5/CSS 3 mobile experiences. Check out these demos your mobile device to give it a test run: GeoCongress (makes use of geolocation), Solitaire (drag and drop and flip animations), Kiva (provides iPad popover controls).
Sencha Touch allows you to develop web apps that look and feel native on Apple iOS and Google Android touchscreen devices. It&#39;s built specifically to leverage HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript and makes use of HTML5 to deliver components like audio and video, as well as a localStorage proxy for saving data offline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things@kureno Lorem Ipsum Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/thingskureno-lorem-ipsum-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/thingskureno-lorem-ipsum-tool/</guid>
      <description>things@kureno has a fantastic lorem ipsum tool that lets you select the type of copy you want to generate (paragraphs, headings, lists, etc.) and the voice of the writer (business, design studio, tech talk), and then copy the styled text as html.
http://things.kureno.com/Lorem-Ipsum-tool</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Extensions for web developers </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/google-chrome-extensions-web-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/google-chrome-extensions-web-developers/</guid>
      <description>Google Chrome’s developer extensions are useful in-browser web development tools for such things as testing pages on various screen resolutions, analyzing app performance, working with HTML, CSS, JS, generating lorem ipsum greeking, and more.
https://chrome.google.com/extensions/featured/web_dev</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrometric: Color Blindness Simulator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/chrometric-color-blindness-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/chrometric-color-blindness-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Chrometric is an excellent color application that simulates eight types of color blindness, blur (&amp;quot;forgotten glasses&amp;quot;), and reduced contrast (a.k.a my laptop screen on a sunny day). It is essentially a web browser, and allows you to check webpage address you enter into it. It&amp;rsquo;s an Adobe AIR, so it works on Mac/Linux/Win.
http://enably.com/chrometric/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Scheme Designer 3</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/color-scheme-designer-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/color-scheme-designer-3/</guid>
      <description>Petr Stanicek&amp;rsquo;s Color Scheme Designer is a web-based color scheme selector that allows you to select a color, generate a palette of color combinations, view the palette as a sample web page, and with color deficit simulators. Lastly, the color palette you generated can be exported as HTML/CSS or as a Photoshop palette.
http://colorschemedesigner.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GestureWorks Open Source Multitouch Gesture Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</guid>
      <description>GestureWorks is a multitouch authoring environment for Flash and Flex that ships with a library of over 20 unique gestures. This gesture library is built upon an open source gesture framework, allowing developers to customize and extend the “gesture object” to create support for new gestures. The library is available for GestureWorks, and posters in PNG, PDF and AI format are also provided.
http://gestureworks.com/about/open-source-gesture-library/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Grid Overlay with CSS and JQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/quick-grid-overlay-css-and-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/quick-grid-overlay-css-and-jquery/</guid>
      <description>Griddy is a simple JQuery plugin that overlays a customizable grid over any element.
http://devgrow.com/griddy/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch Gesture Reference Guide</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/touch-gesture-reference-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/touch-gesture-reference-guide/</guid>
      <description>Luke Wroblewski&amp;rsquo;s Touch Gesture Reference Guide is a set of resources for software designers and developers working on touch-based user interfaces. The guide contains: 1) an overview of the core gestures used for most touch commands 2) how to utilize these gestures to support major user actions 3) visual representations of each gesture to use in design documentation and deliverables 4) an outline of how popular software platforms support core touch gestures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vyoopoint Design Presentations Tool - A Must-Have for Every Creative Professional</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/vyoopoint-design-presentations-tool-must-have-every-creative-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/vyoopoint-design-presentations-tool-must-have-every-creative-professional/</guid>
      <description>Vyoopoint is an online design presentations tool. It makes it easy to create and review a website design presentation or any other design project. Suitable for creative professionals - from freelancers to large advertising agencies. It supports flash files, allows not only text comments but also image markups and video markups, has automated version control and many more&amp;hellip; Check its features!
http://vyoopoint.com/about/why/why_vyoopoint/index.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When can I use... HTML5, CSS3, etc.</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</guid>
      <description>Can I Use provides compatibility tables for features in HTML5, CSS3, SVG and other upcoming web technologies.
http://caniuse.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A wireframe kit for Google Drawings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/wireframe-kit-google-drawings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/wireframe-kit-google-drawings/</guid>
      <description>Morten Just created wireframe templates using the new drawing tools available for Google Docs. The illustration tools in Docs gives you basic shapes you need to create UI elements that can be combined and grouped to create components. The biggest advantage is that since it&amp;rsquo;s document authoring in the Docs cloud, you can do collaborative editing.
For what it&#39;s worth, I don&#39;t think this is ideal, but it is interesting because of the online collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gesturecons: Multi-Touch Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gesturecons-multi-touch-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gesturecons-multi-touch-icons/</guid>
      <description>Gesture icons created for wireframing touch interfaces. High resolution multi-touch vector icons, scalable and alterable (.pdf, .ai, .eps file types.) Free for personal use, and commercial licenses are available.
http://gesturecons.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicker Studio: Touchscreen Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/kicker-studio-touchscreen-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/kicker-studio-touchscreen-stencils/</guid>
      <description>Gesture stencils based on drawings Rachel Glaves did for the book, &amp;quot;Designing Gestural Interfaces,&amp;quot; suitable for using in documentation. The drawings are of hands performing common touchscreen gestures like tap, slide, point, drag, pinch, and spread. Available in OmniGraffle, Illustrator, Photoshop, Fireworks and SVG formats.
http://www.kickerstudio.com/blog/2008/12/touchscreen-stencils/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typinator: Automatic text software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/typinator-automatic-text-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/typinator-automatic-text-software/</guid>
      <description>Since starting work at Balsamiq I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing customer support every day. Part of that work is repeatedly referencing the same URLS and instructions for frequently asked questions. Peldi and Val handle the volume by using Typinator, a Mac utility that lets you define text shortcuts that you trigger to complete these answers.
Years ago, pre-OS X, used something called TypeIt4Me to handle this and am stoked to have this kind of a tool back in my aresenal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Feedback - Website Review Community</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback-website-review-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback-website-review-community/</guid>
      <description>Concept Feedback is a website review community with over 5,000 web designers and developers, marketers and entrepreneurs. Once a website is posted on Concept Feedback, members are invited to provide reviews. On average, a concept receives 12 or more unique reviews, while some can generate as many as 100. Because of the nature of the community, feedback can cover a variety of topics, including design, usability, content and strategy. Concept Feedback is best for getting design-related feedback from a wide audience and can be used at all stages of development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenHallway: Unmoderated Remote Usability Testing with Screen Recording</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/openhallway-unmoderated-remote-usability-testing-screen-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/openhallway-unmoderated-remote-usability-testing-screen-recording/</guid>
      <description>Inspired by the 5 second test, a lot web-based services have cropped up to support remote usability testing. In the past few years, I&#39;ve been experimenting with some of these to conduct super small, unmoderated remote usability testing sessions. I&#39;ve used Morae extensively in the past, but for most of my needs, that&#39;s like using a sledgehammer on a pushpin.
I&#39;d been successful using fivesecondtest and Usabilla, who decided to sponsor me after I participated in the beta and gave feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML-Ipsum</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/html-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/html-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>HTML Ipsum gives you HTML versions of lorem ipsum, with markup for stuff like lists and forms.
http://html-ipsum.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal Coda Clips</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/drupal-coda-clips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/drupal-coda-clips/</guid>
      <description>Dezinerfolio&amp;rsquo;s free Drupal snippet library for the Coda editor (Mac OS only) provides a very useful set of code clips for theming Drupal sites.
http://www.dezinerfolio.com/freebie/drupal-coda-clips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LESS: Simple CSS variables and more</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/less-simple-css-variables-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/less-simple-css-variables-and-more/</guid>
      <description>The LESS Ruby gem compiles LESS code into CSS. LESS extends CSS with variables, mixins, operations, and extended rules, and uses existing CSS syntax. You simply rename your .css files as .less files and compile with a plugin or a simple app like LESS.app for the Mac.
http://lesscss.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhoneGap | Cross platform mobile framework</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/phonegap-cross-platform-mobile-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonegap-cross-platform-mobile-framework/</guid>
      <description>PhoneGap is an open source development tool for building fast, easy mobile apps with JavaScript. If you’re a web developer who wants to build mobile applications in HTML and JavaScript while still taking advantage of the core features in the iPhone, Android, Palm, Symbian and Blackberry SDKs, PhoneGap is for you.
http://phonegap.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau Public: Visualization Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/tableau-public-visualization-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/tableau-public-visualization-service/</guid>
      <description>Tableau Public is a free service that lets anyone publish interactive data to the web. Once on the web, anyone can interact with the data, download it, or create their own visualizations of it. No programming skills are required. Windows is required for the desktop application.
The free version of Tableau Public is for writers, bloggers, students, professors, hobbyists, journeymen, critics, citizens and more. It’s also meant for organizations, but only as an introductory service, and for continued use requires commercial licensing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Stencil for Omnigraffle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ipad-stencil-omnigraffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ipad-stencil-omnigraffle/</guid>
      <description>iA have created an iPad stencil for OmniGraffle. Contains backgrounds, title bars, buttons, selectors, and other iPhone UI elements. Based the iPad PSD GUI by Teehan+Lax. Text is fully editable on lists, title bars, buttons, and scroll wheels
Download and read more at iA
http://informationarchitects.jp/ipad-stencil-for-omnigraffle/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhoneOS Design Stencil for iPhone and iPad</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphoneos-design-stencil-iphone-and-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphoneos-design-stencil-iphone-and-ipad/</guid>
      <description>An iPhone OS OmniGraffle stencil for designing applications for iPhone, iPod touch and iPad devices. The stencil, for now, is targeted at developers familiar with the default characteristics of views and controls provided by UIKit. The stencil shapes are all vector based. The initial focus is on views and controls provided by UIKit and recommended application styles as discussed in the iPhone and iPad Human Interface Guidelines.
http://www.morford.org/iphoneosdesignstencil/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SublimeVideo HTML 5 Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sublimevideo-html-5-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sublimevideo-html-5-video-player/</guid>
      <description>SublimeVideo is an HTML5 video player with full screen play and scrubbing controls. Because it&amp;rsquo;s HTML5, the controls may be styled and no plugins are required. Presently supports Safari, Chrome, and IE with Chromeframe installed. Firefox support forthcoming. Will be available for free for non-commercial use.
Via @dandean
http://jilion.com/sublime/video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brosho - Design CSS in the browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/brosho-design-css-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/brosho-design-css-browser/</guid>
      <description>This plugin allows you to reduce the amount of time spent switching between browser windows. With this jquery plugin included on a page, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to select individual elements and write css code for it right in your browser. Changes are updated on the fly, so you can see your style changes as you write them.
The CSS generated by your edits can then be generated and copy-pasted into your stylesheet file for minor edits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SimpleDiagrams</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/simplediagrams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/simplediagrams/</guid>
      <description>SimpleDiagrams is an Adobe AIR desktop application for diagramming. It&amp;rsquo;s useful for simple illustrations that you might create on a whiteboard or in a tool like OmniGraffle. There&amp;rsquo;s a free version, which lets you use built in stencil libraries and export to PNG. The paid version gets rid of upgrade reminders, allows you to export to Basecamp, import libraries, and install on multiple machines.
http://www.simplediagrams.com/home</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML Wireframe Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/html-wireframe-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/html-wireframe-tool/</guid>
      <description>Waiting for your thumbnail&amp;hellip;
This is an interesting looking tool that lets you create HTML wireframes using a web interface. You specify your grid, then insert one of the pre-defined UI components into the page. An inspector lets you modify the component attributes. There isn&amp;rsquo;t any information about who is responsible for this tool and if it&amp;rsquo;s merely an experiment or a demo of something we can expect to see in an application or framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> iPhone UI </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-ui/</guid>
      <description>A JavaScript library to prototype web interfaces for the iPhone.
http://iphone.hohli.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LiveView for iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone/</guid>
      <description>LiveView is great little freebie for UI design &amp;amp; prototyping on iPhone. Essentially it sends a 320x480 viewport from your Mac to your iPhone, so is useful for creating quick and dirty simulations, demos, and user experience prototypes.
http://www.zambetti.com/projects/liveview/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabble Client for Yammer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gabble-client-yammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gabble-client-yammer/</guid>
      <description>Gabble is a native Mac OS X client for Yammer, the micro-messaging application for companies.
http://erikhinterbichler.com/software/gabble/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS3 Gradient Generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/css3-gradient-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/css3-gradient-generator/</guid>
      <description>The CSS3 Gradient Generator tool creates the CSS needed to render gradient backgrounds in block elements, e.g. divs and buttons, in Mozilla or Webkit browsers, e.g. Safari or Google Chrome, or the Firefox 3.6 beta.
http://gradients.glrzad.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UKI: Simple UI Kit for complex web apps</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/uki-simple-ui-kit-complex-web-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/uki-simple-ui-kit-complex-web-apps/</guid>
      <description>Uki is a fast and simple JavaScript user interface toolkit for desktop-like web applications. It comes with a rich view-component library ranging from Slider to List and SplitPane.
http://ukijs.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQTouch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/jqtouch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/jqtouch/</guid>
      <description>jQtouch is a jQuery plugin for mobile web development on the iPhone, iPod Touch, and other forward-thinking devices. It provides themed UI components, and behaviors using native Webkit animation.
http://www.jqtouch.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQuery Masonry</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/jquery-masonry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/jquery-masonry/</guid>
      <description>Masonry is a layout plugin for jQuery. Think of it as the flip side of CSS floats. Whereas floating arranges elements horizontally then vertically, Masonry arranges elements vertically then horizontally according to a grid. The result minimizes vertical gaps between elements of varying height, just like a mason fitting stones in a wall.
http://desandro.com/resources/jquery-masonry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy front-end framework</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/easy-front-end-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/easy-front-end-framework/</guid>
      <description>Easy Framework is a CSS/HTML/JavaScript framework created by Alen Grakalic. It provides a simple foundation for creating front end templates and provides a cookbook of jQuery-powered interactive behaviors you can use in your prototypes.
http://easyframework.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Browser Size</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/google-browser-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/google-browser-size/</guid>
      <description>Google Browser Size is a visualization of browser window sizes for web sites. Enter a URL into the app, and the page is displayed behind an overlay showing the percentage of browser users who are able to view the visible portion, based on their browser&amp;rsquo;s available viewport size, and their display&amp;rsquo;s screen resolution. For example, the &amp;quot;90%&amp;quot; contour means that 90% of people visiting the site have their browser window open to at least this size or larger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StaticMatic: Static HTML building framework</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/staticmatic-static-html-building-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/staticmatic-static-html-building-framework/</guid>
      <description>StaticMatic is a Ruby-powered framework for building static HTML prototypes. It builds your directory structure and files, uses templates for common page elements, uses Haml (HTML abstraction markup language) to generate markup, and Sass to create your CSS.
Via Jérôme Gravel-Niquet on the htmlprototyping group
http://staticmatic.rubyforge.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zen Coding: Plugins for HTML and CSS hi-speed coding</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/zen-coding-plugins-html-and-css-hi-speed-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/zen-coding-plugins-html-and-css-hi-speed-coding/</guid>
      <description>Zen Coding is plugin for HTML editors that allows you to use shorthand to generate HTML. I twas created and supported by Sergey Chikuyonok for Aptana, TextMate, Coda and Espresso. It is based on JavaScript (for Aptana) or Python (the rest of all) script and using more advanced Zen HTML Selectors logic for building HTML. The demo video below shows Zen Coding in action.
 Via se on the htmlprototyping group</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>960 grid template for OmniGraffle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/960-grid-template-omnigraffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/960-grid-template-omnigraffle/</guid>
      <description>I’m a big fan of increasing efficiency and consistency from conceptual design to implementation. This OmniGraffle template has helped me quite a bit in that regard, and I decided to share it with others.
http://briancray.com/2009/11/30/omnigraffle-wireframing-960-grid-template/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highcharts: Interactive JavaScript charts</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/highcharts-interactive-javascript-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/highcharts-interactive-javascript-charts/</guid>
      <description>Highcharts is a charting library written in pure JavaScript, offering an easy way of adding interactive charts to your web site or web application. Highcharts currently supports line, spline, area, areaspline, column, bar, pie and scatter chart types. It works with either the jQuery or Moo Tools javascript frameworks and is free for non-commercial use. Commercial licenses are offered as well.
http://highcharts.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ImageOptim: PNG/JPEG/GIF optimizer for Mac OS X</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/imageoptim-pngjpeggif-optimizer-mac-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/imageoptim-pngjpeggif-optimizer-mac-os-x/</guid>
      <description>ImageOptim is a free Macintosh application that optimizes images so they take up less disk space and load faster. It finds the best compression parameters and by removing unnecessary comments and color profiles. It handles PNG, JPEG and GIF animations.
Via @chrismessina
http://imageoptim.pornel.net/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQSlickWrap: Text Wrapping Plugin for jQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/jqslickwrap-text-wrapping-plugin-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/jqslickwrap-text-wrapping-plugin-jquery/</guid>
      <description>jQSlickWrap is a plugin for jQuery that allows you to wrap text around the actual contents of an irregularly-shaped image rather than it&amp;rsquo;s bounding box using CSS floats.
http://jwf.us/projects/jQSlickWrap/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ixEdit: Visual Tool for Prototyping with jQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ixedit-visual-tool-prototyping-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ixedit-visual-tool-prototyping-jquery/</guid>
      <description>ixEdit is a JavaScript-based interaction design tool for the web. With IxEdit, designers can practice DOM-scripting without coding to change, add, move, or transform elements dynamically on your web pages. It&amp;rsquo;s specifically designed for HTML prototyping and allows designers to build interactive interfaces directly in the browser, and provides the code to copy and paste into the HTML page. Works with Firefox, Safari, Chrome, or IE. Watch the video below to see how it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chroma-Hash Password Masking</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/chroma-hash-password-masking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/chroma-hash-password-masking/</guid>
      <description>Chroma-Hash is a jQuery script that Mattt Thompson created to explore a visual method for confirmation password matches during confirmation on login and registration forms. The idea is similar to Identicon, but uses a small colored bars in the input to visually check your strings. He describes the project on Mattt.com and you can try the demo out on GitHub or download it. Versions supporting other libraries are also linked from this page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone-like Passwords using jQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-passwords-using-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-passwords-using-jquery/</guid>
      <description>Stefan Ullrich&amp;rsquo;s jQuery plugin on the DECAF site provides a behavior for masking passwords that is familiar to mobile users. The plugin obscures previously entered characters at delayed intervals or when new characters are entered. It falls back on using the browser&amp;rsquo;s password masking when JS is disabled.
http://blog.decaf.de/2009/07/iphone-like-password-fields-using-jquery/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockingbird</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mockingbird/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mockingbird/</guid>
      <description>Mockingbird is a web-based service for quickly creating multi-page, click through wireframes or prototypes using a library of UI components. It&amp;rsquo;s written on the Cappuccino web framework, so the prototypes don&amp;rsquo;t require Flash.
http://gomockingbird.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protoscript: Prototype Scripting Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/protoscript-prototype-scripting-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/protoscript-prototype-scripting-library/</guid>
      <description>Protoscript is a prototype scripting library utilizing both jQuery and YUI behaviors to add interactivity to HTML elements. By combining different behaviors with different elements and events you can create complex interactions without writing JavaScript.
Via @egregilon
http://protoscript.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchy Axure Widget Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketchy-axure-widget-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketchy-axure-widget-library/</guid>
      <description>Ascentium have posted a library of sketch-style wireframe stencils/widgets. You can view more information and download the stencils from their blog and view a functional prototype of the widgets.
http://xrm.ascentium.com/blog/ux-seo/Post222.aspx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrollbar Contents (aka Visual Page Contents)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/scrollbar-contents-aka-visual-page-contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/scrollbar-contents-aka-visual-page-contents/</guid>
      <description>Scrollbar Contents is a jQuery plugin created by Thomas Hooper to create a scrollbar that represents post/comment volume visually.
http://www.stainlessvision.com/scrollbar-contents-aka-visual-page-contents</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 3G Stencil</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-3g-stencil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-3g-stencil/</guid>
      <description>This is a new version of Theresa Neil&amp;rsquo;s iPhone stencil for the 3G phone. Includes standard interface components for the iPhone 3G: buttons, fields, map elements, keyboards, and icons.
http://www.graffletopia.com/stencils/495</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABtests.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/abtestscom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/abtestscom/</guid>
      <description>ABtests.com is a new service from Bokardo, Performable, and Kissmetrics that will allow people test their web sites/applications and share that knowledge with others, making everyone smarter in the process. They&amp;rsquo;ll let you upload and share your results, view other people&amp;rsquo;s test results. http://www.abtests.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn any webform into a powerful wizard with jQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/turn-any-webform-powerful-wizard-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/turn-any-webform-powerful-wizard-jquery/</guid>
      <description>The FormToWizard plugin for jQuery allows you to break up form fieldsets to create a stepped wizard-like flow. You can download and view the demo via Janko at Warp Speed.
http://www.jankoatwarpspeed.com/post/2009/09/28/webform-wizard-jquery.aspx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk SketchBook Mobile Brings Sketching to iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-brings-sketching-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-brings-sketching-iphone/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had SketchBook Pro for the Mac for a few years now. I bought it before it was acquired by Autodesk from Alias, mostly for art work, but also to experiment with it as a tool for interface sketching. But while I wanted to use it more, I find myself falling back on paper and pencil almost all of the time. Autodesk recently released iPhone versions of the app (1 version is free, and the full version is $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treejack - Information architecture testing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/treejack-information-architecture-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/treejack-information-architecture-testing/</guid>
      <description>Treejack is a tool to help you test the effectiveness of an information architecture.&amp;nbsp; Use it to find out which categories are strong, which labels need tweaking and what tasks people are struggling with.&amp;nbsp; Because you can upload an existing or proposed IA, and test with participants remotely, you get rapid feedback at a fraction of the cost of in-person testing.
Often, usability testing only reveals flaws with the interaction and interface elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ForeUI: Create Skinnable &amp; Interactive Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/foreui-create-skinnable-interactive-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/foreui-create-skinnable-interactive-prototype/</guid>
      <description>ForeUI is a handy UI prototyping tool. It can rapidly create skinnable and
clickable UI prototype for your website or software, and run the interactive
simulation in your web browser.
ForeUI provides a set of predefined elements for creating mockup, you can drag
them into the editing area and tweak them. You can also create your own elements
and libraries.
ForeUI makes prototype skinnable, by changing the UI theme, all elements in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fontcapture.com: Create fonts from your handwriting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/fontcapturecom-create-fonts-your-handwriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/fontcapturecom-create-fonts-your-handwriting/</guid>
      <description>fontcapture might be interesting to people who create sketch-style wireframes, but don&amp;rsquo;t like using Apple&amp;rsquo;s Casual or Comic Sans. Simply download and fill in the font template, scan and upload it to fontcatpure, and download your completed font, usable on both Windows and Mac computers.
http://www.fontcapture.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Sketchbook: iPhone App Sketchbook</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/app-sketchbook-iphone-app-sketchbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/app-sketchbook-iphone-app-sketchbook/</guid>
      <description>This is sweet. A sketchbook made for iPhone app design. Features three actual-size iPhone templates per page, pixel (20px) ruler and title bar markings, ruled section for app development notes, and 600 screens (100 double-sided pages).
http://appsketchbook.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camtasia for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/camtasia-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/camtasia-mac/</guid>
      <description>TechSmith, makers of Morae and Snagit, have released a Mac version of Camtasia, the screencast video recording software. The software allows you to capture the screen, audio and iSight input, and provides simple drag and drop editing including a lot of built-in transitions and effects. You can then easily export the HTML and SWF for embedding in a web page. Looks like an easy to use alternative that might take the work out of producing screencasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenr Screencasting Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/screenr-screencasting-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/screenr-screencasting-service/</guid>
      <description>Screenr is a web-based screen capture tool that lets you record screen video and audio from your Mac or PC and posts a link to the video, hosted on Screenr.com, to your Twitter stream.
http://screenr.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SlideSix Multimedia Presentation Sharing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/slidesix-multimedia-presentation-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/slidesix-multimedia-presentation-sharing/</guid>
      <description>SlideSix is a presentation sharing service that let&amp;rsquo;s you upload presentations (PowerPoint, OpenOffice, PDF) with recorded narration or video imported from the web, e.g. from YouTube. Presentation pages provide social features (comments and chat), embedding info, and rating.
http://slidesix.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napkee: Create Prototypes from Balsamiq Mockups</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/napkee-create-prototypes-balsamiq-mockups/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/napkee-create-prototypes-balsamiq-mockups/</guid>
      <description>Napkee is a very exciting tool that extends the quick and easy wireframing process in Balsamiq Mockups by importing your Balsamiq files and generating interactive prototypes in Flex or HTML version.
To start off, you build your series of wireframes in Mockups, optionally creating links between pages. The screenshot below shows a wireframe of a fictional news site I created to try it out. I mocked up a site home page, and a login screen for my test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When can I use... (Browser Technology Compatibility Table)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-browser-technology-compatibility-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-browser-technology-compatibility-table/</guid>
      <description>When can I use is a browser compatibility table for features in HTML5, CSS3, SVG and other upcoming web technologies. Select the technologies/standards you want to implement and the browsers you want to test. Color coded tables show which browser versions will support what you&amp;rsquo;ve selected.
http://a.deveria.com/caniuse/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NonVisual Desktop Access (NVDA) Screen Reader     </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/nonvisual-desktop-access-nvda-screen-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/nonvisual-desktop-access-nvda-screen-reader/</guid>
      <description>NonVisual Desktop Access (NVDA) is a free and open source screen reader for the Microsoft Windows operating system. Providing feedback via synthetic speech and Braille, it enables blind or vision impaired people to access computers running Windows for no more cost than a sighted person. Major features include support for over 20 languages and the ability to run entirely from a USB drive with no installation.
http://www.nvda-project.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to CSS support in email clients</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/guide-css-support-email-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/guide-css-support-email-clients/</guid>
      <description>Campaign Monitor provides a table showing the level of CSS support in the 23 different email clients they test, and covers all the popular applications across desktop, web and mobile email. The web-based version of the guide focusses on the 10 most popular email clients on the market, and they provide a complete report on all 23 email clients in PDF format.
http://www.campaignmonitor.com/css/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start-Up Forms Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/start-forms-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/start-forms-library/</guid>
      <description>Orrick Start-Up Tool Kit provides free legal forms that you will need to start and grow your company.
(via @balsamiq)
http://www.orrick.com/practices/corporate/emergingCompanies/startup/forms_index.asp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Prism: CSS color inspector</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/css-prism-css-color-inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/css-prism-css-color-inspector/</guid>
      <description>CSS Prism is a tool created by Ryan Berg to inspect the colors used in a CSS file.
http://cssprism.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fireworks Script for iPhone App Prototypes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/fireworks-script-iphone-app-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/fireworks-script-iphone-app-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>The iPhone extension helps create a mockup of an iPhone application in Fireworks. It automatically adds the iPhone wrapper when you preview the mockup, or package it for distribution as an AIR application. The slide-in, slide-out effects that are charecteristic of iPhone can be generated using this extension.Updated resolution to 480X320.
http://www.adobe.com/cfusion/exchange/index.cfm?event=extensionDetail&amp;extid=1786031</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OverSite: Wireframe Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/oversite-wireframe-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/oversite-wireframe-software/</guid>
      <description>OverSite is a cross-platform application for wireframing and prototyping. It uses a drag and drop interface and can build HTL prototypes from your linked pages.
The app lets you define the hierarchy of your website or application, create sections and subsections, fill them with pages and screens, and rearrange your structure using a drag-and-drop interface. The app automatically generates a site map, and any changes you make to your structure will instantly be reflected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UserTesting.com: Automated usability testing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usertestingcom-automated-usability-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usertestingcom-automated-usability-testing/</guid>
      <description>UserTesting is a commercial service that promises automated usability testing.
You might think of this as a series of task-oriented usability test sessions where you only need enter a number of tasks for a test that will take approximately 15 minutes, enter the demographics (age, income) and technographics (computer experience) for the user you&#39;d like to target. UserTesting has a pool of paid testers who accept sessions, view your site with a floating layer that shows the tasks to complete while they record their voice, mouse clicks and movements, and page changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS 3 Cheat Sheet (PDF)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/css-3-cheat-sheet-pdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/css-3-cheat-sheet-pdf/</guid>
      <description>Smashing Magazine&amp;rsquo;s printable CSS 3 Cheat Sheet provides a complete listing of all the properties, selectors types and allowed values in the current CSS 3 specification from the W3C. Each property is provided in a section that attempts to match it with the section (module) that it is most actively associated within the W3C specification. Next to each property is a listing of the expected values that that property takes (normal text shows named values it accepts and italics shows value types it will accept).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Explorer Collection: Installs multiple IE versions on 1 PC</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/internet-explorer-collection-installs-multiple-ie-versions-1-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/internet-explorer-collection-installs-multiple-ie-versions-1-pc/</guid>
      <description>Internet Explorer Collection is an installer that allows you to install multiple versions of IE on 1 Windows instance. It includes the IE 1.0, 1.5, 2.01, 3.0, 4.01, 5.01, 5.5, 6.0, 7.0, and 8.0.
http://utilu.com/IECollection/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infomaki: Open Source Usability Testing Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/infomaki-open-source-usability-testing-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/infomaki-open-source-usability-testing-software/</guid>
      <description>Infomaki is a Ruby on Rails application developed by the New York Public Library as a way of rapidly testing alternate designs and navigation language with minimal disruption to users. NYPL are using it to power http://usability.nypl.org and test new designs for the main NYPL.org web site. More and documentation is available at the NYPL Labs blog, http://labs.nypl.org.
https://sourceforge.net/projects/infomaki/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SlickMap CSS: HTML Sitemapping Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/slickmap-css-html-sitemapping-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/slickmap-css-html-sitemapping-tool/</guid>
      <description>Matt Everson of Astuteo has created SlickMap CSS, a simple stylesheet for displaying finished sitemaps directly from HTML unordered list navigation. It’s suitable for most web sites – accommodating up to three levels of page navigation and additional utility links – and can easily be customized to meet your own individual needs, branding, or style preferences.
Via David Kaneda
http://astuteo.com/slickmap/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EightShapes Unify  </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/eightshapes-unify/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/eightshapes-unify/</guid>
      <description>EightShapes Unify is a collection of templates, libraries, and other assets that enable user experience designers to create more consistent, effective deliverables faster. The system utilizes the Adobe Creative Suite of products; primarily, Adobe InDesign is the key authoring tool.
http://unify.eightshapes.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Userfocus 247 Web Usability Guidelines</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/userfocus-247-web-usability-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/userfocus-247-web-usability-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Userfocus provides guidelines for evaluating web site usability. The cover the following different contexts.
 Home page usability Task orientation Navigation and IA Forms and data entry Trust and credibility Writing and content quality Page layout and visual design Search usability Help, feedback and error tolerance 
http://www.userfocus.co.uk/resources/guidelines.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictaculous Color Palette Generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/pictaculous-color-palette-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/pictaculous-color-palette-generator/</guid>
      <description>Pictaculous is a color service provided by MailChimp that takes an image you upload, samples the colors, and then provides a palette from the color samples, color palette suggestions from Kuler and Colour Lovers, and a downloadable Adobe color swatch. Works on the iPhone as well by emailing photos to the service.
http://pictaculous.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 1Kb CSS Grid</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/1kb-css-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/1kb-css-grid/</guid>
      <description>The 1KB Grid is a simple, lightweight CSS framework that weighs in at 1K and handles fixed or fluid layouts. More info here.
http://www.1kbgrid.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Check My Colours: Analyse the color contrast of your web pages</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/check-my-colours-analyse-color-contrast-your-web-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/check-my-colours-analyse-color-contrast-your-web-pages/</guid>
      <description>CheckMyColours is a tool for checking foreground and background color combinations of all DOM elements and determining if they provide sufficient contrast when viewed by someone having color deficits. All the tests are based on the algorithms suggested by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C).
(Via SwissMiss)
http://www.checkmycolours.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldspace Accesibility Analysis Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/worldspace-accesibility-analysis-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/worldspace-accesibility-analysis-service/</guid>
      <description>Worldspace is an accessibility analysis tool designed by Deque to identify errors with Section 508, and the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines.
http://worldspace.deque.com/wsservice/eval/checkCompliance.jsp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Feedback</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Concept Feedback.com is a free community where designers and developers can exchange feedback on design projects. Registered users have the ability to post marketing concepts for free. Concepts may include, but are not limited to, websites, logos, newsletters, landing pages, advertisements and videos. Reviewers can offer constructive feedback on each concept using a proprietary feedback tool. Feedback is automatically collected and archived for the user to help improve the final concept and get better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dey Alexander&#39;s User Experience Design Resources </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/dey-alexanders-user-experience-design-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/dey-alexanders-user-experience-design-resources/</guid>
      <description>Dey Alexander Consulting&amp;rsquo;s user experience design resources directory is an extensive, categorized collection of bibliographies, tools, and resources.
http://deyalexander.com/resources/uxd/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAApps: UX Software Directory</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iaapps-ux-software-directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iaapps-ux-software-directory/</guid>
      <description>IAApps is a directory of usability, information architecture, and user experience design software.
http://www.iaapps.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use It Better: Usability Testing Service for Flash Sites</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/use-it-better-usability-testing-service-flash-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/use-it-better-usability-testing-service-flash-sites/</guid>
      <description>Use It Better is an online tool for recording user sessions for testing &amp;amp; analysing user experience and usability on Adobe Flash websites.
http://www.useitbetter.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clixpy.com Click Path Tracking</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/clixpycom-click-path-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/clixpycom-click-path-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Clixpy is a service that tracks everything your site’s users do, from mouse movement, clicks, and scrolling, to form inputs. The user sessions are as video for you to analyze. Installation requires pasting a few lines of JavaScript into your pages. Check out their excellent demo to see how it works.
http://clixpy.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handbook of Usability Testing: Templates and Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/handbook-usability-testing-templates-and-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/handbook-usability-testing-templates-and-forms/</guid>
      <description>The Handbook of Usability Testing, by Jeffrey Rubin and Dana Chisnell, describes how to plan, design, and conduct effective tests. The books site includes a downloads page with templates and examples of usability test plans, questionairres, test scripts, and consent forms.
http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/WileyTitle/productCd-0470185481,descCd-DOWNLOAD.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usability.gov Templates &amp; Examples</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usabilitygov-templates-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usabilitygov-templates-examples/</guid>
      <description>Usability.gov has a very comprehensive set of templates, forms, and examples that are organized by steps in the usability process: Plan, Analyze, Design, Test and Refine. They can be customized for your organization&amp;rsquo;s usability needs. All of these are in the public domain and can be freely downloaded.
Among the most useful of the files you&amp;rsquo;ll find in this collection are commonly used usability test plan templates, waivers and consent forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Grids CSS</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/yahoo-grids-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/yahoo-grids-css/</guid>
      <description>The Yahoo! UI Library&amp;rsquo;s Grids CSS framework might seem hard to grok at first, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for the past year on a commercial project and find that it&amp;rsquo;s solid for liquid CSS layouts. The grid builder helps to visualize what&amp;rsquo;s possible and view the rather obscure naming conventions they use in CSS classes.
The framework offers four preset page widths, six preset templates, and the ability to stack and nest subdivided regions of two, three, or four columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boks: Visual Grid Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/boks-visual-grid-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/boks-visual-grid-editor/</guid>
      <description>Boks is a cross-platform AIR app for visually creating grids using the Blueprint CSS framework. The app provides an inspector for setting up the page, column and gutter widths, provides typography settings for setting the vertical rhythm of your text, and generates the CSS and grid background image for you to export. Once your grid is set, draw sections in your grid, add lorem ipsum greeking, and the export file will include an HTML template with all of your divs laid out for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FlairBuilder: Interactive Wireframes and Software Prototypes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/flairbuilder-interactive-wireframes-and-software-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/flairbuilder-interactive-wireframes-and-software-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>FlairBuilder is a cross-platform tool for rapid authoring of interactive wireframes and software prototypes. It focuses purely on wireframing/prototyping, and provides an experience that looks like it&#39;s targeted at apps like Axure, but work will cross-platform because it&#39;s built on Adobe AIR.
 The application provides a page/canvas editor onto which you may drag and drop UI components. Selecting a component provides a properties inspector so that may set dimensions and stylistic properties, text values, and any other available UI options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zef[a]media UX Templates</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</guid>
      <description>zef[a]media&amp;rsquo;s UX Template package contains sample paper prototypes/wireframes, personas, sitemaps, and user flow diagrams. Requires MS Visio, Word, and Excel.
http://www.zefamedia.com/websites/free-ux-templates/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PolyPage: HTML Prototyping JavaScript Plugin</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/polypage-html-prototyping-javascript-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/polypage-html-prototyping-javascript-plugin/</guid>
      <description>Polypage is a JQuery plugin that was designed to ease the process of showing multiple page states in html mock-ups. By simply adding class names to a document you can imply state and conditional view logic.
You can view a tutorial for setting up a Polypage project at 24 ways. The latest version is available from the github repository.
http://code.new-bamboo.co.uk/polypage/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touchscreen Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/touchscreen-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/touchscreen-stencils/</guid>
      <description>Dan Saffer of Kicker Studio provides free touch screen gesture stencils for OmniGraffle, Visio, Illustrator, and Fireworks. The icons are designed by Rachel Glaves for Saffer&amp;rsquo;s book, Designing Gestural Interfaces, and depict hands performing common touchscreen gestures like tap, slide, point, drag, pinch, and spread.
http://www.kickerstudio.com/blog/2008/12/touchscreen-stencils/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility Checklist</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/accessibility-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/accessibility-checklist/</guid>
      <description>Ben Cano has created an accessibility checklist with priority categorized accesibility checkpoints or criteria that map to 14 accessibility principles. Going through the prioritized checklist, the designer/developer takes a gradual approach from minimal acecessibility towards optimal or most accessible.
(This entry posted on behalf of Ben Cano)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usabilla</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla/</guid>
      <description>Usabilla is a remote usability testing service that allows you to quickly create short tests that solicit feedback from your users. The service allows you to direct a few questions using screenshots of pages, e.g. you might ask users what do you like/not like about this page, where would you look to find X? Users then click on screenshot to add markers with their notes or answers.
http://usabilla.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loop11: Online, Unmoderated User Testing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/loop11-online-unmoderated-user-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/loop11-online-unmoderated-user-testing/</guid>
      <description>Loop11 is a web-based user-experience testing tool, allowing companies to conduct online, unmoderated user testing.
Loop11 provides the ability to gain detailed insights and understandings of user behaviour. These insights are obtained via a live interactive environment where users are asked to complete a series of tasks and questions on your website or interface. All interactions are captured, processed and made available in real-time reports.
Loop11 is not a survey or web analytics tool, but a user experience tool helping you to understand user behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Browser Templates (Photoshop)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/web-browser-templates-photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/web-browser-templates-photoshop/</guid>
      <description>An Adobe Photoshop .PSD template with Internet Explorer, Firefox for Mac, and Firefox for Windows browser chrome. Provides a layered PSD of browser windows at the following resolutions: 800×600 pixels, 1024×768 pixels, and 1280×1024 pixels.
http://www.junglejar.com/2009/02/01/browser-templates-webdesign-webapplications/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OS X Widget Library for Axure RP</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/os-x-widget-library-axure-rp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/os-x-widget-library-axure-rp/</guid>
      <description>Free library of OS X widgets for Axure users.
http://www.archive.org/details/AriFeldmanAxureOSXWidgetLibraryv1.01</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silverback Usability Testing Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/silverback-usability-testing-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/silverback-usability-testing-software/</guid>
      <description>Silverback is a simple to use usability testing application that allows you to capture screen activity, record audio and video of the participant’s voice, add chapter markers on the fly, control recording with the remote, and export to Quicktime.
http://silverbackapp.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely Charts Online Diagramming Application</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/lovely-charts-online-diagramming-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/lovely-charts-online-diagramming-application/</guid>
      <description>This is a review of Lovely Charts, a free online diagramming tool that provides wire frame, flow chart, and site map stencils. I like the unique, simple method they provide for quickly creating flow charts and site maps. In this screencast I show how to do a few simple flow diagrams and a wireframe, as well as discussing the features that I&amp;rsquo;d like to see for creating prototypes from this tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSScaffold</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/csscaffold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/csscaffold/</guid>
      <description>Anthony Short produced a video demonstration of CSScaffold, a CSS framework takes the structural principles and architecture of current grid systems like Blueprint and the generation engine of Shaun Inman&amp;rsquo;s CSS Cacheer, and creates a CSS Grid System Builder that lets you define the rules for your layouts using meaningfully named CSS ids and classes, and automatically generates the grid system to those rules. It&amp;rsquo;s a framework that lets you focus on fitting the CSS to your design, rather than the reverse, and gives you the ability to focus on meaningful abstractions and naming rather than structural ones, so you can easily make changes in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>userfly: Instant web-based usability testing service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/userfly-instant-web-based-usability-testing-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/userfly-instant-web-based-usability-testing-service/</guid>
      <description>userfly.com from Chris Estreich on Vimeo. Userfly is a new web-based usability testing service that looks pretty exciting. When you set up a new test on the service, you&amp;rsquo;re given JavaScript to enter into your site template. Userfly captures sessions including link clicks and time spent on the page, and records screen events including mouse movement and keystrokes. This looks like a pretty nice service for certain types of observation. There doesn&amp;rsquo;t appear to be any options for interacting with users, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Commission Website Stencil Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-website-stencil-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-website-stencil-kit/</guid>
      <description>Design Commission have begun selling their web stencil kit! The kit includes:
 Stainless steel stencil with all your favorite user interface iconography Heavyweight paper pad with browser chrome on top Zebra mechanical pencil 
http://www.designcommission.com/shop/dc-website-stencil-kit/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layers App Creates Layered PSDs from Screen Captures</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/layers-app-creates-layered-psds-screen-captures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/layers-app-creates-layered-psds-screen-captures/</guid>
      <description>Just when you thought there couldn&amp;rsquo;t be a way to improve the screencapture app space, Layers hits the net. Layers for the Mac, captures your displays as a Photoshop layered image. Press the capture hotkey or customize your capture in the inspector and you&amp;rsquo;ll obtain a full fledged PSD file with one layer per window, including menu and desktop icons, dock and menubar. Sweetness.
Via @davidkaneda
http://layersapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups To Go: UI Components for Balsamiq</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mockups-go-ui-components-balsamiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mockups-go-ui-components-balsamiq/</guid>
      <description>Mockups To Go is a very cool blog featuring a user-contributed collection of ready-to-use UI components and design patterns built using Balsamiq Mockups. Share your mockups by sending an email of your docs. See the site sidebar for details.
http://mockupstogo.net/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uni-Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/uni-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/uni-form/</guid>
      <description>Uni-Form is a cool tool from Dragan Babić of Superawesome. The CSS library standardizes form markup (xhtml) and css, and &amp;ldquo;modularizes&amp;rdquo; it so even people with only basic knowledge of these technologies can get nice looking, well structured, highly customizable, semantic, accessible and usable forms. Download the plug and play XHTML and CSS and you&amp;rsquo;re ready to go.
http://sprawsm.com/uni-form/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Todd Warfel&#39;s Persona Templates</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/todd-warfels-persona-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/todd-warfels-persona-templates/</guid>
      <description>Todd Warfel has posted templates for his data-driven personas. The main file is an InDesign (INDD) file and the visual chart is in Illustrator file. Both are made with CS4.
http://zakiwarfel.com/archives/persona-templates/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mocklinkr Prototyping and Review Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mocklinkr-prototyping-and-review-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mocklinkr-prototyping-and-review-tool/</guid>
      <description>Mocklinkr is another new design mockup review service to hit the web. This one adds a little twist, however, that might be pretty useful. After you upload images of your designs or wireframes, Mocklinkr let&amp;rsquo;s you create clickable sections on the image linking to another image. This let&amp;rsquo;s you do very simple click-through prototypes to change state and navigate between pages. In a way, this seems a bit like the Berkeley GUIR Denim tool, which is sadly no longer available at the GUIR site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Commission Web Stencil Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-web-stencil-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-web-stencil-kit/</guid>
      <description>This is the excellent web stencil kit from Design Commission, which you will apparently be able to order soon! Comes with sketchpad, complete with browser chrome and grid, custom etched metal stencils, and a Zebra mechanical pencil. Hot stuff. Drop them a line if you want one when they run another job.
http://www.designcommission.com/blog/web-stencil-kit-hot-off-the-press/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STC Usability Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/stc-usability-toolkit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/stc-usability-toolkit/</guid>
      <description>The STC Usability Toolkit is a resource I&amp;rsquo;ve borrowed from over the years and continue to find myself back at fro time to time. The toolkit is a collection of forms, checklists and other useful documents for conducting usability tests and user interviews. http://www.stcsig.org/usability/resources/toolkit/toolkit.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Magazine iPhone PSD Vector Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/smashing-magazine-iphone-psd-vector-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/smashing-magazine-iphone-psd-vector-kit/</guid>
      <description>Smashing Magazine releases their own iPhone design kit, designed by Renee Rist.
http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2008/11/26/iphone-psd-vector-kit/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ecommr: e-commerce interface and design elements</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ecommr-e-commerce-interface-and-design-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ecommr-e-commerce-interface-and-design-elements/</guid>
      <description>Tom Sullivan has launched ecommr, a collection of screen captures of e-commerce design and interface elements. From product listing pages to e-mail newsletters, ecommr is a resource to view all of the individual pieces that make up the e-commerce puzzle. More info from his personal blog:
Working in the e-commerce field, I often find myself looking at other retailers to gather ideas on how to best present various elements of e-commerce sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protonotes: HTML prototyping collaboration tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/protonotes-html-prototyping-collaboration-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/protonotes-html-prototyping-collaboration-tool/</guid>
      <description>Protonotes provides a service to allow teams to add notes directly onto html prototypes. Check out the video below for a demo. After you register the confirmation email provides a few snippets of javascript to put into your html prototypes to insert a menubar over the top of your site. The menubar provides controls for creating notes and can be configured to be unobtrusive.  http://www.protonotes.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PolyPage HTML Prototyping Javascript Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/polypage-html-prototyping-javascript-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/polypage-html-prototyping-javascript-library/</guid>
      <description>Polypage is a JQuery-based HTML prototyping javascript library that was designed to ease the process of showing multiple page states in html mock-ups. By adding simply adding class names to a document you can imply state and conditional view logic. Brilliant.
http://code.new-bamboo.co.uk/polypage/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Gestures Pattern Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-gestures-pattern-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-gestures-pattern-library/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Gestures Pattern Library is a promising looking wiki that collects gestural interface information and patterns, such as found on such devices as the iPhone and Wii.
http://www.interactivegestures.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five second test: A simple online usability test</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/five-second-test-simple-online-usability-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/five-second-test-simple-online-usability-test/</guid>
      <description>The five second test is a simple usability test that helps you measure the effectiveness of your user interfaces by getting users to look at a screen for 5 seconds, and then asking them to recall what they saw. This is something I typically do at the start of a usability test to see what users understand at a high level. Show them a screen, take it away, have them talk, ask them questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cockburn&#39;s Basic Use Case Template</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/cockburns-basic-use-case-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/cockburns-basic-use-case-template/</guid>
      <description>Just discovering that Dr. Alistair Cockburn, whose Writing Effective Use Cases book got me through many a project, has a wiki. On the wiki he offers some great resources like the basic use case templates. If you don&#39;t have the book, this is a pretty good substitute for understanding use case writing.
http://alistair.cockburn.us/index.php/Basic_use_case_template</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure Design Pattern Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/axure-design-pattern-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/axure-design-pattern-library/</guid>
      <description>Loren Baxter has created an excellent looking set of design patterns for Axure users. The kit provides droppable interface elements for demonstrating rich interactions like editing in place, lightbox effects, video embedding, and a bunch more. When I worked in a Windows only company, we used Axure and I loved how easy it made wireframing and prototyping simple interactions by just dragging and dropping. This tool kit will definitely make the job even easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop Custom Comping Elements</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/photoshop-custom-comping-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/photoshop-custom-comping-elements/</guid>
      <description>Bad Assembly provides a layered Photoshop file with common user interface elements for design comping. It&amp;rsquo;s like the PSD analog to a wireframing UI stencil. http://radassembly.com/blog/?p=23</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProofHQ</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/proofhq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/proofhq/</guid>
      <description>ProofHQ is a collaborative tool for reviewing creative projects such as photography and graphic design. The tool allows you to upload anything from a PDFs, PSDs, and JPGs to Word and PowerPoint files up to 75 MB. The functionality is a bit like a mashup of Flickr and Skitch. It allows users to annotate, mark up, and comment on the work. The art can be embedded into a web site with the provided embed code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone GUI PSD</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-gui-psd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-gui-psd/</guid>
      <description>The iPhone GUI PSD by teehan+lax is an editable layered Photoshop file with graphic elements including the iPhone, buttons and controls, form inputs, and application chrome. Thanks to Designnotes for the tip.
http://www.teehanlax.com/blog/?p=447</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backboard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/backboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/backboard/</guid>
      <description>Backboard is a very simple collaboration service that allows teams to upload images (e.g. schematics, design comps, and screenshots) to a web page and elicit feedback from team members. http://getbackboard.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usability Test Data Logger for Excel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usability-test-data-logger-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usability-test-data-logger-excel/</guid>
      <description>User Focus&amp;rsquo; Todd Zazelenchuk provides an excellent Microsoft Excel tool with macros that turn the document into an application for collecting usability test data. &amp;ldquo;This spreadsheet allows you to measure task completion rates, analyse questionnaire data, and summarise participant comments. It even includes a timer so you can measure time-on-task. The spreadsheet is highly customisable.&amp;rdquo;
Download the Excel document and documentation for free.
http://www.userfocus.co.uk/resources/datalogger.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>960 Grid System</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/960-grid-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/960-grid-system/</guid>
      <description>The 960 Grid System is a CSS Framework based on 960px width and can be used with 12 or 16 column grid. 12 column grid uses 60 px wide columns and 16 column grid is used with 40 px columns. Each has 10px gutters on either side or 20px combined between columns. 960 px was chosen as a base number because it is divisible by 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 10, 12, 15, 16, 20, 24, 30, 32, 40, 48, 60, 64, 80, 96, 120, 160, 192, 240, 320 and 480.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IETester: Testing Multiple IE Versions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ietester-testing-multiple-ie-versions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ietester-testing-multiple-ie-versions/</guid>
      <description>IETester is a free WebBrowser that allows you to have the rendering and javascript engines of IE8 beta 1, IE7 IE 6 and IE5.5 on Vista and XP, as well as the installed IE in the same process. Thanks to Chad for the tip.
http://www.my-debugbar.com/wiki/IETester/HomePage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Mockups: Prototyping Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/balsamiq-mockups-prototyping-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/balsamiq-mockups-prototyping-software/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq Mockups is an incredible application for creating user interface mockups. The application allows you layout interface sketches using the 50 interface controls included. Controls are added to the canvas or notebook by dragging and dropping or by using an insert input with auto-completion suggestions. As with Visio, many controls may be easily customized by editing values in the properties panel, and may be modified to show state, e.g. selected, disabled, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grid Calculator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/grid-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/grid-calculator/</guid>
      <description>Matthew Pennel&amp;rsquo;s Grid Calculator is a tool to calcuate a grid based on easy to use slider controls and forms. [A]llows you to choose the font size you are going to use, and then select the number of columns, column width, and gutter width based on that base font size. As you fiddle with the dimensions, the total width is dynamically updated, so you can check that you haven’t gone over that magic 1024px!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GridMaker Script for PhotoShop</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gridmaker-script-photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gridmaker-script-photoshop/</guid>
      <description>Andrew Ingram&amp;rsquo;s GridMaker is a brilliant script for Photoshop that can be used to automatically generate guides in your PSD. The script allows you to enter the series of columns that should be laid out both horizontally and vertically. Then you set the maximum dimensions for the canvas. To generate a Blueprint grid, for instance, you&amp;rsquo;d enter &amp;ldquo;30,10&amp;rdquo; to create a PSD with a series of repeating columns of alternating 30 pixel units and 10 pixel gutters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencil Project: Open Source Drawing and Prototyping Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/pencil-project-open-source-drawing-and-prototyping-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/pencil-project-open-source-drawing-and-prototyping-software/</guid>
      <description>Duong Thanh An has begun work on Pencil, an open source diagramming tool to free users from commercial products such as Visio and OmniGraffle. Pencil is an application that runs on the Mozilla Gecko engine and can be run as a Firefox 3 tool, or in standalone mode (Windows and Linux only for now). The first version looks very promising and provides the basic functionalities needed to create diagrams and page schematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch paper for the mobile designer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</guid>
      <description>Erlend posted on the Artueel blog about a great idea they had for mobile designers&amp;#8212;a sketchpaper document you can print out (PDF and PSD formats available) so you can get your ideas on paper. They&amp;rsquo;ve created sketchpaper for the iPhone and the Nokia N95. Since we‘re all big fans of the iPhone and the mobile future in general, we want to help the mobile designer achieving his goals. For those who like to sketch the design/flow of their mobile app or website we present you: sketch paper for the iPhone and Nokia N95.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Design Pattern Library Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/yahoo-design-pattern-library-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/yahoo-design-pattern-library-stencils/</guid>
      <description>The Yahoo! Design Pattern Library have released stencils for design patterns in OmniGraffle, Visio, PDF, PNG, and SVG format. I had planned to do the same for OmniGraffle users, but they beat me to the punch. :) This has easily become the best resource out there for design pattern examples. Congrats to Christian Crumlish and his team.
http://developer.yahoo.com/ypatterns/wireframes/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Deficit Simulators</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/color-deficit-simulators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/color-deficit-simulators/</guid>
      <description>There are several applications and web services that help you determine if the colors used in your designs will be accessible to users that cannot view all colors. My personal favorite is the Sim Daltonism app for the Mac (pictured above).  Sim Daltonism is a color blindness simulator for Mac OS X. It filters in real-time the area around the mouse pointer and displays the result — as seen by a color blind person — in a floating palette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GridFox - The Grid Layout Firefox Extension</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gridfox-grid-layout-firefox-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gridfox-grid-layout-firefox-extension/</guid>
      <description>GridFox is a Firefox extension that overlays a grid on any website. If you can open it in Firefox, you can put a grid on top of it. It’s easy to customize, allowing you to create the exact grid you designed your layout around.
Via DigitalWeb
http://www.puidokas.com/portfolio/gridfox/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone Wireframes Stencil for OmniGraffle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-wireframes-stencil-omnigraffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-wireframes-stencil-omnigraffle/</guid>
      <description>A wireframe stencil for designing iPhone interfaces.
http://www.graffletopia.com/stencils/358</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS with Vertical Rhythm</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/css-vertical-rhythm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/css-vertical-rhythm/</guid>
      <description>drewish.com provides a nice script that takes a base font and line height and generates a scale of font classes with font sizes, line height, and margins calculated as ems. It&#39;s an odd selection of scale however with fonts sized at 12, 14, 16, 18, 20, 22, and 24 px. You can easily set this to a more familiar 12, 14, 16, 18, 21, 24, 36px. Or following Mark Boulton&#39;s lead, you can set to 11, 13, 16, 18, 24px.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install multiple versions of IE on your PC</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/install-multiple-versions-ie-your-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/install-multiple-versions-ie-your-pc/</guid>
      <description>The Multiple IE Installer is a must have resource for front end developers. I had to configure a new computer for myself because of a recent job change, so that meant installing all of my design/development tools again. On my new MacBook Pro, I run VMWare and just ran Tredosoft&amp;rsquo;s Multiple IE Installer for Windows XP. On an XP machine with IE7 (you must upgrade to IE7 before running this), the application will allow you to select versions of IE 3, 4, 5, and 6 to install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus: Test your email and website designs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/litmus-test-your-email-and-website-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/litmus-test-your-email-and-website-designs/</guid>
      <description>Litmus provides testing of web sites and email messages across all browser and email platforms for a fee.
http://litmusapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textism Word HTML Cleaner</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/textism-word-html-cleaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/textism-word-html-cleaner/</guid>
      <description>In my old days working on a corporate portal, I occasionally had to take someone&amp;rsquo;s HTML, which was generated by Microsoft Word, and drop it into an entry on a CMS. But before I could just cut and paste, I had to run a series of regular expression replacements in vi or Allaire HomeSite to strip out any of the god awful HTML that Word generated. To pay homage to the past, fate recently dropped a Word HTML file in my lap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS Hex Color Picker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mac-os-hex-color-picker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mac-os-hex-color-picker/</guid>
      <description>The free Hex Color Picker from Waffle Software lets you get and edit hexadecimal HTML color codes in the standard Mac color panel. Requires Mac OS X Tiger.
http://wafflesoftware.net/hexpicker/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mondrianum, A Kuler Color Plugin for the Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mondrianum-kuler-color-plugin-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mondrianum-kuler-color-plugin-mac/</guid>
      <description>Lithoglyph’s Mondrianum is a plug-in that enables Mac applications use color palettes created by the kuler community. Mondrianum acts like a built-in, system-wide color picker, available in any application that supports this feature, including iWork, iLife, OmniGraffle Photoshop, Illustrator, Coda.
Thanks to Andrew for the tip!
http://www.lithoglyph.com/mondrianum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blind Text Generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/blind-text-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/blind-text-generator/</guid>
      <description>I prefer not to use dummy text, because creating wireframes and comps that reflect how they will really look and function is what people pay me for, and is a sign of a lazy IA/IXD. Plus it can be really enjoyable to write real fake copy. Having said that, I have to admit to being the lazy IA from time to timeand have gone to gone to lipsum.com to generate dummy text.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>