<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technical support on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/technical-support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technical support on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/technical-support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Your Cache</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/refresh-your-cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/refresh-your-cache/</guid>
      <description>I used to do a lot of technical support, and still do some occasionally. Refresh Your Cache is a simple guide to clearing browser cache that you can send to your customers rather than sleuthing platform and browser, because Shift-Refresh doesn&#39;t work all the time for all browsers.
Via Ben in a backchannel. ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are your favorite customer support sites and why?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-are-your-favorite-customer-support-sites-and-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-are-your-favorite-customer-support-sites-and-why/</guid>
      <description>What I&#39;m doing
I&#39;m doing a review of customer support sites, looking mostly for software (desktop and web) and services-related sites that provide a customer support site for getting answers to questions, and viewing documentation and tutorials. Why I&#39;m doing it
Some sites have better search capabilities for questions than others. Other sites do well at presenting documentation. I&#39;m finding that there&#39;s sometimes a difference in how companies handle giving answers to the most granular questions as opposed to presenting a unified view of a product via a manual-like experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifting Feature at Nintendo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gifting-feature-nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gifting-feature-nintendo/</guid>
      <description>Nintendo provides excellent illustrations to describe the gifting process on the Wii, using storyboards. The gifting page shows a table of contents at the top, for each use case: sending, receiving, confirmation, and faq. Clicking one of the use cases jumps the user down to the storyboard illustrating steps to complete each case. It&#39;s a simple, very clear, and visual. I wish every support site worked that way. Thanks to Boon Sheridan for the tip.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
