<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>a-z index on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/a-z-index/</link>
    <description>Recent content in a-z index on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/a-z-index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fever Progressive Disclosure</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fever-progressive-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fever-progressive-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>The Fever RSS news reader provides some useful progressive disclosure/enhancement behaviors that hide features until they are needed. Many of the primary features are also provided as keyboard shortcuts. The resulting experience provides a subtle and minimalist aesthetic without compromising features.
1. The initial view of the app shows groups of items and the pages linking to them. The main navigator is shown in left sidebar.2. Selecting a category (&amp;quot;UX&amp;quot; in this example) displays a second column for browsing feeds in that category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Lives Here Glossary</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ed-lives-here-glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ed-lives-here-glossary/</guid>
      <description>Paper manufacturer NewPage provides the Ed Lives Here site, a useful resource with information about paper, printing, and design. One of the features of this site is a glossary of printing terms. The glossary provides categorized sub-glossaries, as well as the typical a-z index of terms, and a search input. Browsing through the glossary is facilitated by the A-Z links, which use a fish eye lens to bring focus to a section of the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OfficeMax A-Z Index</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-z-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-z-index/</guid>
      <description>OfficeMax displays an a-z index of the store directory in the global navigation. When users hover over any of the letters, a page-wide flyout menu appears to display entries. Clicking on one of the letters, displays the same listing of entries in full page view.
1. A-Z index displayed in global navigation. Hovering over letter shows wide flyout menu of directory entries.2. Directory display for B&#39;s. http://www.officemax.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
