<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick Add on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/quick-add/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quick Add on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/quick-add/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Quick Add</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-quick-add/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-quick-add/</guid>
      <description>The video queue on Netflix offers a &#34;Quick Add&#34; functionality at the bottom of the queue that lets users search for a particular title and add it to their queue without having to view the video page. It&#39;s a single input with an auto-completion behavior to suggest videos based on what you type. Clicking a title from the suggestion list or hitting return on an exact match adds the video and shows a confirmation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-calendar/</guid>
      <description>Where Google Search gave us syntax for doing all kinds of advanced searching, Google Calendar goes a more natural route. When Calendar was released, it introduced a lot of people to the idea of the natural language command line for the web via the &#34;Quick Add&#34; feature. Via a simple form input, you enter basic event info, e.g. &#34;Lunch with Judy on Thusday at 1pm.&#34; The event is quickly added, and you click the event title in the calendar to edit the details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presdo Calendaring</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/presdo-calendaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/presdo-calendaring/</guid>
      <description>Presdo is a calendaring service that uses a simple form input as the command line for entering natural language commands for events. To use, enter event statements as with Google Calendar. It is always assumed that you are the subject&amp;#8212;the WHO. You just have to fill in the rest of the WHAT, WITH WHOM, and WHERE parts of the statement, e.g. &#34;Have lunch with Judy on Thursday at 1pm.&#34; Once you&#39;ve submitted the basic event info, you&#39;re presented with a more complete UI for entering event details, and this is where the service far surpasses Google&#39;s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>