<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buxton Collection</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton has been collecting input and interactive devices whose design struck him as interesting, useful, or important. In the process, he has assembled a great collection spanning over 30 years of the history of pen computing, pointing devices, touch technologies, as well as an illustration of the nature of how new technologies emerge.
The collection can be browsed in HTML or via the PivotViewer Silverlight interface. PivotViewer provides a richer experience with faceted filtering, search, and hypertext links for metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reframer: Qualitative data analysis system</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/reframer-qualitative-data-analysis-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/reframer-qualitative-data-analysis-system/</guid>
      <description>Reframer is a collaborative web app for collecting and analyzing qualitative data. You start by capturing data into the app&amp;#8212;things like customer feedback, free text responses in surveys, emails, interviews, and usability test data. The system then uses the aggregated information and provides a view reframed with quantitative values based on a significance rating that team members apply. These values can also be used to prioritize issues to assess feasibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye Tracking Research on Reading on iPad vs. Newspaper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/eye-tracking-research-reading-ipad-vs-newspaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/eye-tracking-research-reading-ipad-vs-newspaper/</guid>
      <description>Miratech observed the difference between reading an article in a newspaper and on an iPad in an eye tracking study. They concluded that readers are more likely to skim over articles on an iPad than in a newspaper.

The type of medium doesn&#39;t influence reading time when the text is short (like an article).
It is easier to assimilate and retain information read in a newspaper than on an iPad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Rimino, The Future of Mobile Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/project-rimino-future-mobile-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/project-rimino-future-mobile-experience/</guid>
      <description>Project Rimino is an interaction design project proposing a hypothetical e-paper mobile device. The project was created by Amid Moradganjeh, an interaction design student from Umea Institute of Design in Sweden, for his masters degree project on mobile experience design. The design is based on both observational and experimental design research methods. Watch the video below for the concept.

Some of the ideas are pretty exciting. I particularly like the emphasis on everyday tasks, utilizing the materials of the device to create minimal, task-focussed interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apparent usability vs. inherent usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apparent-usability-vs-inherent-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apparent-usability-vs-inherent-usability/</guid>
      <description>Occasionally the argument about the affect of aesthetics or beauty on usability seems to come up in UX discussion, and this CHI short paper from 1995 is referred to. This is an article by members of the Design Center, Hitachi discusses the team&#39;s research on determinants to apparent usability, based on tests of design and psychology students. These results show that the apparent usability is less correlated with the inherent usability compared to to the apparent beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClickTale Scrolling Research Report</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/clicktale-scrolling-research-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/clicktale-scrolling-research-report/</guid>
      <description>ClickTale makes observations about scrolling based on their research of users&amp;rsquo; browsing behaviors around &amp;ldquo;the fold.&amp;rdquo; Their report on scrolling makes the following conclusions: [I[t appears that visitors scroll in a relative way - about the same percentage of page views will reach the middle of a web page regardless of the actual page height in pixels.
Visitors appear to be using the location of the scroll bar but not the size of the tracker when scrolling, since the scroll bar location is a relative indicator and the scroll tracker size is an indicator of page height.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Research for Personas and Other Audience Models</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-research-personas-and-other-audience-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-research-personas-and-other-audience-models/</guid>
      <description>In UX Matters, Steve Baty describes the user research methodologies we can draw on when creating audience models and some alternative ways of communicating the results of an audience analysis.
http://www.uxmatters.com/mt/archives/2009/04/user-research-for-personas-and-other-audience-models.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Science Research Service Launches</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/crowd-science-research-service-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/crowd-science-research-service-launches/</guid>
      <description>Crowd Science is a new comer among user research services that allow you to prompt small sets of users to participate in questionnaires while they&amp;rsquo;re browsing your site.
Crowd Science Demographics is a new analytics service that builds detailed reports on the demographics and attitudes of website audiences. By surveying a small number visitors with carefully constructed questionnaires, Crowd Science Demographics is able to build comprehensive audience profiles that give publishers a deep understanding of their audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for One User (Bespoke User Interfaces)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-one-user-bespoke-user-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-one-user-bespoke-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>Chris Fahey discusses the merits of bespoke UI design, referencing the successful design of John King&#39;s touch wall which was created for King by Perceptive Pixel. Bespoke design--the practice of designing something specifically for and individual--might be more prevalent in the digital world than most people realize. The examples provided out in the quotes of software designers and developers point out the most common case where this is happening. Designers who design products by focusing on what they want/need for themselves is common enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Path ROI Report Offered for Free</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-roi-report-offered-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-roi-report-offered-free/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Path release Janice Fraser and Scott Hirsch&#39;s research on the ties between business value and user experience. “Leveraging Business Value: How ROI Changes User Experience” originally cost $395, but is now being offered for free.
Download the report (412K PDF)
http://www.adaptivepath.com/blog/2008/09/22/is-your-organization-experienced/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study of User Response to Fake Dialogs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/study-user-response-fake-dialogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/study-user-response-fake-dialogs/</guid>
      <description>Ars reports on a study by the psychology department at NC State that will appear in the Proceedings of the Human Factors and Ergonomics Society. The study tested how college students respond to fake dialog boxes in browser popup windows and found that the students are so anxious to get the dialog out of the way, they click right through obvious warning signs. Follow-up questions revealed that the students seemed to find any dialog box a distraction from their assigned task; nearly half said that all they cared about was getting rid of these dialogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hold the front page</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hold-front-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hold-front-page/</guid>
      <description>The Economist reports on some research undertaken by Fang Wu and Bernardo Huberman, a pair of researchers at Hewlett-Packard&amp;rsquo;s laboratory in Palo Alto, California, to compare two strategies used on news sites: one based on the previous popularity of a story, the other on its novelty. The researchers based their study on analysis of articles posted to digg, and the article provides some insight into the digg algorithm and the half-life of an entry (about 69 minutes before an entry gets demoted from the home page).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer Unlocks Wii&#39;s Hidden Potential</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</guid>
      <description>CNET reports on Johnny Chung Lee&amp;rsquo;s interaction experiments with the Wii Remote. Lee, a Phd student at Carnegie Melon, does a quick demo of head tracking for VR displays and multi point interaction using the wii remote. His experiments describe with incredible clarity how the wii remote fundamentally works and how the remote might be exploited to do much more than point at single points on the screen and control them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23 Actionable Lessons from Eye-Tracking Studies</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/23-actionable-lessons-eye-tracking-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/23-actionable-lessons-eye-tracking-studies/</guid>
      <description>Christina Laun summarizes the top lessons to take away from eyetracking studies.
 Text attracts attention before graphics. Initial eye movement focuses on the upper left corner of the page. Users initially look at the top left and upper portion of the page before moving down and to the right. Readers ignore banners. Fancy formatting and fonts are ignored. Show numbers as numerals. Type size influences viewing behavior. Users only look at a sub headline if it interests them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Direct Marketing and User Experience Are the Same</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-direct-marketing-and-user-experience-are-same/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-direct-marketing-and-user-experience-are-same/</guid>
      <description>Usability blogger, John S. Rhodes writes in Apogee that Direct Marketing and UX are the same, or at least share common goals and methodologies. This quote sums up these parallel ways of thinking and working:
There is a serious emphasis on testing and measurement. Metrics are the law. Success is based on tangible results: number of phone calls, number of and type of brochures requested, number of email address captured, number of comments made, number of web page views and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>