<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>captcha on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/captcha/</link><description>Recent content in captcha on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/captcha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Photojojo Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photojojo-captcha/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photojojo-captcha/</guid><description>Yes, I know you hate captchas and they're riddled with problems. Why do it if you don't have to? But if you do it, at least make it a brainless action like this.
1. Click to answer the captcha challenge. http://photojojo.com/contact/</description></item><item><title>CAPTCHAs' Effect on Conversion Rates</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/captchas-effect-conversion-rates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/captchas-effect-conversion-rates/</guid><description>SEOmoz user chenry posted some i8nteresting data showing captcha's effect on conversion rates vs. reduction in spam. Chenry was given the task of eliminating spam that was being submitted through a web form. Disliking the captcha solution, he decided run a test to compare the data after adding captcha for a period of time, with data captured after turning captcha off. He made the following observation:
From the data you can see that with CAPTCHA on, there was an 88% reduction in SPAM but there were 159 failed conversions.</description></item><item><title>Interaction-Design.org Tickmark Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/interaction-designorg-tickmark-captcha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/interaction-designorg-tickmark-captcha/</guid><description>The captcha on Interaction-Design.org, which requires a verification of tickmarks sum.
http://www.interaction-design.org/</description></item><item><title>Capzles Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/capzles-captcha/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/capzles-captcha/</guid><description>Capzles, a photo management and sharing services uses animated text in a Flash captcha to trick the robots. This is the most sophisticated attempt I've seen to make captchas unreadable. It still can't beat the spam sweatshops, but it seems to me like a very good option for defeating OCR.
http://capzles.com</description></item><item><title>Photoshop Express Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photoshop-express-captcha/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photoshop-express-captcha/</guid><description>Adobe's new online service, Photoshop Express, uses handwritten fonts for Captcha forms.
https://www.photoshop.com/express/landing.html</description></item><item><title>Drupal Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/drupal-captcha/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/drupal-captcha/</guid><description>Drupal's captcha module offers some creative alternatives to the typical distorted text of image captchas. These are a few of the examples that are much more readable, and arguably less frustrating. 1. ASCII art captcha2. Math captcha3. Text captcha4. Lost character captcha5. Phrase captcha6. Riddler captcha http://drupal.org</description></item><item><title>Oranges Contact Form</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/oranges-contact-form/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/oranges-contact-form/</guid><description>Edward Pistachio is a writer pulping fine short stories. Consistent with the lighthearted tone of this site, he provides a contact form that is also all about words. Getting his email address requires solving a few jumbles, and then decoding the address from letters found in the jumbles. Sure it may be frustrating if you can't figure out the jumbles, and is one of the cleverest ways I've ever seen to gain access to a bit of info.</description></item><item><title>Digg Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-captcha/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-captcha/</guid><description>Digg's captcha input has nice conversational labels. Sadly they've redesigned the registration form so that the nicely chunked form areas all flow into one block.
http://digg.com/register/</description></item><item><title>Google Registration</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-registration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-registration/</guid><description>A quick and simple registration form that's compressed into a small area. The labels could be right-aligned for better readability in that 2 column format and the submit button could be aligned left with the inputs to really clean this up.
https://google.com/accounts/NewAccount?service=mail</description></item><item><title>Yahoo! Registration</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-registration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-registration/</guid><description>We happened to catch the Yahoo! registration pages when they were being redesigned in 2007. The first version was captured in November 2007 and the second is the prior version. The redesigned version is subtle, but really improves the user's flow through the form. It compresses the vertical height of the form and uses more conversational labels.
1. Registration screen2. Old registration screen prior to Fall 2007 https://edit.yahoo.com/registration</description></item></channel></rss>