<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Must Read on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/must-read/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Must Read on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/must-read/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Skills Considered Harmful</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/presentation-skills-considered-harmful/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/presentation-skills-considered-harmful/</guid>
      <description>I don&#39;t like public speaking. I love talking to people one to one and in very small groups. But public speaking and me don&#39;t mix, and if you&#39;ve ever seen me speak, you probably agree. In the handful of times that I have spoken publicly, I think only two were really worth coming to see and hear. I believe the only reason the worthwhile talks were not utter failures was because I had something to share that I think people wanted to hear, and could get something out of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pace</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pace/</guid>
      <description>Hannah Donovan&amp;rsquo;s essay in A List Apart considers the issue of pace of delivery of information in web products. In a world where information is streamed constantly to us if we allow it, sometimes a slower pace, selective or scant data delivery, and better signal to noise is more appropriate and valuable. Context, medium, and place of use are important factors for determining delivery and pace.
I&#39;ve been interested in the slow movement in recent years, as it relates to sustainable living, slow design, slow food, and the 1K Movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your app is a collection of tiny details</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/your-app-collection-tiny-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/your-app-collection-tiny-details/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Getting the details right is the difference between something that delights, and something customers tolerate.&#34;
&amp;#8212;Jeff Atwood
I didn&#39;t read Jeff Atwood&#39;s article about cat feeders right away, because it really is 90% about a cat product. It&#39;s also a terrific demonstration of what he&#39;s saying above. The first version of the product, a cat feeder, served a core need well enough for him to satisfice with its shortcomings because the net return in time savings and improved quality of life, for him anyway, was absolutely worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letting Go</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/letting-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/letting-go/</guid>
      <description>Two great slides from Yiibu&#39;s presentation, Letting Go, a talk about design in an time of increasing disruption.
 &#34;Issuing your customers with something that is rough, incomplete, and possibly even substandard seems counterintuitive but there is growing evidence that people don&#39;t necessarily want the perfect product. They prefer to deal with something ragged around the edges that they can adapt or improve.&#34;
&amp;#8212; Martin Thomas in &#34;Loose: The Future of Business is Letting Go&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caterina Fake on why working hard is overrated</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/caterina-fake-why-working-hard-overrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/caterina-fake-why-working-hard-overrated/</guid>
      <description>Caterina Fake, founder of Flickr and Hunch, talks about why working hard isn&amp;rsquo;t as important as working on the right things. Or as I once heard on a cartoon as a kid&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;you have to work smarter not harder.&amp;rdquo;
Much more important than working hard is knowing how to find the right thing to work on. Paying attention to what is going on in the world. Seeing patterns. Seeing things as they are rather than how you want them to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton on How to Keep Innovating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-how-keep-innovating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-how-keep-innovating/</guid>
      <description>In BusinessWeek, Bill Buxton discusses how to keep innovating, with the main idea being that you can continue to cultivate creativity and innovation by finding new things that you have a passion for. He suggests that when you get good enough at a thing, you should find something else to be passionate about, and commit and throw yourself into learning how to do it. You&#39;ll be bad at it at first, but the experience of learning something new, no matter how bad you are at it at first, may affect your creativity in positive ways that you won&#39;t realize until you experience it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton on Innovation and the Long Nose Theory</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-innovation-and-long-nose-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-innovation-and-long-nose-theory/</guid>
      <description>Bolt|Peters summarizes Bill Buxton&amp;rsquo;s talk at CHI 2008, which is focussed largely around his theory of long nose. The article in BusinessWeek describes the danger of trying to innovate around the long tail theory alone, and attempts to create awareness for this other phenomenon which he calls the long nose. The theory describes how the bulk of innovation is low-amplitude and takes place over a long period of time. [T]he bulk of innovation behind the latest &amp;ldquo;wow&amp;rdquo; moment (multi-touch on the iPhone, for example) is also low-amplitude and takes place over a long period—but well before the &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; idea has become generally known, much less reached the tipping point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#39;s Design process</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apples-design-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apples-design-process/</guid>
      <description>Michael Lopp, Senior Engineering Manager at Apple discussed Apple&#39;s design process at a presentation given at SXSW. Business Week summarized the points, excerpted below.  Pixel Perfect Mockups
This, Lopp admitted, causes a huge amount of work and takes an enormous amount of time. But, he added, “it removes all ambiguity.” That might add time up front, but it removes the need to correct mistakes later on.
10 to 3 to 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shneiderman&#39;s Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/shneidermans-eight-golden-rules-interface-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/shneidermans-eight-golden-rules-interface-design/</guid>
      <description>Ben Shneiderman&#39;s Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design are user interface design rules described in Designing the User Interface: Strategies for Effective Human-Computer Interaction. Shneiderman proposed this collection of principles that are derived heuristically from experience and applicable in most interactive systems after being properly refined, extended, and interpreted.
To improve the usability of an application it is important to have a well designed interface and these &#34;Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>