<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>customer service on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/customer-service/</link><description>Recent content in customer service on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/customer-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What are your favorite customer support sites and why?</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-are-your-favorite-customer-support-sites-and-why/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-are-your-favorite-customer-support-sites-and-why/</guid><description>What I'm doing
I'm doing a review of customer support sites, looking mostly for software (desktop and web) and services-related sites that provide a customer support site for getting answers to questions, and viewing documentation and tutorials. Why I'm doing it
Some sites have better search capabilities for questions than others. Other sites do well at presenting documentation. I'm finding that there's sometimes a difference in how companies handle giving answers to the most granular questions as opposed to presenting a unified view of a product via a manual-like experience.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Rose interview with Jeff Bezos</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/charlie-rose-interview-jeff-bezos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/charlie-rose-interview-jeff-bezos/</guid><description>This is a fantastic interview of Jeff Bezos on Charlie Rose where Bezos talks about why Kindle shouldn't be the iPad and why Amazon's new mission is &amp;quot;Earth's most customer-centric company.&amp;quot;
http://www.charlierose.com/view/interview/11138</description></item><item><title>Why Zappos Pays New Employees to Quit</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/why-zappos-pays-new-employees-quit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/why-zappos-pays-new-employees-quit/</guid><description>The stories of Zappos' commitment to superior customer service has become nearly legendary. From regular upgrades to next day delivery at no cost to the story of a customer service reps delivery of flowers to a customer whos mother passed away. Now, in Harvard Business Online, Bill Taylor tells of Zappos' unusual customer training program. Zappos offers new employees a $1000 offer to quit after a 4 week training session. The idea behind this tactic is that by weeding out people who take the offer, they keep the ones who will be committed to the company.</description></item></channel></rss>