<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>music on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/music/</link><description>Recent content in music on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beatport Pro Music Store</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/beatport-pro-music-store/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/beatport-pro-music-store/</guid><description>Beatport's Pro app for the Mac offers a shopping experience that's tailored for the way DJs shop for music. The app lets users analyze their music (tracks, sounds, and playlists) to prepare sets and add music to their playlists. Here are some of the elements of the version 2 interface related to shopping in the app.
Beatport comes close to the experience of shopping in a record store, breaking down music into genres and sub-genres.</description></item><item><title>Bruce Springsteen on Creativity</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bruce-springsteen-creativity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bruce-springsteen-creativity/</guid><description>I'd like to talk about the one thing that's been consistent over the years—the genesis and power of creativity. ... It’s all about how you’re putting what you do together. The elements you’re using don’t matter. Purity of human expression and experience is not confined to guitars, to tubes, to turntables, to microchips. There’s no right way, no pure way of doing it—there’s just doing it.
From Bruce Springsteen's inspiring 2012 SXSW Keynote Speech.</description></item><item><title>Debussy on White Space</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/debussy-white-space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/debussy-white-space/</guid><description>"Music is the space between the notes."
&amp;#8212;Claude Debussy, as quoted in Turning Numbers into Knowledge (2001) by Johnathan G. Koomey</description></item><item><title>Filtersage</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/filtersage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/filtersage/</guid><description>Filtersage connects the present to the past. You can discover great movies and music or share your knowledge by making new connections. http://www.filtersage.com</description></item><item><title>Sick City Club</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sick-city-club/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sick-city-club/</guid><description>Sick City Club are a new band hotly tipped for 2009 by UK's Radio One. The new site was designed and built by Zaum &amp;amp; Brown. It's a full flash build powered by an xml cms. The design was inspired by traveling around a city, always being on the go. The sites most prominent feature is the bands new video playing as the background.
http://www.sickcityclub.net</description></item><item><title>thesixytone</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/thesixytone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/thesixytone/</guid><description>Hard to believe that independent music sites continue to find ways to create social experiences around listening to music in the wake of huge, established communities like last.fm scrobbling and one to one experiences like muxtape playlist sharing. thesixtyone brings band and listener contribution together by letting musicians upload music, while listeners surface the tracks that deserve attention. It's a nice minimal design that focuses on the experience of playing the new and popular music people are listening to and favoriting.</description></item><item><title>The Show</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/show/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/show/</guid><description>Big bold typography that functions as navigation, full screen photography that functions as backdrop, a simple message, and a lasting product that does justice to live music performances and the people who love them.
http://www.theshowlive.com/</description></item><item><title>The Filter</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/filter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/filter/</guid><description>The Filter is an portal that aggregates music, TV, and video content. The project was started by Peter Gabriel and is looking to get amass a community of users who are willing to rate content so they can provide recommendations back to the community.
The site is looking to be a comprehensive consumer experience for all media, and essentially is pulling content from various sources and providing a single interface for adding recommendations and usage metadata to that content within the confines of this community.</description></item><item><title>Adtunes.com</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/adtunes-com/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/adtunes-com/</guid><description>Adtunes is a portal for finding music from TV commercials, film trailers, TV show and film soundtracks, and video games. I've used the forums on this site several times to track down the creators of music in TV commercials.
http://adtunes.com/</description></item><item><title>evelMerch</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/evelmerch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/evelmerch/</guid><description>http://www.evelmerch.com/</description></item><item><title>RCRD LBL</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/rcrd-lbl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/rcrd-lbl/</guid><description>http://rcrdlbl.com</description></item><item><title>alisa.mtv.ru</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/alisa-mtv-ru/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/alisa-mtv-ru/</guid><description>http://alisa.mtv.ru</description></item></channel></rss>