<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tv on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/tv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tv on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/tv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MTV&#39;s brand new look</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mtvs-brand-new-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mtvs-brand-new-look/</guid>
      <description>MTV International / Mad Drummer from Universal Everything on Vimeo.
 Awesome motion graphics by Universal Everything for MTV. Creative Review reviews the new work on MTV&amp;rsquo;s new look, which is a forward-looking transformation that reminds me feel that reminds me of Cartoon Network&amp;rsquo;s recent rebranding in the Tristan Eaton designed character videos.
http://creativereview.co.uk/cr-blog/2009/june/mtvs-brand-new-look</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC.com Microsoft Surface Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/msnbccom-microsoft-surface-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/msnbccom-microsoft-surface-videos/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve caught Chuck Todd using a desktop touch interface a few times on MSNBC to click through poll charts. While John King has been using a Perceptive Pixel-designed touch wall, Todd has been using a Microsoft Surface interface on a desktop. The device and manipulation of data on the screen looks very natural on this show, especially for the kind of information he&amp;rsquo;s speaking to. I think whenever there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of visual information to add to a story, this kind of an interface has potential to be very helpful and I look forward to seeing what they do at MSNBC and on other shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillcrest Labs Remote Control</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hillcrest-labs-remote-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hillcrest-labs-remote-control/</guid>
      <description>Hillcrest Labs provides a vision of the pointing and navigating future with their demonstration of Freespace motion-controlled TV remote.
 I came across the video demos of Hillcrest Labs&#39; remote control via NewTeevee. The video above shows a demo at the Consumer Electronics Show last winter, but check the NewTeevee link for the more complete demo of their Freespace motion control technology (sadly they won&#39;t let me embed it here). The demo shows a proof of concept software interface for the TV that allows the user to navigate and access media on their TV/Computer using the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Xbox Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-xbox-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-xbox-experience/</guid>
      <description>Kotaku reports on the New Xbox Experience, which does away with the Blade interface, and replaces with a remote-control type UI with cover-flow-like browsability. We&amp;rsquo;ll have to see what the reception will be for this. Xbox are integrating Netflix soon, and may be hoping to simplify the experience for a wider audience. I found the Blade UI to be pretty interesting the few times I got to use it.
http://kotaku.com/5025143/the-new-xbox-experience-just-the-facts-and-maybe-some-conjecture</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roku Netflix Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/roku-netflix-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/roku-netflix-player/</guid>
      <description>Yet another set top box makes a move to bring the 10 foot Internet TV and movie experience to your living room. This time Roku, maker of the Soundbridge audio player, has teamed up with Netflix to deliver their video on demand service to a set top box designed for Netflix service only. The $100 box allows you to navigate your queue, view show/movie information, and stream videos that were previously only available for Internet streaming to Windows users previously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple filing depicts Apple TV with iChat widget interface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-filing-depicts-apple-tv-ichat-widget-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-filing-depicts-apple-tv-ichat-widget-interface/</guid>
      <description>AppleInsider discovers an August 2006 patent filing by Apple for features having to do with broadcast video sent over Apple TV. The patent discusses interesting ideas for widgets that overlay the screen to allow such display of information as data related to what is on, and interactions such as purchasing tickets to performances, and doing video chat.
View photo on Flickr
http://www.appleinsider.com/articles/08/02/07/apple_filing_depicts_apple_tv_with_ichat_widget_interface.html</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>