<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>must watch on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/must-watch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in must watch on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/must-watch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Sierra on Creating Awesome Users</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kathy-sierra-creating-awesome-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kathy-sierra-creating-awesome-users/</guid>
      <description>The model for sustaining customer loyalty is reverse engineering user awesomeness.
Peldi pointed me to a video of Kathy Sierra&#39;s presentation at Business of Software 09, where she talks about sustaining passionate and loyal customers. Positioning and generating sustainable relationships is not what you think it should be about. It&#39;s about user benefits, and not features--about how they feel about themselves in the context of what you provide them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Bierut: 5 Secrets from 86 Notebooks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/michael-bierut-5-secrets-86-notebooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/michael-bierut-5-secrets-86-notebooks/</guid>
      <description>This is fantastic presentation from Pentagram&#39;s Michael Bierut at The 99 Percent conference. Shows how a quiet, humble, and empathetic bedside manner can be such useful attributes in a designer.
Renowned graphic designer Michael Bierut claims that he&#39;s not creative. Instead, he likens his job to that of a doctor who tends to patients – &#34;the sicker, the better.&#34; Digging into the 86 notebooks he&#39;s kept over the course of his career, Bierut walks us through 5 projects – from original conception to final execution – extracting a handful of simple lessons (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Schwartz on the Paradox of Choice</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/barry-schwartz-paradox-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/barry-schwartz-paradox-choice/</guid>
      <description>Psychologist Barry Schwartz takes aim at a central tenet of western societies on TED: freedom of choice. In Schwartz&#39;s estimation, choice has made us not freer but more paralyzed, not happier but more dissatisfied.
The idea that more choice leads to paralysis rather than happiness resonates strongly with me. I think about where I am in terms of my spiritual and psychological development, and I do feel dissatisfied when things aren&#39;t perfect today and I find it troublesome that I think this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So you&#39;re thinking about becoming a designer?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/so-youre-thinking-about-becoming-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/so-youre-thinking-about-becoming-designer/</guid>
      <description>Liz Danzico sought out the advice of digital designers and designer conspirers to ask them to respond to the following statement:
So you’re thinking about becoming a designer? If I could tell you only one thing about going into the field, my advice would be ___________ .
 The suggestions ranged from the philosophical to the pragmatic. Below are the ones that resounded with me. Focus on empathy and understanding problems  Being empathetic helps designers create things that move people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside IDEO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/inside-ideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/inside-ideo/</guid>
      <description>Design Observer points to the 1999 ABC Nightline program that took an inside look at IDEO. How does the process of designing a better product work? To show you, Nightline went to Palo Alto, CA to the designers at IDEO, and gave them the toughest problem we could think of. Take something old and familiar like the shopping cart and completely redesign it in just five days.
IDEO&#39;s unique brand of brainstorming is called &#39;&#39;Deep Dive,&#39;&#39; a sort of total immersion into the problem at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paula Scher gets serious at TED</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/paula-scher-gets-serious-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/paula-scher-gets-serious-ted/</guid>
      <description>Fantastic TED video of Paula Scher looking back at her career for those moments where she was able to devote time and effort to serious play and create wonderful work, and contrasting it with the unfortunate moments when the serious becomes solemn. I love how this retrospective observation of her career brings her to conclude that the best of times for her as a designer is when she comes into a project with no grounding or bearing--those times where lack of history or reference point allows that kind of play to emerge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton Lecture on Sketching and Experience Design at Stanford</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton gives a lecture at the Stanford University Human-Computer Interaction Seminar (CS 547, June 1, 2007) giving an excellent deep dive into some of the topics in his book, Sketching User Experiences.
 Designing for experience comes with a whole new level of complexity. This is especially true in this emerging world of information appliances, reactive environments, and ubiquitous computing, where, along with those of their users, we have to factor in the convoluted behaviors of the products themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clover Innovates the Coffee Maker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/clover-innovates-coffee-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/clover-innovates-coffee-maker/</guid>
      <description>The $11,000 Clover Coffee Maker brews one cup of coffee at a time using a method similar to a French Press, but with the ability to customize water volume and temperature per cup. The machine is programmable and has a network connection, so the machine can use brewing parameters for specific roasts. Check the video below for the Clover in action.  According to Wired Magazine, Howard Schultz, the founder of Starbucks described the coffee by saying, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
