<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>search on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/search/</link><description>Recent content in search on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/search/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pinterest Tag Search and Suggestions</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-tag-search-and-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-tag-search-and-suggestions/</guid><description>Pinterest's search feature shows tag and board suggestions in the auto-completion list. Select terms/tags to display, and a horizontal list (accordion) of correlating tags to refine or narrow your your search are displayed below the search box.
Screencast / Video https://www.pinterest.com/</description></item><item><title>Bing Maps</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bing-maps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bing-maps/</guid><description>Microsoft has been doing some interesting work with Bing Maps. The augmented reality demos at the TED conference this week generated some buzz. The photo and video overlays were cool.
"We see this space, three-dimensional environment as being a canvas on which all sorts of applications can play out," says Bing Maps' Blaise Aguera y Arcas. "Maps, directions are really just one of them."
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tQzimblL3g8</description></item><item><title>uxfind</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/uxfind/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/uxfind/</guid><description>UXFind is a mashup that uses Google Custom Search Engine and Google App Engine. It provides a search engine tailored for User Experience pros. It indexes over 200 of user experience web sites and blogs. Oddly, they index my old blog iaslash, but not Konigi, so I guess the sources might not be so fresh. It's a great idea, and I've tried to do this in the past too, to just limit to sources I trust.</description></item><item><title>The UX of moving house: Real Estate Site Review</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-moving-house-real-estate-site-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-moving-house-real-estate-site-review/</guid><description>Martin Belam recently underwent the process of finding a house using real estate agency sites and has documented his observations. His notes are in a 2 part series looking first at site search and information architecture and following up with a review of results displays.
http://www.currybet.net/cbet_blog/2010/01/ux_moving_house_1.php</description></item><item><title>Google's New Fade In UI</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/googles-new-fade-ui/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/googles-new-fade-ui/</guid><description>Google launched a new behavior on the search page that hides everything but the logo and search form on load, and fades in the rest of the surrounding interface when the user moves the mouse. The idea is to give focus to search for the primary use case, where a user hits the page and starts typing without moving the mouse. They talk about the new behavior on the Google Blog.</description></item><item><title>iStockphoto Search</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/istockphoto-search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/istockphoto-search/</guid><description>iStockphoto takes a rather approach to search that offers plenty of options. When the user is logged out, they're presented with a search form on the front page with options that appear when the input is in focus. The user may then select typical options, e.g. size under photos, number of credits under illustration, format for video. On the results page, a simpler search form is displayed at the top of the page.</description></item><item><title>Kontain Search</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/kontain-search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/kontain-search/</guid><description>Kontain is a social media site for sharing photos, video, and music. The site provides a large, simple search form at the top of most aggregate pages, and a pared down version of the search form in the upper right corner of single asset pages. A pull down menu to the right of the search input displays options for searching everything, or restricting to media types, users, or just updates. The options are displayed as circles, and should function as radios.</description></item><item><title>New York Magazine Search</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-magazine-search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-magazine-search/</guid><description>New York Magazine provides a site search form in the header with options to limit the scope of search, and features advanced filtering options on results page. The results page is simple on the surface, but provides powerful filtering options in the sidebar. The search strategy is shown with actions for removing terms from the search or clear all.
I found some of the behaviors on filtering options to be inconsistent with others.</description></item><item><title>Read the &amp;amp;quot;Search User Interfaces&amp;amp;quot; book for free online</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/read-search-user-interfaces-book-free-online/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/read-search-user-interfaces-book-free-online/</guid><description>Marti Hearst and Cambridge University Press have made the Search User Interfaces book available for free online. About the book:
This book focuses on the human users of search engines and the tool they use to interact with them: the search user interface. The truly worldwide reach of the Web has brought with it a new realization among computer scientists and laypeople of the enormous importance of usability and user interface design.</description></item><item><title>Designing for Faceted Search</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</guid><description>Stephanie Lemieux discusses issues to consider when designing faceted navigation interfaces for search in the latest UIE newsletter.
Faceted search is a very popular and powerful solution when done well; it allows users to deconstruct a large set of results into bite-size pieces and navigate based on what’s important to them. But faceted search by itself is not necessarily going to make your users lives easier. You need to understand your users’ mental models (how they seek information), test your assumptions about how they will interpret your terms and categories and spend time refining your approach.</description></item><item><title>iWantMyName</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/iwantmyname/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/iwantmyname/</guid><description>iWantMyName is a service for international domain registration and management.
http://iwantmyname.com</description></item><item><title>Sideline Twitter Search App from Yahoo!</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/sideline-twitter-search-app-yahoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/sideline-twitter-search-app-yahoo/</guid><description>Sideline is an Adobe AIR desktop application built with the Yahoo! User Interface Library (YUI) that allows users to create and group custom queries by topics of interest, as well as view topic trends. Very nicely done. Am looking at at how the advanced search works at the moment. Looks very easy to build up an seems like it might be the perfect app for a lurker or follower who doesn't post much.</description></item><item><title>Zappos Search Results Filtering</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</guid><description>The Zappos' search engine provides a nice results filtering interfaces that presents the user with facets for refining their search. The user can click on the terms at the top of the search results page to narrow the set, and a breadcrumb trail shows the selections they've made. Each term in the breadcrumb provides a checkbox to remove any one of those selections and broaden their search.
1. Users run a search using the site's global search box.</description></item><item><title>NIKEFOOTBALL Search Box</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/nikefootball-search-box/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/nikefootball-search-box/</guid><description>The Nike Football site uses a deceptively simple trick to draw attention to its unobtrusive search box. The narrow sidebar navigation menu features what looks like a search box that is a bit too small to be usable. Clicking what you think is the search box expands a real search input adjacent to the sidebar in the body.
It's a clever method, but as you can see from the comments, it's not without problems.</description></item><item><title>Google Quick Search Box</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/google-quick-search-box/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/google-quick-search-box/</guid><description>Google's Quick Search Box is a QuickSilver-like launcher that lets you search your computer for applications and data, as well as search the web, and your Google Apps accounts. I presume this will also eventually replace the search interface provided by Google Desktop. The project is in beta and is provided via the Labs.
From their blog:
One of our goals at Google is to make your search experience as fluid as possible.</description></item></channel></rss>