<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>floating layers on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/floating-layers/</link><description>Recent content in floating layers on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/floating-layers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apture Text Editing</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apture-text-editing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apture-text-editing/</guid><description>The Apture service allows web site publishers to easily find and incorporate multimedia content from the web into their site. Apture requires one line of javascript code to work. The service embeds dynamic links in the page that allow users to preview content from the outside sites in AJAX layers over the page content. Publishers can choose to automatically generate links from certain sites, e.g. YouTube and Wikipedia. They can also create links by selecting text on the page and finding the content they want to embed.</description></item><item><title>Daylife Favoriting</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-favoriting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-favoriting/</guid><description>Daylife provides an excellent mechanism for favoriting. The news portal, which is published to demonstrate the company's news delivery product, provides a simple method for saving favorites that uses a star icon. The site classifies articles into topics which are simply terms describing a subject matter, person, or company/organization. Users see star icons when they hover over a link to a topic or a story. Starring the link adds the topic or story to their "</description></item><item><title>i'minlikewithyou Comments</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iminlikewithyou-comments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iminlikewithyou-comments/</guid><description>i'minlikewithyou's full Flash interface pushes the boundaries of what can be done with user interfaces in terms of social interaction. The comment feature on the site's news articles and videos allows users to place comments (including a drawing) over the media. In the case of video, the comments appear briefly on top of the video at the points where people have placed them. Because of the volume of commenting on these videos, tons of comments will roll by in a frenzied flash, so it's hard to read them all.</description></item></channel></rss>