<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interface on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/interface/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interface on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/interface/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Usabilla Discover</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</guid>
      <description>Usabilla Discover is like a mashup of Pinterest and LittleBigDetails, or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a social LittleSnapper. Whatever the pitch, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty useful to share screenshots of interface and visual designs you like. Now to figure out how to get my over 2,000 screenshots into it.
Note: To get in during the beta, sign up here with code &amp;quot;KONIGI&amp;quot;, good for the first 200 who use the code.
http://discover.usabilla.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Design Pattern Gallery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil&amp;rsquo;s forthcoming book, Mobile Design Pattern Gallery, is set to be released by O&amp;rsquo;Reilly in the Fall of 2011.
Theresa launched a site to go along with the book that includes a fantastic gallery of 70 user interface design patterns for mobile devices with 400+ supporting examples from iOS, Android, BlackBerry, WebOS, Windows Mobile, and Symbian applications. The gallery covers a broad range of problems from designing your application&#39;s navigation to choosing the right invitation technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper 2011 Update</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-2011-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-2011-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 years since I updated the printable graph paper PDFs I provide for user interface design sketching. You can download the printable PDFs from here. (Yes, I use the word &amp;quot;Here&amp;quot; in links.)
In the last year I&#39;ve gotten a lot of requests to replenish the inventory of wireframe and storyboard graphpaper notepads that I fulfilled via Amazon.com, and the wirebound sketch books. I feel bummed every time I tell people that I decided to get out of that little business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Koblin: Artfully visualizing our humanity</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</guid>
      <description>From Aaron Koblin&amp;rsquo;s TED presentation:
&amp;ldquo;Artist Aaron Koblin takes vast amounts of data &amp;ndash; and at times vast numbers of people &amp;ndash; and weaves them into stunning visualizations. From elegant lines tracing airline flights to landscapes of cell phone data, from a Johnny Cash video assembled from crowd-sourced drawings to the &amp;ldquo;Wilderness Downtown&amp;rdquo; video that customizes for the user, his works brilliantly explore how modern technology can make us more human.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Interaction Design Patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Android Patterns is a community-contributed site with interaction patterns for Android app design. The site is created by the folks at Dutch interaction design firm, UNITiD, who also provide an mobile wireframe templates for Android and Blackberry devices.
http://www.androidpatterns.com/wiki</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phonedoo: Dry erase iPhone sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo makes a nice iPhone UI sketching product called Phone Doos. They are 6.8&amp;quot; by 3.5&amp;quot; dry erase iPhone surfaces with faint grid lines and magnetic backing. A pack contains 10 Phone Doos.
I like that these gives you a surface to work on that can be re-arranged easily on a table and presented on a metallic wall. They have some good screenshots using them arranged on a whiteboard with flow arrows pointing between them, which is another thing that&#39;s probably much easier with these as opposed to using paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Templates and Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-templates-and-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-templates-and-stencils/</guid>
      <description>Emily Chang rounds up the offering of iPad UI stencils. Some nice OmniGraffle and Photoshop sets in there.
http://emilychang.com/2010/03/ipad-templates-and-stencils/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17 guidelines for better information architecture from 1991</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/17-guidelines-better-information-architecture-1991/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/17-guidelines-better-information-architecture-1991/</guid>
      <description>Jussi Pasanen of Volkside pulls out an HCI gem in Kent L. Norman&amp;rsquo;s The Psychology of Menu Selection: Designing Cognitive Control at the Human/Computer Interface, and repurposes the list of guidelines from the Checklist for Menu Design to provide a set of suitable guidelines for information architects to use with today’s websites. Norman&amp;rsquo;s book is available for free on the web.
Via @BogieZero
http://www.volkside.com/2010/03/15-guidelines-for-better-information-architecture-from-1991/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best/Worst UI You&#39;ve Ever Used</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bestworst-ui-youve-ever-used/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bestworst-ui-youve-ever-used/</guid>
      <description>UX Exchange throws down on The Best UI You&amp;rsquo;ve Ever Used.
Stack Overflow throws up The Worst UI You&#39;ve Ever Used.
http://stackoverflow.com/questions/238177/worst-ui-youve-ever-used</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BiDi Screen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</guid>
      <description>BiDi Screen was demonstrated at SIGGRAPH Asia this year. It is a thin, depth-sensing LCD for 3D interaction using light fields.
The BiDi Screen is an example of a new type of I/O device that possesses the ability to both capture images and display them. This thin, bidirectional screen extends the latest trend in LCD devices, which has seen the incorporation of photo-diodes into every display pixel. Using a novel optical masking technique developed at the Media Lab, the BiDi Screen can capture lightfield-like quantities, unlocking a wide array of applications from 3-D gesture interaction with CE devices, to seamless video communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mobileHCI 2009 Proceedings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobilehci-2009-proceedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobilehci-2009-proceedings/</guid>
      <description>The full text of the proceedings of MobileHCI09, the 11th International Conference on Human-Computer Interaction with Mobile Devices and Services is available online. The event, which covers mobile and wearable computing devices and services took place September, 2009 at the University of Bonn in Germany.
http://mobilehci.uni-siegen.de/mhci2009.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the close tab behaviour in Google Chrome</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>Basil Safwat does a very thorough comparison of the the tabs in Mac Safari and Chrome, pointing out the subtleties in the close button positioning and behavior. While Mac close icons are on the left by convention, Chrome positions them to the right of the tab and keeps them visible, while Safari positions them to the left and only displays the close icon on hover. I initially had to relearn the close button position because Firefox also places them on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s New Fade In UI</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/googles-new-fade-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/googles-new-fade-ui/</guid>
      <description>Google launched a new behavior on the search page that hides everything but the logo and search form on load, and fades in the rest of the surrounding interface when the user moves the mouse. The idea is to give focus to search for the primary use case, where a user hits the page and starts typing without moving the mouse. They talk about the new behavior on the Google Blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq Exports Multi-Canvas Mockups to Single PDF</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/balsamiq-exports-multi-canvas-mockups-single-pdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/balsamiq-exports-multi-canvas-mockups-single-pdf/</guid>
      <description>Balsamiq announced that Mockups now supports export of multiple canvases to a single PDF that includes links. This means that your multi-canvas mockups can now be used as click through prototypes in Acrobat. Download the demo PDF file for a test drive.
http://www.balsamiq.com/blog/2009/11/13/weekly-release-export-to-pdf-a-fresh-coat-of-paint/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Log in or sign up?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</guid>
      <description>Leah Culver discusses the design of hybrid sign up / login forms, showing a few examples and the final form as implemented for Leafy Chat. Uses the familiar I&amp;rsquo;m a customer/I&amp;rsquo;m new here radios that we know from Amazon, but positions it before the password field, which I find an improvement over the Amazon implementation. Lots of ideas in the comments.
http://blog.leahculver.com/2009/11/log-in-or-sign-up.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design GalleRIA</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-galleria/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-galleria/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil has started a Tumblog design gallery and showcase of Rich Internet Applications.
http://designgalleria.tumblr.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpoolCast with Todd Zaki Warfel: Prototyping Experiences</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/spoolcast-todd-zaki-warfel-prototyping-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/spoolcast-todd-zaki-warfel-prototyping-experiences/</guid>
      <description>Jared Spool talks with Todd Zaki Warfel about his forthcoming Prototyping book to be published by Rosenfeld Media, and got him to talk about his 2 years of research while working on the book.
Todd&amp;rsquo;s firm, Message First, utilizes prototypes as a core element of the design process and has been giving a series of presentations and workshops recently to describe his research into the different prototyping practices of UX pros, and talk about the utility of the prototype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for the iPhone 3G: Tips and Tools</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-iphone-3g-tips-and-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-iphone-3g-tips-and-tools/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil updated her iPhone 3G stencil set for OmniGraffle at Graffletopia, and posted a few tips and tools that might be helpful to iPhone designers. http://theresaneil.wordpress.com/2009/09/16/iphone3g-design-resources/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notepod: The sketchbook for your app ideas</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/notepod-sketchbook-your-app-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/notepod-sketchbook-your-app-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Notepod is an iPhone graph paper sketchbook. The specs:
Three 60 x 110mm, 100pp Notepods printed on both sides. 80gsm laser throughout with a stiff black strawboard back.
Front: 52mm by 77mm of blank space floating in darkness. Endless possibilities in a form reminiscent of a popular smart phone.
Back: A light 6mm grid, perfect for notes or jotting down the phone number of a hot geek.
 I&amp;rsquo;m getting a set, even though I don&amp;rsquo;t typically do iPhone design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencils, Pens &amp; Markers Sets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pencils-pens-markers-sets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pencils-pens-markers-sets/</guid>
      <description>This one is for all you interface sketchers. Wireframes Magazine asked designers what their favorite pens, pencils, and markers are for UI sketching, and posted photos of the responses. Click the first photo to view the expanded gallery of tools.
http://wireframes.linowski.ca/2009/09/markers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Prototyping Tools Revisited</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/rapid-prototyping-tools-revisited/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rapid-prototyping-tools-revisited/</guid>
      <description>Dan Harrelson at adaptive path posts his updated list of prototyping tools. You can view the Google Doc directly here.
Via @andrewkorf
http://www.adaptivepath.com/blog/2009/09/16/rapid-prototyping-tools-revisited/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils, Version 3</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils-version-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils-version-3/</guid>
      <description>Version 3 of the OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils has been posted. Download it now.
Modified all form and controls elements for color consistency. Added the following: sliders, new form icons, tag clouds and lists, a-z lists, IAB advertising units, iphone chrome, web browser chrome. You&amp;rsquo;ll also see the start of a style guide based on the UI components here, which is being used for the Prototyping Kit we&amp;rsquo;re developing.
http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Portfolios Using Google Maps UI</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-portfolios-using-google-maps-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-portfolios-using-google-maps-ui/</guid>
      <description>It appears there are quite a designers who are using the navigation tools for Google Maps to create pannable portfolios. Follow the links via Heavy Backpack and GoogleMapsMania.
http://www.heavy-backpack.com/archives/articles/design-folios-with-google-maps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barry Schwartz on the Paradox of Choice</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/barry-schwartz-paradox-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/barry-schwartz-paradox-choice/</guid>
      <description>Psychologist Barry Schwartz takes aim at a central tenet of western societies on TED: freedom of choice. In Schwartz&amp;rsquo;s estimation, choice has made us not freer but more paralyzed, not happier but more dissatisfied.
The idea that more choice leads to paralysis rather than happiness resonates strongly with me. I think about where I am in terms of my spiritual and psychological development, and I do feel dissatisfied when things aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect today and I find it troublesome that I think this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Removes Rounded Corners</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-removes-rounded-corners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-removes-rounded-corners/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not terribly newsworthy, but Facebook&amp;rsquo;s design team announced that they&amp;rsquo;ve stopped rounding corners on all elements. I noticed, however, that they kept the slight (3px?) rounding of names in the To: field of the messaging section. That somehow feels like a natural place for an exception to rounding corners for some reason. You know, so you don&amp;rsquo;t get impaled when backspacing in the field. Kidding. This is a quote from their announcement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing UI Complexity</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/managing-ui-complexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/managing-ui-complexity/</guid>
      <description>Brandon Walkin&amp;rsquo;s article &amp;ldquo;Managing UI Complexity&amp;rdquo; offers some excellent pointers or reminders of concepts and techniques that help reduce complexity in an interface, including progressive diclosure, contextual actions, aligment and hierarchy. There&amp;rsquo;s an abundance of examples with screenshots and deconstruction of interfaces to demonstrate the techniques in practice.
http://www.brandonwalkin.com/blog/2009/08/10/managing-ui-complexity/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversational UX Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/conversational-ux-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/conversational-ux-design/</guid>
      <description>[I]f you make it easy to talk to me, I will immediately be a lot more likely to keep talking.
Zeus Jones has a great write up about using conversational language and cues to invite users through interactions. The deconstruction of the lazy trial/registration process in Tumblr is used to demonstrate how this type of engagement makes the learning process natural and inviting. The discussion picks up on the Cluetrain meme of markets as conversations, positing that systems are conversations, and turning front ends into actors that use conversational language as interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Lang&#39;s Top 10 UX Myths</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/keith-langs-top-10-ux-myths/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/keith-langs-top-10-ux-myths/</guid>
      <description>Keith Lang, co-founder of plasq.com, wrote a fantastic article for Think Vitamin about UX Myths. It&amp;rsquo;s full of references and examples debunking stuff we hear repeated enough times that they begin to go unquestioned.
The top 10 UX myth list:
 The Design Has to be Original People Read People Know What They Like Design Always with Implementation in Mind Can’t Decide? Make it a Preference If you Have Great Search, You Don’t Need Great Information Architecture UX Design Stops at the Edges of the Product Design to Avoid Clicks People Don’t Change If the Design is a Good One, You Don’t Need to Test It  Some of these become so ingrained, that it takes a lot of effort to convince clients or colleagues otherwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically generate table of contents using jQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/automatically-generate-table-contents-using-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/automatically-generate-table-contents-using-jquery/</guid>
      <description>Janko at Warp Speed demonstrates a technique using jQuery to provide a navigable table of contents menu using the headings in your page content. I particularly like the method he&amp;rsquo;s come up with for displaying headings to show the proportion of content for each section relative to the whole. I think you could do some nice styling to display the blocks as small multiples of proportion and scale in the margin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Sprites with Inline Images</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/css-sprites-inline-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/css-sprites-inline-images/</guid>
      <description>CSS-Tricks wrote up a tutorial demonstrating how to use CSS clipping to use image sprite on inline elements that flow with content. This is a nice little technique for small icons that you want to come immediately after text, for example. Check it out.
http://css-tricks.com/css-sprites-with-inline-images/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MOBIFY: Mobile Site Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobify-mobile-site-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobify-mobile-site-service/</guid>
      <description>MOBIFY is a service that lets you create a mobile version of your site for free. You start by entering your site url, and selecting regions of your page design to be used in the mobile template, using their online template editor. For many sites, one template may be sufficient to serve all of your page types. After selecting regions, you may change their order in preview mode, as well as add custom HTML and modify CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone is all Fun and Games</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-all-fun-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-all-fun-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Fred Beecher wrote the excellent article &amp;ldquo;The iPhone is Not Easy to Use: A New Direction for User Experience&amp;rdquo; on Johnny Holland to talk about why the iPhone is not easy to use (at first), and why it changes the game for user experience designers. The examples illustrate how gestural interfaces are hidden, and lack the affordances of physical buttons. But the real story here is how the iPhone brings one thing to the experience that is more important than usability&amp;#8212;fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframing over the shoulder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-over-shoulder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-over-shoulder/</guid>
      <description>This is a video on From The Couch podcast showing David Perel sketching wireframes for the Obox Theme. The first half shows David sketching, and during the second half he talks through the interface.
View the article for more.
http://www.from-the-couch.com/post.cfm/title/wireframing-over-the-shoulder</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realizations of Rounded Rectangles</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/realizations-rounded-rectangles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/realizations-rounded-rectangles/</guid>
      <description>Plasq designer, Keith Lang, recounts the story from computer folklore of how the rounded rectangle came to dominate the Mac OS, and discusses its effect on visual cognition. He gets Professor Jürg Nänni, author of Visual Perception to offer his opinion.
A rectangle with sharp edges takes indeed a little bit more cognitive visible effort than for example an ellipse of the same size. Our “fovea-eye” is even faster in recording a circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Forget Heuristics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dont-forget-heuristics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dont-forget-heuristics/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil continues her tips for designing great Flex UX&amp;rsquo;s showcasing interfaces that exemplify Jakob Nielsen&amp;rsquo;s 10 usability heuristics.
Don’t forget the usability basics. Jakob Nielsen’s Ten Usability Heuristics are as relevant now as they were in 1999. I stress this because I looked at the Flex showcase recently, and it looks like many of the applications are not built with these best practices in mind.
 Read more at Theresa Neil&amp;rsquo;s blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiments in Password Masking</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/experiments-password-masking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/experiments-password-masking/</guid>
      <description>Jakob Nielsen recently called for an end to password masking, and a few people have come up with interesting approaches that try to find a middle ground between the typical prractice of masking passwords with asterisks. arc90 are experimenting with a half-masking technique. The method partially obscures the password by placing a few blurred characters in the background so that the characters are not easily read by someone looking over the user&amp;rsquo;s shoulder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helveticons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/helveticons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/helveticons/</guid>
      <description>Helveticons are royalty-free vector icons, glyphs and symbols based on the Helvetica Bold typeface. http://helveticons.ch/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redub Designs a Better Online Magazine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/redub-designs-better-online-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/redub-designs-better-online-magazine/</guid>
      <description>I came across Redub&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Make Me Scroll&amp;rdquo; presentation embedded above, which looks at the current offering of magazine readers which are modeled after print layouts, are difficult to read, SEO-unfriendly, and which rarely use the full capabilities provided by web browsers, e.g. multi-media. Or they&amp;rsquo;re modeled largely after blogs with articles are long and scrolling, are limited by the possibilities of HTML/CSS, and have layouts that aren&amp;rsquo;t differentiated from blogs and which pale in comparison to the layout in the printed version of the original magazine article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Microcopy</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/writing-microcopy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/writing-microcopy/</guid>
      <description>Joshua Porter writes about the use of microcopy to create confidence and alleviate concerns in customers about the actions they take on your site. Ironically, the smallest bits of copy, microcopy, can have the biggest impact. &amp;hellip; Microcopy is small yet powerful copy. It’s fast, light, and deadly. It’s a short sentence, a phrase, a few words. A single word. It’s the small copy that has the biggest impact. Don’t judge it on its size…judge it on its effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Login Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/100-login-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/100-login-forms/</guid>
      <description>Design Reviver collects and captures a massive set of 100 login forms.
http://designreviver.com/inspiration/100-sites-with-outstanding-login-forms/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read the &amp;amp;quot;Search User Interfaces&amp;amp;quot; book for free online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/read-search-user-interfaces-book-free-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/read-search-user-interfaces-book-free-online/</guid>
      <description>Marti Hearst and Cambridge University Press have made the Search User Interfaces book available for free online. About the book:
This book focuses on the human users of search engines and the tool they use to interact with them: the search user interface. The truly worldwide reach of the Web has brought with it a new realization among computer scientists and laypeople of the enormous importance of usability and user interface design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi DIY Wireframe Magnets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-diy-wireframe-magnets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-diy-wireframe-magnets/</guid>
      <description>The Konigi DIY Wireframe Magnet Kit is based on the wireframe stencils and includes 3 sheets of elements that might be useful in whiteboard prototyping. Simply download and print the PDFs onto magnet sheets. They were designed and tested for use with Avery 3270 Printable Magnet Sheets for Inkjet Printers. Lamination is also recommended so they&amp;rsquo;re usable with dry-erase markers. Enjoy!
http://konigi.com/tools/wireframe-magnets-diy-kit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Labs Design Challenge: Reinventing Tabs in the Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mozilla-labs-design-challenge-reinventing-tabs-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mozilla-labs-design-challenge-reinventing-tabs-browser/</guid>
      <description>Mozilla Labs together with IxDA and Johnny Holland presented the Summer 09 Design Challenge as part of their Concept Series. The challenge theme is &amp;ldquo;Reinventing Tabs in the Browser - How can we create, navigate and manage multiple web sites within the same browser instance?&amp;rdquo; Voting on concept submissions ends on July 5. Will take a while to make it through the over 120 concepts!
http://design-challenge.mozilla.com/summer09/showcase.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing with DIY UI Magnets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/playing-diy-ui-magnets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/playing-diy-ui-magnets/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m experimenting with making magnets of some of the elements of the Wireframe Stencil to use for prototyping. Was an interesting experiment printing and cutting these. Next time I think I&amp;rsquo;ll have to laminate the sheet first, and then cut. The lamination might make it possible to write on them with dry erase marker. If you write directly on the magnet sheets the ink will stay permanently I&amp;rsquo;d think. The surface seems kind of porous and a little textured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/axure-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/axure-mac/</guid>
      <description>Axure started a blog to discuss progress on the MAxure, a Mac version of Axure RP. Nice.
http://www.axureformac.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Testing Results for LessAccounting.com Call To Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ui-testing-results-lessaccountingcom-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ui-testing-results-lessaccountingcom-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Less Everything did a couple of A-B tests on the call to action buttons on the home page of their Less Accounting product. Their first test modified the design of 2 buttons (see tour, try), using 1 button instead for the &amp;ldquo;Try Less Accounting&amp;rdquo; link and a text link for &amp;ldquo;See Tour&amp;rdquo;. They noticed a small increase in conversion when they went to the single button, and then did a second test, reversing the position of the button and link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone UX Reviews</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-ux-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-ux-reviews/</guid>
      <description>iPhone UX Reviews is a blog devoted to user experience reviews of iPhone apps &amp;amp; advice on creating apps.
http://www.iphoneuxreviews.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EightShapes Unify: Wireframes Preview</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/eightshapes-unify-wireframes-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/eightshapes-unify-wireframes-preview/</guid>
      <description>EightShapes demonstrates the Adobe InDesign system for wireframing within their Unify Framework.
http://unify.eightshapes.com/wireframes/wireframes-preview/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Life Cycle of a Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/life-cycle-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/life-cycle-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>Nick Finck&amp;rsquo;s Puget Sound SIGCHI lecture on the Lifecycle of the Wireframe discusses Nick&amp;rsquo;s IA process. My overall strategy for IA is 3 step process; understanding the problem (note: not merely identifying the problem but really understanding it), find a solution (there may be more than one solution, but there is often only one right solution), and present the solution (a large part of your job as a IA is presenting your work so the client can understand the results).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Verbs As Nouns in User Interfaces</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/using-verbs-nouns-user-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/using-verbs-nouns-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>There&#39;s an interesting discussion in UX Matters prompted by a question regarding the use of verbs as nouns. This wording used in an enterprise context is the example provided, &#34;Click here to view your views.&#34; Confusing and awkward. A dialogue follows with several designers, who seem to agree that understanding the language of the business and context, and using that in the given situation is the right approach. It&#39;s a matter of unearthing the terminology, whether through contextual inquiry and exercises like card sorting, and using what&#39;s appropriate and familiar in the context, so users can &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons, Royalty Free, EPS and PNG</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-royalty-free-eps-and-png/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-royalty-free-eps-and-png/</guid>
      <description>Based on demand to use the wireframe icons on web sites, and to use them in Adobe Illustrator and Visio, I&amp;rsquo;ve created EPS and PNG versions that include a Royalty Free license agreement. You may use them in your UX documents, but the license also permits you to use them in web sites. There are restrictions for use on commercial products or commercial applications that offer products
or services for sale or for fee-based usage, however.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing For Sign Up</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-sign/</guid>
      <description>View more presentations from Joshua Porter.   Joshua Porter&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Designing for Sign Up&amp;rdquo; presentation from Webstock, 2009, does a great job of focusing the task of sign up on user motivation and anxiety, and thinking through scenarios that help remove barriers to entry. As he says, the form itself is the least of your concerns. Porter describes the entire experience leading up to the call to action, providing excellent examples that ease users into sign up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highrise Contacts Design Exploration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/highrise-contacts-design-exploration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/highrise-contacts-design-exploration/</guid>
      <description>Jason Zimdars describes the explorations and iterations over 37 Signals&amp;rsquo; Highrise CRM application. There&amp;rsquo;s some nice description of the decision making process to arrive at modifications to the UI that clean up the use of tags clouds, organize listings of contacts, and attention to details around type and proportion. http://jasonzimdars.com/svn/highrise.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The future of wireframes?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/future-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/future-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>On Made By Many, Isaac Pinnock looks back at his 10 year history using wireframes and their evolution in IA practice from time consuming deliverable in functional specifications, to disposable artifacts of the design process. The notion that highly visual wireframes should be part of the design process resonates with me. http://www.madebymany.co.uk/the-future-of-wireframes-00991</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chartbeat dashboard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/chartbeat-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/chartbeat-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Slick real time data visualization in the dashboard of web analytics service chartbeat. http://chartbeat.com/dashboard/?url=avc.com&amp;k=317a25eccba186e0f6b558f45214c0e7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A4 sketching paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/a4-sketching-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/a4-sketching-paper/</guid>
      <description>More printable sketch paper options, this time from Henk Wijnholds.
Via i heart wireframes.
http://www.concept7.nl/henk/prolonging-the-magic-a4-sketching-paper/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call To Action Buttons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/call-action-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/call-action-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Lee Munroe has collected a slew of examples of Signup and Download call to action buttons that exemplify good CTA button design. He has 4 criteria for designing a good call to action button, involving the appropriate use of color, language, size, and white space around the button.
http://www.leemunroe.com/web-design-trends-call-to-action-signup-download-buttons/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touchscreen Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/touchscreen-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/touchscreen-stencils/</guid>
      <description>Dan Saffer of Kicker Studio provides free touch screen gesture stencils for OmniGraffle, Visio, Illustrator, and Fireworks. The icons are designed by Rachel Glaves for Saffer&amp;rsquo;s book, Designing Gestural Interfaces, and depict hands performing common touchscreen gestures like tap, slide, point, drag, pinch, and spread.
http://www.kickerstudio.com/blog/2008/12/touchscreen-stencils/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Excellent Examples of Lazy Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/12-excellent-examples-lazy-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/12-excellent-examples-lazy-registration/</guid>
      <description>This is a short entry about sites that use &amp;ldquo;Lazy Registration,&amp;rdquo; or registration/sign up processes that often don&amp;rsquo;t require any information from the user while they try out a site, until they decide to commit to using it. In some cases, sites bypass signup altogether, and in others, users are permitted to register once they&amp;rsquo;ve decided to go beyond simply &amp;ldquo;testing out&amp;rdquo; a site or application. As noted, the process of &amp;ldquo;getting your feet wet by trying,&amp;rdquo; most likely leads to more sign ups because of the frictionless experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for Faceted Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</guid>
      <description>Stephanie Lemieux discusses issues to consider when designing faceted navigation interfaces for search in the latest UIE newsletter.
Faceted search is a very popular and powerful solution when done well; it allows users to deconstruct a large set of results into bite-size pieces and navigate based on what’s important to them. But faceted search by itself is not necessarily going to make your users lives easier. You need to understand your users’ mental models (how they seek information), test your assumptions about how they will interpret your terms and categories and spend time refining your approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Update (v. 2.4)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-update-v-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-update-v-24/</guid>
      <description>The OmniGraffle UX Template has been updated. I finally got around to cleaning up the Persona example from the old version 1 (the urlgreyhot version), added a detailed persona, a site map example with diagramming style (.gdiagramstyle file), and a mental model example. Download from the Tools page.
http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Prototyping Webtrends</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-prototyping-webtrends/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-prototyping-webtrends/</guid>
      <description>Justin Garrity writes about Web Trends&amp;rsquo; use of paper prototyping to design the applications&amp;rsquo; Tag Builder.
http://blog.webtrends.com/2009/04/22/a-new-user-experience-part-2-of-5-paper-prototyping/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle 5 Keyboard Shortcuts Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-5-keyboard-shortcuts-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-5-keyboard-shortcuts-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>For all you Grafflers out there, Nick Finck has created a sweet single page cheat sheet illustrating OmniGraffle&amp;rsquo;s numerous and well hidden keyboard shortcuts. Nick took the multi-page Help file provided by Omni and consolidated all of the tips into a single tabloid poster that you can print and stick on your wall to make life easier. More info at the OmniMouth.
Download the graffle directly here or from the OmniGraffle Extras page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunkering: Putting Disorientation into the Design Process</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hunkering-putting-disorientation-design-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hunkering-putting-disorientation-design-process/</guid>
      <description>Jared Spool talks about &#34;visual disorientation,&#34; a designer&#39;s technique for evaluating your design work in the middle of a process. It&#39;s certainly common to see designer&#39;s tack up pieces of paper around their project space, e.g. schematics, pictures with references to other objects that provide inspiration, etc. Hunkering, however, is more of a technique to create disorientation and change in one&#39;s perspective momentarily, to assess what you&#39;ve done. Visual disorientation is a fast way to identify the places where things don&#39;t quite match up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchy Wireframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchy-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchy-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>Aaron Hursman shares an example of his sketch-style wireframes using Jonathan Abbett&amp;rsquo;s Sketch Stencils for Visio.
Thanks to Andrew for the link.
http://aaron.hursman.com/2009/04/sketchy-wireframes_08.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Vision: The design superpower also known as The Squint Test</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-vision-design-superpower-also-known-squint-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-vision-design-superpower-also-known-squint-test/</guid>
      <description>UX Hero points out a technique that you may not be using, but should consider. Stepping back and squinting to evaluate your work is something I was told to do repeatedly when I was first learning to paint, and is something I still do today as an interface designer. It helps you see the whole of your screen and look for anything that stands out, and see what needs to draw more attention, depending on the priority and hierarchy of your page elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Whiteboarding with Twiddla</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</guid>
      <description>Twiddla is an easy to use collaborative whiteboard service, but it&amp;rsquo;s really got the potential to be much more. The whiteboard lets you mark up websites and graphics, and even use a drag-drop library of interface elements for working on interface concepts collaboratively. You communicate with others in the meeting with the chat window, and you can also use built in audio-conferencing capabilities. Very impressive, and free. Would make sense for there to be options for private meetings as well as embedding the whiteboard into your CMS or intranet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigation Markup After Content</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/navigation-markup-after-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/navigation-markup-after-content/</guid>
      <description>CSS tips offers an SEO tip for putting navigation after content and repositioning back to top by absolutely positioning the navigation block absolutely inside a relative block.
http://css-tricks.com/navigation-markup-after-content/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justinmind Prototyper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/justinmind-prototyper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/justinmind-prototyper/</guid>
      <description>Justinmind Prototyper is a tool to design wireframes and run simulations for web, desktop and mobile applications. The product looks similar to Axure, and lets you define user interface elements using a drag and drop environment with component libraries, and attach actions to components. The prototypes allow you to map interactive behaviors to elements, define process logic and flow, and add functional specifications and annotations. Looks very full featured and offers the possibility of running a web server to deploy multiple prototypes that are viewable in a browser and allow users to comment on designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research: Product Comparison and Pricing Tables</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/research-product-comparison-and-pricing-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/research-product-comparison-and-pricing-tables/</guid>
      <description>Nick Finck talks about the design of Product Comparison Tables.
http://www.nickfinck.com/blog/entry/research_product_comparison_and_pricing_tables/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone Mockup</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-mockup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-mockup/</guid>
      <description>iPhone Mockup looks like a cool proof of concept for a sketchy mockup app for iPhone. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit like Balsamiq in spirit, but is done completely with JQuery. Firefox and Safari are the target browsers, and there is no option for doing secure mockups. Whatever you do will be visible to the world, so don&amp;rsquo;t plan on using it for anything other than playing. Nice concept though. Thanks, Andrew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16 Design Tools for Prototyping and Wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/16-design-tools-prototyping-and-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/16-design-tools-prototyping-and-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Gary Barber does a roundup of wireframing and prototyping tools at Sitepoint.
http://www.sitepoint.com/article/tools-prototyping-wireframing/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Sitemap and Footer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/modern-sitemap-and-footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/modern-sitemap-and-footer/</guid>
      <description>Web Designer Wall collects screenshots from 20 sites with footer sitemaps.
Via @dreamtime
http://www.webdesignerwall.com/trends/modern-sitemap-and-footer/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Updated (v. 2.2)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-v-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-v-22/</guid>
      <description>The UX Template has been updated (Vers. 2.2) with some minor fixes. The iPhone template was recreated using OmniGraffle drawing tools rather than imported PNGs to shrink file size. Template was converted to flat XML format rather than bundle. Guides cleaned up on all pages.
http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/get-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/get-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Grace Smith has posted a lengthy list of articles, applications, and resources related to wireframing.
http://www.gracesmith.co.uk/get-wireframing-the-all-in-one-guide/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SingleFunction</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/singlefunction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/singlefunction/</guid>
      <description>A showcase of single-serving or single-function sites.
Via ehub
http://singlefunction.com/showcase/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframes for the Wicked Slides</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframes-wicked-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframes-wicked-slides/</guid>
      <description>Wireframes for the Wicked  Slides from the SXSWi presentation with Nick Finck, Donna Spencer, and myself. The slides cover our introductory overview of wireframes, which led to our 1&amp;frasl;2 hour discussion panel afterwards. http://www.slideshare.net/nickf/wireframes-for-the-wicked</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Tips for a Great Flex UX</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/6-tips-great-flex-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/6-tips-great-flex-ux/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil is writing a 6 part series of articles on designing great Adobe Flex/Air user experiences. The first 3 parts are up now.
After designing several large enterprise applications for diverse clients and industries, I’ve noticed some barriers to crafting a great experience in Flex. I think these barriers arise from the relative newness of the technology (and RIAs in general), the initial focus on development over design, and the confidence that Flex can provide a great UX out of the box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sockyung Hong&#39;s Vimeo Sketches on Flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sockyung-hongs-vimeo-sketches-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sockyung-hongs-vimeo-sketches-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Sockyung Hong posts sketches of Vimeo design concepts on Flickr. Very nice to examples of peoples&amp;rsquo; design sketches like this.
Via agentangelo
http://flickr.com/photos/soxiam/tags/sketch,vimeo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchy Wireframes for Visio</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchy-wireframes-visio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchy-wireframes-visio/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m guessing many Visio users out there already know about it, but in case you don&amp;rsquo;t, Wireframes Magazine points to Niklas Wolkert&amp;rsquo;s Sketchy UI Shapes (found on Henrik Olsen&amp;rsquo;s GUUUI) and the updated Updated Sketch shapes by Jonathan Abbett. http://wireframes.linowski.ca/?p=445</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQuery Sparklines</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jquery-sparklines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jquery-sparklines/</guid>
      <description>The jQuery Sparklines plugin generates sparklines (small inline charts) directly in the browser using data supplied either inline in the HTML, or via javascript. The plugin is compatible with most modern browsers and has been tested with Firefox 2+, Safari 3+, Opera 9 and Internet Explorer 6 &amp;amp; 7.
Via @darrengeraghty
http://www.omnipotent.net/jquery.sparkline/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A to Z Indexes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/z-indexes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/z-indexes/</guid>
      <description>uxRefresh has collected a handful of examples of A-Z indexes of titles on large sites. Also useful might be a look at the article I wrote about KWIC/KWOC/A-Z Site Indexes work I did while at Bell Labs, and for a deeper dive, look at the list of links of indexer-designed examples on the Montague Institute&amp;rsquo;s site. Many of the latter are still valid, but there&amp;rsquo;s some link rot there too. James Kalbach also recently wrote on A-Z indexes, and in particular demonstrated the use of indexes in search auto-completion using Elsevier bibliographic database EMBASE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Shows How to Do Low Fi Concept Demos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</guid>
      <description>The Drawing Board: Commuter Buddy from Cooper Journal on Vimeo. Cooper Interactive&amp;rsquo;s Commuter Buddy concept video is another great find via Dave Malouf&amp;rsquo;s Engage blog. You might have already seen this one, but as Dave points out, it is a great example of using personas, narrative, and really low fidelity sketches to demonstrate a concept.
The video above uses still photography, super-imposed photos of whiteboard drawings, and voice over narrative to describe the idea for a mobile phone application that helps a commuter to get to his ride on time, and even to remember to get off if he becomes engrossed in an article, for instance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Rhode&#39;s Wireframes Sketch Set on Flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mike-rhodes-wireframes-sketch-set-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mike-rhodes-wireframes-sketch-set-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Mike Rhode&amp;rsquo;s set of http://www.flickr.com/photos/rohdesign/sets/72157614397535202/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;wireframe sketches on Flickr is some beautiful stuff. Also check out Mike&amp;rsquo;s sketch notes and other design work on his blog.
Via Nick Finck
http://www.flickr.com/photos/rohdesign/sets/72157614397535202/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untitled Document Syndrome</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/untitled-document-syndrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/untitled-document-syndrome/</guid>
      <description>John Gruber laments the illogical, yet human, tendency to avoid saving new documents, which occasionally leads users to the loss of data when an &#34;Untitled Document&#34; is left in limbo and a crash leaves them scrambling to figure out what happened to it. The point is that users often can&#39;t be bothered with things like figuring out where to put this thing on a file system because we&#39;re too busy with the task at hand, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Steps to Better Wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/20-steps-better-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/20-steps-better-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Think Vitamin&amp;rsquo;s Clive Howard says &amp;ldquo;Wireframing is one of the first steps in your planning process and arguably it’s one of the most important ones.&amp;rdquo; In this article, Howard goes through the wireframing process, discussing who should be involved, which tools to use, and offers sound tips to enable you to make better wireframes. Among my favorite points are those about ownership and involvement. This is to do with ensuring that someone is driving the process and iterations, and making sure that the interaction design process doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen in a vacuum, but is reviewed, validated, and informed by key team members, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Essential Controls for RIA Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/30-essential-controls-ria-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/30-essential-controls-ria-design/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neill, co-author of Designing Web Interfaces lists her 30 essential controls for Rich Interface Application design, and provides a list of frameworks that provide these controls, in the second article in a three part series on patterns and principles for RIA design.
1) Standard Screen Patterns: 12 patterns w/100 examples
2) Essential Controls: 30 controls for RIA design and development
3) Components for Commonly Requested Features: 15 patterns and examples (Forthcoming)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompareNetworks jQuery&#39;d Bread Crumb</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/comparenetworks-jqueryd-bread-crumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/comparenetworks-jqueryd-bread-crumb/</guid>
      <description>The JQuery&amp;rsquo;d Breadcrumb is an odd breadcrumb interface that collapses all nodes in the branch upon page load, and then expands to show each node the user mouses over. Their explanation:
This collapsible breadcrumb was developed to deal with deeply nested, verbosely named pages. Rather than limit the amount of elements shown on the sever side, we decided to go with a client side solution for usability and SEO reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Times Article Skimmer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ny-times-article-skimmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ny-times-article-skimmer/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times&amp;rsquo; Article Skimmer prototype provides a nice gallery view of top articles, and utilizes a categories sidebar to filter articles. Keyboard shortcuts are also provided to navigate prev/next category, or to jump to a specific category. Very nice way to view articles. The dense tabloid style of the regular site can be overwhelming sometimes. Via SwissMiss
http://prototype.nytimes.com/gst/articleSkimmer/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Work on OmniGraffle Sketch Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/starting-work-omnigraffle-sketch-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/starting-work-omnigraffle-sketch-stencils/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following this blog, you may know how I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to do sketch/jitter line styles in OmniGraffle to produce sketchy diagrams and wireframes. After David&amp;rsquo;s demo of his method for doing sketch shapes on the Design Commission blog got me started figuring out how to get the effect natively in OG, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to finally create sketch versions of the Wireframe Stencils. Above is a screenshot of the forms set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Experience on Carousels</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/smart-experience-carousels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/smart-experience-carousels/</guid>
      <description>Smart Experience has posted a 5 minute video showing different kinds of carousels in action and teaches you the three key design criteria you need to know to create your own. Excellent stuff and the best discussion of why carousels are effective, and a thorough review of the different kinds of carousels you might use. Check it for free now. This micro-seminar goes on sale soon.
http://smartexperience.org/sp/ixd-skills-carousels/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons Updated (v. 1.1): PNGs and new icons added</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-11-pngs-and-new-icons-added/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-11-pngs-and-new-icons-added/</guid>
      <description>The Wireframe Icons have been updated. PNG versions and contact sheet has been added for all icons. New icons including User (silhouette from front), Groups, Microphone, Clock, Phone, Printer, Power, TV Widescreen, Remote controls, Volume, alternate versions of Cart and Image, and much more have been added. Additionally, some icons have been modified for stylistic consistency. If you&amp;rsquo;ve previously purchased these icons, you can update your set by logging in and heading to your Account page where you will see a &amp;ldquo;Files&amp;rdquo; link under your user name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 jQuery plugins for Form Usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/top-10-jquery-plugins-form-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/top-10-jquery-plugins-form-usability/</guid>
      <description>For all you front end techs and html prototypers, Steve Reynolds has collected his top 10 list of Jquery plugins for form usability. Includes useful plugins including validation, password strength, and tool tips.
http://www.reynoldsftw.com/2009/01/top-10-jquery-plugins-for-form-usability/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap is the New Click</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/tap-new-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/tap-new-click/</guid>
      <description>NYC IxDA - Tap is the New Click - Dan Saffer from Interaction Design Association on Vimeo. Dan Saffer gave a fantastic NYC IXDA presentation, Tap Is the New Click, discussing the rise of touch interfaces, their place and adoption in society, and the role of the interaction designer in designing these direct manipulation interfaces. Every IA and IXD needs to watch this. A summary of the talk below:
Even though the technology has been around for decades, only now are we starting to see mass production and adoption of touchscreen and gestural devices for the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Sketch Style Screencast</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-sketch-style-screencast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-sketch-style-screencast/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting for the past year or so to do sketch style wireframes in OmniGraffle. My first requests for sketchy line styles were made to OmniGroup in the Spring of 08 along with a few other users, and I posted this comment to the OG List about this feature. I knew how to do this in Visio, and had read that CAD users have something called a &amp;ldquo;Jitter&amp;rdquo; line style, so I quietly campaigned for this feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JazzMutant multi-touch controllers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jazzmutant-multi-touch-controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jazzmutant-multi-touch-controllers/</guid>
      <description>JazzMutant creates the Lemur and Dexter, multi-touch hardware controllers for audio production, live music and media performance. What I like about this is that it shows how much closer multi-touch brings devices to the experience of using analogous hardware controls like knobs, buttons, and sliders without any physical limitations. I once blog bitched about the fact that the Traktor DJ software I played for a few years limited the fun, and the ability to mix with two hands because at the time you could only use one input device, the mouse, to control the mixer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous and Next Actions in Web Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/previous-and-next-actions-web-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/previous-and-next-actions-web-forms/</guid>
      <description>Nice short article in UIE by Luke Wroblewski illustrating the issues to think of when designing previous/next buttons in forms. http://www.uie.com/articles/previous_next_luke</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Gmail Client Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>I posted on Twitter about how frustrating it can be to have to use email. With every day that I use Twitter via Twhirl I become less and less interested in using email. So I moaned to my Twitter peeps about the pain I feel. Some people wanted to know what I wanted, so I responded with the ideal flow, using Mac OS X&amp;rsquo;s Growl alerting app as the starting point:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Website Wireframe in Illustrator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/building-website-wireframe-illustrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/building-website-wireframe-illustrator/</guid>
      <description>Sean Hodge at AiBURN provides some great tips for laying out wireframes in Adobe Illustrator.
http://aiburn.com/article/building_a_website_wireframe_in_illustrator</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Multi Level Navigation Menu Techniques</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-multi-level-navigation-menu-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-multi-level-navigation-menu-techniques/</guid>
      <description>devSnippets collects 10 examples of multi-level navigation menus using Javascript libraries and CSS, and adds a little annotation about the methods and how they effects are accomplished. Via @nourayehia
http://devsnippets.com/reviews/10-brilliant-multi-level-navigation-menu-techniques.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Techniques for an Effective Call to Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-techniques-effective-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-techniques-effective-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Boagworld looks at 10 ways to design an effective call to action.
Having an effective call to action is an essential part of any website. A call to action is not just limited to ecommerce sites. Every website should have an objective it wants users to complete whether it is filling in a contact form, signup for a newsletter or volunteering their time.
A call to action provides&amp;hellip;
Focus to your site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing Web Interfaces: 12 Standard Screen Patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-web-interfaces-12-standard-screen-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-web-interfaces-12-standard-screen-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Bill Scott and Theresa Neil&amp;rsquo;s new O’Reilly book, “Designing Web Interfaces: Principles and Patterns for Rich Interactions,” presents more than 75 design patterns for building web interfaces that provide rich interaction. They&amp;rsquo;ve shared the full set of principles and patterns they use for RIA design in this article.
http://designingwebinterfaces.com/designing-web-interfaces-12-screen-patterns</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-icons/</guid>
      <description>The Konigi OmniGraffle Wireframe Icon Set is a set of grayscale cursors and icons that come in handy when designing wireframes, aka user interface schematics. This product includes a standard set of cursors, and many of the icons you need for the design of web-based user interfaces.
This set of icons is designed to work well with your wireframe stencils. You&amp;rsquo;ll find rich text editor controls, file system actions, social interaction symbols, ratings and voting, and a host of other icons for most of the behaviors you may want to communicate with an icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPlotz Wireframing Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iplotz-wireframing-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iplotz-wireframing-service/</guid>
      <description>iPlotz is another new product offering web-based services for wireframing, mockup, and prototyping of websites and applications. This service allows users to create multiple projects, wireframe them with sketch-style editable components, generate images or PDFs of the wireframes, manage tasks associated with screens, and solicit comments from team members.
http://www.iplotz.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Secrets of the Amazon Shopping Cart</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hidden-secrets-amazon-shopping-cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hidden-secrets-amazon-shopping-cart/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m just seeing for the first time Bryan Eisenberg&amp;rsquo;s GrokDotCom article from Feb 2008 on the evolution of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s shopping cart. It&amp;rsquo;s a great article that makes observations about Amazon&amp;rsquo;s tweaking and testing of their shopping cart buttons over the years. I put all of his screenshots together in the image above.
http://www.grokdotcom.com/2008/02/26/amazon-shopping-cart/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacemaker Mobile MP3 DJ Device Gets a GUI Redesign</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pacemaker-mobile-mp3-dj-device-gets-gui-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pacemaker-mobile-mp3-dj-device-gets-gui-redesign/</guid>
      <description>Pacemaker, the mobile MP3 DJ device that debuted last year with a 120 GB hard drive, is getting a 2.0 release this spring and offering an additional lower capacity 60 GB hard drive option, and a new user interface. I was enamored with this device and the way they could incorporate most of the possible mixer and track selection controls for 2 deck track mixing into a single, albeit large, handheld device with their original product UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing decorative from meaningful elements in UI design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/distinguishing-decorative-meaningful-elements-ui-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/distinguishing-decorative-meaningful-elements-ui-design/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Singer posted a article on 37 Signals, deconstructing the design of the global navigation header on Github. In his example he points out the problem with the &amp;ldquo;Repositories: All | Search&amp;rdquo; links in the account box in the upper right of the screen, which suggests that those links are scoped to the user shown in the box. This a great example of how visual grouping and proximity could be more effectively utilized to help users make sense of the available controls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Quick Search Box</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/google-quick-search-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/google-quick-search-box/</guid>
      <description>Google&amp;rsquo;s Quick Search Box is a QuickSilver-like launcher that lets you search your computer for applications and data, as well as search the web, and your Google Apps accounts. I presume this will also eventually replace the search interface provided by Google Desktop. The project is in beta and is provided via the Labs.
From their blog:
One of our goals at Google is to make your search experience as fluid as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stickyframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/stickyframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/stickyframes/</guid>
      <description>Wireframes Magazine featured an entry on using sticky notes for UI design. I know a lot of us have done something like this before, whether it&amp;rsquo;s using sticky notes or something else. I have occasionally sketched large and used transparent vellum with tape in the past. http://wireframes.linowski.ca/?p=96</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>patternBrowser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/patternbrowser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/patternbrowser/</guid>
      <description>patternBrowser is an amazing design pattern library produced by the Interface Design Team of the University of Applied Sciences Potsdam. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a little time looking through the interaction design category, and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of great examples there, and most importantly they&amp;rsquo;ve done the work of organizing and describing each problem/solution thoroughly. Check it out.
http://www.patternbrowser.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grid Designer: CSS grid generator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/grid-designer-css-grid-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/grid-designer-css-grid-generator/</guid>
      <description>This is a cool browser-based CSS grid generator created by Rasmus Schultz of mindplay.dk. Lets you quickly set some column, gutter, and margin sizes using forms inputs or button controls. Similarly you can set typography with form controls, and the results are shown on screen. When you&amp;rsquo;re happy, you can bookmark your work, and export the CSS. Sweet.
Via @emenel
http://grid.mindplay.dk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking About Sketching About Interacting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/talking-about-sketching-about-interacting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/talking-about-sketching-about-interacting/</guid>
      <description>Talking About Sketching About Interacting
View SlideShare presentation or Upload your own. (tags: dotdotdot mfa)   This the audio and slides from the presentation Chris Fahey gave at SVA&amp;rsquo;s Interaction Design Program series dot dot dot. In this excellent short short talks (16 minutes), Chris talks about sketching and shows plenty of examples from his notebooks. Great series of events that Liz Danzico and company are putting on. Chris will be on the faculty of the MFA program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle vs. iPhone/iPod Touch: Human/Machine Interaction &amp; User Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kindle-vs-iphoneipod-touch-humanmachine-interaction-user-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kindle-vs-iphoneipod-touch-humanmachine-interaction-user-experience/</guid>
      <description>Tog&#39;s comparison and analysis of the human computer interaction versus the user experience with both the Amazon Kindle and the iPhone/iPod Touch is excellent. The separation of HCI/UX in his analysis really drives the point home that good interaction and industrial design can make the experience, and a good experience isn&#39;t only about the design.
I don&#39;t use a Kindle daily, so I can&#39;t comment personally on it, but the industrial design was a showstopper for me and kept me from wanting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils Update</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</guid>
      <description>This is a major revision to the OmniGraffle Wireframe Shapes that I&amp;rsquo;ve been providing at urlgreyhot since OG version 1.x. It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year since the last update to that version. This version adds new elements and is formatted for OG 5.x. You can get it here in the Tools section.
http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 100% Easy-2-Read Standard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/100-easy-2-read-standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/100-easy-2-read-standard/</guid>
      <description>I just stumbled onto ia.jp&amp;rsquo;s web type manifesto for the first time and whole heartedly agree. http://informationarchitects.jp/100e2r/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kurafire and Smashing Mag on Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kurafire-and-smashing-mag-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kurafire-and-smashing-mag-pagination/</guid>
      <description>Faruk Ateş provides some suggestions for implementing pagination, all of which I would agree with. After the suggestion list, Ateş shows quite a few examples and discusses what&#39;s good and bad about them. There&#39;s a huge list of examples on Smashing Magazine as well, although some of them are a little fussy.
Oddly enough, while a few of the examples show the method of using an ellipsis plus the last few page numbers as a way to show number of pages, Ateş doesn&#39;t count that as a recommended practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shades of Gray: Wireframes as Thinking Device</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/shades-gray-wireframes-thinking-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/shades-gray-wireframes-thinking-device/</guid>
      <description>Will Evans discusses how he uses wireframes in his design process. The story is one you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard before. It&amp;rsquo;s a description of concept design, using wireframes as the tool for finding the right design. One could use sketching just as well. He&amp;rsquo;s talking about that path we take as designers to frame the problem for discussion, extrapolate solutions from that discussion, and generate possible solution concepts. He calls his process one of divergence, transformation, and covergence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframes Magazine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframes-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframes-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Jakub Linowski has started publishing Wireframes Magazine, a blog to showcase people&amp;rsquo;s user interface wireframes.
http://wireframes.linowski.ca/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>typeface.js: Rendering text with Javascript, canvas, and VML</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/typefacejs-rendering-text-javascript-canvas-and-vml/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typefacejs-rendering-text-javascript-canvas-and-vml/</guid>
      <description>I just came across typeface.js, a type face replacement method like SIFR and FLIR, that lets you embed custom fonts in your pages using CSS. On the backend, javscript is used with  or VML to draw the glyphs for your fonts. Compared with SIFR, this suffers from some issues. Biggest one perhaps is that you can&amp;rsquo;t select text since it&amp;rsquo;s rendered as an image. Not so with SIFR. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t go using this method for body text, but if you&amp;rsquo;re already considering doing image replacement for elements like headings, this would be a library to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing Sketch Iterations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/doing-sketch-iterations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/doing-sketch-iterations/</guid>
      <description>These are just more illustrations of the process I&amp;rsquo;ve been using for design iterations. When I have the Konigi notebook available, I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing some screencasts to describe this process in detail, and why I felt the need to make these graph paper notebooks and pads.
What you see above:
1) Annotated UI Spec (Wireframes) after design review.
2) Sketches for design and new ideas, on the Konigi Design Notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Input Masks in Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/input-masks-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/input-masks-forms/</guid>
      <description>Luke Wroblewski pointed to Josh Bush&amp;rsquo;s Masked Input Plugin for JQuery. Luke writes that the plugin &amp;ldquo;integrate(s) formatting cues directly into an input field to help signal how to correctly answer a question. These formatting instructions are automatically included in an input and cannot be removed by a user. More importantly, a user cannot enter other non-valid characters into the input field. Check out the demo at Masked Input Plugin.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Fail Safe When You Can Poka-yoke?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/why-fail-safe-when-you-can-poka-yoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/why-fail-safe-when-you-can-poka-yoke/</guid>
      <description>Poka-Yoke is a Japanese word for &amp;ldquo;fail-safing&amp;rdquo; that I just came across and suspect might be entering my UI vocabulary soon. The entry from Wikipedia:
Poka-yoke (IPA: [poka joke]) is a Japanese term that means &amp;ldquo;fail-safing&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Foolproof&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;mistake-proofing&amp;rdquo; — avoiding (yokeru) inadvertent errors (poka)) is a behavior-shaping constraint, or a method of preventing errors by putting limits on how an operation can be performed in order to force the correct completion of the operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Tool Design: Design by Sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/software-tool-design-design-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/software-tool-design-design-sketching/</guid>
      <description>The second part of Stephen Chambers&amp;rsquo; series on designing the ANTS Profiler tool, a .NET code profiler, discusses how a team leader challenged a group to really work collaboratively on developing the concept for the tool&amp;rsquo;s interface by taking away computers and requiring that the team work with only paper, whiteboards, pencils, and markers.
James, the team leader had just read Bill Buxton&amp;rsquo;s Sketching the User Experience and wanted to try to get his engineers to rally around the idea that everyone can participate in this ideation phase, and no one needed any specific skill to propose and sketch ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growl-Like Alerts in Web Pages</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/growl-alerts-web-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/growl-alerts-web-pages/</guid>
      <description>I just came across two Growl-like alert plugins that should be of interest to HTML prototypers. Growl is a Mac OS X application that functions like a service that other applications can use to show unobtrusive messages in the monitor when things happen on the system.
These javascript plugins work for the Moo Tools or JQuery libraries to provide small in-page layers in a corner or center of the page to do such things as show AJAX alerts for new content updates, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframing Experiences and Applications with Flash Catalyst</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-experiences-and-applications-flash-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-experiences-and-applications-flash-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>Peter Flynn gives a demo of wireframing in Adobe Flash Catalyst, aka Thermo. Every online demo I&amp;rsquo;ve seen of this product looks more and more exciting, and this is truly going to give Mac users a way to do easy interactive prototypes as our PC brothers and sisters can do with tools like Axure. I fully expect to be using this thing when it gets out of Preview release. It&amp;rsquo;s only slightly ironic that his first 5 minutes are talk about how wireframes are by definition, low fidelity, given my last post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scribbles, incredibly simple drawing app for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/scribbles-incredibly-simple-drawing-app-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/scribbles-incredibly-simple-drawing-app-mac/</guid>
      <description>Scribbles is perhaps the simplest drawing program I&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried. The app, created by atebits, gives you 4 tools: brush, move, pan, and zoom. There are 12 brush styles, a color picker, a big slider for brush size, and a layer manager. It looks deceptively simple on the surface, but when you explore a bit, you&amp;rsquo;ll find some really interesting functionalities that even the advanced Mac freehand drawing tools like Sketchbook and ArtRage don&amp;rsquo;t do well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of the High Fidelity Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fear-high-fidelity-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fear-high-fidelity-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>In Twitter today, I posted a message that I need to resist putting rounded corners on boxes in wireframes. Then I got a few replies essentially saying that stylized elements shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be in wireframes. Context is everything. Taken out of context, it is very difficult to possibly critique a specific design technique without knowing the how and why you&amp;rsquo;re using it. Because of that 140 character constraint in Twitter, I didn&amp;rsquo;t really explain that this rounded corner example came from my hybrid high-fidelity wireframing and visual design document I was working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Sign-in: 8 Design Mistakes to Avoid</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/account-sign-8-design-mistakes-avoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/account-sign-8-design-mistakes-avoid/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;I don&#39;t want to develop a relationship with these guys. I just want to buy something.&amp;quot; That&#39;s what some of your customers are saying when you ask them to register or sign in, and some of them will walk away with their dollars if you frustrate them enough. UIE rounds up the most common mistakes they observe from watching users in testing sessions try to sign in to user accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Booth: Free Website Usability Testing Reviews &amp; UX Blog</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-booth-free-website-usability-testing-reviews-ux-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-booth-free-website-usability-testing-reviews-ux-blog/</guid>
      <description>The UX Booth is a group that writes about User Experience, and offers free Website Usability Reviews that all designers and developers can benefit from.
Via Digital Web
http://www.uxbooth.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appopedia, Business App Reviews</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/appopedia-business-app-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/appopedia-business-app-reviews/</guid>
      <description>The AppGap releases the Appopedia, a directory and review site for &amp;ldquo;2.0 apps&amp;rdquo; for work.
http://www.theappgap.com/reviews</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colors and the UI</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/colors-and-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/colors-and-ui/</guid>
      <description>On InfoQ Tobias Komischke highlights some aspects of colors and color perception together with recommendations for UI design.
http://www.infoq.com/articles/Colors-UI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Konigi OG Toolset is Coming</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-og-toolset-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-og-toolset-coming/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s OmniGraffle, not Original Gangster. It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year since the last update to my OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils. I&amp;rsquo;m due for a new version after some cleanup and organization into separate stencils to make use of OG5&amp;rsquo;s nice new stencil panel. The above is the current state of my working stencil in all its ugly glory. Also in my stencil directory are a bunch of pre-fabricated stencils for the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on in the past 2 years at Sling and at Traction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working through Screens Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/working-through-screens-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/working-through-screens-book/</guid>
      <description>Flashbulb Interactions&amp;rsquo;s Working through Screens is an excellent, well-illustrated ebook on concept design for designers and product developers. The key point here is how to use design tools and methodologies to get the right design for the problem. Working through Screens is an online book for product teams creating new or iteratively improved applications for thinking work. Written for use during early, formative conversations, it provides teams with a broad range of considerations for setting the overall direction and priorities for their onscreen tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Designer&#39;s Review of Books</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designers-review-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designers-review-books/</guid>
      <description>Andy Polaine&amp;rsquo;s review of books for designers.
Although there are several good design websites that occasionally have book reviews, there didn’t seem to be a single place online where you could get constant updates and reviews of new (and sometimes old) design books.
Design books are often expensive and contrary – sometimes the book is worth having for the physical production values alone, sometimes for the images, sometimes for the words and, occasionally, for all three.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Your Own Magnetic Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/create-your-own-magnetic-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/create-your-own-magnetic-prototype/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Path&amp;rsquo;s Alexa Andrzejewski suggests how to create your own magnetic prototypes using printable magnets for user interface elements. Good stuff. Customizable and inexpensive.
http://www.adaptivepath.com/blog/2008/11/17/magneticprototyping/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sling.com Launches</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/slingcom-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/slingcom-launches/</guid>
      <description>The video portal I worked on last year went Public Beta today. Check it out at Sling.com. If you have a Sling Box, you can also now view your sling player in a web browser as well (IE/Windows only for now). I guess the rollout of features will be gradual. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait until Clip N Sling is available for Sling Box owners and more social features are released. We designed a number of very interesting interfaces which don&amp;rsquo;t appear to be available yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Gorgeous Navigation Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/50-gorgeous-navigation-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/50-gorgeous-navigation-menus/</guid>
      <description>Vandelay Website Design posts a 2 part series of screenshots of navigation menus. Part 2 is here.
http://vandelaydesign.com/blog/galleries/inspirationalnavigation-menus/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Methodologie Browser Size Test</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/methodologie-browser-size-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/methodologie-browser-size-test/</guid>
      <description>Mmmmm, grids. Methodologie uses stats from The Counter to display the screen resolutions supported by users&amp;rsquo; computers in their 10&amp;frasl;2008 numbers.
http://www.methodologie.com/sizer/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napkin Look &amp; Feel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/napkin-look-feel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/napkin-look-feel/</guid>
      <description>Napkin Look and Feel is a cool looking open source tool for Java developers to produce application prototypes with a low-fidelity sketchy interface.
The idea is to try to develop a look and feel that can be used in Java applications that looks informal and provisional, yet be fully functional for development. Often when people see a GUI mock-up, or a complete GUI without full functionality, they assume that the code behind it is working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Patterns Wiki</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/social-patterns-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/social-patterns-wiki/</guid>
      <description>Christian Crumlish and Erin Malone are writing a book on designing social interfaces and are starting to post the design patterns they are writing as they work through the chapters. Each pattern is open for folks to modify / give feedback.
From the looks of that list of forward links to be added, they have a very ambitious list of design problems they&amp;rsquo;re going to be researching and providing design patterns for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebIconSets.com: The Best Free Web Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/webiconsetscom-best-free-web-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/webiconsetscom-best-free-web-icons/</guid>
      <description>WebIconSets.com lists the best icon sets suitable for web use. All the icon sets are of professional quality and free to use in your own projects.
http://www.webiconsets.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twingr Registration: My mind was made up before I even tried the product</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twingr-registration-my-mind-was-made-i-even-tried-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twingr-registration-my-mind-was-made-i-even-tried-product/</guid>
      <description>I very rarely will say anything about a site if the only opinion I have is negative. Twingr looked like an interesting idea. The service let&amp;rsquo;s you create your own Twitter-clone microblogging site, as does Yammer, but without any constraints regarding who you may invite. Alas, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I know what the experience is like because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get past the front door, so I walked away possibly never to return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper Website Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/newspaper-website-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/newspaper-website-design/</guid>
      <description>Smashing Magazine does a newspaper roundup in a week that saw the FT.com make news for its redesign. These days, the design lines between blogs and newspapers are starting to converge a bit with those newspapers that take the threat of the blog format seriously. Smashing Mag does a good design of screenshooting and comparing what news sites are doing. http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2008/11/11/newspaper-website-design-trends-and-examples/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>16 User Interface Prototyping Tools</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/16-user-interface-prototyping-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/16-user-interface-prototyping-tools/</guid>
      <description>Russel Wilson of Dexo Design has done an excellent review of available UI Prototyping tools and provided tables comparing attributes including how fun they are to use, time to ramp up, and support for interactivity. His final assessment is below:
1) Low fidelity mockups for idea exploration and communication: Balsamiq
2) Interactive prototypes to test and communicate interactions: Adobe Flex (Thermo may change my mind)
3) High fidelity drawing tool: Adobe Illustrator or OmniGraffle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Kind to the Color Blind</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/be-kind-color-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/be-kind-color-blind/</guid>
      <description>Chris Campbell or Particle Tree provides an excellent set of guidelines and examples for designing with users with color deficiencies in mind.
http://particletree.com/features/interfaces-and-color-blindness/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Standards Project</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/email-standards-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/email-standards-project/</guid>
      <description>The Email Standards Project is a community effort to ensure that emails render consistently. Similar to the Web Standards Project, the Email Standards Project community works with email client developers and the design community to improve web standards support and accessibility in email.
http://www.email-standards.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MIT UID Teatime Blog</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mit-uid-teatime-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mit-uid-teatime-blog/</guid>
      <description>The User Interface Design Group at MIT has started their Teatime Blog. Info about the blog from entry #1:
The sharing of knowledge and ideas is of fundamental importance to the advancement of technology. With this goal in mind, MIT’s User Interface Design group meets once a day at Tea Time to brainstorm new ideas, review new technologies and ideas, and share their experiences working in the field.
If we hope to herald innovation by sharing ideas with a research group , then there’s a boundless value to sharing ideas and thoughts with the world at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch Usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/touch-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/touch-usability/</guid>
      <description>Kevin Arthur&amp;rsquo;s Touch Usability is a blog devoted to usability news and research on touch screen interfaces.
http://www.touchusability.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GazoPa Image Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/gazopa-image-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/gazopa-image-search/</guid>
      <description>Gazopa provides image upload and drawing interfaces for image search. The idea of finding similar images by comparing against a submitted image or drawing is not new, but search tools that use this tech have failed to catch on in consumer sites. People with information retrieval background might be familiar with IBM&amp;rsquo;s QBIC, query by image content, technology for instance. Gazopa looks very interesting, and the results are not bad at all, even with my crude bicycle drawing above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Planner - View and Create User Flows, Viral Loops, and More.</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/product-planner-view-and-create-user-flows-viral-loops-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/product-planner-view-and-create-user-flows-viral-loops-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Product Planner is one an brilliant idea. Deconstruct the user flow of web sites, illustrate the flow with annotated screenshot flowcharts, allow users to copy the flow and reuse on the site. Like Konigi, this does a great job of capturing examples of alternative approaches to interaction, showcases them for you to compare, and allows you to select the best examples to learn from and inform you of approaches you may not have thought of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radial Menu Tests in Firefox</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/radial-menu-tests-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/radial-menu-tests-firefox/</guid>
      <description>Testing of proof of concept prototypes of radial menus. The idea is to get users to try to select the same menu item repeatedly as the radial menu changes from state to state and capture participants feedback on usability of the interface.
http://jonoscript.wordpress.com/2008/10/28/pie-in-the-sky/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 7 Revealed</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/windows-7-revealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/windows-7-revealed/</guid>
      <description>InformationWeek previews Windows 7, the successor to Vista, with 24 screenshots from a demo given by Julie Larson Green, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s vice president for Windows experience. Read more about Windows 7 in the InformationWeek article.
http://www.informationweek.com/galleries/showImage.jhtml?galleryID=268&amp;imageID=1&amp;articleID=211601289</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTunes Nomenclature needs a refresh</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/itunes-nomenclature-needs-refresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/itunes-nomenclature-needs-refresh/</guid>
      <description>Or maybe we&amp;rsquo;re just comfortable with the mix in of apps and music? No, not me. Artist and Album are certainly just wrong. Don&amp;rsquo;t know how they can make that legacy labeling generic across music/movie/application. Creator instead of artist, perhaps. And just leave album blank for apps and movies. Album doesn&amp;rsquo;t serve a purpose for apps does it? The link doesn&amp;rsquo;t appear to work.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/jibbajabba/2980855655/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design patterns (User experience design resources)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-patterns-user-experience-design-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-patterns-user-experience-design-resources/</guid>
      <description>Dey Alexander Consulting&#39;s site includes a lengthy bibiliography of articles, discussions, and links to resources on user interface design patterns.
http://deyalexander.com/resources/uxd/design-patterns.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for One User (Bespoke User Interfaces)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-one-user-bespoke-user-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-one-user-bespoke-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>Chris Fahey discusses the merits of bespoke UI design, referencing the successful design of John King&#39;s touch wall which was created for King by Perceptive Pixel. Bespoke design--the practice of designing something specifically for and individual--might be more prevalent in the digital world than most people realize. The examples provided out in the quotes of software designers and developers point out the most common case where this is happening. Designers who design products by focusing on what they want/need for themselves is common enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UXrepublic</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/uxrepublic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/uxrepublic/</guid>
      <description>UXrepublic launches to provide another user-generated showcase for user interface examples.
http://uxrepublic.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC.com Microsoft Surface Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/msnbccom-microsoft-surface-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/msnbccom-microsoft-surface-videos/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve caught Chuck Todd using a desktop touch interface a few times on MSNBC to click through poll charts. While John King has been using a Perceptive Pixel-designed touch wall, Todd has been using a Microsoft Surface interface on a desktop. The device and manipulation of data on the screen looks very natural on this show, especially for the kind of information he&amp;rsquo;s speaking to. I think whenever there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of visual information to add to a story, this kind of an interface has potential to be very helpful and I look forward to seeing what they do at MSNBC and on other shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Magazine Pricing Tables Showcase</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/smashing-magazine-pricing-tables-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/smashing-magazine-pricing-tables-showcase/</guid>
      <description>Smashing Magazine does a roundup of pricing comparison table examples.
http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2008/10/13/pricing-tables-showcase-examples-and-best-practices/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Design Tools</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/concept-design-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/concept-design-tools/</guid>
      <description>Victor Lombardi discusses concept design in Digital Web Magazine, pointing out that digital designers should take some inspiration from design processes for ideation and concept generation from the fields of architecture and industrial design. I think the main idea is to learn from the practices and methods from these fields, and use that as inspiration for what might be useful in your concept design practice. That is not to say that every project needs to result in a dozen concepts that need to be prototyped at high fidelity and therefore at significant cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ease of Use Makes Money and Saves Money</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ease-use-makes-money-and-saves-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ease-use-makes-money-and-saves-money/</guid>
      <description>Lawrence Najjar provides a bibliography of literature to help you make the ROI argument for investing in ease of use.
http://www.tandemseven.com/insights/blog/details/41/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GUI Prototyping Tools</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/gui-prototyping-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/gui-prototyping-tools/</guid>
      <description>Cunningham &amp;amp; Cunningham have a wiki page listing a great collection of prototyping tools.
http://c2.com/cgi/wiki?GuiPrototypingTools</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using the Microsoft Ribbon without anyone getting hurt</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/using-microsoft-ribbon-without-anyone-getting-hurt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/using-microsoft-ribbon-without-anyone-getting-hurt/</guid>
      <description>In Flow Interactive&amp;rsquo;s blog, Phil Barrett offers advice for those who are considering implementing Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Ribbon in their applications. The Ribbon has received praise from usability folks who see the benefit this offers in terms of ease of use and better, more visible contextual controls. But it has also met with resistance from individuals who find the large menu-heavy approach disruptive.
The ribbon is a decent piece of interface, but like most things in UX, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to design it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Periodic Table of Visualization Methods</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/periodic-table-visualization-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/periodic-table-visualization-methods/</guid>
      <description>This is a neat table listing and categorizing visualization methods from the folks at Visual Literacy
http://www.visual-literacy.org/periodic_table/periodic_table.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRID In-Game Motion Graphics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/grid-game-motion-graphics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/grid-game-motion-graphics/</guid>
      <description>Motionographer has some cool video of the in-game menus and motion graphics in RACE DRIVER GRID video game from Codemasters.
http://motionographer.com/2008/06/30/real-time-motion-graphics-grid/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lighthouse International - Making Text Legible</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/lighthouse-international-making-text-legible/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/lighthouse-international-making-text-legible/</guid>
      <description>Lighthouse provides 10 basic guidelines for designing for people with partial sight. &#34;Impaired vision often makes reading difficult by: Reducing the amount of light that enters the eye, Blurring the retinal image, Damaging the central portion of the retina best suited to reading.&#34;
http://www.lighthouse.org/accessibility/legible/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Interaction Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/thoughts-interaction-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/thoughts-interaction-design/</guid>
      <description>Just getting around to reading Jon Kolko&amp;rsquo;s Thoughts on Interaction Design, which is available online now that the printed book is no longer available.
http://thoughtsoninteraction.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Launches CS4 Suite of Applications</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/adobe-launches-cs4-suite-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adobe-launches-cs4-suite-applications/</guid>
      <description>Ars rounds up the new features in the forthcoming release of the Adobe CS4 suite to be released sometime next month. I think I&#39;ll have to upgrade for the multipage docs in Illustrator alone.
Photoshop CS4
 * GPU-based drawing of documents onscreen
* 64-bit for Windows
* Expanded 3-D paint, lighting and rendering tools
Illustrator CS4
 * Multipage documents with different sizes
* Indesign-style separations preview
* Many updated tools like gradient and blob brush</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study of User Response to Fake Dialogs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/study-user-response-fake-dialogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/study-user-response-fake-dialogs/</guid>
      <description>Ars reports on a study by the psychology department at NC State that will appear in the Proceedings of the Human Factors and Ergonomics Society. The study tested how college students respond to fake dialog boxes in browser popup windows and found that the students are so anxious to get the dialog out of the way, they click right through obvious warning signs. Follow-up questions revealed that the students seemed to find any dialog box a distraction from their assigned task; nearly half said that all they cared about was getting rid of these dialogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Konigi Store</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-konigi-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-konigi-store/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to announce the first of a series of products that I&amp;rsquo;m producing for creatives involved in design for the screen. The first 2 products are graph paper notepads formatted for user interface design and design of time-related sequences.
The Wireframe Graph Paper Notepad is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects designing for the screen. The notepad has 50 sheets at 8 1&amp;frasl;2 x 11 inches on white 70# paper, glued on the left side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal.org crowd wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/drupal-org-crowd-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/drupal-org-crowd-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Leisa Reichelt starts up some participatory design by getting Drupal contributors to sketch suggestions for things they&amp;rsquo;d like to see change on Drupal.org.
http://www.disambiguity.com/drupalorg-come-wireframe-with-me/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swype Text Input for Screens</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/swype-text-input-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/swype-text-input-screens/</guid>
      <description>CNet reports on Swype, a new keyboard technology for touch screens created by the inventory of the T9 keyboard technology for numeric keypads. Swype lets the user drag their finger across the screen, touching each of the letters in the words they want to enter, and predictive software selects the word they wanted. This could be a great tool to the improve the typing experience on the iPhone, which I find pretty awful compared to a hardware keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquity</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ubiquity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ubiquity/</guid>
      <description>Ubiquity for Firefox from Aza Raskin on Vimeo. I&amp;rsquo;ve been really impressed by Aza Raskin&amp;rsquo;s Ubiquity add on for Firefox, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with a lot lately. It completely makes up for the less than exciting experience I had with Enso, which never came close to a Quicksilver experience on Windows. Ubiquity is pretty much the Quicksilver experience brought to your web browser. A smart tool that is summoned by a keyboard shortcut, and provides shortcuts to frequently used tools, and contextually relevant paths to using selected content in the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox 3.1 Alpha Video Demo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-3-1-alpha-video-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-3-1-alpha-video-demo/</guid>
      <description>Ars Technica reports on the 3.1 Alpha of Firefox, which includes support for the HTML 5 Video element which provides some functionality to developers that is not possible with Flash. Video can be interspersed with other web content, playback can be manipulated with JavaScript, and video elements can be directly accessed through the document object model.
Bluish Coder demonstrates the Video tag in SVG to implement a Silverlight style demo in Firefox 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 JQuery Methods for Interactive Menu Effects</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/3-jquery-methods-interactive-menu-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/3-jquery-methods-interactive-menu-effects/</guid>
      <description>3 recent articles show how to get interactive effects on menus, proving that you don&amp;rsquo;t need Flash for this kind of simple interactivity.  Dave Shea&amp;rsquo;s tutorial in ALA shows how to create interactive menu hover effects using CSS sprites and the JQuery Javascript library. A sprite image is a single graphic with multiple states mapped on the graphic, a technique borrowed from game design, where game characters are shown in different states of action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Comic Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/google-chrome-comic-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/google-chrome-comic-book/</guid>
      <description>Google explains it&amp;rsquo;s new open source, Webkit-based Chrome Web Browser with a 28 page comic book inked by Scott McCloud. The Chrome browser beta becomes available to Windows users on September 2, 2008. Mac and Linux versions are also planned.
http://www.google.com/googlebooks/chrome/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Map Usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/site-map-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/site-map-usability/</guid>
      <description>Jakob Nielsen&#39;s Alertbox reports on their study of sitemaps, observing that among the sites they tested, sitemaps continue to be a useful tool to some people. While their study shows that they are rarely used, they can be simple, inexpensive tools to generate for the users who find value in the sense-making cues that a visual overview provides. Their recommendation is to continue to use them if you already produce them, but keep them static and don&#39;t add interactive effects to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The what, when and why of wireframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-when-and-why-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-when-and-why-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>James Kelway&amp;rsquo;s article on wireframes in the User Pathways blog summarizes what the different types are, what their purpose is, who the audience for their use are, and how they are typically implemented. There are several nice illustrations in this article for those that need to explain what they are.
http://userpathways.com/2008/06/26/the-what-when-and-why-of-wireframes/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Leaves Concept UI for iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/falling-leaves-concept-ui-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/falling-leaves-concept-ui-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Not sure if the user on Vimeo who posted this is THE Woz, but he or she posted this concept user interface for an iPhone menu application that looks very interesting. The video opens with a UI that displays falling media that appear like little square stamps dropping like leaves to a desktop with contacts, photos, videos, etc. on the face of the leaves. The user can apparently pick up one of the pieces, and if it&amp;rsquo;s a video for example, start playing that video in the UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanmail Paper Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hanmail-paper-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hanmail-paper-prototype/</guid>
      <description>Video of a paper prototype created for Daum&amp;rsquo;s AJAX-based hanmail.net webmail service. It&amp;rsquo;s a little hard to know what&amp;rsquo;s going on without hearing the test participant think out loud, but it&amp;rsquo;s a nice demo of the prototype.
Via IATV.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GrV2SZuRPv0</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Update</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the OmniGraffle web design template formerly hosted on my blog at urlgreyhot. The new UX template is now formatted for OmniGraffle Pro version 5. In this template you&amp;rsquo;ll find shared layers (masters) for a title page, wireframe, wireframe/storyboard hybrid, simple storyboard, and storyboard with notes. Guides and adherence to a regular grid make it easy to use. The doc is sized so you can work at 100%, and print at 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fi on Wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fi-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fi-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Fi do a little show and tell of their Visio wireframes and discuss their use on Think Swedish.
http://www.thinkswedish.com/blog/fi/973/Wireframing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Usability Post, A design and usability blog</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/usability-post-design-and-usability-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/usability-post-design-and-usability-blog/</guid>
      <description>Dmitry Fadeyev&amp;rsquo;s new blog, The Usability Post is posting some thoughtful entries on design usability.
http://www.usabilitypost.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillcrest Labs Remote Control</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hillcrest-labs-remote-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hillcrest-labs-remote-control/</guid>
      <description>Hillcrest Labs provides a vision of the pointing and navigating future with their demonstration of Freespace motion-controlled TV remote.
 I came across the video demos of Hillcrest Labs&#39; remote control via NewTeevee. The video above shows a demo at the Consumer Electronics Show last winter, but check the NewTeevee link for the more complete demo of their Freespace motion control technology (sadly they won&#39;t let me embed it here). The demo shows a proof of concept software interface for the TV that allows the user to navigate and access media on their TV/Computer using the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone GUI PSD</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-gui-psd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-gui-psd/</guid>
      <description>The iPhone GUI PSD by teehan+lax is an editable layered Photoshop file with graphic elements including the iPhone, buttons and controls, form inputs, and application chrome. Thanks to Designnotes for the tip.
http://www.teehanlax.com/blog/?p=447</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low-Cost Multi-point Interactive Whiteboards Using the Wiimote</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</guid>
      <description>Researcher provides another Wii Remote hack, this time to help business users create interactive whiteboards on the cheap.
 You might remember the incredible Wiimote hacks by by Johnny Chung Lee, who gave us head tracking demo for desktop VR displays. Lee, a PhD student in the Human-Computer Interaction Institute at Carnegie Mellon University is back with some more useful Wiimote hacks, this time to turn any surface into an interactive whiteboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year&#39;s 10 Best Application UIs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/years-10-best-application-uis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/years-10-best-application-uis/</guid>
      <description>Jakob Nielsen reveals the winners of a competition to identify the 10 best-designed application user interfaces for 2008.
The winners:
 Campaign Monitor by Eyeblaster (Israel): Integrated management of multiple advertising campaigns for media buyers. CMSBox by CMSBox (Switzerland): Content management system FotoFlexer by Arbor Labs (USA): Photo editor PRISMAprepare by Océ (The Netherlands): Print shop software. Seating Management by Magellan Network and DesignBox (USA): Hostess-stand reservation book for restaurants. SQL diagnostic manager by Idera (USA): Database performance monitoring and diagnostics SugarSync by Sharpcast (USA): Synchronizing files across multiple computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton Lecture on Sketching and Experience Design at Stanford</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton gives a lecture at the Stanford University Human-Computer Interaction Seminar (CS 547, June 1, 2007) giving an excellent deep dive into some of the topics in his book, Sketching User Experiences.
 Designing for experience comes with a whole new level of complexity. This is especially true in this emerging world of information appliances, reactive environments, and ubiquitous computing, where, along with those of their users, we have to factor in the convoluted behaviors of the products themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Ipsum Widget</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/corporate-ipsum-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/corporate-ipsum-widget/</guid>
      <description>If you ever get tired of writing sample copy in your design documents, at least be semi-lazy rather than completely lazy. Use Corporate Ipsum.
http://www.doubleforte.net/widgets/corporate/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction-Patterns.org</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-patterns-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-patterns-org/</guid>
      <description>Interaction-Patterns.org is the Stimmt AG - Uni Basel Pattern Catalogue. The Patterns page lists each design pattern name, a very brief description of the interaction, and a link to the page that describes the design pattern, e.g. YUI or Welie pages.
http://www.interaction-patterns.org/wiki/index.php?title=Patterns</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interface and Interaction Design Video Bloggers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interface-and-interaction-design-video-bloggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interface-and-interaction-design-video-bloggers/</guid>
      <description>I recently noticed that I&#39;m not the only one posting interface design and interaction videos on Vimeo. Here are 4 Vimeo users who are doing this now:
 Alex G Christian Schlatter Ivan Bachev Michael Angeles (Me)  Know of any other UI and Interaction Design video bloggers? Let me know about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Path Aurora Concept Video, Part 1</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Path, as part of Mozilla Lab&#39;s concept video series, provides some suggestions for the possible future of the web experience with Aurora. This forward looking concept focuses on 4 high priority elements: context awareness, natural interaction, continuity, and multi-user applications.
Aurora (Part 1) from Adaptive Path on Vimeo. The scenario laid out is one in which one user starts an audio chat and screen sharing sesion with another user and we begin to see how users can find information from their history and share it and remix it with others in the session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pattern Tap Launches</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pattern-tap-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pattern-tap-launches/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m psyched to see that Squared Eye has launched a veritable smorgasbord of interface and visual design inspiration with the user-generated screenshot gallery on Pattern Tap. Get your Tap on! http://patterntap.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Search Sketch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twitter-search-sketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twitter-search-sketch/</guid>
      <description>In Twitter&amp;rsquo;s blog entry describing how Summize will be rolled into Twitter, they included a neat little sketch to illustrate.
http://blog.twitter.com/2008/07/finding-perfect-match.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Xbox Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-xbox-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-xbox-experience/</guid>
      <description>Kotaku reports on the New Xbox Experience, which does away with the Blade interface, and replaces with a remote-control type UI with cover-flow-like browsability. We&amp;rsquo;ll have to see what the reception will be for this. Xbox are integrating Netflix soon, and may be hoping to simplify the experience for a wider audience. I found the Blade UI to be pretty interesting the few times I got to use it.
http://kotaku.com/5025143/the-new-xbox-experience-just-the-facts-and-maybe-some-conjecture</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>I spend a lot of time sketching interface ideas on paper. Typically I sketch wireframes and storyboards on graph paper, then redo the final documents in OmniGraffle. But lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using paper for more than just sketching. Now, after spending time sketching ideas and working out design issues, I start to do higher fidelity drawings on paper, scan them, post them to our system. We discuss and iterate, and the process repeats until we&amp;rsquo;re happy, and I spend less time pushing pixels around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paper Version of the Web</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-version-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-version-web/</guid>
      <description>After posting the Konigi Graph Paper, someone pointed me to Deeplinking&amp;rsquo;s collection of photos of paper prototypes and user interface sketches.
http://deeplinking.net/paper-web/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick and Easy Flash Prototypes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/quick-and-easy-flash-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/quick-and-easy-flash-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>Boxes and Arrows has a very detailed tutorial by Alexa Andrzejewski, interaction designer at Adaptive Path, on creating prototypes in Flash. To tackle the classic “how to prototype rich interactions” problem, I developed a process for translating static screen designs (from wireframes to visual comps) into interactive experiences using Flash. Requiring some fairly basic ActionScript knowledge, these prototypes proved to be a quick yet powerful way to bring interaction designs to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wordle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wordle/</guid>
      <description>Wordle is a toy for generating “word clouds” from text that you provide. The clouds give greater prominence to words that appear more frequently in the source text. You can tweak your clouds with different fonts, layouts, and color schemes.
http://wordle.net/create</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAKISSA - Podcasting Interface Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dakissa-podcasting-interface-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dakissa-podcasting-interface-design/</guid>
      <description>Victor Lombardi of Smart Experience and I begin DAKISSA, a podcast that looks at innovations in interface design. You can view the podcast on Konigi or at dakissa.blip.tv where you can subscribe via your RSS reader or iTunes.
http://dakissa.blip.tv/#986656</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CamSpace Webcam Game Controller</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/camspace-webcam-game-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/camspace-webcam-game-controller/</guid>
      <description>Camspace is pretty slick. The people at CamTrax are demoing the PC camera-based interface. At first blush, I thought it similar to the gimicky Eye Toy games, but this is much better. CamTrax is a software-based technology that enables the tracking of hand-held objects in real time, with high reliability. What you see in the demo is that the software recognizes the hand-held objects and effectively turns them into pointers and other controls that can be used to act on the simple end as a cursor, and on the more sophisticated end as a game controller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Mobile Concept Video</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</guid>
      <description>Firefox Mobile Concept Video from Aza Raskin on Vimeo. Aza Raskin demonstrates a touch interface concept for a Firefox Mobile browser. The mocked up prototype includes features including spatial browsing of browser tabs, and touch gestures for summoning application menus.
http://azarask.in/blog/post/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DestroyFlickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/destroyflickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/destroyflickr/</guid>
      <description>Tina pointed to DestroyFlickr, an excellent AIR application for viewing Flickr photos.
DestroyFlickr explores alternative methods for viewing and sharing Flickr content. Its user interface provides an environment that benefits photos rather than hindering them. With the ability to look at a photo on a dark, neutral background, you can view it without the interference of a brighter surrounding. By using workspaces and canvases, DestroyFlickr is able to retain a constant history of where you have navigated, offering the ability to revisit an area without the need to reload the entire page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Address Fields in Web Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/international-address-fields-web-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/international-address-fields-web-forms/</guid>
      <description>Luke Wroblewski writes, in UX Matters, about how to deal with international addresses in form fields. I don&amp;rsquo;t think this is a topic covered in the web form design book, so be sure to check it out.
http://uxmatters.com/MT/archives/000295.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NameThis: Crowdsourced Project Naming</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/namethis-crowdsourced-project-naming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/namethis-crowdsourced-project-naming/</guid>
      <description>NameThis is an innovative new crowdsourced community that uses the wisdom of crowds to name products and services. Companies or individuals who are looking to name something pay $99 to request help in naming the thing. Participants provide suggestions and vote or invest a stake in the suggestions that have been posted. Kluster&amp;rsquo;s robots decide which is best, and participants get paid back when they&amp;rsquo;ve invested in the winner. You can find out more about how it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsourced Color Explorer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/crowdsourced-color-explorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/crowdsourced-color-explorer/</guid>
      <description>I have to admit, that this crowdsourced color explorer is one of the coolest ideas I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in, oh, the last few weeks. On the Dolores blog, Brendan explains how Mechanical Turk was used to present a set of random colors to participants in an exercise designed to observe how people name colors. The project was inspired by the World Color Survey. The result was the color explorer, aka &amp;ldquo;The Amazing Color Label Wheel!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch paper for the mobile designer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</guid>
      <description>Erlend posted on the Artueel blog about a great idea they had for mobile designers&amp;#8212;a sketchpaper document you can print out (PDF and PSD formats available) so you can get your ideas on paper. They&amp;rsquo;ve created sketchpaper for the iPhone and the Nokia N95. Since we‘re all big fans of the iPhone and the mobile future in general, we want to help the mobile designer achieving his goals. For those who like to sketch the design/flow of their mobile app or website we present you: sketch paper for the iPhone and Nokia N95.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing from the Inside Out</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-inside-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-inside-out/</guid>
      <description>Laura Richardson writes in interactions magazine, May/June 2008 (subscription required for full text) about a philosophy of industrial design whose goal is to &amp;ldquo;get to the heart of the matter&amp;#8212;meaningful interactions at the core of great product design.&amp;rdquo; In a sense, I can boil this down to needs. People have needs, explicit and unexpressed, that have to be described in relation to your product. The successful products are those where the flow between need and fulfillment are fluid and natural.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Streamlining Application Authorization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-streamlining-application-authorization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-streamlining-application-authorization/</guid>
      <description>Facebook have announced to developers that they are going to remove the installation requirement screen and allow users to try an application before installing it. What this means is that users won&amp;rsquo;t see the intimidating list of checkboxes to try an application out, and will get to install the application afterwards. This was meant as a preventative measure against spammy methods used by some applications. The developer announcement described the migration to the new requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Usability of Everyday Products</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/measuring-usability-everyday-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/measuring-usability-everyday-products/</guid>
      <description>David Travis reports for UserFocus on &#34;ISO 2082, Ease of Operation of Every Day Products.&#34; While web-focussed interaction designers and information architects may not be involved in the design of everyday products, we should probably be interested at a high level, in the processes discussed. As Travis points out, clients are increasingly concerned with objective measurements of usability, and standards such as this &#34;...will help ensure that we have robust and reliable test methods for all interactive designs, whether these are products, software or web sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Design Pattern Library Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/yahoo-design-pattern-library-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/yahoo-design-pattern-library-stencils/</guid>
      <description>The Yahoo! Design Pattern Library have released stencils for design patterns in OmniGraffle, Visio, PDF, PNG, and SVG format. I had planned to do the same for OmniGraffle users, but they beat me to the punch. :) This has easily become the best resource out there for design pattern examples. Congrats to Christian Crumlish and his team.
http://developer.yahoo.com/ypatterns/wireframes/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! BrowserPlus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-browserplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-browserplus/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! BrowserPlus is software that extends the capabilities of web browsers to make rich web experiences possible. Websites can use the software to support behaviors like drag and drop from the desktop, easier file uploads, acquisition of feeds and information, and native desktop notifications. The site is showing very cool demos right now including dragging and dropping photos from the desktop to a web browser, live image manipulation, and live refreshing IRC chatrooms in the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Gives Glimpse of Future Gears Goodies</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/google-gives-glimpse-future-gears-goodies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/google-gives-glimpse-future-gears-goodies/</guid>
      <description>Webware reports that Chris Prince, a lead Gears engineer, provided some insight into what Google plans to do with Gears to advance the web browser&amp;rsquo;s reach into the desktop. Among the features mentioned are notifications on the desktop of various events, support for location information, better interactions with a computer&amp;rsquo;s file system, and technology to let large file uploads proceed even when hampered by intermittent network connectivity. Prince demonstrated the following prototypes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OK-Cancel or Cancel-OK?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ok-cancel-or-cancel-ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ok-cancel-or-cancel-ok/</guid>
      <description>Jakob Nielsen&#39;s latest Alertbox recommends that order of OK vs Cancel should be determined by the standard order defined by the platform&#39;s interface guidelines. Alas, if you&#39;re designing for the web, order becomes problematic because Windows interface guidelines put OK first, whereas Apple guidelines put it last. Nielsen suggests that you base the order on the installed platform of your audience, i.e. if you have predominantly Windows users, you might be best served by putting OK on the left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TextFlow</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/textflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/textflow/</guid>
      <description>TextFlow is a new parallel document editing application and service that allows multiple users to work on a document simultaneously. The service should appeal to people who use the Track Changes feature of Microsoft Word. TextFlow lets users edit documents, and instantly see the changes suggested. One person can review the changes and apply them. The difference between this service and something like Google Docs or working in a wiki, is that the changes are indicated visually, rather than having to go through the diff displays in revision history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schmap Guides for the iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/schmap-guides-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/schmap-guides-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Schmap provides a local guide service for major cities. Listings are provided with general guide information, reviews, photos, and location on a map. The iPhone service attempts to maximize the unique features of that device. Listings are simple lists with thumbnails, but if you rotate the phone to landscape orientation, the listings then display alongside a map with markers to show where each place is located. Rotating back returns to the list view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File Extensions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/file-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/file-extensions/</guid>
      <description>File.Extensions demystifies file name extensions, providing a list of extensions by type. Each extension shows a .ico file if available, describes the type of file, and applications which may be used to open the file.
http://www.file-extensions.org/extensions/most-visited</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Contextual User Interfaces</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/rise-contextual-user-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rise-contextual-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>In Alex Iskold&#39;s article, The Rise of Contextual User Interfaces, the writer and CEO of software company AdaptiveBlue talks about the rise of contextual interfaces on the desktop an in the services we use on the web.
He points out the failing of choice over context in the old paradigm of UI design. Standardization of UI elements (tabs, combo boxes, etc.) was meant as a way to keep users from having to learn how to use an interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Hashtags</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twitter-hashtags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twitter-hashtags/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m just coming across the idea of hashtags for creating groupings on Twitter after seeing them in factoryjoe&amp;rsquo;s tweets and following a link from merylkevans to the page Twitter Fan Wiki on hashtags. This is a great example of how new uses of an application emerge can be defined by users.
Hashtags are a community-driven convention for adding additional context and metadata to your tweets. They&amp;rsquo;re like tags on Flickr, only added inline to your post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brand and celeb tags</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/brand-and-celeb-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/brand-and-celeb-tags/</guid>
      <description>Noah Brier&amp;rsquo;s celeb tags and brand tags sites is a crowdsourced tagging game that asks participants to tag a brand or celebrity and then see how others have tagged the brand or celeb. The game can be played in reverse as well, by viewing a tag cloud and trying to guess what the brand or celeb is.
I tried to take screenshots, but the celebrities&amp;rsquo; tag results were full of nonsensical tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwittEarth: Another globe interface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twittearth-another-globe-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twittearth-another-globe-interface/</guid>
      <description>TwittEarth is another spinning earth globe interface for displaying geolocalized information that&#39;s similar to the Yahoo Newsglobe and wii news channel interfaces. I don&#39;t care much for viewing the public twitter feed, so it&#39;s not very interesting to me. I&#39;m still trying to imagine the context that makes these interfaces practical for everyday use. The place where it makes most sense to me is in the 10 foot experience, as with the wii news channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zebra Striping: Does it Really Help?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/zebra-striping-does-it-really-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/zebra-striping-does-it-really-help/</guid>
      <description>The conclusions in this A List Apart article about zebra striping, the method of using alternating row colors in tables, strike me as odd. My first reaction to the article was, &amp;ldquo;Why do you need to study the usability of that technique?&amp;rdquo; I wonder if the issue isn&amp;rsquo;t so much a question of usability, but rather of aesthetic sensibility. Bad table row style without zebra striping can adversely affect readability as much as good zebra striping or horizontal rule style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Form Design: Filling in the blanks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/web-form-design-filling-blanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/web-form-design-filling-blanks/</guid>
      <description>Luke Wroblewski&#39;s book on form design is finally out. From the author:
Forms make or break the most crucial online interactions: checkout (commerce), registration (community), data input (participation and sharing), and any task requiring information entry. In Web Form Design, Luke Wroblewski draws on original research, his considerable experience at Yahoo! and eBay, and the perspectives of many of the field&#39;s leading designers to show you everything you need to know about designing effective and engaging Web forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 CSS Properties You Probably Never Use (but perhaps should)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/15-css-properties-you-probably-never-use-perhaps-should/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/15-css-properties-you-probably-never-use-perhaps-should/</guid>
      <description>On seomoz, Matthew Inman points to 15 rarely used CSS properties, and why you might want to be aware of if you don&amp;rsquo;t already use them. I have to admit to only using a handful of these, and not with any regularity.
 clip visibility text-shadow content quotes counter-reset and counter-increment marks page-break-before and page-break-after orphans and widows font-size-adjust font-stretch font-variant caption-side table-layout empty-cells 
http://www.seomoz.org/blog/css-properties-you-probably-never-use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Interface Implementations of Faceted Browsing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-implementations-faceted-browsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-implementations-faceted-browsing/</guid>
      <description>Mike Padilla offers up a description of facets and their use on web sites for browsing and filtering. He defines the types of interactions or behaviors that are typically found on sites with faceted browsing, describes what happens in terms of the system when you apply filters, and shows some examples of faceted browsing in use on sites including my favorite, Nike.com.
http://www.digital-web.com/articles/user_interface_implementations_of_faceted_browsing/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Screenshot Utilities You Should Know About</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/6-screenshot-utilities-you-should-know-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/6-screenshot-utilities-you-should-know-about/</guid>
      <description>I use different screen capture utilities depending on the type of screen I&amp;rsquo;m trying to grab. Some are great for a quick and dirty capture of a page I want to send someone. Others are good for annotating an interface I want to post to a web page. And still others are best for archival screen capture or for interfaces with video. Below are the 6 screenshot utilities that Mac users should know about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeframe: A Javascript Control For Date Ranges</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/timeframe-javascript-control-date-ranges/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/timeframe-javascript-control-date-ranges/</guid>
      <description>Stephen Celis&#39; Timeframe javascript library allows you to create a calendar that allows users to select date-ranges by first clicking a start or end date, and then clicking the other end of the range. The range is shown as you expect in desktop calendar applications with a filled bar between the dates. Hover over the range and click the X control to delete. Nice.
http://stephencelis.com/projects/timeframe#example_information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Dashcode</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-dashcode/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-dashcode/</guid>
      <description>Apple&#39;s Dashcode widget builder provides a nice library interface for viewing the parts you can include in your widget, and a code library to view snippets.
http://developer.apple.com/tools/dashcode/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sh*tty Data Visualization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sh-tty-data-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sh-tty-data-visualization/</guid>
      <description>I like single serving sites. The Letter pointed to this one, which shows the number of links to variations of the phrase &amp;ldquo;oh shit&amp;rdquo; when using multiple i&amp;rsquo;s. I wonder about the freshness of these results though, and I think the scale of the bars is a little off. :)
http://www.ohshiit.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Users around the world translate Facebook for free</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/users-around-world-translate-facebook-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/users-around-world-translate-facebook-free/</guid>
      <description>Facebook is tapping its international user community to help translate it&#39;s interface, namely the copy for its guidelines, into nearly the 2 dozen languages that represent the community&#39;s market outside the US. The localization effort is a massive crowdsourcing task that has been both criticized and lauded. The critics often point to the unpredictability and inconsistency of translations. Proponents of the effort applaud the boldness at utilizing an already eager community to contribute to making the application better for users in other non English-speaking countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton on Innovation and the Long Nose Theory</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-innovation-and-long-nose-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-innovation-and-long-nose-theory/</guid>
      <description>Bolt|Peters summarizes Bill Buxton&amp;rsquo;s talk at CHI 2008, which is focussed largely around his theory of long nose. The article in BusinessWeek describes the danger of trying to innovate around the long tail theory alone, and attempts to create awareness for this other phenomenon which he calls the long nose. The theory describes how the bulk of innovation is low-amplitude and takes place over a long period of time. [T]he bulk of innovation behind the latest &amp;ldquo;wow&amp;rdquo; moment (multi-touch on the iPhone, for example) is also low-amplitude and takes place over a long period—but well before the &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; idea has become generally known, much less reached the tipping point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand Spanking New Mini Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/brand-spanking-new-mini-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/brand-spanking-new-mini-icons/</guid>
      <description>This set of 113 free 10x10px grayscale mini icons from Brand Spanking New is a nice set of small, unobtrusive icons that can function inline with text or in places where smaller type might be used, e.g. with metadata. This is not a new set of icons, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to start collecting examples of icons here.
http://www.brandspankingnew.net/archive/2006/12/hohoho.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placement on a Page: The Missing Ad Metric</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/placement-page-missing-ad-metric/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/placement-page-missing-ad-metric/</guid>
      <description>Paidcontent reports on a study conducted by MarketingSherpa on advertising bechmarks, which showed the effect of online ad placement in relation to the fold.
According to the report, most individuals don‘t see most ads served to them—especially ads served below the fold. Despite this result, media delivery reports rarely include information on whether, or what percentage of, a media buy was served above or below the fold. On the chart below, the bottom of the blue area represents the percent of total viewers who see an ad; the top represents the percent of total viewers who scroll to a point where the ad is visible on their screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr Video!</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/flickr-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/flickr-video/</guid>
      <description>Flickr have announced that they are now letting Pro account users post video up to 90 seconds to their accounts. An invitation only group called Video! Video! Video! was created to showcase some of this new content. I&amp;rsquo;d love to post small videos to my Flickr account. I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved that my digital cameras limit me to capturing only the short moments. In a way, it reminds me of haiku, in that is forced to create poetry within the constraints and rules of the format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Must See Comment Designs for Web Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/30-must-see-comment-designs-web-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/30-must-see-comment-designs-web-designers/</guid>
      <description>The Blog Design Blog has collected 30 examples of comment interfaces on weblogs.
Thanks, swissmiss.
http://www.blogdesignblog.com/blog-design/30-comment-designs-for-webdesigners/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/search-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/search-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Peter Morville&#39;s Search Patterns Collection on Flickr provides examples, patterns, and anti-patterns for search interface design. Peter is additionally blogging about the search at findability.org. Excellent stuff.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/morville/collections/72157603785835882/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Web Design Template Updated</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-web-design-template-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-web-design-template-updated/</guid>
      <description>I updated the OmniGraffle Web Design Template.
This web design template is for people who do wireframes and storyboards. The template was created for OmniGraffle Professional provides the basic layout for a design deliverable including the following master canvases: document title, section title, wireframe (portrait and landscape), storyboard, and blank. The wireframes were created at 950px wide with guides following the Blueprint CSS Grid system. Wireframes also have 2 small hairline marks around the 600px point to mark the approximate fold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CiUI - CNET iPhone UI</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ciui-cnet-iphone-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ciui-cnet-iphone-ui/</guid>
      <description>Vladimir Olexa describes the CiUI iPhone library he created for the CNET iPhone app (http://iphone.cnet.com). The library is inspired by iUI and is available for download at CNET&#39;s common libraries page.
http://clientside.cnet.com/cnet-js-standards/ciui-cnet-iphone-ui/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Templates for Creating Blueprint-Compatible Comps</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/templates-creating-blueprint-compatible-comps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/templates-creating-blueprint-compatible-comps/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve created Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator templates for creating comps that work with Olav Bjorkoy&#39;s Blueprint CSS Framework. The templates are simply documents with guides based on the 24 units provided by Blueprint. The background image of the grid is also provided with a layer to show unit numbers if you like, and the Illustrator document shows a fake comp to demonstrate positioning on the grid.
You may download the templates here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoFuse: Hosted Mobile Website Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mofuse-hosted-mobile-website-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mofuse-hosted-mobile-website-service/</guid>
      <description>MoFuse is a service that allows site owners to provide a .mobi experience for their existing sites. The service allows you simply plug an RSS feed url into your account settings for a new site, and delivers a mobile formatted version of that feed. They also provide the ability to publish as an iPhone app, using the IUI interface, which you can experience on Google and FaceBook mobile sites. The service also allows you to create static pages, and customize the colors of the UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple TV 2.0 Review</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-tv-2-0-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-tv-2-0-review/</guid>
      <description>Apple TV owners got a software update pushed to their boxes this week, and Gizmodo has a review of the software complete with screenshots and a description of the rental and purchase services now offered. I was a bit disappointed by the update at first, but like my 6 year old son said on the second day, &#34;I&#39;m getting used to it.&#34; Gone is the simple, single panel with left/right hierarchical navigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! NewsGlobe vs. Wii News Channel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-newsglobe-vs-wii-news-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-newsglobe-vs-wii-news-channel/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! launched the News Globe, which shows the top news stories of the day using a rotatable globe for navigation. The stories are depicted as red blocks stacked over geographic regions of the globe, with taller stacks indicating more stories. By default the interface will autoplay through the top stories, spinning the globe to get from story to story. Clicking a link to a news article jetisons you out of this otherworldly view of earth, and into text land on a separate page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple filing depicts Apple TV with iChat widget interface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-filing-depicts-apple-tv-ichat-widget-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-filing-depicts-apple-tv-ichat-widget-interface/</guid>
      <description>AppleInsider discovers an August 2006 patent filing by Apple for features having to do with broadcast video sent over Apple TV. The patent discusses interesting ideas for widgets that overlay the screen to allow such display of information as data related to what is on, and interactions such as purchasing tickets to performances, and doing video chat.
View photo on Flickr
http://www.appleinsider.com/articles/08/02/07/apple_filing_depicts_apple_tv_with_ichat_widget_interface.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone versus tPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-versus-tphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-versus-tphone/</guid>
      <description>Edward Tufte posted an essay and video with commentary about the iPhone. Tufte is complimentary, for the most part, about the interface being predominantly free of administrative debris, but makes suggestions for how the iPhone can make better use of its screen resolution. As expected, his argument calls for more data density when possible.
He notes that the iPhone has elegantly removed administrative clutter in many places, using the information as the interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer Unlocks Wii&#39;s Hidden Potential</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</guid>
      <description>CNET reports on Johnny Chung Lee&amp;rsquo;s interaction experiments with the Wii Remote. Lee, a Phd student at Carnegie Melon, does a quick demo of head tracking for VR displays and multi point interaction using the wii remote. His experiments describe with incredible clarity how the wii remote fundamentally works and how the remote might be exploited to do much more than point at single points on the screen and control them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Prototyping with Morae</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-prototyping-morae/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-prototyping-morae/</guid>
      <description>Userfocus provides some inspiration for capturing paper prototype tests with Morae and a webcam. Their method invovlves positioning the camera over the prototype, connect the cam directly to the PC, viewing the camera live in a video editor, and recording the output of the editor in Morae. This method is ingenious. It gives you all of the agility of doing a paper prototype, with the flexbility and control of using Morae for the observation, note taking, and highlight reel creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shneiderman&#39;s Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/shneidermans-eight-golden-rules-interface-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/shneidermans-eight-golden-rules-interface-design/</guid>
      <description>Ben Shneiderman&#39;s Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design are user interface design rules described in Designing the User Interface: Strategies for Effective Human-Computer Interaction. Shneiderman proposed this collection of principles that are derived heuristically from experience and applicable in most interactive systems after being properly refined, extended, and interpreted.
To improve the usability of an application it is important to have a well designed interface and these &#34;Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern Libraries and UI Guidelines</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-pattern-libraries-and-ui-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-pattern-libraries-and-ui-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for conventional, reliable, and tested user interface patterns for common interface problems, look no further.
Pattern Libraries  Welie Interaction Design Pattern Library Yahoo! Design Pattern Library UI Patterns Peter Morville&amp;rsquo;s Search Patterns Collection on Flickr The Design Of Sites Book See also: Tom Erickson&amp;rsquo;s Interaction Design Patterns page which provides a listing of further design pattern resources.  User Interface Guidelines  Apple Human Interface Guidelines Usability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>23 Actionable Lessons from Eye-Tracking Studies</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/23-actionable-lessons-eye-tracking-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/23-actionable-lessons-eye-tracking-studies/</guid>
      <description>Christina Laun summarizes the top lessons to take away from eyetracking studies.
 Text attracts attention before graphics. Initial eye movement focuses on the upper left corner of the page. Users initially look at the top left and upper portion of the page before moving down and to the right. Readers ignore banners. Fancy formatting and fonts are ignored. Show numbers as numerals. Type size influences viewing behavior. Users only look at a sub headline if it interests them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>