<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>interface on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/interface/</link><description>Recent content in interface on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/interface/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Usabilla Discover</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</guid><description>Usabilla Discover is like a mashup of Pinterest and LittleBigDetails, or maybe it's a social LittleSnapper. Whatever the pitch, it's pretty useful to share screenshots of interface and visual designs you like. Now to figure out how to get my over 2,000 screenshots into it.
Note: To get in during the beta, sign up here with code &amp;quot;KONIGI&amp;quot;, good for the first 200 who use the code.
http://discover.usabilla.com/</description></item><item><title>Mobile Design Pattern Gallery</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/mobile-design-pattern-gallery/</guid><description>Theresa Neil's forthcoming book, Mobile Design Pattern Gallery, is set to be released by O'Reilly in the Fall of 2011.
Theresa launched a site to go along with the book that includes a fantastic gallery of 70 user interface design patterns for mobile devices with 400+ supporting examples from iOS, Android, BlackBerry, WebOS, Windows Mobile, and Symbian applications. The gallery covers a broad range of problems from designing your application's navigation to choosing the right invitation technique.</description></item><item><title>Konigi Graph Paper 2011 Update</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-2011-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-2011-update/</guid><description>It's been about 3 years since I updated the printable graph paper PDFs I provide for user interface design sketching. You can download the printable PDFs from here. (Yes, I use the word &amp;quot;Here&amp;quot; in links.)
In the last year I've gotten a lot of requests to replenish the inventory of wireframe and storyboard graphpaper notepads that I fulfilled via Amazon.com, and the wirebound sketch books. I feel bummed every time I tell people that I decided to get out of that little business.</description></item><item><title>Aaron Koblin: Artfully visualizing our humanity</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</guid><description>From Aaron Koblin's TED presentation:
"Artist Aaron Koblin takes vast amounts of data -- and at times vast numbers of people -- and weaves them into stunning visualizations. From elegant lines tracing airline flights to landscapes of cell phone data, from a Johnny Cash video assembled from crowd-sourced drawings to the "Wilderness Downtown" video that customizes for the user, his works brilliantly explore how modern technology can make us more human.</description></item><item><title>Android Interaction Design Patterns</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</guid><description>Android Patterns is a community-contributed site with interaction patterns for Android app design. The site is created by the folks at Dutch interaction design firm, UNITiD, who also provide an mobile wireframe templates for Android and Blackberry devices.
http://www.androidpatterns.com/wiki</description></item><item><title>Phonedoo: Dry erase iPhone sketching</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</guid><description>Cohdoo makes a nice iPhone UI sketching product called Phone Doos. They are 6.8&amp;quot; by 3.5&amp;quot; dry erase iPhone surfaces with faint grid lines and magnetic backing. A pack contains 10 Phone Doos.
I like that these gives you a surface to work on that can be re-arranged easily on a table and presented on a metallic wall. They have some good screenshots using them arranged on a whiteboard with flow arrows pointing between them, which is another thing that's probably much easier with these as opposed to using paper.</description></item><item><title>iPad Templates and Stencils</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ipad-templates-and-stencils/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ipad-templates-and-stencils/</guid><description>Emily Chang rounds up the offering of iPad UI stencils. Some nice OmniGraffle and Photoshop sets in there.
http://emilychang.com/2010/03/ipad-templates-and-stencils/</description></item><item><title>17 guidelines for better information architecture from 1991</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/17-guidelines-better-information-architecture-1991/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/17-guidelines-better-information-architecture-1991/</guid><description>Jussi Pasanen of Volkside pulls out an HCI gem in Kent L. Norman's The Psychology of Menu Selection: Designing Cognitive Control at the Human/Computer Interface, and repurposes the list of guidelines from the Checklist for Menu Design to provide a set of suitable guidelines for information architects to use with today’s websites. Norman's book is available for free on the web.
Via @BogieZero
http://www.volkside.com/2010/03/15-guidelines-for-better-information-architecture-from-1991/</description></item><item><title>The Best/Worst UI You've Ever Used</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bestworst-ui-youve-ever-used/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bestworst-ui-youve-ever-used/</guid><description>UX Exchange throws down on The Best UI You've Ever Used.
Stack Overflow throws up The Worst UI You've Ever Used.
http://stackoverflow.com/questions/238177/worst-ui-youve-ever-used</description></item><item><title>BiDi Screen</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</guid><description>BiDi Screen was demonstrated at SIGGRAPH Asia this year. It is a thin, depth-sensing LCD for 3D interaction using light fields.
The BiDi Screen is an example of a new type of I/O device that possesses the ability to both capture images and display them. This thin, bidirectional screen extends the latest trend in LCD devices, which has seen the incorporation of photo-diodes into every display pixel. Using a novel optical masking technique developed at the Media Lab, the BiDi Screen can capture lightfield-like quantities, unlocking a wide array of applications from 3-D gesture interaction with CE devices, to seamless video communication.</description></item><item><title>mobileHCI 2009 Proceedings</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/mobilehci-2009-proceedings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/mobilehci-2009-proceedings/</guid><description>The full text of the proceedings of MobileHCI09, the 11th International Conference on Human-Computer Interaction with Mobile Devices and Services is available online. The event, which covers mobile and wearable computing devices and services took place September, 2009 at the University of Bonn in Germany.
http://mobilehci.uni-siegen.de/mhci2009.html</description></item><item><title>About the close tab behaviour in Google Chrome</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</guid><description>Basil Safwat does a very thorough comparison of the the tabs in Mac Safari and Chrome, pointing out the subtleties in the close button positioning and behavior. While Mac close icons are on the left by convention, Chrome positions them to the right of the tab and keeps them visible, while Safari positions them to the left and only displays the close icon on hover. I initially had to relearn the close button position because Firefox also places them on the right.</description></item><item><title>Google's New Fade In UI</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/googles-new-fade-ui/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/googles-new-fade-ui/</guid><description>Google launched a new behavior on the search page that hides everything but the logo and search form on load, and fades in the rest of the surrounding interface when the user moves the mouse. The idea is to give focus to search for the primary use case, where a user hits the page and starts typing without moving the mouse. They talk about the new behavior on the Google Blog.</description></item><item><title>Balsamiq Exports Multi-Canvas Mockups to Single PDF</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/balsamiq-exports-multi-canvas-mockups-single-pdf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/balsamiq-exports-multi-canvas-mockups-single-pdf/</guid><description>Balsamiq announced that Mockups now supports export of multiple canvases to a single PDF that includes links. This means that your multi-canvas mockups can now be used as click through prototypes in Acrobat. Download the demo PDF file for a test drive.
http://www.balsamiq.com/blog/2009/11/13/weekly-release-export-to-pdf-a-fresh-coat-of-paint/</description></item><item><title>Log in or sign up?</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</guid><description>Leah Culver discusses the design of hybrid sign up / login forms, showing a few examples and the final form as implemented for Leafy Chat. Uses the familiar I'm a customer/I'm new here radios that we know from Amazon, but positions it before the password field, which I find an improvement over the Amazon implementation. Lots of ideas in the comments.
http://blog.leahculver.com/2009/11/log-in-or-sign-up.html</description></item></channel></rss>