<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>scheduling on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/scheduling/</link><description>Recent content in scheduling on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/scheduling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PowWow</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/powwow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/powwow/</guid><description>PowWow is a free simple service for scheduling user research using your Google Calendar. The fine folks at Pointless Corp (aka Viget) created this as a side project for handling scheduling of user interviews and testing, but could be used for any kind of event.
There are other apps like this that remove the fuss of coordinating schedules via email. PowWow does it simply, and provides a polished and pleasing experience.</description></item><item><title>Schedule and Cost Summary Calculator Template</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/schedule-and-cost-summary-calculator-template/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/schedule-and-cost-summary-calculator-template/</guid><description>So it's my birthday today. One thing that I've learned about birthdays from having a child, is that it's a lot of fun to give gifts away on your birthday. I'm now a seasoned goodie bag shopper and can tell you some interesting places to go in Manhattan and Brooklyn to find unusual gifts for boys age 8-10. But since I can't give all of you rare swag from Tokyo Toy, I thought I'd offer up a template that freelancers might find useful.</description></item><item><title>When is Good</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</guid><description>When Is Good is a tool that does one thing&amp;#8212;helps a group of people choose the time for their next meeting or event. One person starts by clicking (or clicking and dragging down) all the times that they are available on a calendar grid that shows 2 1/2 weeks of time slots. When Is Good then provides a link to circulate to participants, who see the proposed times and click on when they are free.</description></item></channel></rss>