<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Environment on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/environment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Environment on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/environment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>User-Centered Innovation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-centered-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-centered-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Roberto Verganti&#39;s article in HBR, &amp;quot;User-Centered Innovation Is Not Sustainable,&amp;quot; discusses how focussing on what user&#39;s say they want isn&#39;t a strategy for innovation. Not news to you, but his take looks at what that means regarding innovation from a sustainability perspective. I found it thought-provoking in other ways as well. The main idea is this. Forward-looking designers and business or policy decision makers may have a greater role and influence regarding designing sustainability products than customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Re-nourish: Design Sustainably</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/re-nourish-design-sustainably/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/re-nourish-design-sustainably/</guid>
      <description>Re-nourish.com is an independent online toolkit for sustainable graphic design.
By providing reliable, accessible sustainability tools untethered to commercial interests, we empower graphic designers to implement sustainable decision making in their day-to-day work. Our mission is nothing short of changing the industry, helping truly sustainable graphic design become what design is, not merely what it &amp;quot;could be.&amp;quot;
Check it out and learn how to change your business&#39; impact on the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iYo YoYo Charger for iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iyo-yoyo-charger-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iyo-yoyo-charger-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Peter Thuvander&amp;rsquo;s concept for a YoYo powered battery charger for USB devices like the iPhone is brilliant. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of efforts to provide clever alternative energy sources from human-powered generators.
Via Core77, yo.
http://www.peterthuvander.se/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovate or Die Winner, The Aquaduct</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/innovate-or-die-winner-aquaduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/innovate-or-die-winner-aquaduct/</guid>
      <description>The winners of Specialized&#39;s Innovate or Die Pedal-Powered Machine competition have been selected. The Aquaduct Mobile Filtration Vehicle was invented by five students from California: Adam Mac, Brian Mason, John Lai, Paul Silberschatz, and Eleanor Morgan.
 The Aquaduct transports, filters, and stores water for the developing world. A peristaltic pump attached to the pedal crank draws water from a large tank, through a carbon filter, to a smaller clean tank.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>