<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>video on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/video/</link><description>Recent content in video on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:11:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Storyboarder</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/storyboarder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:11:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/storyboarder/</guid><description>Wonderunit’s Storyboarder is a free storyboarding application for the Mac that lets you visualize a story quickly. Quickly sketch your stick figures, then create and show animatics to others.</description></item><item><title>Graphic Design Basics</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/graphic-design-basics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 16:16:30 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/graphic-design-basics/</guid><description>Designers Ellen Lupton and Jennifer Cole Phillips, authors of the book Graphic Design, The New Basics and Directors of the MFA Program at Maryland Institute College of Art offer a free 35 minute Skillshare course walking through 5 basic principles of graphic design. The course is a quick primer on design principles suited to various visual design projects.</description></item><item><title>VideoSWS: HTML5 Video Player Comparison</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/videosws-html5-video-player-comparison/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/videosws-html5-video-player-comparison/</guid><description>I like this &amp;quot;See What Sucks&amp;quot; table of HTML5 Video players, for comparing features of the video players like library dependencies, flash fallback, playlist and audio support. Starred products indicate the &amp;quot;Suck less than others&amp;quot; rating.
http://praegnanz.de/html5video/</description></item><item><title>Design inspired by nature</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/design-inspired-nature/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/design-inspired-nature/</guid><description>Via @leonbarnard</description></item><item><title>Call Recorder for Skype</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</guid><description>ecamm's Call Recorder for Mac captures audio and video to save Skype calls as QuickTime movies. Useful for user interviews or screensharing sessions.
Thanks to Thomas @vanderwal for the tip
http://www.ecamm.com/mac/callrecorder/</description></item><item><title>Aaron Koblin: Artfully visualizing our humanity</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</guid><description>From Aaron Koblin's TED presentation:
"Artist Aaron Koblin takes vast amounts of data -- and at times vast numbers of people -- and weaves them into stunning visualizations. From elegant lines tracing airline flights to landscapes of cell phone data, from a Johnny Cash video assembled from crowd-sourced drawings to the "Wilderness Downtown" video that customizes for the user, his works brilliantly explore how modern technology can make us more human.</description></item><item><title>Charlie Rose interview with Jeff Bezos</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/charlie-rose-interview-jeff-bezos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/charlie-rose-interview-jeff-bezos/</guid><description>This is a fantastic interview of Jeff Bezos on Charlie Rose where Bezos talks about why Kindle shouldn't be the iPad and why Amazon's new mission is &amp;quot;Earth's most customer-centric company.&amp;quot;
http://www.charlierose.com/view/interview/11138</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle for iPad Video</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ipad-video/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ipad-video/</guid><description>The OmniGroup now has video up of the OmniGraffle for iPad showing what looks to be an awesome product. I can't wait to get my hands on it.
http://www.omnigroup.com/products/omnigraffle-ipad/videos/</description></item><item><title>SublimeVideo HTML 5 Video Player</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/sublimevideo-html-5-video-player/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/sublimevideo-html-5-video-player/</guid><description>SublimeVideo is an HTML5 video player with full screen play and scrubbing controls. Because it's HTML5, the controls may be styled and no plugins are required. Presently supports Safari, Chrome, and IE with Chromeframe installed. Firefox support forthcoming. Will be available for free for non-commercial use.
Via @dandean
http://jilion.com/sublime/video</description></item><item><title>25 User Experience Videos That Are Worth Your Time</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/25-user-experience-videos-are-worth-your-time/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/25-user-experience-videos-are-worth-your-time/</guid><description>Smashing Magazine have curated a list of 25 videos UX videos and presentations worth watching. It will take you more than 16 hours to watch all of these videos.
http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2010/01/05/25-user-experience-videos-that-are-worth-your-time/</description></item><item><title>Webgriffe</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</guid><description>The portfolio site of the Webgriffe does an excellent job highlighting the work of a web agency with interests in both the fashion and design trends. The site immerse the user in a business catwalk video on the background. The studio worked hard to realize a SEO friendly dinamic flash site with deep linking navigation and high attention to usability.
http://www.webgriffe.com</description></item><item><title>Michael Bierut: 5 Secrets from 86 Notebooks</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/michael-bierut-5-secrets-86-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/michael-bierut-5-secrets-86-notebooks/</guid><description>This is fantastic presentation from Pentagram's Michael Bierut at The 99 Percent conference. Shows how a quiet, humble, and empathetic bedside manner can be such useful attributes in a designer.
Renowned graphic designer Michael Bierut claims that he's not creative. Instead, he likens his job to that of a doctor who tends to patients – "the sicker, the better." Digging into the 86 notebooks he's kept over the course of his career, Bierut walks us through 5 projects – from original conception to final execution – extracting a handful of simple lessons (e.</description></item><item><title>Barry Schwartz on the Paradox of Choice</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/barry-schwartz-paradox-choice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/barry-schwartz-paradox-choice/</guid><description>Psychologist Barry Schwartz takes aim at a central tenet of western societies on TED: freedom of choice. In Schwartz's estimation, choice has made us not freer but more paralyzed, not happier but more dissatisfied.
The idea that more choice leads to paralysis rather than happiness resonates strongly with me. I think about where I am in terms of my spiritual and psychological development, and I do feel dissatisfied when things aren't perfect today and I find it troublesome that I think this way.</description></item><item><title>Camtasia for Mac</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/camtasia-mac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/camtasia-mac/</guid><description>TechSmith, makers of Morae and Snagit, have released a Mac version of Camtasia, the screencast video recording software. The software allows you to capture the screen, audio and iSight input, and provides simple drag and drop editing including a lot of built-in transitions and effects. You can then easily export the HTML and SWF for embedding in a web page. Looks like an easy to use alternative that might take the work out of producing screencasts.</description></item><item><title>Screenr Screencasting Service</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/screenr-screencasting-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/screenr-screencasting-service/</guid><description>Screenr is a web-based screen capture tool that lets you record screen video and audio from your Mac or PC and posts a link to the video, hosted on Screenr.com, to your Twitter stream.
http://screenr.com/</description></item></channel></rss>