<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ideation on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/ideation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ideation on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/ideation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Give it five minutes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/give-it-five-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/give-it-five-minutes/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m certainly no stranger to being opinionated and argumentative. I&#39;ve put my foot in my mouth a few times by pushing back on others&#39; ideas, and am well aware that being quick to react can be detrimental. The older I get, the more I realize how little I know and how much more time I need to spend thinking after listening, before I open my mouth or start to type to respond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shades of Grey: Wireframes as Thinking Device</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/shades-grey-wireframes-thinking-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/shades-grey-wireframes-thinking-device/</guid>
      <description>Will Evans writes for UX Mag about his process for creating wireframes, or more precisely how he uses wireframes for ideation and problem solving. Will breaks his design process into three phases: divergence, transformation, and convergence.
This seems similar to a common theme I come across when designers talk about their process--framing/ideating, reframing/ideating, selection/refining. Buxton also refers to this, citing Stuart Pugh&#39;s idea by illustrating the expanding/contracting nature of a designer&#39;s concept selection, which I find easy to map to sketching-wireframing as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Design Tools</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/concept-design-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/concept-design-tools/</guid>
      <description>Victor Lombardi discusses concept design in Digital Web Magazine, pointing out that digital designers should take some inspiration from design processes for ideation and concept generation from the fields of architecture and industrial design. I think the main idea is to learn from the practices and methods from these fields, and use that as inspiration for what might be useful in your concept design practice. That is not to say that every project needs to result in a dozen concepts that need to be prototyped at high fidelity and therefore at significant cost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
