<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>industrial design on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/industrial-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in industrial design on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/industrial-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Smith ID Sketch Demos on Core77</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jeff-smith-id-sketch-demos-core77/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jeff-smith-id-sketch-demos-core77/</guid>
      <description>I could watch Jeff Smith sketching with a Sharpie all day. Core 77 featured Smith, principal/Design Director at Reflex Design, doing sketch demos for the students at Virginia Tech&#39;s ID department.
 More on the Core 77 Boards.
http://www.core77.com/blog/tools/forum_frenzy_sketch_demos_from_blaster701_19745.asp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Interaction Design Contest | Building the Internet of Things</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/1st-interaction-design-contest-building-internet-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/1st-interaction-design-contest-building-internet-things/</guid>
      <description>IDAT, the Institute of Design, Art and Technology of Barcelona is holding its 1st Interaction Design Competition based on the theme of designing applications for the next generation Internet of Things.
The competition calls for ideas of interfaces, interactions, and applications that can be designed with technologies such as embedded Radio Frequency Identification (RFID), short-range wireless communication, ubiquitous data networks, mobile devices, hardware prototyping tools and digital fabrication.
The deadline to submit projects is December 15, 2010, and the award is 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside IDEO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/inside-ideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/inside-ideo/</guid>
      <description>Design Observer points to the 1999 ABC Nightline program that took an inside look at IDEO. How does the process of designing a better product work? To show you, Nightline went to Palo Alto, CA to the designers at IDEO, and gave them the toughest problem we could think of. Take something old and familiar like the shopping cart and completely redesign it in just five days.
IDEO&#39;s unique brand of brainstorming is called &#39;&#39;Deep Dive,&#39;&#39; a sort of total immersion into the problem at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle vs. iPhone/iPod Touch: Human/Machine Interaction &amp; User Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kindle-vs-iphoneipod-touch-humanmachine-interaction-user-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kindle-vs-iphoneipod-touch-humanmachine-interaction-user-experience/</guid>
      <description>Tog&#39;s comparison and analysis of the human computer interaction versus the user experience with both the Amazon Kindle and the iPhone/iPod Touch is excellent. The separation of HCI/UX in his analysis really drives the point home that good interaction and industrial design can make the experience, and a good experience isn&#39;t only about the design.
I don&#39;t use a Kindle daily, so I can&#39;t comment personally on it, but the industrial design was a showstopper for me and kept me from wanting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooper-Hewitt, National Design Museum: People&#39;s Design Award</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-hewitt-national-design-museum-peoples-design-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-hewitt-national-design-museum-peoples-design-award/</guid>
      <description>Results are in of the People&#39;s Choice award for the Cooper-Hewitt&#39;s National Design Award. The Zon Hearing Aid grabbed the prize.
http://peoplesdesignaward.cooperhewitt.org/2008/browse/all/0</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iStik Designers Make a Better iPod Holder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/istik-designers-make-better-ipod-holder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/istik-designers-make-better-ipod-holder/</guid>
      <description>Core77 talks about a couple that makes good with self-designed iPod accessory, the iStik. Great example of designers finding buyers in a market saturated with accessory makers. They stand out because they&#39;ve thought of the problem, researched how to make the better mousetrap and deliver a product that sells the story of sticking your nano wherever you want when you work out. They&#39;ve made $50K in 6 months. Excellent stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droog</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/droog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/droog/</guid>
      <description>droog is a Dutch company, led by Gijs Bakker and Renny Ramakers, that art directs and sells products collaboratively created with designers worldwide. The site showcases the droog collection, whose products are categorized as accessories, lighting, furniture and objects, publications, and limited editions.
The design aesthetic is modern and minimalist, and conveys a sense of wit which mostly comes across in the product photos. There are unexpected twists, like a right aligned breadcrumb, and simple touches like the category/product/designer drop down menus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clover Innovates the Coffee Maker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/clover-innovates-coffee-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/clover-innovates-coffee-maker/</guid>
      <description>The $11,000 Clover Coffee Maker brews one cup of coffee at a time using a method similar to a French Press, but with the ability to customize water volume and temperature per cup. The machine is programmable and has a network connection, so the machine can use brewing parameters for specific roasts. Check the video below for the Clover in action.  According to Wired Magazine, Howard Schultz, the founder of Starbucks described the coffee by saying, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future Of Apple Is In 1960s Braun</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/future-apple-1960s-braun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/future-apple-1960s-braun/</guid>
      <description>Gizmodo puts Dieter Rams&#39; designs at Braun next to Jonathan Ives&#39; designs at Apple.
10 principles of design according to Rams:
 Good design is innovative. Good design makes a product useful. Good design is aesthetic. Good design helps us to understand a product. Good design is unobtrusive. Good design is honest. Good design is durable. Good design is consequent to the last detail. Good design is concerned with the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing from the Inside Out</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-inside-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-inside-out/</guid>
      <description>Laura Richardson writes in interactions magazine, May/June 2008 (subscription required for full text) about a philosophy of industrial design whose goal is to &#34;get to the heart of the matter&amp;#8212;meaningful interactions at the core of great product design.&#34; In a sense, I can boil this down to needs. People have needs, explicit and unexpressed, that have to be described in relation to your product. The successful products are those where the flow between need and fulfillment are fluid and natural.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>studio.lo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/studio-lo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/studio-lo/</guid>
      <description>http://studio.lo.neuf.fr/index.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designer Pages</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/designer-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/designer-pages/</guid>
      <description>http://www.designerpages.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovate or Die Winner, The Aquaduct</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/innovate-or-die-winner-aquaduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/innovate-or-die-winner-aquaduct/</guid>
      <description>The winners of Specialized&#39;s Innovate or Die Pedal-Powered Machine competition have been selected. The Aquaduct Mobile Filtration Vehicle was invented by five students from California: Adam Mac, Brian Mason, John Lai, Paul Silberschatz, and Eleanor Morgan.
 The Aquaduct transports, filters, and stores water for the developing world. A peristaltic pump attached to the pedal crank draws water from a large tank, through a carbon filter, to a smaller clean tank.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
