<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>touch interfaces on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/touch-interfaces/</link>
    <description>Recent content in touch interfaces on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/touch-interfaces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What If DJ Controllers Had Built In Screens?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-if-dj-controllers-had-built-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-if-dj-controllers-had-built-screens/</guid>
      <description>This is a cool design challenge that showed up on DJ Tech Tools&#39; blog to mock up DJ controllers. DJ gear vendor Numark is reported to be releasing a controller with a screen. That&#39;s kind of interesting, because it could potentially let digital DJs that use them close their computer screen and focus on performing.
While there are CDJs that already have color LCDs to preview deck track information, midi controllers are largely comprised of faders, buttons, knobs, toggle switches, jog wheels, and touch sensitive strips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Multi-touch Interactions on the Apple iPad</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-multi-touch-interactions-apple-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-multi-touch-interactions-apple-ipad/</guid>
      <description>Craig Villamor and Luke Wroblewski summarize the new interactions we&#39;ll be seeing in the iPad.
During Apple&#39;s 90 minute unveiling of the iPad this week, a lot of new multi-touch interactions were shown off. But they went by fast. So as a service to digital product designers everywhere, we took the time to extract 8 minutes of new user interface demos from the iPad keynote. Now you can quickly just catch the UI in action on Apple&#39;s new native iPad and iWork applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch User Interface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/touch-user-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/touch-user-interface/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered Touch User Interface, a blog that reports regularly on touch interface projects, and provides links to resources related to designing for touch screen interfaces.
http://www.touchuserinterface.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Touch System I have Known and Loved</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/multi-touch-system-i-have-known-and-loved/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/multi-touch-system-i-have-known-and-loved/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton&#39;s &#34;Multi-Touch System I have Known and Loved&#34; has been updated as of Sept. 2009. The article provides examples and a history of the multi touch systems Buxton has been involved with or known about over the years. Multi-touch technologies have a long history. To put it in perspective, my group at the University of Toronto was working on multi-touchin 1984 (Lee, Buxton &amp;amp; Smith, 1985), the same year that the first Macintosh computer was released, and we were not the first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audi Car Configurator on Surface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/audi-car-configurator-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/audi-car-configurator-surface/</guid>
      <description>This is video showing the interaction design of a Surface interface to configure the Audi A4.
Audi A4 Car Configurator by Neue Digitale / Razorfish in collaboration with Realtime Technology AG. Showcased at this year’s IAA - the world’s leading automotive fair. The application allows multiple users to configure an Audi A4 simultaneously by changing the car&#39;s paint finishes, rims and by selecting and coloring style package components. The configured A4 is experienced in an immersive 3d environment, in which users can navigate seamlessly by zooming and panning using a multitouch-enabled interface</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BumpTop 3D Desktop</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bumptop-3d-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bumptop-3d-desktop/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m becoming more and more intrigued by the latest offering of inexpensive touch screen PCs like the MSI Wind Top that have been released recently, as well as the rumored Apple Tablet. I&#39;m excited for the penetration of touch interfaces on higher resolution desktop applications, which will start to spread at a much greater rate to a wider audience when we see low cost devices like tablets and touch screen desktops at netbook prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larva Labs Intelligent Home Screen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/larva-labs-intelligent-home-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/larva-labs-intelligent-home-screen/</guid>
      <description>Larva Labs&#39; Intelligent Home Screen is a home screen replacement for Google Android devices that provides an information stream or feed. It divides the stream into 2 panels: private information on top (messages, calendar events) and public information on bottom (stock quotes, news). It provides color-coded category markers, and a draggable menubar that allows the user to selectively change the volume of information between top and bottom lists, and when pushed to a single end, provides focus on that category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That design is money! Pentagram redesigns an ATM UI</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-money-pentagram-redesigns-atm-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-money-pentagram-redesigns-atm-ui/</guid>
      <description>Holger Struppek has written an article describing the design and prototyping process for the redesign of the Wells Fargo ATM user interface by Pentagram. This is a rare, in-depth look at the prototyping process for an interface that we come into contact regularly.
The agency was contracted to abandon the prior touch screen/solid state UI, and transform the software to work with touch screen interfaces only and improve flow and visual design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Razorfashion Retail Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/razorfashion-retail-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/razorfashion-retail-experience/</guid>
      <description>Razorfashion Retail Experience from Razorfish - Emerging Experiences on Vimeo.
 Razorfish shows off their concept for touch screen retail experiences using the Razorfish Touch Framework.
http://emergingexperiences.com/2009/05/introducing-the-razorfashion-retail-experience/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typography Is the UI on the Zune HD</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/typography-ui-zune-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typography-ui-zune-hd/</guid>
      <description>Zune HD Video Hands On from Gizmodo on Vimeo.
 http://fosat.tumblr.com/post/114567959/typography-is-the-user-interface-the-new-zune-hd</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap is the New Click</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/tap-new-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/tap-new-click/</guid>
      <description>NYC IxDA - Tap is the New Click - Dan Saffer from Interaction Design Association on Vimeo. Dan Saffer gave a fantastic NYC IXDA presentation, Tap Is the New Click, discussing the rise of touch interfaces, their place and adoption in society, and the role of the interaction designer in designing these direct manipulation interfaces. Every IA and IXD needs to watch this. A summary of the talk below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JazzMutant multi-touch controllers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jazzmutant-multi-touch-controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jazzmutant-multi-touch-controllers/</guid>
      <description>JazzMutant creates the Lemur and Dexter, multi-touch hardware controllers for audio production, live music and media performance. What I like about this is that it shows how much closer multi-touch brings devices to the experience of using analogous hardware controls like knobs, buttons, and sliders without any physical limitations. I once blog bitched about the fact that the Traktor DJ software I played for a few years limited the fun, and the ability to mix with two hands because at the time you could only use one input device, the mouse, to control the mixer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacemaker Mobile MP3 DJ Device Gets a GUI Redesign</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pacemaker-mobile-mp3-dj-device-gets-gui-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pacemaker-mobile-mp3-dj-device-gets-gui-redesign/</guid>
      <description>Pacemaker, the mobile MP3 DJ device that debuted last year with a 120 GB hard drive, is getting a 2.0 release this spring and offering an additional lower capacity 60 GB hard drive option, and a new user interface. I was enamored with this device and the way they could incorporate most of the possible mixer and track selection controls for 2 deck track mixing into a single, albeit large, handheld device with their original product UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch Usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/touch-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/touch-usability/</guid>
      <description>Kevin Arthur&#39;s Touch Usability is a blog devoted to usability news and research on touch screen interfaces.
http://www.touchusability.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNL Megapixel Giant Touch Map</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/snl-megapixel-giant-touch-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/snl-megapixel-giant-touch-map/</guid>
      <description>Not to be outdone by CNN&#39;s Chuck Todd or John King, SNL Weekend Update&#39;s Fred Armisen previews their Megapixel Giant Touchmap. http://www.hulu.com/watch/40678/saturday-night-live-update-freds-mapfix-it?c=98:255</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
