<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>user flow on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/user-flow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in user flow on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/user-flow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Lessons Learned From Offline Experiences</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-lessons-learned-offline-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-lessons-learned-offline-experiences/</guid>
      <description>Jon Phillips writes about how the user experience of restaurant flow can be redesigned by illustrating the flow in a cafeteria-style space from entry, order and pickup to seating and exit. In his great diagrams he shows how the orginal flow frustrated diners (users) and could be easily re-designed to consider a flow that was immediately understandable--the design he experienced made him feel stupid. Sound familiar?
I think about interior spaces like lines at Whole Foods, where sometimes it makes absolutely no sense (I&#39;m looking at you Columbus Circle) and where other lines seem to have considered this (Union Square sometimes feels efficient).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Sitemaps Don&#39;t Work: Two Alternatives</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/when-sitemaps-dont-work-two-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/when-sitemaps-dont-work-two-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>Interesting discussion in M. Jackson Wilkinson&#39;s blog about the altnernatives to hierarchical sitemaps, and the use of concept maps or user flows as alternatives when hierarchy doesn&#39;t work in your documentation. I have to agree with one point, in that site maps don&#39;t always serve documentation well when the notion of a strict hierarchy just doesn&#39;t exist. But I think there&#39;s utility in sitemaps at conveying the organization of a site or application at some level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Planner - View and Create User Flows, Viral Loops, and More.</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/product-planner-view-and-create-user-flows-viral-loops-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/product-planner-view-and-create-user-flows-viral-loops-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Product Planner is one an brilliant idea. Deconstruct the user flow of web sites, illustrate the flow with annotated screenshot flowcharts, allow users to copy the flow and reuse on the site. Like Konigi, this does a great job of capturing examples of alternative approaches to interaction, showcases them for you to compare, and allows you to select the best examples to learn from and inform you of approaches you may not have thought of.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
