<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Browser on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/web-browser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Browser on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/web-browser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Below 600px</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/life-below-600px/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/life-below-600px/</guid>
      <description>Paddy Donnelly flips the bird at the fold.
What I&#39;m proposing is for you to think twice about these ‘rules’ which are preached so often around the web and aim to create something original. Don&#39;t live in the old world of pushing all your quality content on the visitor at once because they&#39;ve only got 4 seconds before their attention drops (or whatever other statistic is doing the rounds at present).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the close tab behaviour in Google Chrome</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>Basil Safwat does a very thorough comparison of the the tabs in Mac Safari and Chrome, pointing out the subtleties in the close button positioning and behavior. While Mac close icons are on the left by convention, Chrome positions them to the right of the tab and keeps them visible, while Safari positions them to the left and only displays the close icon on hover. I initially had to relearn the close button position because Firefox also places them on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MOBIFY: Mobile Site Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobify-mobile-site-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobify-mobile-site-service/</guid>
      <description>MOBIFY is a service that lets you create a mobile version of your site for free. You start by entering your site url, and selecting regions of your page design to be used in the mobile template, using their online template editor. For many sites, one template may be sufficient to serve all of your page types. After selecting regions, you may change their order in preview mode, as well as add custom HTML and modify CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>@font-face: The Potential of Web Typography</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/font-face-potential-web-typography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/font-face-potential-web-typography/</guid>
      <description>How can @font-face be used with currently implemented CSS selectors to create engaging, nuanced and more mature typography? Ian Lynam &amp;amp; Craig Mod discuss the potential of using @font-face now that Firefox 3.5 is out. http://craigmod.com/journal/font-face/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Labs Design Challenge: Reinventing Tabs in the Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mozilla-labs-design-challenge-reinventing-tabs-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mozilla-labs-design-challenge-reinventing-tabs-browser/</guid>
      <description>Mozilla Labs together with IxDA and Johnny Holland presented the Summer 09 Design Challenge as part of their Concept Series. The challenge theme is &amp;ldquo;Reinventing Tabs in the Browser - How can we create, navigate and manage multiple web sites within the same browser instance?&amp;rdquo; Voting on concept submissions ends on July 5. Will take a while to make it through the over 120 concepts!
http://design-challenge.mozilla.com/summer09/showcase.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus Browser Testing Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/litmus-browser-testing-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/litmus-browser-testing-software/</guid>
      <description>Litmus is a web browser testing service that lets you test your web pages against 23 browser versions on 3 platforms as well as testing email on 16 different mail clients. The service offers a very intuitive experience for running tests, viewing the full page screenshots, and verifying compatibility.
They also just released Alkaline, a Mac app that lets you view your tests of Windows clients without going to the web site, which is shown in the screenshot above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Browser Wars</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/browser-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/browser-wars/</guid>
      <description>Cool infographic from Pixel Labs depicting the Browser wars, based on W3 Schools Browser Stats. Reminds me of the &amp;ldquo;Napoleon&amp;rsquo;s March&amp;rdquo; graphic in Tufte&amp;rsquo;s book.
http://www.pixellabs.com/images/browserwars.png</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Methodologie Browser Size Test</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/methodologie-browser-size-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/methodologie-browser-size-test/</guid>
      <description>Mmmmm, grids. Methodologie uses stats from The Counter to display the screen resolutions supported by users&amp;rsquo; computers in their 10&amp;frasl;2008 numbers.
http://www.methodologie.com/sizer/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScreenToaster Free Online Screen Recorder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/screentoaster-free-online-screen-recorder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/screentoaster-free-online-screen-recorder/</guid>
      <description>ScreenToaster is a pretty incredible web application that lets you record your web browser screen without having to download desktop software. Currently, to record a screen, you open up ScreenToaster in a browser tab, navigate to the page you want to capture, click a keyword combination, and the applet starts recording. Press another key combination to stop. The service saves the session and almost immediately gives you a flash video with your recording.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radial Menu Tests in Firefox</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/radial-menu-tests-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/radial-menu-tests-firefox/</guid>
      <description>Testing of proof of concept prototypes of radial menus. The idea is to get users to try to select the same menu item repeatedly as the radial menu changes from state to state and capture participants feedback on usability of the interface.
http://jonoscript.wordpress.com/2008/10/28/pie-in-the-sky/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquity</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ubiquity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ubiquity/</guid>
      <description>Ubiquity for Firefox from Aza Raskin on Vimeo. I&amp;rsquo;ve been really impressed by Aza Raskin&amp;rsquo;s Ubiquity add on for Firefox, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with a lot lately. It completely makes up for the less than exciting experience I had with Enso, which never came close to a Quicksilver experience on Windows. Ubiquity is pretty much the Quicksilver experience brought to your web browser. A smart tool that is summoned by a keyboard shortcut, and provides shortcuts to frequently used tools, and contextually relevant paths to using selected content in the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox 3.1 Alpha Video Demo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-3-1-alpha-video-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-3-1-alpha-video-demo/</guid>
      <description>Ars Technica reports on the 3.1 Alpha of Firefox, which includes support for the HTML 5 Video element which provides some functionality to developers that is not possible with Flash. Video can be interspersed with other web content, playback can be manipulated with JavaScript, and video elements can be directly accessed through the document object model.
Bluish Coder demonstrates the Video tag in SVG to implement a Silverlight style demo in Firefox 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Chrome Comic Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/google-chrome-comic-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/google-chrome-comic-book/</guid>
      <description>Google explains it&amp;rsquo;s new open source, Webkit-based Chrome Web Browser with a 28 page comic book inked by Scott McCloud. The Chrome browser beta becomes available to Windows users on September 2, 2008. Mac and Linux versions are also planned.
http://www.google.com/googlebooks/chrome/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Path Aurora Concept Video, Part 1</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Path, as part of Mozilla Lab&#39;s concept video series, provides some suggestions for the possible future of the web experience with Aurora. This forward looking concept focuses on 4 high priority elements: context awareness, natural interaction, continuity, and multi-user applications.
Aurora (Part 1) from Adaptive Path on Vimeo. The scenario laid out is one in which one user starts an audio chat and screen sharing sesion with another user and we begin to see how users can find information from their history and share it and remix it with others in the session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Mobile Concept Video</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</guid>
      <description>Firefox Mobile Concept Video from Aza Raskin on Vimeo. Aza Raskin demonstrates a touch interface concept for a Firefox Mobile browser. The mocked up prototype includes features including spatial browsing of browser tabs, and touch gestures for summoning application menus.
http://azarask.in/blog/post/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! BrowserPlus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-browserplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-browserplus/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! BrowserPlus is software that extends the capabilities of web browsers to make rich web experiences possible. Websites can use the software to support behaviors like drag and drop from the desktop, easier file uploads, acquisition of feeds and information, and native desktop notifications. The site is showing very cool demos right now including dragging and dropping photos from the desktop to a web browser, live image manipulation, and live refreshing IRC chatrooms in the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Gives Glimpse of Future Gears Goodies</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/google-gives-glimpse-future-gears-goodies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/google-gives-glimpse-future-gears-goodies/</guid>
      <description>Webware reports that Chris Prince, a lead Gears engineer, provided some insight into what Google plans to do with Gears to advance the web browser&amp;rsquo;s reach into the desktop. Among the features mentioned are notifications on the desktop of various events, support for location information, better interactions with a computer&amp;rsquo;s file system, and technology to let large file uploads proceed even when hampered by intermittent network connectivity. Prince demonstrated the following prototypes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do websites need to look exactly the same in every browser?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/do-websites-need-look-exactly-same-every-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/do-websites-need-look-exactly-same-every-browser/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s one hell of a domain name: http://dowebsitesneedtolookexactlythesameineverybrowser.com/
http://dowebsitesneedtolookexactlythesameineverybrowser.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designers Toolbox: OS Form Elements</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designers-toolbox-os-form-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designers-toolbox-os-form-elements/</guid>
      <description>The Designers Toolbox provides a nice resource for designers looking to create form elements in design comps or wireframes. The site displays every type of form element that can be generated by Windows XP IE and Firefox, and Mac OS X Safari and Firefox. Photoshop files can be downloaded for each form element.
Thanks, swissmiss.
http://www.designerstoolbox.com/designresources/elements/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Resolution Statistics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/screen-resolution-statistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/screen-resolution-statistics/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to researching user&#39;s screen resolution, I&#39;m a strong believer that vertical positioning matters most when considering key issues such as location of identifying elements like site name and h1-type headings, and elements that satisfy business rules such as ad location. The B&amp;amp;A article, &#34;Blasting the Myth of the Fold&#34; addresses this issue well, and I&#39;m in agreement that &#34;the fold&#34; matters little if the above issues are dealt with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple&#39;s Safari 3.1 to support downloadable web fonts and more</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/apples-safari-3-1-support-downloadable-web-fonts-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apples-safari-3-1-support-downloadable-web-fonts-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Apple Insider reports that Apple will ship Safari 3.1 with downloadable web fonts, HTML5&amp;rsquo;s SQL storage application programming interface, and HTML5 video and audio tags. They provide the following description of these new features.
For example, CSS Transforms and CSS Animations will join web downloadable fonts in allowing Safari 3.1 and iPhone users to render web pages and web apps with enhanced design messages and real-time visual effects. By applying Transforms, developers can author trigger actions that scale, rotate, skew and translate HTML boxes in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>