<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Icons on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/icons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Icons on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/icons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One div: Pure CSS icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/one-div-pure-css-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/one-div-pure-css-icons/</guid>
      <description>One Div is a library of icons that are realised in pure css with only one html div as an alternative to SVG. Icons allow precise borders even when resized—same as one would expect with vector icons.
http://one-div.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steedicons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/steedicons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/steedicons/</guid>
      <description>The Steedicons set by Kyle Steed contains 300+ hand drawn icons available as a font or in vector format (.ai, .eps, .csh) for Illustrator, Photoshop, or the wireframing tool of your choice. The bold, sketchy icons would would work perfectly in Balsamiq Mockups or alongside the Konigi Sketch stencils.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a small sample of the icons available in this set.  Buy them here.
http://steedicons.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vector Doodlekit Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/vector-doodlekit-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/vector-doodlekit-icons/</guid>
      <description>The Doodlekit Icons set contains 700+ hand-drawn icons for use in sketch-style wireframes. You can buy them in vector format to use in the design tool of your choice, or download the free set of 32 x 32 px PNGs. Here&amp;rsquo;s a screenshot of the icons in the new custom icon feature that&amp;rsquo;s available in the pre-release version of Mockups.  More info here.
http://doodlekit.imagiag.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X and iOS Icon Templates from Cohdoo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mac-os-x-and-ios-icon-templates-cohdoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mac-os-x-and-ios-icon-templates-cohdoo/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo have created downloadable iOS and OS X icon templates for Photoshop that lay out all the different sizes of assets for a given platform and state where they were to be used.
Download the PSD templates here.
http://blog.cohdoo.com/post/9293679992/icon-grids</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gesturecons: Multi-Touch Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gesturecons-multi-touch-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gesturecons-multi-touch-icons/</guid>
      <description>Gesture icons created for wireframing touch interfaces. High resolution multi-touch vector icons, scalable and alterable (.pdf, .ai, .eps file types.) Free for personal use, and commercial licenses are available.
http://gesturecons.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons Update v. 1.5 for OmniGraffle and EPS Versions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-update-v-15-omnigraffle-and-eps-versions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-update-v-15-omnigraffle-and-eps-versions/</guid>
      <description>The OmniGraffle Wireframe Icons and the Royalty Free EPS/PNG icons have been updated.
In the OmniGraffle version, all icons have been converted to vector format so they are editable in OmniGraffle. You can now modify the shapes and easily change their colors. The vector icons also reduce file size of OG documents. In both OmniGraffle and EPS/PNG versions, I&#39;ve cleaned up all existing icons for consistency and added new icons including: globe, wrench/screwdriver, lightning bolt, spaces, desktop, gun sight, cloud, bug, books, presentation, twitter bird, bullhorn, megaphone, rocket, windows, mac, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icons for Interaction</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/icons-interaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/icons-interaction/</guid>
      <description>This is the presentation from Jon Hicks&amp;rsquo; @media 2009 Icons for Interation talk in London, which includes speaking notes for every slide. Hicks demonstrates effective design and strategies for use, providing plenty of examples, and a link list that points to the resources and tips mentioned. You can download the PDF of the talk.
http://hicksdesign.co.uk/journal/icons-for-interaction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helveticons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/helveticons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/helveticons/</guid>
      <description>Helveticons are royalty-free vector icons, glyphs and symbols based on the Helvetica Bold typeface. http://helveticons.ch/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended License Agreement added for EPS Wireframe Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/extended-license-agreement-added-eps-wireframe-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/extended-license-agreement-added-eps-wireframe-icons/</guid>
      <description>An Extended License Agreement option has been added for use on commercial web sites and web apps. The Standard Royalty Free (RF) License allows for use on commercial web sites and print collateral. Purchase with this option if you plan to use the icons in Wireframes, personal, private use, and use on commercial sites. This license does not cover commercial web services and apps that utilize the icons.
The Extended Royalty Free (ERF) License permits use on commercial web apps and services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons, Royalty Free, EPS and PNG</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-royalty-free-eps-and-png/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-royalty-free-eps-and-png/</guid>
      <description>Based on demand to use the wireframe icons on web sites, and to use them in Adobe Illustrator and Visio, I&amp;rsquo;ve created EPS and PNG versions that include a Royalty Free license agreement. You may use them in your UX documents, but the license also permits you to use them in web sites. There are restrictions for use on commercial products or commercial applications that offer products
or services for sale or for fee-based usage, however.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons for Axure RP Pro</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-axure-rp-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-axure-rp-pro/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the great feedback from a few new readers and colleagues, and with a little help from Axure, the Konigi Store now offers the wireframe icons for Axure RP Pro. This is the same set of icons offered in the OmniGraffle stencil, formatted as an Axure library that you can import into your widgets panel. As with the OG set, this is priced at a super low $10 with lifetime upgrades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons Updated (v. 1.2)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-12/</guid>
      <description>The wireframe icons have been updated to add a bunch of new icons and crop the PNGs to 16 x 16 px. Still recession priced at $10, with lifetime free upgrades. If you own this set, go to your account page and click the &amp;ldquo;Files&amp;rdquo; link.
New icons: home, currency symbols, light bulb, hour glass, bell, rubber stamp, text tool, drawing tool, layout, calculator, medal, ribbon, puzzle piece/plugin, key, asterisk/new, wand/wizard, music, exit, pagination arrows, mobile phone, iPhone, happy face, and sad face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons Updated (v. 1.1): PNGs and new icons added</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-11-pngs-and-new-icons-added/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-11-pngs-and-new-icons-added/</guid>
      <description>The Wireframe Icons have been updated. PNG versions and contact sheet has been added for all icons. New icons including User (silhouette from front), Groups, Microphone, Clock, Phone, Printer, Power, TV Widescreen, Remote controls, Volume, alternate versions of Cart and Image, and much more have been added. Additionally, some icons have been modified for stylistic consistency. If you&amp;rsquo;ve previously purchased these icons, you can update your set by logging in and heading to your Account page where you will see a &amp;ldquo;Files&amp;rdquo; link under your user name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-icons/</guid>
      <description>The Konigi OmniGraffle Wireframe Icon Set is a set of grayscale cursors and icons that come in handy when designing wireframes, aka user interface schematics. This product includes a standard set of cursors, and many of the icons you need for the design of web-based user interfaces.
This set of icons is designed to work well with your wireframe stencils. You&amp;rsquo;ll find rich text editor controls, file system actions, social interaction symbols, ratings and voting, and a host of other icons for most of the behaviors you may want to communicate with an icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realmac Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/realmac-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/realmac-software/</guid>
      <description>Realmac Software is the maker of LittleSnapper and RapidWeaver apps for the Macintosh. Their site sports the kind of clean rounded corners and beveled edges we come to associate with Apple, but brings in a more colorful and rich palette with excellent illustrations and product icons throughout. Glassy reflective marquees melt into the 2 column product info below, and big icons and buttons make clear targets for calls to action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Beautiful Icon Sets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/50-beautiful-icon-sets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/50-beautiful-icon-sets/</guid>
      <description>Noupe rounds up their &amp;ldquo;50 most beautiful icon sets of 2008.&amp;ldquo;.
http://www.noupe.com/icons/50-most-beautiful-icon-sets-created-in-2008.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebIconSets.com: The Best Free Web Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/webiconsetscom-best-free-web-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/webiconsetscom-best-free-web-icons/</guid>
      <description>WebIconSets.com lists the best icon sets suitable for web use. All the icon sets are of professional quality and free to use in your own projects.
http://www.webiconsets.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sesame Street</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/sesame-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/sesame-street/</guid>
      <description>The Sesame Workshop and PBS produce excellent Flash sites for kids. Among my favorites are the Sesame Street and Arthur sites. The recent redesign of the Sesame Street site adds new navigation options, a more YouTube-like video section, and most notably, user profiles. The best of the new features is the ability to add favorites to &amp;ldquo;Your Street,&amp;rdquo; a user profile page that uses your favorites to display a start page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Icons and Controls Set Coming</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-icons-and-controls-set-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-icons-and-controls-set-coming/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been accumulating a bunch of icons and other miscellaneous controls in my OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencil and think it&amp;rsquo;s about time to separate those into their own stencil set. The icons you see here are some of the ones I plan to include in this new set. Any others you&amp;rsquo;d like to see here that aren&amp;rsquo;t already represented? These are the ones I&amp;rsquo;ve actually had to use in the past 3 or 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icon Design Explained (Quickly)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/icon-design-explained-quickly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/icon-design-explained-quickly/</guid>
      <description>Jon Hicks describes his guidelines and workflow when creating icons.
http://www.hicksdesign.co.uk/journal/icon-design-explained-quickly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Icon Sets on deviantART</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/beautiful-icon-sets-deviantart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/beautiful-icon-sets-deviantart/</guid>
      <description>Noupe curates a list of 40 free icon sets showcased in the deviantART icons gallery.
http://www.noupe.com/freebie/40-extremely-beautifull-icon-sets-hand-picked-from-deviantart.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icojoy</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/icojoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/icojoy/</guid>
      <description>http://www.icojoy.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand Spanking New Mini Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/brand-spanking-new-mini-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/brand-spanking-new-mini-icons/</guid>
      <description>This set of 113 free 10x10px grayscale mini icons from Brand Spanking New is a nice set of small, unobtrusive icons that can function inline with text or in places where smaller type might be used, e.g. with metadata. This is not a new set of icons, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to start collecting examples of icons here.
http://www.brandspankingnew.net/archive/2006/12/hohoho.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Mistakes in Icon Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-mistakes-icon-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-mistakes-icon-design/</guid>
      <description>Denis Kortunov provides a nice illustrated list of common mistakes in icon design.
 Insufficient differentiation between icons Too many elements in one icon Unnecessary elements Lack of unity of style within a set of icons Unnecessary perspective and shadows in small icons Overly original metaphors National or social characteristics not being taken into account Images of real interface elements in icons Text inside icons Outside the pixel framework</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/flow/</guid>
      <description>Extendmac&amp;rsquo;s Flow is an FTP application. The slick effect of that gorgeous wave form in the header and footer, and the nice illustrations and icons on the Features page make this site design enviable.
http://extendmac.com/flow</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>