<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>personas on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/personas/</link><description>Recent content in personas on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/personas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Understand Your Users with Personas</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-understand-your-users-personas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-understand-your-users-personas/</guid><description>Brad Colbow and Indi Young explain personas using comics on Carsonified.
http://carsonified.com/blog/design/how-to-understand-your-users-with-personas/</description></item><item><title>User Research for Personas and Other Audience Models</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-research-personas-and-other-audience-models/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-research-personas-and-other-audience-models/</guid><description>In UX Matters, Steve Baty describes the user research methodologies we can draw on when creating audience models and some alternative ways of communicating the results of an audience analysis.
http://www.uxmatters.com/mt/archives/2009/04/user-research-for-personas-and-other-audience-models.php</description></item><item><title>zef[a]media UX Templates</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</guid><description>zef[a]media's UX Template package contains sample paper prototypes/wireframes, personas, sitemaps, and user flow diagrams. Requires MS Visio, Word, and Excel.
http://www.zefamedia.com/websites/free-ux-templates/</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle UX Template Update (v. 2.4)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-update-v-24/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-update-v-24/</guid><description>The OmniGraffle UX Template has been updated. I finally got around to cleaning up the Persona example from the old version 1 (the urlgreyhot version), added a detailed persona, a site map example with diagramming style (.gdiagramstyle file), and a mental model example. Download from the Tools page.
//konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description></item><item><title>Cooper Shows How to Do Low Fi Concept Demos</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</guid><description>The Drawing Board: Commuter Buddy from Cooper Journal on Vimeo. Cooper Interactive's Commuter Buddy concept video is another great find via Dave Malouf's Engage blog. You might have already seen this one, but as Dave points out, it is a great example of using personas, narrative, and really low fidelity sketches to demonstrate a concept.
The video above uses still photography, super-imposed photos of whiteboard drawings, and voice over narrative to describe the idea for a mobile phone application that helps a commuter to get to his ride on time, and even to remember to get off if he becomes engrossed in an article, for instance.</description></item><item><title>Todd Warfel's Persona Templates</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/todd-warfels-persona-templates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/todd-warfels-persona-templates/</guid><description>Todd Warfel has posted templates for his data-driven personas. The main file is an InDesign (INDD) file and the visual chart is in Illustrator file. Both are made with CS4.
http://zakiwarfel.com/archives/persona-templates/</description></item><item><title>Designing for One User (Bespoke User Interfaces)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-one-user-bespoke-user-interfaces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-one-user-bespoke-user-interfaces/</guid><description>Chris Fahey discusses the merits of bespoke UI design, referencing the successful design of John King's touch wall which was created for King by Perceptive Pixel. Bespoke design--the practice of designing something specifically for and individual--might be more prevalent in the digital world than most people realize. The examples provided out in the quotes of software designers and developers point out the most common case where this is happening. Designers who design products by focusing on what they want/need for themselves is common enough.</description></item></channel></rss>