<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>inline forms on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/inline-forms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in inline forms on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/inline-forms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelley Blue Book Mad Libs Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kelley-blue-book-mad-libs-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kelley-blue-book-mad-libs-form/</guid>
      <description>The Kelley Blue Book features Mad Libs-style inline form elements for its contact form. The contact form, which was previously displayed with right-aligned labels adjacent to to left aligned fields, is now displayed as an inline form with &amp;quot;fill in the blanks&amp;quot; style prompts for input.
 http://www.kbb.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huffduffer Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/huffduffer-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/huffduffer-registration/</guid>
      <description>Huffduffer, a hybrid bookmarking/podcast service features a whimsical inline registration form that&#39;s formatted in sentences with blank areas that the user fills out with their name, password, etc. Kind of a fun, unexpected way to format the form. Reminds me of the kinds of forms you&#39;d fill out by hand in days of old, which goes with the retro style of the site.
Via SwissMiss.
 http://huffduffer.com/signup/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise 2.0 Conference Inline Login Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/enterprise-2-0-conference-inline-login-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/enterprise-2-0-conference-inline-login-form/</guid>
      <description>The Enterprise 2.0 Conference site, which is run on Jive Clearspace, provides an inline form for logging into the site. Clicking the Login link in the header replaces the header content with a form where inputs and labels are displayed in a single row.
1. Header global navigation with login link.2. Clicking login link replaces the navigation bar with the inline login form. http://community.e2conf.com/index.jspa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Inline Login Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/konigi-inline-login-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/konigi-inline-login-form/</guid>
      <description>Seems strange to feature this site here, but I&#39;m building up a set of this inline form design convention. Konigi provides an unobtrusive control for logging in via the user&#39;s site login/password or Open ID login in a utility navigation area. Clicking one of these log in links allows the user to enter their credentials without navigating to a form on a separate page.
1. Header with login options in utility nav on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
