<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>information design on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/information-design/</link><description>Recent content in information design on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/information-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>visualizing.org</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/visualizingorg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/visualizingorg/</guid><description>Visualizing.org looks like an exciting new community devoted to information design and sensemaking--making sense of complex issues through data and design. An excerpt from their about page describes the site:
It's a place to showcase work, get feedback, ensure that your work is seen by lots of people and gets used by teachers, journalists, and conference organizers to help educate the public about various world issues. Visualizing is also a free resource to search for data.</description></item><item><title>Tableau Public: Visualization Service</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/tableau-public-visualization-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/tableau-public-visualization-service/</guid><description>Tableau Public is a free service that lets anyone publish interactive data to the web. Once on the web, anyone can interact with the data, download it, or create their own visualizations of it. No programming skills are required. Windows is required for the desktop application.
The free version of Tableau Public is for writers, bloggers, students, professors, hobbyists, journeymen, critics, citizens and more. It’s also meant for organizations, but only as an introductory service, and for continued use requires commercial licensing.</description></item><item><title>InfoGraphic Designs: Overview, Examples and Best Practices</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/infographic-designs-overview-examples-and-best-practices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/infographic-designs-overview-examples-and-best-practices/</guid><description>Anders Ross provides a definition, brief history, and best practices for designing infographics followed by a huge number of example screenshots. View them all at Infoshift.
http://www.instantshift.com/2009/06/07/infographic-designs-overview-examples-and-best-practices/</description></item><item><title>The Browser Wars</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/browser-wars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/browser-wars/</guid><description>Cool infographic from Pixel Labs depicting the Browser wars, based on W3 Schools Browser Stats. Reminds me of the "Napoleon's March" graphic in Tufte's book.
http://www.pixellabs.com/images/browserwars.png</description></item><item><title>NY Times Visualization Lab</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ny-times-visualization-lab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ny-times-visualization-lab/</guid><description>The New York Times teams up with IBM's Many Eyes project to provide word visualizations of data in the Vizlab.
http://vizlab.nytimes.com/</description></item><item><title>A Periodic Table of Visualization Methods</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/periodic-table-visualization-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/periodic-table-visualization-methods/</guid><description>This is a neat table listing and categorizing visualization methods from the folks at Visual Literacy
http://www.visual-literacy.org/periodic_table/periodic_table.html</description></item><item><title>Everymoment Now News Visualization</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/everymoment-now-news-visualization/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/everymoment-now-news-visualization/</guid><description>everymomentnow is a beautiful news visualization site designed and developed by Craig Mod. The idea is to provide a sense of volume and correlation between keywords within a given subject area. The current incarnation focuses on Obama/McCain in the news. The clean, minimalist interface allows the user to visualize spikes in news article occurrences for each keyword a the highest level. You choose a single focal point using a keyword (e.</description></item><item><title>Information Design Patterns</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/information-design-patterns/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/information-design-patterns/</guid><description>Christian Behrens' information design pattern repository collects solutions for "...the display, behavior, and user interaction of complex infographics. The collection is available in the form of a 200-page book that additionally includes a profound historical record of information design as well as an introduction inthe research field of design patterns."
http://niceone.org/infodesign/</description></item><item><title>iPhone versus tPhone</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/iphone-versus-tphone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/iphone-versus-tphone/</guid><description>Edward Tufte posted an essay and video with commentary about the iPhone. Tufte is complimentary, for the most part, about the interface being predominantly free of administrative debris, but makes suggestions for how the iPhone can make better use of its screen resolution. As expected, his argument calls for more data density when possible.
He notes that the iPhone has elegantly removed administrative clutter in many places, using the information as the interface.</description></item></channel></rss>