<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>email on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/email/</link>
    <description>Recent content in email on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Persona Email Client Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/persona-email-client-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/persona-email-client-prototype/</guid>
      <description>Persona is a concept for a theoretical email client prototyped by Ali Seçkin Karayol, Marco Triverio, and Harsha Vardhan at the Copenhagen Institute of Interaction Design. The prototype focusses email on people or conversations rather than presenting the typical data-dense tabular view of messages. The attachment view also offers a nice way of viewing all attached files in a gallery presentation. There are some compelling ideas for re-imagining the focus of email consumption here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of an Apple Email</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/anatomy-apple-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/anatomy-apple-email/</guid>
      <description>Peldi tipped me to this graphic deconstructing one of Apple&#39;s promotional emails.
http://www.flowtown.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2011/01/110110-FLOW-APPLE.png</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to CSS support in email clients</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/guide-css-support-email-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/guide-css-support-email-clients/</guid>
      <description>Campaign Monitor provides a table showing the level of CSS support in the 23 different email clients they test, and covers all the popular applications across desktop, web and mobile email. The web-based version of the guide focusses on the 10 most popular email clients on the market, and they provide a complete report on all 23 email clients in PDF format.
http://www.campaignmonitor.com/css/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Gmail Client Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>I posted on Twitter about how frustrating it can be to have to use email. With every day that I use Twitter via Twhirl I become less and less interested in using email. So I moaned to my Twitter peeps about the pain I feel. Some people wanted to know what I wanted, so I responded with the ideal flow, using Mac OS X&#39;s Growl alerting app as the starting point:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twilert - Twitter search alerts via email</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twilert-twitter-search-alerts-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twilert-twitter-search-alerts-email/</guid>
      <description>Twilert is an email alert/notification service for Twitter. Just enter any brand, product, service, or any keyword. Via SwissMiss
http://www.twilert.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Loses Users&#39; Email Notification Settings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-loses-users-email-notification-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-loses-users-email-notification-settings/</guid>
      <description>I got this in my email from Facebook. Unfortunately, the settings that control which email notifications get sent to you were lost. We&#39;re sorry for the inconvenience.
 Wow. Really? I agree with what M. David Peterson had to say about the issue. Sounds like they&#39;ve got some inexperienced engineers running the show. If this had been a web service with critical data that wasn&#39;t backed up, people would be pretty pissed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Standards Project</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/email-standards-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/email-standards-project/</guid>
      <description>The Email Standards Project is a community effort to ensure that emails render consistently. Similar to the Web Standards Project, the Email Standards Project community works with email client developers and the design community to improve web standards support and accessibility in email.
http://www.email-standards.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google have been doing some work getting some of their interfaces to be consistent with each other. GMail and Blogger now provide similar interface behaviors and controls, with slight differences. Other applications like Google Sites and Docs continue to have different controls.
Gmail and Blogger are among the simplest of these text editor interfaces, for good reason. In blogs and email, rich text formatting should be bare bones and out of the way as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Mail Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-mail-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-mail-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Mail&#39;s rich text editor in the composition form is clean and provides the core set of formatting options you&#39;d need. The implementation is simple and intuitive. A few things they do differently include: rolling some commonly visible controls into drop down menus, e.g. text alignment and list style blocks.
1. Font face selection and font size are in HTML form selects. 2. Font color selection. Highlight or background color uses the same color selection control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr Sharing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Flickr have added a sharing interface for their photos and videos. Presumably this is because of the introduction of videos into the ecosystem. The interface is provided via an unobtrusive link that uses AJAX to display contextual menus when clicked.
Prior to the introduction of this interface, users had to go to click the &#34;All Sizes&#34; link to find URLs for the item.
1. &amp;quot;Share This&amp;quot; button appears to the right of photo or video title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Form Auto-completion</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/facebook-form-auto-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/facebook-form-auto-completion/</guid>
      <description>Facebook&#39;s address auto-completion in the compose message form is one of the best examples of auto-completion behavior in a form. The interaction very closely mimics what you would expect to happen in the To field of email applications like Apple Mail and Outlook.
1. Cursor is in the To: field. Contextual help displayed below input.2. Typing characters in the input invokes person/recipient auto-completion suggestions. 3. Selecting a person from auto-completion suggestions, entering a comma, or clicking enter displays the selected recipient in a block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litmus: Test your email and website designs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/litmus-test-your-email-and-website-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/litmus-test-your-email-and-website-designs/</guid>
      <description>Litmus provides testing of web sites and email messages across all browser and email platforms for a fee.
http://litmusapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
