<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sketching on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/sketching/</link><description>Recent content in sketching on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 11:15:21 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/sketching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sketch Zine</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/sketch-zine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 11:15:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/sketch-zine/</guid><description>A little zine made form my UI Sketching talk.</description></item><item><title>5.25 Inch Floppy Sketchbook Is Back</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 12:06:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</guid><description>Remember these? From 2009-2010 I these sketchbooks for a while, using a 5.25&amp;quot; floppy disk as a notebook cover. I kind of missed them, so I made a limited number in blank and grid paper.
It’s a wirebound 5.25 inch square sketchbook with about 120-130 pages (60-65 sheets) of 70 pound white vellum paper, hand-crafted by me in my home North of the SF Bay. You can buy a book with blank sheets or one printed with 1cm grid in warm gray ink.</description></item><item><title>Astropad: Use iPad as Mac Graphics Tablet</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</guid><description>&lt;div class="video">&lt;iframe width="853" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ouwCHT3rGRY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen>&lt;/iframe>&lt;/div>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://astropad.com/">AstroPad&lt;/a> turns your iPad into a Mac graphics tablet, mirroring a section of your Mac's screen when connected via WiFi or USB. Once connected you can sketch/draw on the tablet with an iPad stylus or finger. It will operate pretty much like a Wacom graphics tablet when you're using a Desktop graphics app with a drawing tool like Pixelmator, Photoshop, or Sketchbook Pro. &lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Experimenting with the IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</guid><description>I got an IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard System ($149 retail price) to demo and did a first little experiment. The product consists of a video sensor and interactive pen. You have to have a projector as well. Here's a super rough demo I made for my team at Balsamiq to show how it would work using Balsamiq Mockups.
While the demo is pretty rough given the 15 minutes I gave myself to set up and record with my phone, it's pretty interesting to consider the possibilities for whiteboarding with wireframing software, if you're so inclined.</description></item><item><title>Ridley Scott Demystifies the Art of Storyboarding</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ridley-scott-demystifies-art-storyboarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ridley-scott-demystifies-art-storyboarding/</guid><description>Ridley Scott, director of Alien and Blade Runner, talks about the importance of fast thumbnail sketching and storyboards in helping him make movies. Scott discusses how storyboards help him capture the imagery of scenes, and how talking through storyboards prepare the creative team by establishing a direction for what they intend to create. Read more at the article on Open Culture.
Via Ian Smile.
http://www.openculture.com/2012/05/ridley_scott_demystifies_the_art_of_storyboarding.html</description></item><item><title>Sticky Jots</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</guid><description>Sticky Jots is a set of storytelling sticky note paper and paper prototyping kits for designing mobile and tablet interfaces. The product is designed by Rae Milne and Pamela Jue, two grad students in the SVA Interaction Design program.
Pam writes about the thinking behind Sticky Jots. The idea came from our constant prototyping and ideation process in almost every project this semester. While it’s great to do, it’s still frustrating how time consuming it can be.</description></item><item><title>Protosketch</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</guid><description>Protosketch is a new free app for iOS from UI Stencils to convert sketches to interactive prototypes. The app is made to work with their sketch pads and stencils. Sketch your screens, add them to the app, define hot areas for links, select link destinations, and prototype.
https://protosketch.uistencils.com</description></item><item><title>Responsive Sketch Pad from UI Stencils</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</guid><description>UI Stencils' responsive design sketchpad is made to help figure out breakpoints and how your product might translate to mobile and tablet versions. 2 device silhouettes on the front and 3 on the back. 50 pages on 70# paper in Letter or A4.
http://www.uistencils.com/products/responsive-sketch-pad</description></item><item><title>IPEVO Ziggi Review</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</guid><description>Have you ever done the dance of holding a sketch up to your computer's webcam or taken pictures of them with your iPhone to email to yourself or to colleagues? I've done that sort of thing for all of the years that I've worked remotely on design and development teams, because scanners get tired real fast. Frustrated with this process, I had largely given up, until a few months ago when I was looking for tools to share work on paper between students and teachers.</description></item><item><title>Sketching Interfaces: Speaking notes and mini book</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/sketching-interfaces-speaking-notes-and-mini-book/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/sketching-interfaces-speaking-notes-and-mini-book/</guid><description>I gave a talk at Asbury Agile 2012 and have published my presentation deck and speaking notes as a zine-like mini book in a new section of this site. My friends on Instagram have seen me teasing out this talk for a few months now, and I'm happy to get the ideas out because this is something I've been thinking about ever since I started this site. This is the perspective of someone who is starting over and taking the beginners path.</description></item><item><title>The Sketch Book</title><link>https://konigi.com/design/sketch-book/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/design/sketch-book/</guid><description>This is a small journal and mini book about the approach I take when sketching for interface and interaction design. I'm writing this as I enter what I think may be my 17th year making web sites. The only thing I can say with each passing year is that what I know is still so very little compared to what I have yet to learn. Each time I learn of a new way of working I feel energized and excited about the work I do.</description></item><item><title>Whitelines Link</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</guid><description>Everyone's getting in on on the physical paper capturing game using the iPhone's camera. Whitelines is one of my favorite sketch paper makers. They make great graph paper that reverses the grid using white lines over pale a gray paper. The result is that the grid it more subtle and less distracting
The Whitelines Link product is a free iPhone app that let's you capture sketches made on their new Whitelines Link papers.</description></item><item><title>Evernote Smart Notebook by Moleskine</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</guid><description>I've tried a lot of tools for transferring sketches from analog sketchbook to digital. I was an early Pen-It user, have used page cutters with a scanner, and have lately just resorted to taking photos with my iPhone. The Evernote/Moleskine Smart Notebook looks like it might provide the right mix I'm looking for.
I've given up on the idea of converting paper sketches to vector drawings. What this seems to offer is the ability to use that dotted sheet tech to correctly line up your photos taken with Evernote app, and combines that with some neat stickers that will automatically route your sketches to tags and/or specific notebooks.</description></item><item><title>New sketch gear at JetPens: Maruman sketchbooks</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/new-sketch-gear-jetpens-maruman-sketchbooks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/new-sketch-gear-jetpens-maruman-sketchbooks/</guid><description>People still occasionally ask me if I make the small bound Wireframe Sketchbooks, but I stopped selling them after a few years, and instead just posted instructions for how to make your own. I know that few people have the time or interest to do that, so I've been looking at alternatives for them.
A month ago, Brad from JetPens contacted me to tell me that he started supplying a sketchbook from Maruman that I might like.</description></item><item><title>Pencil Bandoliers for Journals and Sketchbooks</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/pencil-bandoliers-journals-and-sketchbooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/pencil-bandoliers-journals-and-sketchbooks/</guid><description>I'm in love with this Journal Bandolier made of recycled bike inner tubes, made by Cleverhands and sold on Etsy. The bandolier is a strap fitted with small loops for carrying pens, pencils, and other handy tools wrapped around a journal, planner, or other book. I ordered one for the small 3.5&amp;quot; wide Moleskine. Bandoliers for other notebook sizes available as well.
http://www.etsy.com/listing/80431666/mini-bandolier-replace-your-pencil-case</description></item></channel></rss>