<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sketching on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/sketching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sketching on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 11:15:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/sketching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch Zine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-zine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 11:15:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-zine/</guid>
      <description>This is a little zine I made from my Sketch talk.
I&amp;rsquo;m putting these in the package when people buy a sketchbook. I&amp;rsquo;ll be sending one out soon to everyone who already purchased a book. Still working on setting up international shipping. :)

A little zine has been something I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to make. This is a zine in the traditional, DIY photocopy sense. It&amp;rsquo;s not an art piece, as so many beautiful zines are these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5.25 Inch Floppy Sketchbook Is Back</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 12:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</guid>
      <description>Remember these? From 2009-2010 I these sketchbooks for a while, using a 5.25&amp;rdquo; floppy disk as a notebook cover. I kind of missed them, so I made a limited number in blank and grid paper.
It’s a wirebound 5.25 inch square sketchbook with about 120-130 pages (60-65 sheets) of 70 pound white vellum paper, hand-crafted by me in my home North of the SF Bay. You can buy a book with blank sheets or one printed with 1cm grid in warm gray ink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astropad: Use iPad as Mac Graphics Tablet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;video&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&#34;853&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ouwCHT3rGRY&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://astropad.com/&#34;&gt;AstroPad&lt;/a&gt; turns your iPad into a Mac graphics tablet, mirroring a section of your Mac&amp;rsquo;s screen when connected via WiFi or USB. Once connected you can sketch/draw on the tablet with an iPad stylus or finger. It will operate pretty much like a Wacom graphics tablet when you&amp;rsquo;re using a Desktop graphics app with a drawing tool like Pixelmator, Photoshop, or Sketchbook Pro. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sticker UI Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sticker-ui-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sticker-ui-book/</guid>
      <description>The Sticker UI Book is a UI design sketchbook that with templates (web, mobile, and storyboard) and UI element stickers, being produced by Jennifer Williams and Brandy Bora of Killer Inc. You can order one via their Kickstarter campaign which ends Oct 30 2014 7:44 AM PDT. http://stickerui.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimenting with the IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>I got an IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard System ($149 retail price) to demo and did a first little experiment. The product consists of a video sensor and interactive pen. You have to have a projector as well. Here&#39;s a super rough demo I made for my team at Balsamiq to show how it would work using Balsamiq Mockups.
 While the demo is pretty rough given the 15 minutes I gave myself to set up and record with my phone, it&#39;s pretty interesting to consider the possibilities for whiteboarding with wireframing software, if you&#39;re so inclined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridley Scott Demystifies the Art of Storyboarding</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ridley-scott-demystifies-art-storyboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ridley-scott-demystifies-art-storyboarding/</guid>
      <description>Ridley Scott, director of Alien and Blade Runner, talks about the importance of fast thumbnail sketching and storyboards in helping him make movies. Scott discusses how storyboards help him capture the imagery of scenes, and how talking through storyboards prepare the creative team by establishing a direction for what they intend to create. Read more at the article on Open Culture.
Via Ian Smile.
http://www.openculture.com/2012/05/ridley_scott_demystifies_the_art_of_storyboarding.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Jots</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</guid>
      <description>Sticky Jots is a set of storytelling sticky note paper and paper prototyping kits for designing mobile and tablet interfaces. The product is designed by Rae Milne and Pamela Jue, two grad students in the SVA Interaction Design program. 
Pam writes about the thinking behind Sticky Jots. The idea came from our constant prototyping and ideation process in almost every project this semester. While it’s great to do, it’s still frustrating how time consuming it can be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protosketch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</guid>
      <description>Protosketch is a new free app for iOS from UI Stencils to convert sketches to interactive prototypes. The app is made to work with their sketch pads and stencils. Sketch your screens, add them to the app, define hot areas for links, select link destinations, and prototype.
https://protosketch.uistencils.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive Sketch Pad from UI Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</guid>
      <description>UI Stencils&amp;rsquo; responsive design sketchpad is made to help figure out breakpoints and how your product might translate to mobile and tablet versions. 2 device silhouettes on the front and 3 on the back. 50 pages on 70# paper in Letter or A4.
http://www.uistencils.com/products/responsive-sketch-pad</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPEVO Ziggi Review</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever done the dance of holding a sketch up to your computer&amp;rsquo;s webcam or taken pictures of them with your iPhone to email to yourself or to colleagues? I&amp;rsquo;ve done that sort of thing for all of the years that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked remotely on design and development teams, because scanners get tired real fast. Frustrated with this process, I had largely given up, until a few months ago when I was looking for tools to share work on paper between students and teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketching Interfaces: Speaking notes and mini book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketching-interfaces-speaking-notes-and-mini-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketching-interfaces-speaking-notes-and-mini-book/</guid>
      <description>I gave a talk at Asbury Agile 2012 and have published my presentation deck and speaking notes as a zine-like mini book in a new section of this site. My friends on Instagram have seen me teasing out this talk for a few months now, and I&#39;m happy to get the ideas out because this is something I&#39;ve been thinking about ever since I started this site. This is the perspective of someone who is starting over and taking the beginners path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sketch Book</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/articles/sketch-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/articles/sketch-book/</guid>
      <description>This is a small journal and mini book about the approach I take when sketching for interface and interaction design. I&#39;m writing this as I enter what I think may be my 17th year making web sites. The only thing I can say with each passing year is that what I know is still so very little compared to what I have yet to learn. Each time I learn of a new way of working I feel energized and excited about the work I do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whitelines Link</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</guid>
      <description>Everyone&amp;rsquo;s getting in on on the physical paper capturing game using the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s camera. Whitelines is one of my favorite sketch paper makers. They make great graph paper that reverses the grid using white lines over pale a gray paper. The result is that the grid it more subtle and less distracting
The Whitelines Link product is a free iPhone app that let&amp;rsquo;s you capture sketches made on their new Whitelines Link papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Smart Notebook by Moleskine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried a lot of tools for transferring sketches from analog sketchbook to digital. I was an early Pen-It user, have used page cutters with a scanner, and have lately just resorted to taking photos with my iPhone. The Evernote/Moleskine Smart Notebook looks like it might provide the right mix I&amp;rsquo;m looking for.
I&#39;ve given up on the idea of converting paper sketches to vector drawings. What this seems to offer is the ability to use that dotted sheet tech to correctly line up your photos taken with Evernote app, and combines that with some neat stickers that will automatically route your sketches to tags and/or specific notebooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New sketch gear at JetPens: Maruman sketchbooks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-sketch-gear-jetpens-maruman-sketchbooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-sketch-gear-jetpens-maruman-sketchbooks/</guid>
      <description>People still occasionally ask me if I make the small bound Wireframe Sketchbooks, but I stopped selling them after a few years, and instead just posted instructions for how to make your own. I know that few people have the time or interest to do that, so I&#39;ve been looking at alternatives for them.
A month ago, Brad from JetPens contacted me to tell me that he started supplying a sketchbook from Maruman that I might like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchbooks: DIY Instructions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbooks-diy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbooks-diy/</guid>
      <description>This is a guide for binding your own sketchbooks. I offer it to you designers, developers, makers, and tinkerers out there who are looking for a way to physically connect to your practice of designing interfaces, or who maybe just want a fun and practical way to get your hands dirty.
I started making my own sketchbooks and pads a few years ago. At the time there weren&#39;t many options for interface sketching and storyboarding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencil Bandoliers for Journals and Sketchbooks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pencil-bandoliers-journals-and-sketchbooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pencil-bandoliers-journals-and-sketchbooks/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in love with this Journal Bandolier made of recycled bike inner tubes, made by Cleverhands and sold on Etsy. The bandolier is a strap fitted with small loops for carrying pens, pencils, and other handy tools wrapped around a journal, planner, or other book. I ordered one for the small 3.5&amp;quot; wide Moleskine. Bandoliers for other notebook sizes available as well.
http://www.etsy.com/listing/80431666/mini-bandolier-replace-your-pencil-case</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper 2011 Update</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-2011-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-2011-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 years since I updated the printable graph paper PDFs I provide for user interface design sketching. You can download the printable PDFs from here. (Yes, I use the word &amp;quot;Here&amp;quot; in links.)
In the last year I&#39;ve gotten a lot of requests to replenish the inventory of wireframe and storyboard graphpaper notepads that I fulfilled via Amazon.com, and the wirebound sketch books. I feel bummed every time I tell people that I decided to get out of that little business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Smith ID Sketch Demos on Core77</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jeff-smith-id-sketch-demos-core77/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jeff-smith-id-sketch-demos-core77/</guid>
      <description>I could watch Jeff Smith sketching with a Sharpie all day. Core 77 featured Smith, principal/Design Director at Reflex Design, doing sketch demos for the students at Virginia Tech&#39;s ID department.
 More on the Core 77 Boards.
http://www.core77.com/blog/tools/forum_frenzy_sketch_demos_from_blaster701_19745.asp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Invest in Sketching?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/why-invest-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/why-invest-sketching/</guid>
      <description>Jumping in and immediately starting to build the product, even if it does get completed and ship, is almost guaranteed to produce a mediocre product in which there is little innovation or market differentiation. When you have only one kick at the can, the behaviour of the entire team and process is as predictable as it will be pedestrian.
&amp;#8212;Bill Buxton in Sketching the User Experience
Buxton writes in this passage on the impact of iterative sketching on risk, exploration and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Stickynotes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-stickynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-stickynotes/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had a UX Stickynotes pad near me for a few weeks to play with. I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a sticky notes nerd. I mostly like to place them in sketchbooks to mark and annotate, but also like them for brainstorming and doing info organization exercises. Sticky notes for UI sketches and sketchboards makes sense.
The sticky notes are A5 sized, with light non-photo blue dot grid, and the browser version has 960gs markers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Sketchboards in Mockups</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/creating-sketchboards-mockups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/creating-sketchboards-mockups/</guid>
      <description>Sketching interfaces is a path focussed on generating many ideas and finding the right design. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about how to adapt the activity of physically sketching on paper to get the same results in Mockups. On the Balsamiq UX blog, I wrote about a technique I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with to do sketchboards in Mockups using a Symbols library. http://blogs.balsamiq.com/ux/2011/04/28/sketching-in-mockups/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a nice day</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/have-nice-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/have-nice-day/</guid>
      <description>Don&#39;t let anyone tell you that the tools you choose are wrong or inappropriate. Find the right design and keep winning.
Occasionally I&#39;m asked to provide an opinion about a topic that people think I should have some authority to comment on for some reason. That topic, as you might guess, is wireframing.
I enjoy pointing people towards good resources, or helping them with a problem using a tool that I&#39;m familiar with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phonedoo: Dry erase iPhone sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo makes a nice iPhone UI sketching product called Phone Doos. They are 6.8&amp;quot; by 3.5&amp;quot; dry erase iPhone surfaces with faint grid lines and magnetic backing. A pack contains 10 Phone Doos.
I like that these gives you a surface to work on that can be re-arranged easily on a table and presented on a metallic wall. They have some good screenshots using them arranged on a whiteboard with flow arrows pointing between them, which is another thing that&#39;s probably much easier with these as opposed to using paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MORE/REAL Stylus Cap</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/morereal-stylus-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/morereal-stylus-cap/</guid>
      <description>Don Lehman&amp;rsquo;s MORE/REAL Stylus Cap is a cool iPad stylus project looking for funding via Kickstarter. The idea is to create a cap with a conductive tip that will fit over a Sharpie, Bic, or Fineliner pen. Lehman&amp;rsquo;s introductory video below shows the stylus cap at work.
 Looks fantastic and simple, and you&amp;rsquo;ll have one fewer thing to carry with you because it acts as pen and stylus. Sweet. You can help fund the project and reserve a cap by heading to the Kickstarter page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Dry Erase Board</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-dry-erase-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-dry-erase-board/</guid>
      <description>New sketching goodies hit the shelves at UI Stencils, from our good friends Design Commission. They&amp;rsquo;ve created an iPad dry erase board with dot grid, and updated their awesome iPhone sticky pads. Definitely want to get my hands on the dry erase board.
Update: 
Mine arrived and I have to say that this is the nicest dry erase board I have now. It&#39;s made on hard particle board, similar to what you&#39;d find on a clipboard, so it feels great in the hands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch, sketch, sketch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-sketch-sketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-sketch-sketch/</guid>
      <description>The sketch is not the end goal. The end goal of the drawing process is what you learn while sketching.
I&#39;m slowly getting back into the groove of reading blogs and updating this site after some time off to enjoy the first month with our new baby. I found 52 weeks&#39; recent post about sketching, and loved the encouraging reminder for UX designers. I&#39;ll quote, because Joshua Brewer says it so well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchnotes 2009 &amp; 2010: A book by Eva-Lotta Lamm</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchnotes-2009-2010-book-eva-lotta-lamm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchnotes-2009-2010-book-eva-lotta-lamm/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty incredible. Eva-Lotta Lamm&amp;rsquo;s self-published book contains 2 years&amp;rsquo; worth of illustrated sketchnotes from dozens of UX / Design events and conferences, featuring talks from over 100 speakers and panelists.
Some of the events covered in the book are UXweek 2009, d.construct 2010, Flash on the Beach 2010, UXcamp Europe 2010, offf 2010, UXcamp London, Internet Week Europe 2010, various London IA events and RSA talks.
The book contains notes from talks by Edward Tufte, Scott McCloud, Jesse James Garrett, Ryan Singer, Tim Berners-Lee, Stephen Fry, Dave Gray, Whitney Hess, Stephen Anderson, Andy Budd, Richard Rutter, Eric Reiss, Giles Colborne, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Stylus Roundup: And the winner is...</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-stylus-roundup-and-winner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-stylus-roundup-and-winner/</guid>
      <description>[Update: This review was updated after getting the latest version of the Stylus Socks.]
My search for the perfect stylus for sketching on the iPad is over. I&#39;ve tried ever stylus I could get my hands on. The three finalists that earned a space on my desk or pocket in the past year have been the iClooly, the Stylus Socks, and the Griffin Stylus for iPad.
Starting off on the wrong foot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking an iClooly iPad Stylus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-iclooly-ipad-stylus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-iclooly-ipad-stylus/</guid>
      <description>The iClooly is the pen I&amp;rsquo;ve been using most for quick sketches on the iPad, but for longer sketches and for drawing the handwritten font I&amp;rsquo;m making in iFontMaker, the short stick kind of sucks. Extending the iClooly stick is an easy hack that almost doesn&amp;rsquo;t merit a post: rip off the back, take apart a mechanical pencil, and mash the two together.
Verbose version: Remove the clicky end and the spring inside, making sure the brush is pressed down and the bristles exposed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note Table at IDEO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/note-table-ideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/note-table-ideo/</guid>
      <description>This notepad table is the coolest little piece of furniture. Looks like it was made for kids. Furniture you can draw on would be great in any studio lounging and waiting areas.
Via @balsamiqVal
http://www.flickr.com/photos/49333842@N00/2108954609/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Sketching Notation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-sketching-notation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-sketching-notation/</guid>
      <description>Jakub Linowski created a sketch annotation system for interaction design and provides a free downloadable PDF describing how to use it.
&amp;quot;The interactive sketching notation is an emerging visual language which affords the representation of interface states and event-based user actions. Through a few simple and standardized rules, what the user sees (drawn in greys and blacks) and does (drawn in red) are unified into a coherent sketching system. This unification of both interface and use, intends to enable designers to tell more powerful stories of interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketching Resources for User Experience Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketching-resources-user-experience-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketching-resources-user-experience-designers/</guid>
      <description>Catriona Cornett created a great list of sketching resources for user experience designers. Includes links to articles, tools, templates, presentations, videos, and examples.
Check it out and add more to the comments. Missing for me are the links to sketch apps for the iPad.
http://www.inspireux.com/2010/06/28/50-sketching-resources-for-user-experience-designers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Showcase</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-showcase/</guid>
      <description>Mike Lohrman&amp;rsquo;s Wireframe Showcase is a user-contributed wireframe and UI sketch gallery. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping, since there is some space on the individual pages for content, that we&amp;rsquo;ll see a little more discussion about process and design thinking here rather than mere visuals of design artifacts. It&amp;rsquo;s always good to see more people showing how they explore ideas with sketches and wireframes.
http://www.wireframeshowcase.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketching with the iClooly Stylus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketching-iclooly-stylus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketching-iclooly-stylus/</guid>
      <description>This seems the ideal solution for my iPad sketching needs. A few days ago, when I thought of hacking my Pogo Sketch, I started researching all of the options for creating my own drawing tool for the iPad&amp;rsquo;s capacitive touch screen, and was researching the styli that were available. I came across the odd design of the iClooly and thought I&amp;rsquo;d try it out of curiosity.
I had low expectations, but was surprised by how well it works for iPad sketching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking a Pogo Stylus for Smoother iPad Sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-pogo-stylus-smoother-ipad-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-pogo-stylus-smoother-ipad-sketching/</guid>
      <description>I blogged about what I thought could possibly make a better stylus recently and thought I&amp;rsquo;d sketch what I was thinking. The above picture shows how I think you could hack the Pogo Sketch stylus so it will glide a little more smoothly on the iPad screen. The capacitive foam creates a little too much friction to feel natural to me. I drilled a small hole in the foam and inserted a plastic nib from an old pressure-sensitive screen stylus into the center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-sketching/</guid>
      <description>Pen and paper are still superior, but iPad sketching is good enough to leave those behind.
The topic of UI sketching on the iPad is coming up pretty regularly for UI designers. People want to know how it feels and if it&#39;s going to replace pen/pencil and paper. After a few months using as many drawing apps as I can get my hands on, I find that it&#39;s more than adequate for UI sketching needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Sketch Group on Flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-sketch-group-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-sketch-group-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Because of @fred_beecher I setup this iPad Sketch Group on Flickr so we can share our UI sketches. I&#39;m going to slowly post what I work on there.
Freehand design sketching on the iPad is for UX designers. Any app that lets you do freehand user interface sketches, either using finger tips or a capacitive stylus like the Pogo Sketch is what we&#39;re sharing here. If you drop non-iPad sketches, they will be booted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fueledbycoffee iPad Sketch Blog</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fueledbycoffee-ipad-sketch-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fueledbycoffee-ipad-sketch-blog/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling people how much I dig Adobe&amp;rsquo;s free Ideas app and Autodesk Sketchbook Pro for sketching on the iPad. Craighton Berman&amp;rsquo;s Fueled by Coffee sketchblog will give you an idea of what sketches can look like using these tools. Ideas is super simple and smoothens your lines so things look naturally drawn.
I&#39;m really loving it. The adjustment is taking time, and it&#39;s not as quick as pen and paper, but it&#39;s slightly more natural using a Pogo Sketch Stylus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Application Sketch Template</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-application-sketch-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-application-sketch-template/</guid>
      <description>Oliver Waters released an iPad graph paper sketch template. 10px squared, with tick marks to indicate indicate the heights of the Status Bar, Navigation Bar, Split View (Landscape Only), Keyboard and Tab Bar. See also his iPhone sketch template.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/owaters/4501918517/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave Gray: Forms, fields and flows</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dave-gray-forms-fields-and-flows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dave-gray-forms-fields-and-flows/</guid>
      <description>I saw Dave Gray demonstrate his visual alphabet at SXSWi last year. If you haven&#39;t seen him demonstrate this, you might want to watch this video now. In the video he illustrates for us how sketching is just combining forms and lines, and all you really need to be able to come up with pictures is to see and use these basic shapes.
 See also Dave&#39;s Basic Rules for Napkin Sketching after you&#39;ve seen the above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All the Right Way to Wireframe Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/all-right-way-wireframe-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/all-right-way-wireframe-videos/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to capture all of the slides and videos into one entry to compare each of the guys&amp;rsquo; approaches. The right way? There isn&amp;rsquo;t one right way. That&amp;rsquo;s the point. The one thread that does carry through, however, is a general process of discovery/research, sketching/ideation, selection/refinement, visual design. Will Evans
   Todd Zaki Warfel

 Russ Unger
 Fred Beecher</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Beautiful Sketches for Website Prototypes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-beautiful-sketches-website-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-beautiful-sketches-website-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>woorkup.com has collected a set of beautifully executed sketches for prototypes.
http://woorkup.com/2009/12/28/10-beautiful-sketches-for-website-prototypes/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchnote Army</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchnote-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchnote-army/</guid>
      <description>Just discovered Mike Rohde&amp;rsquo;s Sketchnote Army.
Sketchnote Army is dedicated to finding and showcasing sketchnotes and sketchnoters from around the world, from events, conferences, workshops or wherever sketchnotes are captured or created. If you sketchnote, send your sketchnotes URL to Mike Rohde to have them featured there.
Via @katerutter
http://sketchnotearmy.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Bierut: 5 Secrets from 86 Notebooks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/michael-bierut-5-secrets-86-notebooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/michael-bierut-5-secrets-86-notebooks/</guid>
      <description>This is fantastic presentation from Pentagram&amp;rsquo;s Michael Bierut at The 99 Percent conference. Shows how a quiet, humble, and empathetic bedside manner can be such useful attributes in a designer.
Renowned graphic designer Michael Bierut claims that he&amp;rsquo;s not creative. Instead, he likens his job to that of a doctor who tends to patients – &amp;ldquo;the sicker, the better.&amp;rdquo; Digging into the 86 notebooks he&amp;rsquo;s kept over the course of his career, Bierut walks us through 5 projects – from original conception to final execution – extracting a handful of simple lessons (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools for Sketching User Experiences</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/tools-sketching-user-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/tools-sketching-user-experiences/</guid>
      <description>On UX Booth, Jason Robb shares the tools and techniques he uses for sketching user interfaces.
http://www.uxbooth.com/blog/tools-for-sketching-user-experiences/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk SketchBook Mobile Brings Sketching to iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-brings-sketching-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-brings-sketching-iphone/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had SketchBook Pro for the Mac for a few years now. I bought it before it was acquired by Autodesk from Alias, mostly for art work, but also to experiment with it as a tool for interface sketching. But while I wanted to use it more, I find myself falling back on paper and pencil almost all of the time. Autodesk recently released iPhone versions of the app (1 version is free, and the full version is $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jane Austin &amp; Chris Neale on Sketch Prototypes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jane-austin-chris-neale-sketch-prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jane-austin-chris-neale-sketch-prototypes/</guid>
      <description>The paper prototype is generally used as a design tool and even usability testing tool, but the folks at IG Index have figured out a creative way to use sketches and paper prototypes as a communication tool in place of wireframes for demonstrating interaction to development teams. Martin Belam posted video from UX London 09 of Jane Austin, Chris Neale and Frances Eida discussing this simple method of taking wireframe/storyboard sketches or paper prototypes, and creating stop-motion animation to demonstrate interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pencils, Pens &amp; Markers Sets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pencils-pens-markers-sets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pencils-pens-markers-sets/</guid>
      <description>This one is for all you interface sketchers. Wireframes Magazine asked designers what their favorite pens, pencils, and markers are for UI sketching, and posted photos of the responses. Click the first photo to view the expanded gallery of tools.
http://wireframes.linowski.ca/2009/09/markers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ForeUI: Create Skinnable &amp; Interactive Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/foreui-create-skinnable-interactive-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/foreui-create-skinnable-interactive-prototype/</guid>
      <description>ForeUI is a handy UI prototyping tool. It can rapidly create skinnable and
clickable UI prototype for your website or software, and run the interactive
simulation in your web browser.
ForeUI provides a set of predefined elements for creating mockup, you can drag
them into the editing area and tweak them. You can also create your own elements
and libraries.
ForeUI makes prototype skinnable, by changing the UI theme, all elements in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The different sketch styles of the designers at 37signals</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/different-sketch-styles-designers-37signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/different-sketch-styles-designers-37signals/</guid>
      <description>The crew at 37signals posted a few pictures of their different sketch styles.
(via @rotkapchen)
http://37signals.com/svn/posts/1880-the-different-sketch-styles-of-the-designers-at-37signals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Sketchbook: iPhone App Sketchbook</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/app-sketchbook-iphone-app-sketchbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/app-sketchbook-iphone-app-sketchbook/</guid>
      <description>This is sweet. A sketchbook made for iPhone app design. Features three actual-size iPhone templates per page, pixel (20px) ruler and title bar markings, ruled section for app development notes, and 600 screens (100 double-sided pages).
http://appsketchbook.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframing over the shoulder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-over-shoulder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-over-shoulder/</guid>
      <description>This is a video on From The Couch podcast showing David Perel sketching wireframes for the Obox Theme. The first half shows David sketching, and during the second half he talks through the interface.
View the article for more.
http://www.from-the-couch.com/post.cfm/title/wireframing-over-the-shoulder</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Binderball: Mini binder with built in pen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/binderball-mini-binder-built-pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/binderball-mini-binder-built-pen/</guid>
      <description>Japanese office products are so cool. This is Binderball, invented by Masayuki Takahata for Sun-Star Stationery. It&amp;rsquo;s a mini-binder with built-in pen that you can attach to a notepad. More about the invention on the Scription blog.
http://www.sun-star-st.jp/private_brand/binderball.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchbook: Conceptual Drawings from the World&#39;s Most Influential Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbook-conceptual-drawings-worlds-most-influential-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbook-conceptual-drawings-worlds-most-influential-designers/</guid>
      <description>Core77 reviews Timothy O&amp;rsquo;Donnell&amp;rsquo;s Sketchbook, which looks at the problem solving processes of influential designers on finished projects through the lens of their sketchbooks. It looks beautiful. Organized in three sections, &amp;ldquo;Rough,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Refined,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Random&amp;rdquo; (plus bonus section &amp;ldquo;Revealed,&amp;rdquo; where O&amp;rsquo;Donnell shows the thumbnail sketches he used to lay out the book), almost all sketches/sketchbook pages are pared with pictures of the finished product side by side. The &amp;ldquo;Rough&amp;rdquo; section features loose artwork and thick lines, but crisp final products, like the way Jason Munn turns simple sketches into iconic music posters, while the &amp;ldquo;Refined&amp;rdquo; section sees Stefan Bucher&amp;rsquo;s gorgeous pens turned into, well, equally iconic logos and business cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Experience Sketches Flickr Group</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-sketches-flickr-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-sketches-flickr-group/</guid>
      <description>New UX sketch group on Flickr. This group is a collection of user experience sketches from a variety of designers solving a various problems from all around the world.
A sketch is
1. Unpreciousness : Sketches are not precious and can destroyed to make room for more ideas.
2. Quick : Sketches don’t take days to make. They are fast as we are fast.
3. Useful : UX sketches lead to solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pretty Sketchy Group on Flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/pretty-sketchy-group-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pretty-sketchy-group-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Jason Santa Maria started a sketchbook group on flickr. Sketchbooks are not about being a good artist, they’re about being a good thinker. In the spirit of awareness, I’ve set up a Flickr group for this very purpose. Post one, and only one, spread/page from your sketchbook. It’s always fun to see how everyone else’s mind works.
 Read more about it in Jason&amp;rsquo;s post Pretty Sketchy.
http://www.flickr.com/groups/prettysketchy/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A4 sketching paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/a4-sketching-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/a4-sketching-paper/</guid>
      <description>More printable sketch paper options, this time from Henk Wijnholds.
Via i heart wireframes.
http://www.concept7.nl/henk/prolonging-the-magic-a4-sketching-paper/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Sketch Book Now Available</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-sketch-book-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-sketch-book-now-available/</guid>
      <description>The sketch book is finally available in the store. It&amp;rsquo;s a small 8.25 x 5.5 inch wirebound book that lays flat, has a 24 x 24 grid with note block on the front (landscape orientation) and 48 x 24 grid on the back (landscape or portrait). Includes 50 perforated sheets (100 pages) printed in non-photo blue ink, and an interior flap on the back cover. For the first set sold, I&amp;rsquo;m also including a Zebra 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Path&#39;s Favorite Sketch Tools</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-paths-favorite-sketch-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-paths-favorite-sketch-tools/</guid>
      <description>Leah Buley lists Adaptive Path&amp;rsquo;s favorite sketch tools. There’s an interesting shift happening in user experience design. After years of making documents that look like they are FEBE (for engineers, by engineers), we’re seeing increasing evidence of the human hand in our own work. Why are sketches and drawing suddenly so prevalent? Well, for one, they can save a lot of time and mitigate the risk of building the wrong thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the transition from paper to Photoshop</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/improving-transition-paper-photoshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/improving-transition-paper-photoshop/</guid>
      <description>On the creative briefing blog, Verne Ho offers some suggestions for creating a fluid process for going from sketch to Photoshop. He shows the sketches for several projects and the resulting visual design comps. http://creativebriefing.com/improving-the-transition-from-paper-to-photoshop/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Wood&#39;s Sketchbook Techniques</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/tim-woods-sketchbook-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/tim-woods-sketchbook-techniques/</guid>
      <description>Brian Pirie recaps Tim Wood’s talk at Interaction 09 conference on how to get the most out of your sketchbook. Wood used examples from artists notebooks to illustrate techniques that might be useful in refining our craft.
http://sensinct.com/interaction-09-sketchbook-techniques/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sockyung Hong&#39;s Vimeo Sketches on Flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sockyung-hongs-vimeo-sketches-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sockyung-hongs-vimeo-sketches-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Sockyung Hong posts sketches of Vimeo design concepts on Flickr. Very nice to examples of peoples&amp;rsquo; design sketches like this.
Via agentangelo
http://flickr.com/photos/soxiam/tags/sketch,vimeo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Shows How to Do Low Fi Concept Demos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cooper-shows-how-do-low-fi-concept-demos/</guid>
      <description>The Drawing Board: Commuter Buddy from Cooper Journal on Vimeo. Cooper Interactive&amp;rsquo;s Commuter Buddy concept video is another great find via Dave Malouf&amp;rsquo;s Engage blog. You might have already seen this one, but as Dave points out, it is a great example of using personas, narrative, and really low fidelity sketches to demonstrate a concept.
The video above uses still photography, super-imposed photos of whiteboard drawings, and voice over narrative to describe the idea for a mobile phone application that helps a commuter to get to his ride on time, and even to remember to get off if he becomes engrossed in an article, for instance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Rhode&#39;s Wireframes Sketch Set on Flickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mike-rhodes-wireframes-sketch-set-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mike-rhodes-wireframes-sketch-set-flickr/</guid>
      <description>Mike Rhode&amp;rsquo;s set of http://www.flickr.com/photos/rohdesign/sets/72157614397535202/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;wireframe sketches on Flickr is some beautiful stuff. Also check out Mike&amp;rsquo;s sketch notes and other design work on his blog.
Via Nick Finck
http://www.flickr.com/photos/rohdesign/sets/72157614397535202/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Work on OmniGraffle Sketch Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/starting-work-omnigraffle-sketch-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/starting-work-omnigraffle-sketch-stencils/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been following this blog, you may know how I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to do sketch/jitter line styles in OmniGraffle to produce sketchy diagrams and wireframes. After David&amp;rsquo;s demo of his method for doing sketch shapes on the Design Commission blog got me started figuring out how to get the effect natively in OG, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to finally create sketch versions of the Wireframe Stencils. Above is a screenshot of the forms set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Commission Website Stencil Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-website-stencil-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-website-stencil-kit/</guid>
      <description>Design Commission have begun selling their web stencil kit! The kit includes:
 Stainless steel stencil with all your favorite user interface iconography Heavyweight paper pad with browser chrome on top Zebra mechanical pencil 
http://www.designcommission.com/shop/dc-website-stencil-kit/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking About Sketching About Interacting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/talking-about-sketching-about-interacting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/talking-about-sketching-about-interacting/</guid>
      <description>Talking About Sketching About Interacting
View SlideShare presentation or Upload your own. (tags: dotdotdot mfa)   This the audio and slides from the presentation Chris Fahey gave at SVA&amp;rsquo;s Interaction Design Program series dot dot dot. In this excellent short short talks (16 minutes), Chris talks about sketching and shows plenty of examples from his notebooks. Great series of events that Liz Danzico and company are putting on. Chris will be on the faculty of the MFA program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframes Magazine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframes-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframes-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Jakub Linowski has started publishing Wireframes Magazine, a blog to showcase people&amp;rsquo;s user interface wireframes.
http://wireframes.linowski.ca/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing Sketch Iterations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/doing-sketch-iterations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/doing-sketch-iterations/</guid>
      <description>These are just more illustrations of the process I&amp;rsquo;ve been using for design iterations. When I have the Konigi notebook available, I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing some screencasts to describe this process in detail, and why I felt the need to make these graph paper notebooks and pads.
What you see above:
1) Annotated UI Spec (Wireframes) after design review.
2) Sketches for design and new ideas, on the Konigi Design Notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Work/Sketch Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cafe-worksketch-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cafe-worksketch-kit/</guid>
      <description>I gave my wife my MacBook to upgrade her from her iBook and got myself a netbook for those times when I&amp;rsquo;m out and need to wait for my son, and for watching Netflix/Hulu/Slingbox in the house. But I&amp;rsquo;m also finding that the netbook, a Lenovo Ideapad S10, is really pretty damned sweet for when I want to head out somewhere and do sketches in a cafe. I use it to post to our Traction server while I&amp;rsquo;m sketching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mocklinkr Prototyping and Review Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mocklinkr-prototyping-and-review-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mocklinkr-prototyping-and-review-tool/</guid>
      <description>Mocklinkr is another new design mockup review service to hit the web. This one adds a little twist, however, that might be pretty useful. After you upload images of your designs or wireframes, Mocklinkr let&amp;rsquo;s you create clickable sections on the image linking to another image. This let&amp;rsquo;s you do very simple click-through prototypes to change state and navigate between pages. In a way, this seems a bit like the Berkeley GUIR Denim tool, which is sadly no longer available at the GUIR site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Tool Design: Design by Sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/software-tool-design-design-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/software-tool-design-design-sketching/</guid>
      <description>The second part of Stephen Chambers&amp;rsquo; series on designing the ANTS Profiler tool, a .NET code profiler, discusses how a team leader challenged a group to really work collaboratively on developing the concept for the tool&amp;rsquo;s interface by taking away computers and requiring that the team work with only paper, whiteboards, pencils, and markers.
James, the team leader had just read Bill Buxton&amp;rsquo;s Sketching the User Experience and wanted to try to get his engineers to rally around the idea that everyone can participate in this ideation phase, and no one needed any specific skill to propose and sketch ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Commission Web Stencil Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-web-stencil-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-web-stencil-kit/</guid>
      <description>This is the excellent web stencil kit from Design Commission, which you will apparently be able to order soon! Comes with sketchpad, complete with browser chrome and grid, custom etched metal stencils, and a Zebra mechanical pencil. Hot stuff. Drop them a line if you want one when they run another job.
http://www.designcommission.com/blog/web-stencil-kit-hot-off-the-press/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scribbles, incredibly simple drawing app for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/scribbles-incredibly-simple-drawing-app-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/scribbles-incredibly-simple-drawing-app-mac/</guid>
      <description>Scribbles is perhaps the simplest drawing program I&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried. The app, created by atebits, gives you 4 tools: brush, move, pan, and zoom. There are 12 brush styles, a color picker, a big slider for brush size, and a layer manager. It looks deceptively simple on the surface, but when you explore a bit, you&amp;rsquo;ll find some really interesting functionalities that even the advanced Mac freehand drawing tools like Sketchbook and ArtRage don&amp;rsquo;t do well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave Gray&#39;s Sketches</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dave-grays-sketches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dave-grays-sketches/</guid>
      <description>Great sketch and sketch note collection in Dave Gray&amp;rsquo;s flickr.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/davegray/sets/1672209/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch of CDJ Setup in djdownload.com Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-cdj-setup-djdownloadcom-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-cdj-setup-djdownloadcom-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>djdownload.com newsletter 02/10/08
http://images.djdownload.com/img/newsletter/02102008/newsletter02102008.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printable Paper Rulers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/printable-paper-rulers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/printable-paper-rulers/</guid>
      <description>This is a pretty cool idea. A collection of rulers you can print.
http://www.vendian.org/mncharity/dir3/paper_rulers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Mobile Sketch Rig: Pilot Couleur Mini Pencils and Moleskine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/my-mobile-sketch-rig-pilot-couleur-mini-pencils-and-moleskine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/my-mobile-sketch-rig-pilot-couleur-mini-pencils-and-moleskine/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of Pilot and Pentel mechanical pencils. At home I use the larger Pentels, but when I&amp;rsquo;m out, I carry around the small red Pilot Couleur above attached to my small Moleskine. Ideas often come when I&amp;rsquo;m away from the desk so I feel like I always have to have pencil and paper wherever I go. The Pilots have a rubberized coating, hold 0.5mm leads, and hide an eraser under the push button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal.org crowd wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/drupal-org-crowd-wireframing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/drupal-org-crowd-wireframing/</guid>
      <description>Leisa Reichelt starts up some participatory design by getting Drupal contributors to sketch suggestions for things they&amp;rsquo;d like to see change on Drupal.org.
http://www.disambiguity.com/drupalorg-come-wireframe-with-me/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low-Cost Multi-point Interactive Whiteboards Using the Wiimote</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</guid>
      <description>Researcher provides another Wii Remote hack, this time to help business users create interactive whiteboards on the cheap.
 You might remember the incredible Wiimote hacks by by Johnny Chung Lee, who gave us head tracking demo for desktop VR displays. Lee, a PhD student in the Human-Computer Interaction Institute at Carnegie Mellon University is back with some more useful Wiimote hacks, this time to turn any surface into an interactive whiteboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton Lecture on Sketching and Experience Design at Stanford</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton gives a lecture at the Stanford University Human-Computer Interaction Seminar (CS 547, June 1, 2007) giving an excellent deep dive into some of the topics in his book, Sketching User Experiences.
 Designing for experience comes with a whole new level of complexity. This is especially true in this emerging world of information appliances, reactive environments, and ubiquitous computing, where, along with those of their users, we have to factor in the convoluted behaviors of the products themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think Draw Make</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/think-draw-make/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/think-draw-make/</guid>
      <description>From the &amp;gt;Think&amp;gt;Draw&amp;gt;Make&amp;gt; about page:
&amp;ldquo;One of the big objectives of this site is to encourage Designers to participate by designing their own visualizations (in 550 by 450 pixels) to match their interpretation of what they think the design process should be.&amp;rdquo;
http://www.thinkdrawmake.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To All the Notebooks I&#39;ve Ever Loved Before</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/all-notebooks-ive-ever-loved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/all-notebooks-ive-ever-loved/</guid>
      <description>I recently talked to someone about the graph/grid paper books I&amp;rsquo;ve acquired over the years which have become a central part of my process. This is a listing of those pads, and a telling of their virtues. Rhodia This is my workhorse. At first I didn&amp;rsquo;t get why so many designers carried these around, until I got my hands on one. To me the Rhodias are an all-around notepad for in office or outside use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Search Sketch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twitter-search-sketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twitter-search-sketch/</guid>
      <description>In Twitter&amp;rsquo;s blog entry describing how Summize will be rolled into Twitter, they included a neat little sketch to illustrate.
http://blog.twitter.com/2008/07/finding-perfect-match.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>About This 8.5 x 11 inch graph paper is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects. You&#39;ll find styles for wireframing user interfaces, and story boarding interaction. I&#39;ve been told that it&#39;s also used by animators and filmmakers. Enjoy.
 Scanning These cyan and gray grid pages are great for sketching, but also work well when producing high fidelity drawings. The boxes and grid lines of the cyan versions are non-photo blue, so you can easily remove them when scanned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>I spend a lot of time sketching interface ideas on paper. Typically I sketch wireframes and storyboards on graph paper, then redo the final documents in OmniGraffle. But lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using paper for more than just sketching. Now, after spending time sketching ideas and working out design issues, I start to do higher fidelity drawings on paper, scan them, post them to our system. We discuss and iterate, and the process repeats until we&amp;rsquo;re happy, and I spend less time pushing pixels around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Paper Version of the Web</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-version-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/paper-version-web/</guid>
      <description>After posting the Konigi Graph Paper, someone pointed me to Deeplinking&amp;rsquo;s collection of photos of paper prototypes and user interface sketches.
http://deeplinking.net/paper-web/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch paper for the mobile designer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</guid>
      <description>Erlend posted on the Artueel blog about a great idea they had for mobile designers&amp;#8212;a sketchpaper document you can print out (PDF and PSD formats available) so you can get your ideas on paper. They&amp;rsquo;ve created sketchpaper for the iPhone and the Nokia N95. Since we‘re all big fans of the iPhone and the mobile future in general, we want to help the mobile designer achieving his goals. For those who like to sketch the design/flow of their mobile app or website we present you: sketch paper for the iPhone and Nokia N95.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fine Art of Wireframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fine-art-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fine-art-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>On the Geniant blog, T.Scott Stromberg exposes his craft of wireframe sketching. I also spend most of my ideation time sketching. It&#39;s lovely to see other people&#39;s methods for getting ideas down. I love Stromberg&#39;s comments and comic book style.
This might sound kind of pathetic, but seeing the pens and paper he uses is the kind of thing I really geek out on. I love that he&#39;s pimping out the Behance dot grid pads.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>