<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>user research on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/user-research/</link><description>Recent content in user research on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:29:32 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/user-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethnio UX Research Incentive Calculator</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/ethnio-incentive-calculator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:29:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/ethnio-incentive-calculator/</guid><description>Estimator for paying incentives to user research participants.</description></item><item><title>How GitHub Uses &amp;amp;quot;Deprivation Testing&amp;amp;quot; To Hone Product Design</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-github-uses-deprivation-testing-hone-product-design/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-github-uses-deprivation-testing-hone-product-design/</guid><description>Fastco interviewed Chrissie Brodigan, design and UX researcher at GitHub to talk about how they're using deprivation to study people's reaction to removing elements from a product.
The gist of the technique is to work with a set of participants who develop a pattern of use around a feature or design characteristic and journal their experience. After some time, at a point when they've had time to be accustomed to that thing, they take away or alter it, and observe through the journal what the users' reactions are to its removal.</description></item><item><title>PowWow</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/powwow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/powwow/</guid><description>PowWow is a free simple service for scheduling user research using your Google Calendar. The fine folks at Pointless Corp (aka Viget) created this as a side project for handling scheduling of user interviews and testing, but could be used for any kind of event.
There are other apps like this that remove the fuss of coordinating schedules via email. PowWow does it simply, and provides a polished and pleasing experience.</description></item><item><title>Call Recorder for Skype</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</guid><description>ecamm's Call Recorder for Mac captures audio and video to save Skype calls as QuickTime movies. Useful for user interviews or screensharing sessions.
Thanks to Thomas @vanderwal for the tip
http://www.ecamm.com/mac/callrecorder/</description></item><item><title>IPEVO Ziggi Review</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</guid><description>Have you ever done the dance of holding a sketch up to your computer's webcam or taken pictures of them with your iPhone to email to yourself or to colleagues? I've done that sort of thing for all of the years that I've worked remotely on design and development teams, because scanners get tired real fast. Frustrated with this process, I had largely given up, until a few months ago when I was looking for tools to share work on paper between students and teachers.</description></item><item><title>Noticeability Evaluation</title><link>http://konigi.com/design/noticeability-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/design/noticeability-evaluation/</guid><description>Definition A research technique for learning whether people notice key elements in your design.
An exercise during which users are asked to re-create a screen based on their memory.
Source: &amp;quot;What UX Research Can You Do with 5 Users in 1 Hour?,&amp;quot; by Tomer Sharon. Asbury Agile 2012.
How to do it 1. Create an evaluation kit
Print any screen Cut the screen into elements (leave some out) Also print/cut some elements that weren't on the screen Mix the pieces up Sharpie and some extra paper 2.</description></item><item><title>Mr. Tappy: Video rig for tablets and mobile devices</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/mr-tappy-video-rig-tablets-and-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/mr-tappy-video-rig-tablets-and-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Mr Tappy is a kit for filming mobile phones, tablet computers and handheld devices from the user's point of view. Looks like a great alternative to setting up your own DIY rig, and costs $289.
Originally designed by Nick Bowmast as a filming rig for iPad usability testing, Mr Tappy lets you capture or share user interaction with mobile devices during user experience research, product demonstrations or classroom presentations. Attach your webcam and any type of mobile device, set the camera height and angle, and record.</description></item><item><title>Reframer: Qualitative data analysis system</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/reframer-qualitative-data-analysis-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/reframer-qualitative-data-analysis-system/</guid><description>Reframer is a collaborative web app for collecting and analyzing qualitative data. You start by capturing data into the app&amp;#8212;things like customer feedback, free text responses in surveys, emails, interviews, and usability test data. The system then uses the aggregated information and provides a view reframed with quantitative values based on a significance rating that team members apply. These values can also be used to prioritize issues to assess feasibility.</description></item><item><title>Cohdoo Highlight: Voice recording iPhone app</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/cohdoo-highlight-voice-recording-iphone-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/cohdoo-highlight-voice-recording-iphone-app/</guid><description>Cohdoo, the company that makes the iPhone whiteboard magnets that I've posted about have just released Highlight a nice iPhone app for voice recordings. It's aimed at helping user researchers record interviews, and is just as useful for recording meetings and conference talks.
To start new sessions, press the New Recording button, and during the recording you can tap the huge green Mark Highlight button, which I could see being useful for marking new questions during interviews, or marking sections of conference talks.</description></item><item><title>Pear Note: Note taking utility for Mac</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/pear-note-note-taking-utility-mac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/pear-note-note-taking-utility-mac/</guid><description>Pear Note from Useful Fruit Software is a powerful note-taking tool for Mac OS X. The application integrates text notes with audio and video you can record from interview sessions, meetings, etc.
The notes are time-marked to the video and slides that are being viewed during the recording, so you can click text from your notes, and the app will jump to that time in the recording so you can watch the video or see the slide that went with the note.</description></item><item><title>AddUse User research service</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/adduse-user-research-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/adduse-user-research-service/</guid><description>AddUse is a commercial user research service that allow you to run and analyze web surveys and allows usability test facilitators to manually capture and analyze the results of test sessions.
http://www.adduse.com/Default.aspx</description></item><item><title>Interaction10: How to Design an Experience for Experience Designers</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction10-how-design-experience-experience-designers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction10-how-design-experience-experience-designers/</guid><description>Jennifer Bove writes for Fast Company about how she and Bill DeRouchey designed the conference experience in &amp;quot;Interaction10: How to Design an Experience for Experience Designers.&amp;quot; It' a great behind the scenes look at how they observed the event the year prior, and thought about every aspect of the attendee experience and designed the IXD10 event to create a service that caters to what's important to the conference-goer at every point.</description></item><item><title>Just add an egg: Usability, User Experience and Dramaturgy</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/just-add-egg-usability-user-experience-and-dramaturgy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/just-add-egg-usability-user-experience-and-dramaturgy/</guid><description>Harry Brignull quotes a passage from Susan Marks' Finding Betty Crocker to tell the story of how the cake mix maker used a clever bit of imagination about the process of using their product to give customers the feeling of playing a desirable role--that of home-maker and cook. They did this by simply requiring that real eggs be used in making cakes, rather than incorporating powered egg, and marketed this as a benefit.</description></item><item><title>Should Design Be Held Back by a Tyranny of Data</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/should-design-be-held-back-tyranny-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/should-design-be-held-back-tyranny-data/</guid><description>The NYTimes interviewed Doug Bowman to talk about his departure from Google, which Bowman wrote about on his blog in March. Bowman came onto Google as their first Visual Designer 3 years ago, and left in March. Some quotes from the article:
Bowman on Google:
“Data eventually becomes a crutch for every decision, paralyzing the company and preventing it from making any daring design decisions,”
Bowman on Twitter, where he is now Creative Director:</description></item><item><title>User Research for Personas and Other Audience Models</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-research-personas-and-other-audience-models/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-research-personas-and-other-audience-models/</guid><description>In UX Matters, Steve Baty describes the user research methodologies we can draw on when creating audience models and some alternative ways of communicating the results of an audience analysis.
http://www.uxmatters.com/mt/archives/2009/04/user-research-for-personas-and-other-audience-models.php</description></item></channel></rss>