<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>big type on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/big-type/</link><description>Recent content in big type on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/big-type/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dom Goodrum</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</guid><description>Portfolio showcasing the favourite projects of designer Dom Goodrum.
http://www.domgoodrum.com</description></item><item><title>Zaum &amp; Brown</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/zaum-brown/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/zaum-brown/</guid><description>Zaum &amp;amp; Brown is the business moniker for freelance designer Richard Brown - offering creative solutions including myspace &amp;amp; cd sleeve design to bands and artists of all shapes and sizes.
http://www.zaum.co.uk</description></item><item><title>whnwlnd</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/whnwlnd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/whnwlnd/</guid><description>Bold type (fantastic use of Cufon) and a great looking portfolio of UX work from this Los Angeles studio.
http://www.whenweland.com/</description></item><item><title>Buddy Carr Skateboards</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/buddy-carr-skateboards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/buddy-carr-skateboards/</guid><description>The Buddy Carr Skateboards site showcases the limited edition design by Antonio Carusone with a minimalist design consistent with the designers typographic treatment of the skateboard graphics.
http://www.buddycarrskateboards.com/index.html</description></item><item><title>WebWork Design Studio Collection</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/webwork-design-studio-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/webwork-design-studio-collection/</guid><description>Randjelovic Milos's portfolio really can't be capture very well in screenshots, so you should check out the site to experience the perfect transitions between pages. Beautiful bold type and simple presentation.
http://www.webwork-studio.org/</description></item><item><title>Tweetizen</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</guid><description>Tweetizen is a simple web-based tool designed to help you filter the daily influx of tweets, and easily embed twitter groups to your own website. http://www.tweetizen.com/</description></item><item><title>Republic Bike</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/republic-bike/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/republic-bike/</guid><description>Republic Bike assembles custom bicycles based on shared design. The build feature on the bike configurator lets you choose among a few "curated" color combinations for components. I like the big heading type and the illustration and table of the bike product page. Via @edfladung
http://www.republicbike.com</description></item><item><title>Squared Eye</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/squared-eye/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/squared-eye/</guid><description>Squared Eye's newly relaunched site goes down in my short list of favorite redesigns. I love the fun art direction and editorial copy throughout the site, starting with the excellent whale logo, the crafty feel of the cutout graphpaper waves in those beiges and workingman blues that remind me of ledger paper, to the excellent copy in the headlines making reference to the water theme, and the attention to detail in every link and mouseover.</description></item><item><title>Nick Finck</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nick-finck/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nick-finck/</guid><description>Redesign of Nick Finck.com, the personal site of Blue Flavor UX/IA partner, speaker, and Digital Web publisher. Designed by Matt Brown. Friendly, big type and a simplified navigation make it a keeper.
http://www.nickfinck.com/</description></item><item><title>Unstoppable Robot Ninja</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unstoppable-robot-ninja/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unstoppable-robot-ninja/</guid><description>This is a bad-ass looking weblog with a very cool header. Big type and ample white space sets up a very clear visual hierarchy and makes it easy to read, and a strong center alignment of header/footer elements directs the eye. I love the big illustrated robot head in the header (kind of expecting it to wink at me) and the character photos in the footer. I also like the way the global navigation shifts so that the center link is whatever section you're viewing, which makes that centered look and directs your eyes downwards.</description></item><item><title>Wilson Miner</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/wilson-miner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/wilson-miner/</guid><description>Designer/developer Wilson Miner's portfolio and weblog is ultra-clean and very easy to read. The large type and great use of white space presents a clear hierarchy of page elements, and attention to details like the simple use of prev/next arrows for carousels and pagination make perusing this site a pleasure.
http://www.wilsonminer.com/</description></item><item><title>DAYTUM</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/daytum/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/daytum/</guid><description>Daytum comes to us from the data obsessed minds of visual designers, Nick Felton and Ryan Case. Felton is the creator of the Feltron personal annual report that we Tufte/stats junkies love and Case is the creative director working on the social media experience at Sling Media. DAYTUM is a wonderful evolution of the personal annual report, bringing obsessive loggers a place to count whatever comes to mind and visualize that data beautifully in the personal and community space.</description></item><item><title>LOVE Creative Manchester</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/love-creative-manchester/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/love-creative-manchester/</guid><description>"Created In Powerpoint" they say. This very simple, witty flash site for the agency Love Creative deserves to be here for its witty, big buttoned, black and white interface alone. http://www.lovecreative.com/</description></item><item><title>NATIONAL TELEVISION</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/national-television/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/national-television/</guid><description>National Television is a video and film production studio in California. It's portfolio site is among the best examples of the use of bold typography as the primary element that defines both the form and interface. The look is clean and undeniably confident.
http://www.natl.tv/</description></item><item><title>The Show</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/show/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/show/</guid><description>Big bold typography that functions as navigation, full screen photography that functions as backdrop, a simple message, and a lasting product that does justice to live music performances and the people who love them.
http://www.theshowlive.com/</description></item></channel></rss>