<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>omnigraffle on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/omnigraffle/</link><description>Recent content in omnigraffle on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/omnigraffle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Omnigraffle Stencil for Twitter Bootstrap 2</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-stencil-twitter-bootstrap-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-stencil-twitter-bootstrap-2/</guid><description>The team at Viget have created a free OmniGraffle stencil for designing interfaces with Twitter Bootstrap.
http://www.viget.com/advance/an-omnigraffle-stencil-for-twitter-bootstrap-2/</description></item><item><title>Form design guidelines crib sheet</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/form-design-guidelines-crib-sheet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/form-design-guidelines-crib-sheet/</guid><description>These form design crib sheets provide examples for laying out forms to get users through the process efficiently. Created by Joe Leech at cxpartners, and available for OmniGraffle, Photoshop, or in PDF vector format.
Via @theresaneil
http://www.cxpartners.co.uk/cxinsights/form_design_guidelines_crib_sheet_free.htm</description></item><item><title>10 Omnigraffle tips you might not know</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-omnigraffle-tips-you-might-not-know/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-omnigraffle-tips-you-might-not-know/</guid><description>All the OmniGraffle users out there will want to check out Todd Moy's list of tips and tricks that all OG power users need to know. The character replacement one in particular will save you time. Although I tend to just clone an entire object's style the style brush with W and OPT+W, you should definitely learn about cloning discrete styles with chicklets. You'll wonder you never did.
Check them all out on Viget Advance and level up your OG skills.</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle UX Template 2.5: Updated with iPad Pages</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-25-updated-ipad-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-25-updated-ipad-pages/</guid><description>@nickf called me out for not having iPad templates in the Konigi OmniGraffle Wireframe Template, so I got off my lazy ass and added some since this thing hasn't been updated in over 2 years! Added iPad Portrait 1 up, iPad Portrait 2 up, iPad Landscape 1 up. They have guides for 2x2 or 3x3 grid.
Note, this is for OmniGraffle Pro ONLY. You will not be able to edit shared layers to modify the headers and other templates.</description></item><item><title>Omnigraffle Sitemap Generator from Sitemap XML</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-sitemap-generator-sitemap-xml/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-sitemap-generator-sitemap-xml/</guid><description>Wireframes Mag pointed to an XML to OmniGraffle Sitmap Generator created by Jason Kunesh at Fuzzy Math to generate a sitemap from an XML file. The script assumes that your XML file consists of url elements, and that parent child relationships are defined by the paths in the url. For instance, //konigi.com/about-site/unicorns would be a child of //konigi.com/about-site. Once you generate a list of your urls and pass it to the script, OmniGraffle generates the sitemap hierarchy for you.</description></item><item><title>How to Make Tree Components in OmniGraffle</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-make-tree-components-omnigraffle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-make-tree-components-omnigraffle/</guid><description>I swear I've answered this question a dozen times, so I'm capturing to refer people in the future. The tree control in my OmnGraffle Wireframe Stencil is a godawful hack that uses tabs and arrow characters. Copying and pasting the arrows, however, screws up the formatting. OmniGraffle just doesn't make this kind of manipulation of text all that easy and I haven't found an ideal solution, but if you want to learn how I do it, read on.</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle for iPad Video</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ipad-video/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ipad-video/</guid><description>The OmniGroup now has video up of the OmniGraffle for iPad showing what looks to be an awesome product. I can't wait to get my hands on it.
http://www.omnigroup.com/products/omnigraffle-ipad/videos/</description></item><item><title>iPad Stencil for Omnigraffle</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/ipad-stencil-omnigraffle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/ipad-stencil-omnigraffle/</guid><description>iA have created an iPad stencil for OmniGraffle. Contains backgrounds, title bars, buttons, selectors, and other iPhone UI elements. Based the iPad PSD GUI by Teehan+Lax. Text is fully editable on lists, title bars, buttons, and scroll wheels
Download and read more at iA
http://informationarchitects.jp/ipad-stencil-for-omnigraffle/</description></item><item><title>iPhoneOS Design Stencil for iPhone and iPad</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iphoneos-design-stencil-iphone-and-ipad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphoneos-design-stencil-iphone-and-ipad/</guid><description>An iPhone OS OmniGraffle stencil for designing applications for iPhone, iPod touch and iPad devices. The stencil, for now, is targeted at developers familiar with the default characteristics of views and controls provided by UIKit. The stencil shapes are all vector based. The initial focus is on views and controls provided by UIKit and recommended application styles as discussed in the iPhone and iPad Human Interface Guidelines.
http://www.morford.org/iphoneosdesignstencil/</description></item><item><title>Wireframe Icons Update v. 1.5 for OmniGraffle and EPS Versions</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-update-v-15-omnigraffle-and-eps-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-update-v-15-omnigraffle-and-eps-versions/</guid><description>The OmniGraffle Wireframe Icons and the Royalty Free EPS/PNG icons have been updated.
In the OmniGraffle version, all icons have been converted to vector format so they are editable in OmniGraffle. You can now modify the shapes and easily change their colors. The vector icons also reduce file size of OG documents. In both OmniGraffle and EPS/PNG versions, I've cleaned up all existing icons for consistency and added new icons including: globe, wrench/screwdriver, lightning bolt, spaces, desktop, gun sight, cloud, bug, books, presentation, twitter bird, bullhorn, megaphone, rocket, windows, mac, and more.</description></item><item><title>960 grid template for OmniGraffle</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/960-grid-template-omnigraffle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/960-grid-template-omnigraffle/</guid><description>I’m a big fan of increasing efficiency and consistency from conceptual design to implementation. This OmniGraffle template has helped me quite a bit in that regard, and I decided to share it with others.
http://briancray.com/2009/11/30/omnigraffle-wireframing-960-grid-template/</description></item><item><title>Designing for the iPhone 3G: Tips and Tools</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-iphone-3g-tips-and-tools/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-iphone-3g-tips-and-tools/</guid><description>Theresa Neil updated her iPhone 3G stencil set for OmniGraffle at Graffletopia, and posted a few tips and tools that might be helpful to iPhone designers. http://theresaneil.wordpress.com/2009/09/16/iphone3g-design-resources/</description></item><item><title>Touchscreen Stencils</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/touchscreen-stencils/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/touchscreen-stencils/</guid><description>Dan Saffer of Kicker Studio provides free touch screen gesture stencils for OmniGraffle, Visio, Illustrator, and Fireworks. The icons are designed by Rachel Glaves for Saffer's book, Designing Gestural Interfaces, and depict hands performing common touchscreen gestures like tap, slide, point, drag, pinch, and spread.
http://www.kickerstudio.com/blog/2008/12/touchscreen-stencils/</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle UX Template Update (v. 2.4)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-update-v-24/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-update-v-24/</guid><description>The OmniGraffle UX Template has been updated. I finally got around to cleaning up the Persona example from the old version 1 (the urlgreyhot version), added a detailed persona, a site map example with diagramming style (.gdiagramstyle file), and a mental model example. Download from the Tools page.
//konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle 5 Keyboard Shortcuts Cheat Sheet</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-5-keyboard-shortcuts-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-5-keyboard-shortcuts-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>For all you Grafflers out there, Nick Finck has created a sweet single page cheat sheet illustrating OmniGraffle's numerous and well hidden keyboard shortcuts. Nick took the multi-page Help file provided by Omni and consolidated all of the tips into a single tabloid poster that you can print and stick on your wall to make life easier. More info at the OmniMouth.
Download the graffle directly here or from the OmniGraffle Extras page.</description></item></channel></rss>