<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>iphone on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/iphone/</link><description>Recent content in iphone on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/iphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starters Guide to iOS Design</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/starters-guide-ios-design/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/starters-guide-ios-design/</guid><description>Ben Taylor's Starters Guide to iOS describes an exhaustive range of topics as intro to iOS design. He covers the deliverables you'll be expected to produce, outlines the constraints of the medium, and introduces fundamental iOS and UI design concepts.
http://taybenlor.com/2013/05/21/designing-for-ios.html</description></item><item><title>POP: Prototyping on Paper</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/pop-prototyping-paper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/pop-prototyping-paper/</guid><description>POP is an iPhone app that lets you take pictures of your sketches, and map areas on each screen to create simple click-through prototypes.
http://popapp.in/</description></item><item><title>Whitelines Link</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</guid><description>Everyone's getting in on on the physical paper capturing game using the iPhone's camera. Whitelines is one of my favorite sketch paper makers. They make great graph paper that reverses the grid using white lines over pale a gray paper. The result is that the grid it more subtle and less distracting
The Whitelines Link product is a free iPhone app that let's you capture sketches made on their new Whitelines Link papers.</description></item><item><title>Phonedoo: Dry erase iPhone sketching</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</guid><description>Cohdoo makes a nice iPhone UI sketching product called Phone Doos. They are 6.8&amp;quot; by 3.5&amp;quot; dry erase iPhone surfaces with faint grid lines and magnetic backing. A pack contains 10 Phone Doos.
I like that these gives you a surface to work on that can be re-arranged easily on a table and presented on a metallic wall. They have some good screenshots using them arranged on a whiteboard with flow arrows pointing between them, which is another thing that's probably much easier with these as opposed to using paper.</description></item><item><title>iPad Dry Erase Board</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-dry-erase-board/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-dry-erase-board/</guid><description>New sketching goodies hit the shelves at UI Stencils, from our good friends Design Commission. They've created an iPad dry erase board with dot grid, and updated their awesome iPhone sticky pads. Definitely want to get my hands on the dry erase board.
Update:
Mine arrived and I have to say that this is the nicest dry erase board I have now. It's made on hard particle board, similar to what you'd find on a clipboard, so it feels great in the hands.</description></item><item><title>Word Lens: Translation using Augmented Reality</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/word-lens-translation-using-augmented-reality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/word-lens-translation-using-augmented-reality/</guid><description>This is one of the most practical uses of augmented reality I've seen. Word Lens translates text you capture from an iPhone's camera to another language. I think it's only Spanish-English/English-Spanish at the moment, and $4.99 per language. If you're skeptical, as some YouTubers seem to be in the comments, you can see an example of the translation I did on my phone of an English magazine page to Spanish.</description></item><item><title>Review: Sync design comps to iPhone</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/review-sync-design-comps-iphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/review-sync-design-comps-iphone/</guid><description>Review is a simple app to review your visual design comps on the iPhone. You install an app on your mac and an app on your iPhone and pair the two. On the Mac, drop images into Review, and they're synced with the iPhone for previewing at full screen.
http://www.getreviewapp.com/</description></item><item><title>Dapp: The App Design App</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/dapp-app-design-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/dapp-app-design-app/</guid><description>Dapp is an Apple UI Standards professional rapid application development tool that runs in the iPhone. It lets you design iPhone app prototypes, publish a spec to PDF, and generate iPhone SDK code.
http://dapp.kerofrog.com.au/</description></item><item><title>LiveView for iPhone &amp; iPad</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone-ipad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone-ipad/</guid><description>LiveView is a free remote screen viewing application created by Nicholas Zambetti to help designers create graphics for mobile applications, and for quick and dirty simulations, demos, and prototypes.
Visual Designers may use it to view artboard while you work. LiveView is compatible with both standard and Retina displays. Interaction Designers can use with iPhone or iPad tethered via WiFi, to interact with software prototypes and demos running on your Mac to communicate and iterate your concepts quickly.</description></item><item><title>iPhoneOS Design Stencil for iPhone and iPad</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iphoneos-design-stencil-iphone-and-ipad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphoneos-design-stencil-iphone-and-ipad/</guid><description>An iPhone OS OmniGraffle stencil for designing applications for iPhone, iPod touch and iPad devices. The stencil, for now, is targeted at developers familiar with the default characteristics of views and controls provided by UIKit. The stencil shapes are all vector based. The initial focus is on views and controls provided by UIKit and recommended application styles as discussed in the iPhone and iPad Human Interface Guidelines.
http://www.morford.org/iphoneosdesignstencil/</description></item><item><title>PhoneGap | Cross platform mobile framework</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/phonegap-cross-platform-mobile-framework/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonegap-cross-platform-mobile-framework/</guid><description>PhoneGap is an open source development tool for building fast, easy mobile apps with JavaScript. If you’re a web developer who wants to build mobile applications in HTML and JavaScript while still taking advantage of the core features in the iPhone, Android, Palm, Symbian and Blackberry SDKs, PhoneGap is for you.
http://phonegap.com/</description></item><item><title> iPhone UI</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-ui/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-ui/</guid><description>A JavaScript library to prototype web interfaces for the iPhone.
http://iphone.hohli.com/</description></item><item><title>LiveView for iPhone</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone/</guid><description>LiveView is great little freebie for UI design &amp; prototyping on iPhone. Essentially it sends a 320x480 viewport from your Mac to your iPhone, so is useful for creating quick and dirty simulations, demos, and user experience prototypes.
http://www.zambetti.com/projects/liveview/</description></item><item><title>iPhone 3G Stencil</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-3g-stencil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-3g-stencil/</guid><description>This is a new version of Theresa Neil's iPhone stencil for the 3G phone. Includes standard interface components for the iPhone 3G: buttons, fields, map elements, keyboards, and icons.
http://www.graffletopia.com/stencils/495</description></item><item><title>Autodesk SketchBook Mobile Brings Sketching to iPhone</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-brings-sketching-iphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/autodesk-sketchbook-mobile-brings-sketching-iphone/</guid><description>I've had SketchBook Pro for the Mac for a few years now. I bought it before it was acquired by Autodesk from Alias, mostly for art work, but also to experiment with it as a tool for interface sketching. But while I wanted to use it more, I find myself falling back on paper and pencil almost all of the time. Autodesk recently released iPhone versions of the app (1 version is free, and the full version is $2.</description></item></channel></rss>