<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>forms on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/forms/</link><description>Recent content in forms on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/forms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basecamp Form Focus</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-form-focus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-form-focus/</guid><description>This is a cute interaction for the input focus and data validation on Basecamp's registration form. The smiling character illustration on the left points out which steps are in focus. When an invalid value is entered, the character makes a concerned face and the pointing hand stays fixed on the highlighted input.
The illustrations on the site do a great job of making you feel like this isn't &amp;quot;business as usual,&amp;quot; which is the reason for switching to Basecamp.</description></item><item><title>Geeklist Sign Up Password Strength</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/geeklist-sign-password-strength/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/geeklist-sign-password-strength/</guid><description>Geeklist's sign up form tells you how secure your password is by indicating how long it would take to crack. Sounds much more understandable and convincing than the typical weak/strong message.
1. A really strong password.2. A dictionary word is weak. 3. Better, but still weak. The messaging may be convincing enough to get users to think about their choice. https://geekli.st/signup</description></item><item><title>Making Infield Form Labels Suck Less</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/making-infield-form-labels-suck-less/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/making-infield-form-labels-suck-less/</guid><description>Jackson Fox and Jeremy Fields did an excellent 2-part write on the use of "infield" labels at Viget. There are several techniques for placing labels inside the input box. For varying reasons we may want to avoid the label on top or side positioning, but as Jackson points out, the infield placement can be problematic. Part 1 talks about the problems using infield labels. Part 2 shows how they deal with the problem by using a visible tooltip that doesn't obscure the input, with a jsFiddle snippet to play with the code.</description></item><item><title>Photojojo Captcha</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photojojo-captcha/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photojojo-captcha/</guid><description>Yes, I know you hate captchas and they're riddled with problems. Why do it if you don't have to? But if you do it, at least make it a brainless action like this.
1. Click to answer the captcha challenge. http://photojojo.com/contact/</description></item><item><title>Slavery Footprint Form: Drag to Select</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</guid><description>The Slavery Footprint website allows consumers to visualize how their consumption habits are connected to modern-day slavery.
They use a set of forms in a wizard-like survey to come up with an estimate of the number of slaves that are impacted by your behavior.
This section of the survey asks the user to drag the icons for items that describe the kind of house and car they own or rent into a drop area in the home above.</description></item><item><title>Kelley Blue Book Mad Libs Form</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kelley-blue-book-mad-libs-form/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kelley-blue-book-mad-libs-form/</guid><description>The Kelley Blue Book features Mad Libs-style inline form elements for its contact form. The contact form, which was previously displayed with right-aligned labels adjacent to to left aligned fields, is now displayed as an inline form with &amp;quot;fill in the blanks&amp;quot; style prompts for input.
http://www.kbb.com/</description></item><item><title>Mad Libs Style Form Increases Conversion 25-40%</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/mad-libs-style-form-increases-conversion-25-40/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mad-libs-style-form-increases-conversion-25-40/</guid><description>Luke Wroblewski reports on A-B tests performed by Ron Kurti and the team at Vast.com, who note that Mad Libs style forms increased conversion across the board by 25-40%. Read more and see the before/after screenshots at LukeW.
Update:
Shortly after posting this, David Kaneda pointed out his post, in which he observes that there is quite a bit more to that Kelly Blue Book form redesign than just switching from vertically arranged fields to inline fields.</description></item><item><title>Deconstructing a CSS trick to display form data as tabular data</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/deconstructing-css-trick-display-form-data-tabular-data/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/deconstructing-css-trick-display-form-data-tabular-data/</guid><description>CSS and Javascript experiments are fun to play around with. I tend to talk about them here because of the questions they raise about whether a technique is worth implementing or if it does more harm than help. Straight forward and familiar are the safe route. Sometimes experiments lead to better ways of doing things, other times they seem like they're gratuitous.
I came across an interesting, if problematic experiment to convert form fields into editable fields that are masked table cells until each input is in focus.</description></item><item><title>The Apple Store's Checkout Form Redesign</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-stores-checkout-form-redesign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/apple-stores-checkout-form-redesign/</guid><description>I finally made some time to read through Luke Wroblewski's excellent review of the changes in the Apple store's redesigned checkout form. According to Wroblewski, &amp;quot;...retail sales data shows that Mac sales were up 21% year-over-year in the months of October and November. So it's interesting to note that Apple's primary online sales channel (Web-based checkout) was redesigned during this time.
I wasn't surprised that the single page checkout form is an improvement over the paged version.</description></item><item><title>Chroma-Hash Password Masking</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/chroma-hash-password-masking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/chroma-hash-password-masking/</guid><description>Chroma-Hash is a jQuery script that Mattt Thompson created to explore a visual method for confirmation password matches during confirmation on login and registration forms. The idea is similar to Identicon, but uses a small colored bars in the input to visually check your strings. He describes the project on Mattt.com and you can try the demo out on GitHub or download it. Versions supporting other libraries are also linked from this page.</description></item><item><title>Confirming Passwords Is Annoying: Is There a Better Way?</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/confirming-passwords-annoying-there-better-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/confirming-passwords-annoying-there-better-way/</guid><description>This an article from March 09 by Kevin Vigneault of Viget that explores some techniques using Javascript to create more usable password inputs in forms. The ideas range from using a checkbox or button to temporarily show the password or changing type from text to password when the input is not in focus. Great ideas.
If you're interested in this topic, you might also want to check out Chris Dary's experiments with password masking.</description></item><item><title>iPhone-like Passwords using jQuery</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-passwords-using-jquery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iphone-passwords-using-jquery/</guid><description>Stefan Ullrich's jQuery plugin on the DECAF site provides a behavior for masking passwords that is familiar to mobile users. The plugin obscures previously entered characters at delayed intervals or when new characters are entered. It falls back on using the browser's password masking when JS is disabled.
http://blog.decaf.de/2009/07/iphone-like-password-fields-using-jquery/</description></item><item><title>Log in or sign up?</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/log-or-sign/</guid><description>Leah Culver discusses the design of hybrid sign up / login forms, showing a few examples and the final form as implemented for Leafy Chat. Uses the familiar I'm a customer/I'm new here radios that we know from Amazon, but positions it before the password field, which I find an improvement over the Amazon implementation. Lots of ideas in the comments.
http://blog.leahculver.com/2009/11/log-in-or-sign-up.html</description></item><item><title>Turn any webform into a powerful wizard with jQuery</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/turn-any-webform-powerful-wizard-jquery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/turn-any-webform-powerful-wizard-jquery/</guid><description>The FormToWizard plugin for jQuery allows you to break up form fieldsets to create a stepped wizard-like flow. You can download and view the demo via Janko at Warp Speed.
http://www.jankoatwarpspeed.com/post/2009/09/28/webform-wizard-jquery.aspx</description></item><item><title>Aardvark Registration</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</guid><description>The registration process on Aardvark provides a modal dialog that uses some nice content previews, content filtering, and progressive disclosure to guide the new user through the form. 1. Clicking sign up button from an invitation opens modal dialog with basic information form. A preview area updates your info as you fill out the form.2. The birthday input filters and corrects date format. City/State shows suggestions. (The one in yellow is a browser auto-completion.</description></item></channel></rss>