<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sitemaps on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/sitemaps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sitemaps on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 09:41:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/sitemaps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VisualSitemaps</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/visualsitemaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 09:41:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/visualsitemaps/</guid>
      <description>A visual sitemap generator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrity: Website link checker and xml sitemap generator for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/integrity-website-link-checker-and-xml-sitemap-generator-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/integrity-website-link-checker-and-xml-sitemap-generator-mac/</guid>
      <description>Doing a website relaunch often requires a good deal of cleanup and checking for link rot. I use a utility called Integrity, created by Shiela Dixon, to crawl a site and generate a report of invalid links, missing links, broken anchors, and broken images. Provides a filterable report and XML export options.
http://peacockmedia.co.uk/integrity/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omnigraffle Sitemap Generator from Sitemap XML</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-sitemap-generator-sitemap-xml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/omnigraffle-sitemap-generator-sitemap-xml/</guid>
      <description>Wireframes Mag pointed to an XML to OmniGraffle Sitmap Generator created by Jason Kunesh at Fuzzy Math to generate a sitemap from an XML file. The script assumes that your XML file consists of url elements, and that parent child relationships are defined by the paths in the url. For instance, //konigi.com/about-site/unicorns would be a child of //konigi.com/about-site. Once you generate a list of your urls and pass it to the script, OmniGraffle generates the sitemap hierarchy for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SlickMap CSS: HTML Sitemapping Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/slickmap-css-html-sitemapping-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/slickmap-css-html-sitemapping-tool/</guid>
      <description>Matt Everson of Astuteo has created SlickMap CSS, a simple stylesheet for displaying finished sitemaps directly from HTML unordered list navigation. It’s suitable for most web sites – accommodating up to three levels of page navigation and additional utility links – and can easily be customized to meet your own individual needs, branding, or style preferences.
Via David Kaneda
http://astuteo.com/slickmap/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zef[a]media UX Templates</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</guid>
      <description>zef[a]media&#39;s UX Template package contains sample paper prototypes/wireframes, personas, sitemaps, and user flow diagrams. Requires MS Visio, Word, and Excel.
http://www.zefamedia.com/websites/free-ux-templates/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Sitemap and Footer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/modern-sitemap-and-footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/modern-sitemap-and-footer/</guid>
      <description>Web Designer Wall collects screenshots from 20 sites with footer sitemaps.
Via @dreamtime
http://www.webdesignerwall.com/trends/modern-sitemap-and-footer/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lovely Charts Online Diagramming Application</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/lovely-charts-online-diagramming-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/lovely-charts-online-diagramming-application/</guid>
      <description>This is a review of Lovely Charts, a free online diagramming tool that provides wire frame, flow chart, and site map stencils. I like the unique, simple method they provide for quickly creating flow charts and site maps. In this screencast I show how to do a few simple flow diagrams and a wireframe, as well as discussing the features that I&#39;d like to see for creating prototypes from this tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Sitemaps Don&#39;t Work: Two Alternatives</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/when-sitemaps-dont-work-two-alternatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/when-sitemaps-dont-work-two-alternatives/</guid>
      <description>Interesting discussion in M. Jackson Wilkinson&#39;s blog about the altnernatives to hierarchical sitemaps, and the use of concept maps or user flows as alternatives when hierarchy doesn&#39;t work in your documentation. I have to agree with one point, in that site maps don&#39;t always serve documentation well when the notion of a strict hierarchy just doesn&#39;t exist. But I think there&#39;s utility in sitemaps at conveying the organization of a site or application at some level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Map Usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/site-map-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/site-map-usability/</guid>
      <description>Jakob Nielsen&#39;s Alertbox reports on their study of sitemaps, observing that among the sites they tested, sitemaps continue to be a useful tool to some people. While their study shows that they are rarely used, they can be simple, inexpensive tools to generate for the users who find value in the sense-making cues that a visual overview provides. Their recommendation is to continue to use them if you already produce them, but keep them static and don&#39;t add interactive effects to them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
