<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>graphics on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/graphics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graphics on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 08:48:51 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/graphics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>unDrawco</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/undrawco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 08:48:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/undrawco/</guid>
      <description>Open-source illustrations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clever PNG Optimization Techniques</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/clever-png-optimization-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/clever-png-optimization-techniques/</guid>
      <description>Sergey Chikuyonok&#39;s Smashing Magazine article on PNG optimization is an oldie, but I just found myself returning to use it for maybe the 4th time since I originally read it. I don&#39;t do web graphics so frequently anymore, so I always return here to get reminded of things like the posterization layer in Photoshop. See also Sergey&#39;s JPEG Optimization article.
http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2009/07/15/clever-png-optimization-techniques/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raphael JavaScript Library for Vector Graphics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/raphael-javascript-library-vector-graphics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/raphael-javascript-library-vector-graphics/</guid>
      <description>Henrik pointed me to Raphaël, a nice JS library for generating interactive charts.
Raphaël is a small JavaScript library that should simplify your work with vector graphics on the web. In case you want to create your own specific chart or image crop-n-rotate widget, you can simply achieve it with this library.
Raphaël uses SVG and VML as a base for graphics creation. Because of that every created object is a DOM object so you can attach JavaScript event handlers or modify objects later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumopaint.com beta - Image Editing in the Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sumopaintcom-beta-image-editing-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sumopaintcom-beta-image-editing-browser/</guid>
      <description>Sumopaint, by Snap Group Ltd is looking to be a really slick Flash-based online graphics creation and editing tool. It has a very complete list of functionalities with shapes, brushes, layers, text editing, filters, and many of the features you&#39;d expect from Photoshop or (ack) GIMP. Users can share images for community editing, create and view versions, and add comments. This looks like it might turn out to be an excellent resource for those looking at doing things like shared whiteboarding and prototyping without the real-time editing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
