<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Omnigraffle Ux Template on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/omnigraffle-ux-template/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Omnigraffle Ux Template on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/omnigraffle-ux-template/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template 2.5: Updated with iPad Pages</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-25-updated-ipad-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-25-updated-ipad-pages/</guid>
      <description>@nickf called me out for not having iPad templates in the Konigi OmniGraffle Wireframe Template, so I got off my lazy ass and added some since this thing hasn&amp;rsquo;t been updated in over 2 years! Added iPad Portrait 1 up, iPad Portrait 2 up, iPad Landscape 1 up. They have guides for 2x2 or 3x3 grid.
Note, this is for OmniGraffle Pro ONLY. You will not be able to edit shared layers to modify the headers and other templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Updated (v. 2.2)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-v-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-v-22/</guid>
      <description>The UX Template has been updated (Vers. 2.2) with some minor fixes. The iPhone template was recreated using OmniGraffle drawing tools rather than imported PNGs to shrink file size. Template was converted to flat XML format rather than bundle. Guides cleaned up on all pages.
http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Gmail Client Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>I posted on Twitter about how frustrating it can be to have to use email. With every day that I use Twitter via Twhirl I become less and less interested in using email. So I moaned to my Twitter peeps about the pain I feel. Some people wanted to know what I wanted, so I responded with the ideal flow, using Mac OS X&amp;rsquo;s Growl alerting app as the starting point:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Updated (Version 2.1)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-version-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-version-21/</guid>
      <description>The OmniGraffle UX Template for interface and interaction designers has been updated to version 2.1. Included in this release are major alignment, grid, and layout changes. Added guides for 24 column grid with vertical and horizontal gutters on wireframes. Added appropriate guides to all templates that necessitated alignment guides. Added small wireframe and iPhone templates. Download it here.
http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>