<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Call to Action on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/call-to-action/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Call to Action on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/call-to-action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mention Call To Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mention-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mention-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Mention.com&#39;s Success Stories section uses this great phrase to introduce the Proof in the drip pan at the bottom of the page.
&amp;quot;They also started with a free trial.&amp;quot; Short and persuasive copy that makes an otherwise common CTA more compelling.
1. Intro text, subdued company logos for the proof (so as not to compete with the CTA), and bold red call to action button to create your first alert and start a free trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should follow me on Twitter: Dustin Curtis experiments with call to action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/you-should-follow-me-twitter-dustin-curtis-experiments-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/you-should-follow-me-twitter-dustin-curtis-experiments-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Dustin Curtis did an interesting experiment with a short call to action at the bottom of his pages, asking users to follow him on Twitter. Comparing the results shows that direct, but informally worded calls to action, and (ugh) using a literal call out like the word &amp;ldquo;here&amp;rdquo; had a pretty significant impact. As the forcefulness and personal identifiability of the phrase increased, the number of clicks likewise increased. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; identifies the reader directly, &amp;ldquo;should&amp;rdquo; implies an obligation, and &amp;ldquo;follow me on twitter&amp;rdquo; is a direct command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Testing Results for LessAccounting.com Call To Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ui-testing-results-lessaccountingcom-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ui-testing-results-lessaccountingcom-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Less Everything did a couple of A-B tests on the call to action buttons on the home page of their Less Accounting product. Their first test modified the design of 2 buttons (see tour, try), using 1 button instead for the &amp;ldquo;Try Less Accounting&amp;rdquo; link and a text link for &amp;ldquo;See Tour&amp;rdquo;. They noticed a small increase in conversion when they went to the single button, and then did a second test, reversing the position of the button and link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call To Action Buttons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/call-action-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/call-action-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Lee Munroe has collected a slew of examples of Signup and Download call to action buttons that exemplify good CTA button design. He has 4 criteria for designing a good call to action button, involving the appropriate use of color, language, size, and white space around the button.
http://www.leemunroe.com/web-design-trends-call-to-action-signup-download-buttons/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Techniques for an Effective Call to Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-techniques-effective-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-techniques-effective-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Boagworld looks at 10 ways to design an effective call to action.
Having an effective call to action is an essential part of any website. A call to action is not just limited to ecommerce sites. Every website should have an objective it wants users to complete whether it is filling in a contact form, signup for a newsletter or volunteering their time.
A call to action provides&amp;hellip;
Focus to your site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pano Logic Expanding Call to Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pano-logic-expanding-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pano-logic-expanding-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Pano Logic sells a simple network PC. Their product site features a large graphic of the product, and 3 simple informational modules at the bottom to find out more about the product, read reviews and press, and watch a demo webinar. The modules expand when the user hovers over each box. There isn&#39;t much information added, except for a call to action that tells the user a little more about what they&#39;ll see if they click the link.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>