<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>link drop on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/link-drop/</link><description>Recent content in link drop on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/link-drop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Link Drop, June 2013</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-june-2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-june-2013/</guid><description>Not a lot of bookmarking this month. Learn X in Y Minutes: Scenic Programming Language Tours iOS 7 - Matt Gemmell Collaborative Design: Lean UX is Haaaard » Zac Halbert Apple - Designed By Apple - Intention - YouTube Video by Apple with phrases paired with visuals that describe the thoughts and emotions that go into creating each Apple product. Remove Duplicates from the “Open With” Right-Click Menu in Mac OS X Get rid of that thing that happens when your Mac lists too many versions of an app in the Open With.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop, May 2013</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-may-2013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-may-2013/</guid><description>Designing (and converting) for multiple mobile densities | Teehan+Lax Converting graphics for different resolution densities. How to be mediocre | neilcrofts Reminders for being aware of when you fall into the traps of medicority. Pure A set of small, responsive CSS modules that you can use in every web project. Hexo - Node.js blog framework A fast, simple &amp;amp; powerful blog framework, powered by Node.js. Commit Message Generator DODOnotes | DODOcase Carry your iPhone naked and also like paper?</description></item><item><title>Link Drop, Apr 2013</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-apr-2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-apr-2013/</guid><description>No to NoUI – Timo Arnall Flat UI Free - PSD&amp;amp;HTML User Interface Kit - Designmodo 10 Apps to Help You Tame Your Monitor at Night | Mac.AppStorm I don't tend to use my computer at night, preferring the iPad, but apparently using a computer screen can have an effect on getting to sleep using the default brightness and color settings you have now. Chrome Web Store - OneTab Better ways to sweep tabs under the rug and pull them back out.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop, Mar 2013</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-mar-2013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-mar-2013/</guid><description>Poor Man’s Agile: Scrum in 5 Simple Steps There are 478 page hard cover books on Scrum? Don't read them. Read Scott Porad's Scrum in 5 steps. Pegleg Crowd-sourced full-length movies on YouTube. greenqloud.com Cloud servers and storage in a carbon-neutral facility that uses 100% renewable energy. Panic Blog » Top 20 Secrets of Coda 2 This is an old one, but I don't know how I missed the Preview in a Simulated iPhone/iPad when you switch user agents.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop, Feb 2013</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-feb-2013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-feb-2013/</guid><description>Why Pinterest-style infinite-scroll layouts are worthless for everyone except Pinterest | Stephen Corwin's Blog A collection of best front-end frameworks with comparison | By usabli.ca Step-By-Step Landing Page Copywriting | Nathan Barry Quickly show and hide hidden files | Finder, Terminal | Mac OS X Tips How to create a new automator workflow that shows a toggle hidden files in the Finder service menu. Kindle Previewer Tool that emulates how books display across Kindle devices and apps.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop, Jan 2013</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-jan-2013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-jan-2013/</guid><description>Switching to monthly link drops rather than weekly. Speakeasy Best way to throw a non-exclusive rave or allow a whole bunch of strangers into your party. MoMA Video Game Collection Sees New York Museum Of Modern Art Embrace Digital Gaming I'm glad Tempest made the list. + My Desk - Miguel Mestre Best hack i've seen in a long time, and free. Here's what I'm using http://pastebin.com/raw.php?i=UiUTz3ZH Trello uses an icon font and so can you!</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (Weeks 47-52 2012, 1-3 2013)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-weeks-47-52-2012-1-3-2013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-weeks-47-52-2012-1-3-2013/</guid><description>Crazy big link drop because the world gets crushingly demanding of one's time around the holidays, and it takes time to recoup. Build Your Own Adobe Creative Suite with Free and Cheap Software How Tom Cruise Ruined Interaction Design Form Follows Function FFF is a collection of interactive experiences created by Jongmin Kim in HTML5. One div - The single element HTML/CSS icon database Pure CSS icons. jKit - jQuery based UI Toolkit - Index Ice T on "</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (Weeks 45, 46)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-weeks-45-46/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-weeks-45-46/</guid><description>&amp;lt;ul class=&amp;quot;ld&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://joshduck.com/periodic-table.html&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Periodic Table of the Elements - Josh Duck&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JNjnv-Gcpnw&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Angelina Fabbro: Inspector Web and the Mystery of the Shadow DOM -- JSConf EU 2012 - YouTube&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://icomoon.io/&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;❍ IcoMoon&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://layervault.tumblr.com/post/35721297597/early-sketches-from-the-webs-finest&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Early sketches from the web's finest — LayerVault Blog&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://github.com/xdissent/ievms&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;xdissent/ievms · GitHub&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Microsoft provides virtual machine disk images to facilitate website testing in multiple versions of IE, regardless of the host operating system.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (Week 44)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-44/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-44/</guid><description>If you can, give to the Red Cross to provide support to Hurricane Sandy victims, and help elect a president who will keep FEMA in tact.
All The Cheat Sheets That A Web Developer Needs | Top Design Magazine - Web Design and Digital Content Competing on easy by Jason Fried of 37signals "[T]he part of easy I like is when you take an existing problem, study it until it becomes clear, toss out everything that makes it blurry, and carefully polish what’s left over.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (Weeks 40-43)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-weeks-40-43/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-weeks-40-43/</guid><description>This is a rather long link drop because I've been doin stuff. Skeleton: Beautiful Boilerplate for Responsive, Mobile-Friendly Development Skeleton is a small collection of CSS files that can help you rapidly develop sites that look beautiful at any size, be it a 17" laptop screen or an iPhone. A Former iPhone UI Designer Defends Apple's Fake-Leather Design Philosophy | Co.Design: business + innovation + design The other side to minimalism and a reason to learn the word "</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (Week 36, 39)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-36-39/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-36-39/</guid><description>Have been busy getting settled on the West coast, so starting back up again and a very short list of links. Starter League Want to be the Unicorn? Do it the now. Learn how to code, design, &amp;amp; ship web apps from the pros. Experience Maps: Understanding Cross-Channel Experiences For Gamers / nForm / Blog Gene Smith's Experience Maps example. Anatomy of an Experience Map From Chris Risdon's article on Adaptive Path, that I missed.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (week 35 of 2012)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-35-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-35-2012/</guid><description>The Cooper Journal: The best interface is no interface Matt Swanson - Move your feet The secret to improving your running—you have to start moving your feet. AKA just do it and start now. Responsive Web Above The Fold | CSS-Tricks Great article about taking vertical placement into consideration when doing responsive design, with techniques for detecting height and adjusting vertical space. Usable yet Useless: Why Every Business Needs Product Discovery Great discovery and "</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (week 34 of 2012)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-34-2012/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-34-2012/</guid><description>Light drop this week because I was out camping for most of it. Little tidbit about the Link Drop name. I like it because it reminds me of a record needle drop. Keeping the goal in sight while designing component flows - (Ryan Singer) Ryan Singer looks at a product component that fails to deliver on satisfying a user's core need, and reminds not to design and reviewing components in isolation.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (week 33 of 2012)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-33-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-33-2012/</guid><description>&amp;lt;ul class=&amp;quot;ld&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.bigbuttonsapp.com/&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Big Buttons - control your Mac with your iPhone&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Control anything that you can script on your Mac with your iPhone.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt; &amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.stephenkenn.com/projects/&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;ttl&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Stephen Kenn: Inheritance collection&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; LA designer learns of a military surplus facility and upcycles tons of fabric into furniture with a mid-century nod in form. The video tells the story of the vison and spirit of Kenn. I love videos like this, and the Made by Hand series, that show how a maker starts with a pure idea that is imbued with the creator's beliefs and turns it into a usable product.</description></item><item><title>Link Drop (week 32 of 2012)</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-32-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/link-drop-week-32-2012/</guid><description>An Unexpected Ass Kicking Great post by Joel Runyon, who talks about getting schooled by Russel Kirsch. 2 takeaways: 1) Nothing is withheld from us which we have conceived to do. 2) Do things that have never been done. The first meaning: if you’ve conceived something in your mind, decide to do it, and are willing to put in the work – nothing can stop you. The second is fairly self-explanatory but carries the extra weight of it coming from the guy who invented the very thing that’s letting me type these words out on the internet.</description></item></channel></rss>