<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>agency on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/agency/</link><description>Recent content in agency on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/agency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>dew</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dew/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dew/</guid><description>Minimalistic website for Dew, strategy consultants agency.
http://www.daeasyway.ro/</description></item><item><title>Zoocha</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/zoocha/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/zoocha/</guid><description>Independent and innovative digital agency; delivering web design, seo, ecommerce, content management and marketing services.
http://zoocha.com</description></item><item><title>Webgriffe</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</guid><description>The portfolio site of the Webgriffe does an excellent job highlighting the work of a web agency with interests in both the fashion and design trends. The site immerse the user in a business catwalk video on the background. The studio worked hard to realize a SEO friendly dinamic flash site with deep linking navigation and high attention to usability.
http://www.webgriffe.com</description></item><item><title>Winkreative</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/winkreative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/winkreative/</guid><description>Winkreative's site is a minimalist site that feels like it makes a few design references to elements of Monocle site they designed for the magazine. I like the clean main content pages, the bento box lay out on some portfolio pages, and the intuitive navigation and portfolio filtering. http://www.winkreative.com/</description></item><item><title>Media Pozitiv</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/media-pozitiv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/media-pozitiv/</guid><description>http://www.mediapozitiv.com/</description></item><item><title>BooneOakley</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/booneoakley/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/booneoakley/</guid><description>Ad agencies are outdoing each other in terms of clever uses of social media. BooneOakley's new web site is actually a series of YouTube videos with links placed via annotations into the videos to connect all of what we might traditionally think of as sections. What they create is something like a network of hypertext connections to hold together a concept of site&amp;#8212;hacked together boundaries that create space within another larger space.</description></item><item><title>Pixmac - royalty-free pictures &amp; illustrations, photos &amp; stock images</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/pixmac-royalty-free-pictures-illustrations-photos-stock-images/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/pixmac-royalty-free-pictures-illustrations-photos-stock-images/</guid><description>Over 3 millions of professional royalty-free photos of about anything are available online through the PIXMAC microstock photobank (www.pixmac.com). Press, graphic designers or bloggers can order photographs they need.
The customers can browse the photos by keywords, or they can use the unique database of fresh, daily updated royalty-free celebrity photos.
Although Pixmac sell the photos cheaply, it pays the authors well thanks to the size of the global Internet market.</description></item><item><title>Anaara Media LLC</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/anaara-media-llc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/anaara-media-llc/</guid><description>The website of RIA company Anaara Media LLC has an interesting flash interface which makes use of expanding cards to present its content.
http://anaara.com</description></item><item><title>Web DynamiX</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/web-dynamix/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/web-dynamix/</guid><description>http://www.webdynamix.biz</description></item><item><title>TMX Interactive</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tmx-interactive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tmx-interactive/</guid><description>This clever, comical page for interactive agency, TMX Interactive, features video of a team led by some McGruber-like dude defusing a bomb while a clock ticks down to zero. The old site with info about the company, including their portfolio is actually a lovely minimal site as well. http://www.tmxinteractive.com/</description></item><item><title>BARITCHI</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/baritchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/baritchi/</guid><description>We take things personally and we always pay attention to details because this is our style, this simply represents our way of living and our understanding of life.
http://www.baritchi.eu</description></item><item><title>Work at Play</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/work-play/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/work-play/</guid><description>Work at Play Social Media Labs is a creative agency in Vancouver, BC that works on social media projects. The behaviors make the site feel like it's rendered in Flash, but the nice card flipping case studies on the home page, and the sliding page transitions are all done with Javascript.
http://www.workatplay.com/</description></item><item><title>YCN</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/ycn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/ycn/</guid><description>Nice minimalist design from this London, UK creative organization that is equal parts industry publisher, awards host, events coordinator, and agency, serving up design and communication needs through the members of its collective. This is a multi-faceted org, and starting with the homepage and looking around through the pages, you get the impression that there's a lot of content on this site, and a lot of people involved.</description></item><item><title>Bond Art + Science</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/bond-art-science/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/bond-art-science/</guid><description>The new site for Bond Art + Science mimics an instant messaging window session where Bond are talking to you directly as a potential client. Messages scroll up from the bottom in a canned discussion, almost as if viewing someone's previous IM session. The device would have been very clever if it was actually functioning as a chat bot. This site manages to do one thing very well&amp;#8212;it gets your attention because the presentation is unexpected.</description></item><item><title>IDEO</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/ideo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/ideo/</guid><description>The redesigned IDEO site has been sitting in a browser tab for a few weeks now because it just felt like one of those things I needed to mull over before writing about. It's one of the few sites this year that just took me by surprise. In short, the deep treasure trove of content unleashed in this redesign is a huge departure from the tightly constrained and minimalist prior design.</description></item></channel></rss>