<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interaction Design on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/interaction-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interaction Design on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/interaction-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Principle for Mac: Animation and Prototyping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</guid>
      <description>Principle for Mac ($99) is a tool for designing animation, primarily for mobile devices. It provides an easy to use interface for prototyping interaction, transitions, or other animated elements in your interface.
You can design with text, rectangles (which can modified with border radius to make circles), or graphics created with other tools, and then hook up animations for actions like taps, scrolling, and drag, and use the drivers UI to connect those actions to drive other properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIX UX: Transition and animation gallery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/six-ux-transition-and-animation-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/six-ux-transition-and-animation-gallery/</guid>
      <description>SIX UX is a gallery of transitions and animations shown as 6 second videos. Andreas Popp combined Vine app videos with tumblr to showcase otherwise ephemeral movements found around the web. Low fi and awesome. Check it.
http://sixux.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaningful Transitions: A collection of transition patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/meaningful-transitions-collection-transition-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/meaningful-transitions-collection-transition-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Meaningful Transitions is the thesis project of Johannes Tonollo, an interface design student at the FH Potsdam, Germany. Johannes wrote his Thesis on &amp;quot;Transitions in the User Interface,&amp;quot; in which he analyzed how motion in the user interface can be a helpful extension to static elements to enhance the user experience.
The collection of transitions is clustered into 6 different categories: Orientation, Spatial Extension, Awaking Controls (Awakening?), Highlight, Feedback, and Feedforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MiniAjax: Rich UI Showcase</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/miniajax-rich-ui-showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/miniajax-rich-ui-showcase/</guid>
      <description>MiniAjax is a nice showcase of javascript libraries for rich interaction behaviors.
http://miniajax.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Interaction Design Patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Android Patterns is a community-contributed site with interaction patterns for Android app design. The site is created by the folks at Dutch interaction design firm, UNITiD, who also provide an mobile wireframe templates for Android and Blackberry devices.
http://www.androidpatterns.com/wiki</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phonedoo: Dry erase iPhone sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/phonedoo-dry-erase-iphone-sketching/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo makes a nice iPhone UI sketching product called Phone Doos. They are 6.8&amp;quot; by 3.5&amp;quot; dry erase iPhone surfaces with faint grid lines and magnetic backing. A pack contains 10 Phone Doos.
I like that these gives you a surface to work on that can be re-arranged easily on a table and presented on a metallic wall. They have some good screenshots using them arranged on a whiteboard with flow arrows pointing between them, which is another thing that&#39;s probably much easier with these as opposed to using paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Interaction Design Contest | Building the Internet of Things</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/1st-interaction-design-contest-building-internet-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/1st-interaction-design-contest-building-internet-things/</guid>
      <description>IDAT, the Institute of Design, Art and Technology of Barcelona is holding its 1st Interaction Design Competition based on the theme of designing applications for the next generation Internet of Things.
The competition calls for ideas of interfaces, interactions, and applications that can be designed with technologies such as embedded Radio Frequency Identification (RFID), short-range wireless communication, ubiquitous data networks, mobile devices, hardware prototyping tools and digital fabrication.
The deadline to submit projects is December 15, 2010, and the award is 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LiveView for iPhone &amp; iPad</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/liveview-iphone-ipad/</guid>
      <description>LiveView is a free remote screen viewing application created by Nicholas Zambetti to help designers create graphics for mobile applications, and for quick and dirty simulations, demos, and prototypes.
Visual Designers may use it to view artboard while you work. LiveView is compatible with both standard and Retina displays. Interaction Designers can use with iPhone or iPad tethered via WiFi, to interact with software prototypes and demos running on your Mac to communicate and iterate your concepts quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ForeUI: Create Skinnable &amp; Interactive Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/foreui-create-skinnable-interactive-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/foreui-create-skinnable-interactive-prototype/</guid>
      <description>ForeUI is a handy UI prototyping tool. It can rapidly create skinnable and
clickable UI prototype for your website or software, and run the interactive
simulation in your web browser.
ForeUI provides a set of predefined elements for creating mockup, you can drag
them into the editing area and tweak them. You can also create your own elements
and libraries.
ForeUI makes prototype skinnable, by changing the UI theme, all elements in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Interaction Design a dead-end job?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-dead-end-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-dead-end-job/</guid>
      <description>In the Cooper Journal, Tim McCoy responds to Bill Moggridge&#39;s comment after a screening of Objectified. He paraphrases Moggridge as saying interaction design has become pervasive, that anyone and everyone can be an interaction designer, and so the role of professional interaction designer is (or is becoming) unnecessary.
McCoy asks if interaction design is really dead. He goes on to point out a few factors that have allowed developers to build better interfaces without interaction designers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Language We Use</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/language-we-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/language-we-use/</guid>
      <description>In &#34;The language we use,&#34; David Malouf discusses how ideas about user interaction can become so ingrained in what we are familiar with, that our language begins to reflect that familiarity. That can lead to a natural tendency to explain away interaction without thought to what it means to the design of a thing. In this case a student describes the change of context in a sketch presentation by using the word &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing Web Interfaces: 12 Standard Screen Patterns</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-web-interfaces-12-standard-screen-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-web-interfaces-12-standard-screen-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Bill Scott and Theresa Neil&amp;rsquo;s new O’Reilly book, “Designing Web Interfaces: Principles and Patterns for Rich Interactions,” presents more than 75 design patterns for building web interfaces that provide rich interaction. They&amp;rsquo;ve shared the full set of principles and patterns they use for RIA design in this article.
http://designingwebinterfaces.com/designing-web-interfaces-12-screen-patterns</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>patternBrowser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/patternbrowser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/patternbrowser/</guid>
      <description>patternBrowser is an amazing design pattern library produced by the Interface Design Team of the University of Applied Sciences Potsdam. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a little time looking through the interaction design category, and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of great examples there, and most importantly they&amp;rsquo;ve done the work of organizing and describing each problem/solution thoroughly. Check it out.
http://www.patternbrowser.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle vs. iPhone/iPod Touch: Human/Machine Interaction &amp; User Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kindle-vs-iphoneipod-touch-humanmachine-interaction-user-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kindle-vs-iphoneipod-touch-humanmachine-interaction-user-experience/</guid>
      <description>Tog&#39;s comparison and analysis of the human computer interaction versus the user experience with both the Amazon Kindle and the iPhone/iPod Touch is excellent. The separation of HCI/UX in his analysis really drives the point home that good interaction and industrial design can make the experience, and a good experience isn&#39;t only about the design.
I don&#39;t use a Kindle daily, so I can&#39;t comment personally on it, but the industrial design was a showstopper for me and kept me from wanting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframing Experiences and Applications with Flash Catalyst</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-experiences-and-applications-flash-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframing-experiences-and-applications-flash-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>Peter Flynn gives a demo of wireframing in Adobe Flash Catalyst, aka Thermo. Every online demo I&amp;rsquo;ve seen of this product looks more and more exciting, and this is truly going to give Mac users a way to do easy interactive prototypes as our PC brothers and sisters can do with tools like Axure. I fully expect to be using this thing when it gets out of Preview release. It&amp;rsquo;s only slightly ironic that his first 5 minutes are talk about how wireframes are by definition, low fidelity, given my last post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fear of the High Fidelity Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fear-high-fidelity-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fear-high-fidelity-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>In Twitter today, I posted a message that I need to resist putting rounded corners on boxes in wireframes. Then I got a few replies essentially saying that stylized elements shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be in wireframes. Context is everything. Taken out of context, it is very difficult to possibly critique a specific design technique without knowing the how and why you&amp;rsquo;re using it. Because of that 140 character constraint in Twitter, I didn&amp;rsquo;t really explain that this rounded corner example came from my hybrid high-fidelity wireframing and visual design document I was working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Your Own Magnetic Prototype</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/create-your-own-magnetic-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/create-your-own-magnetic-prototype/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Path&amp;rsquo;s Alexa Andrzejewski suggests how to create your own magnetic prototypes using printable magnets for user interface elements. Good stuff. Customizable and inexpensive.
http://www.adaptivepath.com/blog/2008/11/17/magneticprototyping/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Interaction Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/thoughts-interaction-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/thoughts-interaction-design/</guid>
      <description>Just getting around to reading Jon Kolko&amp;rsquo;s Thoughts on Interaction Design, which is available online now that the printed book is no longer available.
http://thoughtsoninteraction.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The what, when and why of wireframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-when-and-why-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-when-and-why-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>James Kelway&amp;rsquo;s article on wireframes in the User Pathways blog summarizes what the different types are, what their purpose is, who the audience for their use are, and how they are typically implemented. There are several nice illustrations in this article for those that need to explain what they are.
http://userpathways.com/2008/06/26/the-what-when-and-why-of-wireframes/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton Lecture on Sketching and Experience Design at Stanford</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-lecture-sketching-and-experience-design-stanford/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton gives a lecture at the Stanford University Human-Computer Interaction Seminar (CS 547, June 1, 2007) giving an excellent deep dive into some of the topics in his book, Sketching User Experiences.
 Designing for experience comes with a whole new level of complexity. This is especially true in this emerging world of information appliances, reactive environments, and ubiquitous computing, where, along with those of their users, we have to factor in the convoluted behaviors of the products themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction-Patterns.org</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-patterns-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-patterns-org/</guid>
      <description>Interaction-Patterns.org is the Stimmt AG - Uni Basel Pattern Catalogue. The Patterns page lists each design pattern name, a very brief description of the interaction, and a link to the page that describes the design pattern, e.g. YUI or Welie pages.
http://www.interaction-patterns.org/wiki/index.php?title=Patterns</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interface and Interaction Design Video Bloggers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interface-and-interaction-design-video-bloggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interface-and-interaction-design-video-bloggers/</guid>
      <description>I recently noticed that I&#39;m not the only one posting interface design and interaction videos on Vimeo. Here are 4 Vimeo users who are doing this now:
 Alex G Christian Schlatter Ivan Bachev Michael Angeles (Me)  Know of any other UI and Interaction Design video bloggers? Let me know about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction-Design.org</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-org/</guid>
      <description>Interaction-Design.org is a free, open-content, peer-reviewed Encyclopedia and glossary covering terms from the disciplines of Interaction Design, Human-Computer Interaction (HCI), Design, Human Factors, Usability, Information Architecture, and related fields.
http://www.interaction-design.org/encyclopedia/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CamSpace Webcam Game Controller</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/camspace-webcam-game-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/camspace-webcam-game-controller/</guid>
      <description>Camspace is pretty slick. The people at CamTrax are demoing the PC camera-based interface. At first blush, I thought it similar to the gimicky Eye Toy games, but this is much better. CamTrax is a software-based technology that enables the tracking of hand-held objects in real time, with high reliability. What you see in the demo is that the software recognizes the hand-held objects and effectively turns them into pointers and other controls that can be used to act on the simple end as a cursor, and on the more sophisticated end as a game controller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fine Art of Wireframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fine-art-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fine-art-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>On the Geniant blog, T.Scott Stromberg exposes his craft of wireframe sketching. I also spend most of my ideation time sketching. It&#39;s lovely to see other people&#39;s methods for getting ideas down. I love Stromberg&#39;s comments and comic book style.
This might sound kind of pathetic, but seeing the pens and paper he uses is the kind of thing I really geek out on. I love that he&#39;s pimping out the Behance dot grid pads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone versus tPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-versus-tphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-versus-tphone/</guid>
      <description>Edward Tufte posted an essay and video with commentary about the iPhone. Tufte is complimentary, for the most part, about the interface being predominantly free of administrative debris, but makes suggestions for how the iPhone can make better use of its screen resolution. As expected, his argument calls for more data density when possible.
He notes that the iPhone has elegantly removed administrative clutter in many places, using the information as the interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer Unlocks Wii&#39;s Hidden Potential</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</guid>
      <description>CNET reports on Johnny Chung Lee&amp;rsquo;s interaction experiments with the Wii Remote. Lee, a Phd student at Carnegie Melon, does a quick demo of head tracking for VR displays and multi point interaction using the wii remote. His experiments describe with incredible clarity how the wii remote fundamentally works and how the remote might be exploited to do much more than point at single points on the screen and control them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Pattern Libraries and UI Guidelines</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-pattern-libraries-and-ui-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-pattern-libraries-and-ui-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for conventional, reliable, and tested user interface patterns for common interface problems, look no further.
Pattern Libraries  Welie Interaction Design Pattern Library Yahoo! Design Pattern Library UI Patterns Peter Morville&amp;rsquo;s Search Patterns Collection on Flickr The Design Of Sites Book See also: Tom Erickson&amp;rsquo;s Interaction Design Patterns page which provides a listing of further design pattern resources.  User Interface Guidelines  Apple Human Interface Guidelines Usability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>