<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>resources on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/resources/</link><description>Recent content in resources on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>So you wanna be a user experience designer</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/so-you-wanna-be-user-experience-designer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/so-you-wanna-be-user-experience-designer/</guid><description>Whitney Hess has put together the first part of a series of articles for those looking to get into user experience design. The first part is a collection of resources to get immersed in the topics of the field. Whitney writes:
The best way to learn a new language is to go to a country where it’s spoken and immerse yourself in the confusion. Soon the unfamiliar will become familiar, and before you know it you’ll be fluent.</description></item><item><title>A Project Guide to UX Design</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/project-guide-ux-design/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/project-guide-ux-design/</guid><description>The companion site to the book, Project Guide to UX Design: For User Experience Designers in the Field or in the Making, by authors Russ Unger &amp;amp; Carolyn Chandler contains additional reference materials from the book and a bonus chapter, “A Brief Guide to Meetings”.
http://projectuxd.com/</description></item><item><title>Dey Alexander's User Experience Design Resources</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/dey-alexanders-user-experience-design-resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/dey-alexanders-user-experience-design-resources/</guid><description>Dey Alexander Consulting's user experience design resources directory is an extensive, categorized collection of bibliographies, tools, and resources.
http://deyalexander.com/resources/uxd/</description></item><item><title>IAApps: UX Software Directory</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/iaapps-ux-software-directory/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/iaapps-ux-software-directory/</guid><description>IAApps is a directory of usability, information architecture, and user experience design software.
http://www.iaapps.com/</description></item><item><title>Webmonkey Relaunch</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/webmonkey-relaunch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/webmonkey-relaunch/</guid><description>You remember Webmonkey, that web design resource many of us grew up with when we were cutting our teeth on HTML. Wired redesigned and re-launched with a few new articles, and some of the old tutes and cheat sheets seem to have been updated. The entire code library appears to be a wiki, so it's open for editing. We'll keep our eyes open to see if anyone kicks in some quality material.</description></item></channel></rss>