<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dialogs on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/dialogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dialogs on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/dialogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Delete Timer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-delete-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-delete-timer/</guid>
      <description>YouTube puts up 2 speed bumps when you try to delete a video from the video manager. This technique slows down the user about to peform a destructive action, and protects them from inadvertently deleting content.
1. Selecting Delete action shows dialog confirming action.2. A second confirmation dialog requires confirmation, but the Delete button is disabled until the countdown timer runs out. https://www.youtube.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons, Revised</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</guid>
      <description>We covered Shelfari&#39;s hybrid button in their list views of bookshelf items. That example showed a single push button with an attached icon for drop down menu. The single button allowed for the use of a default behavior, while the drop down arrow allowed for the display of other options for the item. The drop down menu allowed users to make multiple selections, i.e. using checkbox behaviors, rather than just select one value in the drop down list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aardvark Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</guid>
      <description>The registration process on Aardvark provides a modal dialog that uses some nice content previews, content filtering, and progressive disclosure to guide the new user through the form. 1. Clicking sign up button from an invitation opens modal dialog with basic information form. A preview area updates your info as you fill out the form.2. The birthday input filters and corrects date format. City/State shows suggestions. (The one in yellow is a browser auto-completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study of User Response to Fake Dialogs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/study-user-response-fake-dialogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/study-user-response-fake-dialogs/</guid>
      <description>Ars reports on a study by the psychology department at NC State that will appear in the Proceedings of the Human Factors and Ergonomics Society. The study tested how college students respond to fake dialog boxes in browser popup windows and found that the students are so anxious to get the dialog out of the way, they click right through obvious warning signs. Follow-up questions revealed that the students seemed to find any dialog box a distraction from their assigned task; nearly half said that all they cared about was getting rid of these dialogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SugarSync Creating and Moving Items</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-creating-and-moving-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-creating-and-moving-items/</guid>
      <description>SugarSync&#39;s web-based document management application allows users to manage files that are kept on their computers. The interactions for creating and moving folders use an identical design pattern for placing items in a directory on the file system. This is similar to the Save As behavior in operating systems such as the Mac Finder and Windows Explorer, which will let users navigate to a disk drive, and then drill down deeply into a directory location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SugarSync Uploading Files</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-uploading-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-uploading-files/</guid>
      <description>SugarSync&#39;s upload file behavior uses a customized interface that is not typical. Instead of using the browser behavior for handling file uploads using &amp;lt;input type=&#34;file&#34;&amp;gt;, which typically provides an input and browse button in Firefox and Internet Explorer, SugarSync uses a single button to invoke the file browsing window, and then displays the file&#39;s name in HTML. To be fair, Safari provides a slicker interface for file uploads, which doesn&#39;t display an input, but only a button, and then shows the file name next to the button when a file is found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Sites Theme Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-theme-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-theme-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google released the technology acquired by JotSpot as the new Sites tool in the Google Apps suite. The Sites tools provides the interface you see here for modifying the appearance of your site, using pre-defined themes as a starting place, allowing you to modify the layout of content modules in the left column, and the colors used in the layout.
1. Selecting a theme.2. Modifying page elements.3. Configuring a module.4. Setting colors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
