<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>3d on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/3d/</link><description>Recent content in 3d on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BiDi Screen</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</guid><description>BiDi Screen was demonstrated at SIGGRAPH Asia this year. It is a thin, depth-sensing LCD for 3D interaction using light fields.
The BiDi Screen is an example of a new type of I/O device that possesses the ability to both capture images and display them. This thin, bidirectional screen extends the latest trend in LCD devices, which has seen the incorporation of photo-diodes into every display pixel. Using a novel optical masking technique developed at the Media Lab, the BiDi Screen can capture lightfield-like quantities, unlocking a wide array of applications from 3-D gesture interaction with CE devices, to seamless video communication.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Levine Design</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/jeremy-levine-design/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/jeremy-levine-design/</guid><description>The portfolio site of the Jeremy Levine Design does an excellent job highlighting the work of an architecture studio with interests in both the natural and digital environment. The site unfolds, spins, explodes, and collapses on itself to immerse the user in the projects, exploring each environment from multiple facets. The studio worked with Section Seven to realize a site that borrows some of the techniques used in that studio's own portfolio, but contextualizes the experience for exploring 3 dimensional architectural spaces.</description></item><item><title>UNIQLO TRY</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</guid><description>Yugo Nakamura and the Simone Inc. crew are serving up some sick Flash once again for Uniqlo. This time, the mini site is devoted to women's bras. The mood is cheerful as happy electronic strings accompany the dizzying array of women's headshots spinning and combining to create patterns in 3D space. Click on a picture to reveal the details (in Japanese) of one of the women's age, height, and bra size, or use the pop up menus to filter the set down.</description></item><item><title>krolikov</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/krolikov/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/krolikov/</guid><description>Krolikov is the illustration and animation studio of Russian designer Sedova Elena. Great illustration, and the subtle 3d effect of the boxes adds dimension and interest to the frame surrounding the content. The little touches of animation are brilliant, e.g. the plug in effect on the home link electrical cord and the little motion when mousing over the global nav. I was sort of expecting the little character on top of the books to wink at me or something.</description></item><item><title>dasai</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dasai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dasai/</guid><description>http://www.dasai.es/</description></item><item><title>VaryWell</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/varywell/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/varywell/</guid><description>VaryWell is the portfolio of Seattle, Washington designers Ryan and Jason Hickner. The Hickners work on in web sites, interactive displays, and interesting hardware projects including a very cool LED light color mixer. Their portfolio is a nice demonstration of the the Flash Papervision tools. Selecting a project presents a stack of media that are unshuffled and spread around the screen, much as you would spread a set of slides on a lightbox.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Interactive</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dragon-interactive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dragon-interactive/</guid><description>http://dragoninteractive.com/</description></item><item><title>Gutenberg On Line</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/gutenberg-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/gutenberg-line/</guid><description>http://gol.com.pl</description></item></channel></rss>