<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>user experience on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/user-experience/</link><description>Recent content in user experience on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/user-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Letting Go</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/letting-go/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/letting-go/</guid><description>Two great slides from Yiibu's presentation, Letting Go, a talk about design in an time of increasing disruption.
"Issuing your customers with something that is rough, incomplete, and possibly even substandard seems counterintuitive but there is growing evidence that people don't necessarily want the perfect product. They prefer to deal with something ragged around the edges that they can adapt or improve."
&amp;#8212; Martin Thomas in "Loose: The Future of Business is Letting Go"</description></item><item><title>Kathy Sierra on Creating Awesome Users</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/kathy-sierra-creating-awesome-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/kathy-sierra-creating-awesome-users/</guid><description>The model for sustaining customer loyalty is reverse engineering user awesomeness.
Peldi pointed me to a video of Kathy Sierra's presentation at Business of Software 09, where she talks about sustaining passionate and loyal customers. Positioning and generating sustainable relationships is not what you think it should be about. It's about user benefits, and not features--about how they feel about themselves in the context of what you provide them.</description></item><item><title>UX Lessons Learned From Offline Experiences</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-lessons-learned-offline-experiences/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-lessons-learned-offline-experiences/</guid><description>Jon Phillips writes about how the user experience of restaurant flow can be redesigned by illustrating the flow in a cafeteria-style space from entry, order and pickup to seating and exit. In his great diagrams he shows how the orginal flow frustrated diners (users) and could be easily re-designed to consider a flow that was immediately understandable--the design he experienced made him feel stupid. Sound familiar?
I think about interior spaces like lines at Whole Foods, where sometimes it makes absolutely no sense (I'm looking at you Columbus Circle) and where other lines seem to have considered this (Union Square sometimes feels efficient).</description></item><item><title>uxurls.com: A user experience aggregator</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/uxurlscom-user-experience-aggregator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/uxurlscom-user-experience-aggregator/</guid><description>uxurls is a single page aggregator for UX news feeds. The page format is similar to popurls, and is intended for people who are too busy to set themselves up with their own RSS reader, or just fancy a quick glance at the latest UX news. The page is curated by Harry Brignull, creator of 90 percent of everything. Feeds are refreshed once every 24 hours.
http://uxurls.com/</description></item><item><title>52 Weeks of UX</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/52-weeks-ux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/52-weeks-ux/</guid><description>It's nice to have something good to look forward to every week, and Joshua Porter and Joshua Brewer will deliver by writing a weekly blog about user experience. Nice.
http://52weeksofux.com/</description></item><item><title>Webgriffe</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</guid><description>The portfolio site of the Webgriffe does an excellent job highlighting the work of a web agency with interests in both the fashion and design trends. The site immerse the user in a business catwalk video on the background. The studio worked hard to realize a SEO friendly dinamic flash site with deep linking navigation and high attention to usability.
http://www.webgriffe.com</description></item><item><title>Keith Lang's Top 10 UX Myths</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/keith-langs-top-10-ux-myths/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/keith-langs-top-10-ux-myths/</guid><description>Keith Lang, co-founder of plasq.com, wrote a fantastic article for Think Vitamin about UX Myths. It's full of references and examples debunking stuff we hear repeated enough times that they begin to go unquestioned.
The top 10 UX myth list:
The Design Has to be Original People Read People Know What They Like Design Always with Implementation in Mind Can’t Decide? Make it a Preference If you Have Great Search, You Don’t Need Great Information Architecture UX Design Stops at the Edges of the Product Design to Avoid Clicks People Don’t Change If the Design is a Good One, You Don’t Need to Test It Some of these become so ingrained, that it takes a lot of effort to convince clients or colleagues otherwise.</description></item><item><title>User Experience Publications</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-publications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-publications/</guid><description>Nick Finck has created an excellent bibliography of UX web publications. The list is grouped into three main sections; Industry Publications (non-corporate ezines and/or printed magazines), Team &amp;amp; Company Publications (multi-author and/or business focused publications), and Personal Publications (practitioners who write). View the list here.
http://www.nickfinck.com/blog/entry/user_experience_publications/</description></item><item><title>Is Information Architecture Dying?</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/information-architecture-dying/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/information-architecture-dying/</guid><description>Anthony Viviano at Organic asks if Information Architecture is dead, continuing the discussions about the inclusiveness and expanding scope of IA vis-a-vis UX, and hopping on the question about interaction design being a dead end job. Clearly, he doesn't think the practice and craft of IA is dead, just as the craft of Interaction Design is clearly alive. But the role is changing, and while the navel gazing gets resoundingly loud around defining things, the definition of the shifting roles and responsibilities in the field is meaningful.</description></item><item><title>Nick's Top User Experience Books</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/nicks-top-user-experience-books/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/nicks-top-user-experience-books/</guid><description>Nick lists his list of recommended user experience books. http://www.nickfinck.com/blog/entry/nicks_top_user_experience_books</description></item><item><title>A Discussion on User Experience Design</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/discussion-user-experience-design/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/discussion-user-experience-design/</guid><description>I spoke with Russ Perry at the Phoenix Ad Blog to discuss what User Experience Design might mean to graphic designers and marketing professionals, especially those not involved in the design of sites and apps. I don't like getting caught up in the "defining the damned thing" discussions, but there you have it. Oh, and I mention Zappos, not because of their visual or interface design, per se, but about their relevance in terms of the holistic approach to user experience outside of the interface.</description></item><item><title>The History &amp; Evolution of User Experience Design</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/history-evolution-user-experience-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/history-evolution-user-experience-design/</guid><description>On the Tea with Teresa podcast, Teresa Brazen interviews Adaptive Path's Peter Merholz to talk about the history and evolution of User Experience Design. User experience design is, at its core, a philosophy that products and services should be designed so that they are pleasurable and easy for people to use. While that might seem an obvious design approach, it's actually not the way many designers historically thought about making things.</description></item><item><title>User Experience Deliverables</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-deliverables/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-deliverables/</guid><description>Peter Morville and Jeffrey Callender have been compiling a list of UX deliverables and have summarized 20 of them succintly on the Semantic Studios site.
This list describes twenty user experience deliverables with links to relevant resources and examples. Clearly, these artifacts of the process are not the whole story. We must also think about the relationship between goals, methods, and documents. And yet, for many of us, deliverables are the coin of the realm and merit special attention.</description></item><item><title>10 Most Common Misconceptions About User Experience Design</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/10-most-common-misconceptions-about-user-experience-design/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/10-most-common-misconceptions-about-user-experience-design/</guid><description>Whitney Hess asked some of the most influential and widely respected practitioners in UX what they consider to be the biggest misperceptions of what we do. The result is not only a terrific list that debunks myths, but an excellent compilation of quotes that better describe what UX is about than a clinical definition can. Those who were quoted described UX as many things, from the reach and touch of customers with products and companies, to the processes we use and the roles we play when we take part in its design.</description></item><item><title>9 experiences for 2009</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/9-experiences-2009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/9-experiences-2009/</guid><description>Brandon Schauer gives us 9 ideas for experiences whose time has come--the idea being that these are things we can do to create or extend the experience with our businesses because the timing is right. With luck, execution of any of these ideas can turn into real value for businesses and their customers.
http://www.adaptivepath.com/blog/2009/01/05/9-experiences-for-2009/</description></item></channel></rss>