<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>static sites on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/static-sites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in static sites on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 15:15:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/static-sites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots Static Site Builder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 15:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</guid>
      <description>Roots is an open source static site compiler that can help take some of the work out of setting up your own build tasks using taskrunners like gulp or grunt. It runs in your terminal and requires minimal setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo: Konigi is now a Static Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>After many years of being a Drupal user, from version 2 when I started iaslash.org to version 6 on this site, I&amp;rsquo;ve made the move from PHP/MySQL blog to full on static site. Here&amp;rsquo;s why and how I did it.
Choosing Static Site Generators In the past few years, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken a few sites backwards from Drupal and WordPress into the age of static sites. In many ways, it feels like going back to the beginning of my career, when I used Perl and Shell scripts to generate sites in my first job, and later to more sophisticated site generation using MovableType as a middle man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generator Directories</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/static-site-generator-directories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/static-site-generator-directories/</guid>
      <description>These are the 2 main directories listing generators that you can use to build a static site. Each offers a sortable lists to browse by user rating or language.
StaticGen - Lists the top Open Source static site generators only. Filter by language. Sort by rating, issues, forks, titles.
Static Site Generators - Lists Open Source and Commercial static site generators. Sort by rating, license, and language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
