<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tips on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred/Hazel Workflow for Screen Capture</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/alfredhazel-workflow-screen-capture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/alfredhazel-workflow-screen-capture/</guid>
      <description>If you take a lot of screenshots on a Mac like me, you probably have a good workflow for doing it using something like LittleSnapper/Ember, Awesome Screenshot or Skitch. The biggest problem I&#39;ve had is that after I take a screenshot, I often want to do something with it. I can do this by just getting Cloud to watch and upload files passively, but I&#39;ve always wanted to save to my own server after just issuing one command to capture the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Creative People Need to Be Eccentric</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/why-creative-people-need-be-eccentric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/why-creative-people-need-be-eccentric/</guid>
      <description>I love these two posts by Mark McGuiness on the 99% on why eccentricity and how daily routine helps trigger creativity.
He points out three characteristics of a hypnotic trigger:
Uniqueness - it should be something (or a combination of things) you don&#39;t associate with other activities, otherwise the effect will be diluted.
Emotional intensity - the kind you experience when you&#39;re really immersed in creative work.
Repetition - the more times you experience the unique trigger in association with the emotions, the stronger the association becomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Tree Components in OmniGraffle</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-make-tree-components-omnigraffle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-make-tree-components-omnigraffle/</guid>
      <description>I swear I&#39;ve answered this question a dozen times, so I&#39;m capturing to refer people in the future. The tree control in my OmnGraffle Wireframe Stencil is a godawful hack that uses tabs and arrow characters. Copying and pasting the arrows, however, screws up the formatting. OmniGraffle just doesn&#39;t make this kind of manipulation of text all that easy and I haven&#39;t found an ideal solution, but if you want to learn how I do it, read on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups Tips and Tricks, Chapter 1: Working with Controls</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mockups-tips-and-tricks-chapter-1-working-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mockups-tips-and-tricks-chapter-1-working-controls/</guid>
      <description>Peldi from Balsamiq shares some power user tips and tricks for Mockups controls. In this video he shows keyboard shortcuts and methods for selection, snapping, layering, locking, aligning and zooming.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1mnlN4SJxFg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annotating Specs With Tracing Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/annotating-specs-tracing-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/annotating-specs-tracing-paper/</guid>
      <description>Donna Lichaw posted a photo showing a nice method for annotating specs using tracing paper or vellum.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/dlichaw/4053897862/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Tip: Change Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-tip-change-keyboard-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-tip-change-keyboard-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a tip that I blurted out on Twitter in a moment of frustration. I use both Adobe Illustrator and OmniGraffle, and one thing that repeatedly trips me up is using the keyboard shortcuts for grouping/ungrouping between the two apps. Illustrator uses Cmd-G to group, and OmniGraffle uses Shift-Cmd-G. They add the Shift key because CMD-G is assigned to search again which I don&amp;rsquo;t use all that often.
The fix for this, as well as for any Mac application is simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac Tip: Mounting a Server Automatically</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mac-tip-mounting-server-automatically/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mac-tip-mounting-server-automatically/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve always found a chore, being a producer of graphic documents, is versioning and organizing the docs for a team. I&amp;rsquo;ve had to use different tools like Source Safe, Sharepoint, Basecamp, and just shared drives to this. One nice thing I like about working with our Traction server is that it does Webdav for document management and file versioning. That&amp;rsquo;s one of the projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on a preview release of to make the web-based interface a bit more friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>