<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hacks on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/hacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hacks on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/hacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking an iClooly iPad Stylus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-iclooly-ipad-stylus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-iclooly-ipad-stylus/</guid>
      <description>The iClooly is the pen I&#39;ve been using most for quick sketches on the iPad, but for longer sketches and for drawing the handwritten font I&#39;m making in iFontMaker, the short stick kind of sucks. Extending the iClooly stick is an easy hack that almost doesn&#39;t merit a post: rip off the back, take apart a mechanical pencil, and mash the two together.
Verbose version: Remove the clicky end and the spring inside, making sure the brush is pressed down and the bristles exposed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking a Pogo Stylus for Smoother iPad Sketching</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-pogo-stylus-smoother-ipad-sketching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hacking-pogo-stylus-smoother-ipad-sketching/</guid>
      <description>I blogged about what I thought could possibly make a better stylus recently and thought I&#39;d sketch what I was thinking. The above picture shows how I think you could hack the Pogo Sketch stylus so it will glide a little more smoothly on the iPad screen. The capacitive foam creates a little too much friction to feel natural to me. I drilled a small hole in the foam and inserted a plastic nib from an old pressure-sensitive screen stylus into the center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low-Cost Multi-point Interactive Whiteboards Using the Wiimote</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</guid>
      <description>Researcher provides another Wii Remote hack, this time to help business users create interactive whiteboards on the cheap.
 You might remember the incredible Wiimote hacks by by Johnny Chung Lee, who gave us head tracking demo for desktop VR displays. Lee, a PhD student in the Human-Computer Interaction Institute at Carnegie Mellon University is back with some more useful Wiimote hacks, this time to turn any surface into an interactive whiteboard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
