<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sketch-books on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/sketch-books/</link><description>Recent content in sketch-books on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 12:06:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/sketch-books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>5.25 Inch Floppy Sketchbook Is Back</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 12:06:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</guid><description>Remember these? From 2009-2010 I these sketchbooks for a while, using a 5.25&amp;rdquo; floppy disk as a notebook cover. I kind of missed them, so I made a limited number in blank and grid paper.
It’s a wirebound 5.25 inch square sketchbook with about 120-130 pages (60-65 sheets) of 70 pound white vellum paper, hand-crafted by me in my home North of the SF Bay. You can buy a book with blank sheets or one printed with 1cm grid in warm gray ink.</description></item><item><title>Responsive Sketch Pad from UI Stencils</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/responsive-sketch-pad-ui-stencils/</guid><description>UI Stencils' responsive design sketchpad is made to help figure out breakpoints and how your product might translate to mobile and tablet versions. 2 device silhouettes on the front and 3 on the back. 50 pages on 70# paper in Letter or A4.
http://www.uistencils.com/products/responsive-sketch-pad</description></item><item><title>Whitelines Link</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</guid><description>Everyone's getting in on on the physical paper capturing game using the iPhone's camera. Whitelines is one of my favorite sketch paper makers. They make great graph paper that reverses the grid using white lines over pale a gray paper. The result is that the grid it more subtle and less distracting
The Whitelines Link product is a free iPhone app that let's you capture sketches made on their new Whitelines Link papers.</description></item><item><title>Evernote Smart Notebook by Moleskine</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/evernote-smart-notebook-moleskine/</guid><description>I've tried a lot of tools for transferring sketches from analog sketchbook to digital. I was an early Pen-It user, have used page cutters with a scanner, and have lately just resorted to taking photos with my iPhone. The Evernote/Moleskine Smart Notebook looks like it might provide the right mix I'm looking for.
I've given up on the idea of converting paper sketches to vector drawings. What this seems to offer is the ability to use that dotted sheet tech to correctly line up your photos taken with Evernote app, and combines that with some neat stickers that will automatically route your sketches to tags and/or specific notebooks.</description></item><item><title>Sketchbooks: DIY Instructions</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbooks-diy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchbooks-diy/</guid><description>This is a guide for binding your own sketchbooks. I offer it to you designers, developers, makers, and tinkerers out there who are looking for a way to physically connect to your practice of designing interfaces, or who maybe just want a fun and practical way to get your hands dirty.
I started making my own sketchbooks and pads a few years ago. At the time there weren't many options for interface sketching and storyboarding.</description></item><item><title>Sketchbooks: DIY Instructions</title><link>http://konigi.com/tools/sketchbooks-diy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/tools/sketchbooks-diy/</guid><description>This is a guide for binding your own sketchbooks. I offer it to you designers, developers, makers, and tinkerers out there who are looking for a way to physically connect to your practice of designing interfaces, or who maybe just want a fun and practical way to get your hands dirty.
Enjoy! -Michael
I started making my own sketchbooks and pads a few years ago. At the time there weren't many options for interface sketching and storyboarding.</description></item><item><title>App Sketchbook: iPhone App Sketchbook</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/app-sketchbook-iphone-app-sketchbook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/app-sketchbook-iphone-app-sketchbook/</guid><description>This is sweet. A sketchbook made for iPhone app design. Features three actual-size iPhone templates per page, pixel (20px) ruler and title bar markings, ruled section for app development notes, and 600 screens (100 double-sided pages).
http://appsketchbook.com/</description></item></channel></rss>