<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brainstorming on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/brainstorming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brainstorming on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/brainstorming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Edistorm</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/edistorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/edistorm/</guid>
      <description>Edistorm looks like an interesting tool for collaborative brainstorming. Group brainstorming sticky note boards (storms) can be set up with a background template, e.g. 5 up, SWOT, venn diagrams, etc. You place colored sticky notes with text, organize however you want, you can add +1 votes using a voting system, and add comments to notes. There&amp;rsquo;s some kind of recomendations feature that will suggest new topics, which I guess might only work well with certain content types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effectiveness of Brainstorming</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/effectiveness-brainstorming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/effectiveness-brainstorming/</guid>
      <description>Found on smartex, and believed by jibbajabba to occasionally be true of group brainstorming&amp;hellip;
Wikipedia on &amp;ldquo;Brainstorming&amp;rdquo;.
Although brainstorming has become a popular group technique, researchers have generally failed to find evidence of its effectiveness for enhancing either quantity or quality of ideas generated. Because of such problems as distraction, social loafing, evaluation apprehension, and production blocking, brainstorming groups are little more effective than other types of groups, and they are actually less effective than individuals working independently.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>