<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hybrid on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/hybrid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hybrid on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/hybrid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blitz 3.0 Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/blitz-30-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/blitz-30-site/</guid>
      <description>The latest incarnation of the online presence for Blitz Agency. I like the clean interface and the fact they haven&amp;rsquo;t abandoned flash entirely.
http://www.blitzagency.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons, Revised</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</guid>
      <description>We covered Shelfari&#39;s hybrid button in their list views of bookshelf items. That example showed a single push button with an attached icon for drop down menu. The single button allowed for the use of a default behavior, while the drop down arrow allowed for the display of other options for the item. The drop down menu allowed users to make multiple selections, i.e. using checkbox behaviors, rather than just select one value in the drop down list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wowhead Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Wowhead is a database of World of Warcraft information. The database provides a hierarchical subject taxonomy to describe items, and presents that hierarchy in the breadcrumbs for the item. When the user hovers ofer a branch in the breadcrumb trail, a drop down menu is displayed to show the node siblings and drill down to children. 1. Single entry view (database record).2. Hovering over the current entry&#39;s parent category (Daggers) to view siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Breadcrumb Tab</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo&#39;s hybrid tab/breadcrumb navigation is one of my favorite approaches to global and local navigation. This navigation interface answers a few nagging questions that an interface designer might ask. &#34;How do I present the user with an interface that provides focus on the area they&#39;ve navigated to, while providing a path back or to other main areas of interest?&#34;
What&#39;s interesting here is that they provide a row of primary navigation tabs at the top level, and replace that with a hybrid tab/breadcrumb once the user makes the decision to drill down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panic Tabs and Carousel Panel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/panic-tabs-and-carousel-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/panic-tabs-and-carousel-panel/</guid>
      <description>Panic&#39;s product page for Coda provides a hybrid interface utilizing both tabs along the top of the information panel, and arrows on the sides to slide through all of the pages in a carousel.
1. The product information panel in the full page.2. Clicking the next arrow slides to the next panel in the carousel.3. Clicking a tab further to the right, slides all panels off to the left until the target page is reached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Autos Carousel and Accordion Panel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-autos-carousel-and-accordion-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-autos-carousel-and-accordion-panel/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Autos has uses a nice hybrid design pattern for promoting the different categories of top cars selected by users. Situated in the right hand column, the arrows at the upper right allow the user to slide through the different lists. The details for the top car are shown in an exposed panel of the accordion, and the titles of the remaining 4 are displayed as well with large number to indicate order.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>