<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Magazines on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/magazines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Magazines on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/magazines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Offscreen Magazine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/offscreen-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/offscreen-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Offscreen is a print magazine that takes an in-depth look at the life and work of people that create websites and apps. They&amp;rsquo;re interested in telling the less obvious human stories of creativity, passion and hard work that hide behind every interface.
The first issue includes conversations with web standards wizard Dan Cederholm, all-round-talent Drew Wilson, former last.fm design lead Hannah Donovan, 37signals&#39; designer and product manager Ryan Singer, design entrepreneur Andrew Wilkinson and pixel-perfectionist Benjamin de Cock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Experience Publications</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-experience-publications/</guid>
      <description>Nick Finck has created an excellent bibliography of UX web publications. The list is grouped into three main sections; Industry Publications (non-corporate ezines and/or printed magazines), Team &amp;amp; Company Publications (multi-author and/or business focused publications), and Personal Publications (practitioners who write). View the list here.
http://www.nickfinck.com/blog/entry/user_experience_publications/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redub Designs a Better Online Magazine</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/redub-designs-better-online-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/redub-designs-better-online-magazine/</guid>
      <description>I came across Redub&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Make Me Scroll&amp;rdquo; presentation embedded above, which looks at the current offering of magazine readers which are modeled after print layouts, are difficult to read, SEO-unfriendly, and which rarely use the full capabilities provided by web browsers, e.g. multi-media. Or they&amp;rsquo;re modeled largely after blogs with articles are long and scrolling, are limited by the possibilities of HTML/CSS, and have layouts that aren&amp;rsquo;t differentiated from blogs and which pale in comparison to the layout in the printed version of the original magazine article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Magazine Style Website Designs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/25-magazine-style-website-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/25-magazine-style-website-designs/</guid>
      <description>Vandelay collects screenshots of front page designs of 25 magazine sites. http://vandelaydesign.com/blog/galleries/magazine-style-website/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issuu Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/issuu-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/issuu-pagination/</guid>
      <description>Issuu is an online self-publishing service that allows users to create e-magazines and books that are displayed in their slick Flash reader. The service also provides social features around the content. One of the nicest things about the reader is the usable pagination. The reader features the typical next/previous and jump to page features you&#39;d find in an ebook or PDF reader. They also provide some features that are similar to the browsing experience with Preview, the Dock, and QuickLook in the Mac, utilizing miniature thumbnails of pages to scroll through pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr: The Face (1980-2004)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/flickr-face-1980-2004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/flickr-face-1980-2004/</guid>
      <description>A Flickr Group with covers from fashion mag, The Face. As an undergrad in the early 90&amp;rsquo;s, I was friends with an art dealer I worked with for a few years who read this magazine. He used to let me borrow his clothes, and the thing I took most of the time was his The Face t-shirt that I&amp;rsquo;d wear with a black jacket. This set of photos brings back funny memories of that NYC gallery scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veerle&#39;s Inspiration series: Magazines</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/veerles-inspiration-series-magazines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/veerles-inspiration-series-magazines/</guid>
      <description>Veerle Pieters continues her excellent design inspiration series with screenshots from a handful of magazines, both digital and ezine.
http://veerle.duoh.com/blog/comments/inspiration_series_magazines/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>