<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>contact on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/contact/</link><description>Recent content in contact on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/contact/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Digg Contact</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-contact/</guid><description>This is perhaps more about information architecture than interface or interaction design. One thing I like about Digg's About section is the transparency of the company that's suggested here. They only provide email addresses for contacting the company, rather than providing a form. They provide 4 types of contact: feedback, abuse, press, and partners, each type of gets sent to an email address. This exposes you, the sender, as it doesn't allow the sending of anonymous email, and gives them a way to respond to you.</description></item><item><title>Oranges Contact Form</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/oranges-contact-form/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/oranges-contact-form/</guid><description>Edward Pistachio is a writer pulping fine short stories. Consistent with the lighthearted tone of this site, he provides a contact form that is also all about words. Getting his email address requires solving a few jumbles, and then decoding the address from letters found in the jumbles. Sure it may be frustrating if you can't figure out the jumbles, and is one of the cleverest ways I've ever seen to gain access to a bit of info.</description></item><item><title>Sidebar Creative Contact Form</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/sidebar-creative-contact-form/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/sidebar-creative-contact-form/</guid><description>The contact page for this design agency features a clever use of an AJAX slider to allow potential clients to for entering their budget in the range of 10K to 500K. Interesting that the slider increments in 25K's up to 100K, then increments in 100K's. Once you get them on the phone, I suppose you can give them your real budget. Maybe that helps eliminate small jobs?
http://sidebarcreative.com/</description></item></channel></rss>