<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graph Paper on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/graph-paper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graph Paper on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/graph-paper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sticky Jots</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sticky-jots/</guid>
      <description>Sticky Jots is a set of storytelling sticky note paper and paper prototyping kits for designing mobile and tablet interfaces. The product is designed by Rae Milne and Pamela Jue, two grad students in the SVA Interaction Design program. 
Pam writes about the thinking behind Sticky Jots. The idea came from our constant prototyping and ideation process in almost every project this semester. While it’s great to do, it’s still frustrating how time consuming it can be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whitelines Link</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/whitelines-link/</guid>
      <description>Everyone&amp;rsquo;s getting in on on the physical paper capturing game using the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s camera. Whitelines is one of my favorite sketch paper makers. They make great graph paper that reverses the grid using white lines over pale a gray paper. The result is that the grid it more subtle and less distracting
The Whitelines Link product is a free iPhone app that let&amp;rsquo;s you capture sketches made on their new Whitelines Link papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dot Grid Sheets added to the Graph Paper page</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dot-grid-sheets-added-graph-paper-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dot-grid-sheets-added-graph-paper-page/</guid>
      <description>I added some dot grid sheets to the printable graph paper, for sketchers that don&amp;rsquo;t like lines. Download here.
http://konigi.com/tools/graph-paper#dotgrid</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Stickynotes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-stickynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-stickynotes/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had a UX Stickynotes pad near me for a few weeks to play with. I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a sticky notes nerd. I mostly like to place them in sketchbooks to mark and annotate, but also like them for brainstorming and doing info organization exercises. Sticky notes for UI sketches and sketchboards makes sense.
The sticky notes are A5 sized, with light non-photo blue dot grid, and the browser version has 960gs markers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad Application Sketch Template</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-application-sketch-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-application-sketch-template/</guid>
      <description>Oliver Waters released an iPad graph paper sketch template. 10px squared, with tick marks to indicate indicate the heights of the Status Bar, Navigation Bar, Split View (Landscape Only), Keyboard and Tab Bar. See also his iPhone sketch template.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/owaters/4501918517/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made by Many goes SouthWest</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/made-many-goes-southwest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/made-many-goes-southwest/</guid>
      <description>Sweet tweets. The Made by Many crew shows what they&amp;rsquo;re up to at SXSW with this constantly updating status page. Love the fresh/stale indicator.
Via @arainert
http://sxsw.madebymany.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A4 sketching paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/a4-sketching-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/a4-sketching-paper/</guid>
      <description>More printable sketch paper options, this time from Henk Wijnholds.
Via i heart wireframes.
http://www.concept7.nl/henk/prolonging-the-magic-a4-sketching-paper/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Commission Web Stencil Kit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-web-stencil-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/design-commission-web-stencil-kit/</guid>
      <description>This is the excellent web stencil kit from Design Commission, which you will apparently be able to order soon! Comes with sketchpad, complete with browser chrome and grid, custom etched metal stencils, and a Zebra mechanical pencil. Hot stuff. Drop them a line if you want one when they run another job.
http://www.designcommission.com/blog/web-stencil-kit-hot-off-the-press/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Notepads Should Be Available Next Week</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-notepads-should-be-available-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-notepads-should-be-available-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Konigi Notepad inventory will be arriving next week. We&#39;ll have the wireframe paper, storyboard paper, and a few new designs for designers who don&#39;t need all the fuss of the big title boxes--minimalists like me! Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Great Resources for Free Printable  Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/4-great-resources-free-printable-graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/4-great-resources-free-printable-graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve come here for the free wireframe and storyboard graph paper, you might also be interested in these 4 great resources for free printable graphpaper with uses for craftmaking, math, science, and writing.
 Incompetech and PrintFreeGraphPaper
Generator that does a ton of different formats including some excellent specialty papers, e.g. music notation, perspective drawings, geometric grids, and more. Print Free Graph Paper
Generator with graph papers for science and math e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using the Storyboard Paper for Stop Motion Animation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/using-storyboard-paper-stop-motion-animation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/using-storyboard-paper-stop-motion-animation/</guid>
      <description>My son got his hands on the storyboard paper and started sketching a stop motion animation sequence in the cells. He just started his second session in a stop motion class. This is one of the things I used our printed graph paper for, but because that was printed in black/gray on our laser printer, I had a hard time knocking out the grid lines mixed in with his drawings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Konigi Store</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-konigi-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-konigi-store/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to announce the first of a series of products that I&amp;rsquo;m producing for creatives involved in design for the screen. The first 2 products are graph paper notepads formatted for user interface design and design of time-related sequences.
The Wireframe Graph Paper Notepad is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects designing for the screen. The notepad has 50 sheets at 8 1&amp;frasl;2 x 11 inches on white 70# paper, glued on the left side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper Notepad Preview</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-notepad-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-notepad-preview/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m happy to announce that Konigi will soon be offering several products for creatives. I&#39;ve posted some photos I took quickly of the first set below. Better photos will come when the shopping cart is set up.
The first round of gear will include wireframe and storyboard notepads. Each of these pads include 50 sheets at 8 1/2 x 11 inches on white 70# paper, glued on the left side. The ink is a non-photo blue (cyan) so that the grid lines and any sketch lines made in non-photo blue pencil can be knocked out when scanned and processed in graphics software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To All the Notebooks I&#39;ve Ever Loved Before</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/all-notebooks-ive-ever-loved/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/all-notebooks-ive-ever-loved/</guid>
      <description>I recently talked to someone about the graph/grid paper books I&amp;rsquo;ve acquired over the years which have become a central part of my process. This is a listing of those pads, and a telling of their virtues. Rhodia This is my workhorse. At first I didn&amp;rsquo;t get why so many designers carried these around, until I got my hands on one. To me the Rhodias are an all-around notepad for in office or outside use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph Paper Color Modifications</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/graph-paper-color-modifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/graph-paper-color-modifications/</guid>
      <description>I made some color modifications to the graph paper, bumping the cyan of the non-photo lines up slightly. I was noticing that when I print these in grayscale on a black and white laser printer, that the blues were a bit too pale to print clearly. This version works very well when printed. Color printer users will still be able to knock out the blue.
http://konigi.com/tools/graph-paper</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>About This 8.5 x 11 inch graph paper is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects. You&#39;ll find styles for wireframing user interfaces, and story boarding interaction. I&#39;ve been told that it&#39;s also used by animators and filmmakers. Enjoy.
 Scanning These cyan and gray grid pages are great for sketching, but also work well when producing high fidelity drawings. The boxes and grid lines of the cyan versions are non-photo blue, so you can easily remove them when scanned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>About This 8.5 x 11 inch graph paper is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects. You&#39;ll find styles for wireframing user interfaces, and story boarding interaction. I&#39;ve been told that it&#39;s also used by animators and filmmakers. Enjoy.
 Scanning These cyan and gray grid pages are great for sketching, but also work well when producing high fidelity drawings. The boxes and grid lines of the cyan versions are non-photo blue, so you can easily remove them when scanned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>I spend a lot of time sketching interface ideas on paper. Typically I sketch wireframes and storyboards on graph paper, then redo the final documents in OmniGraffle. But lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using paper for more than just sketching. Now, after spending time sketching ideas and working out design issues, I start to do higher fidelity drawings on paper, scan them, post them to our system. We discuss and iterate, and the process repeats until we&amp;rsquo;re happy, and I spend less time pushing pixels around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhodia Drive</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/rhodia-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rhodia-drive/</guid>
      <description>Rhodia Drive is a fantastic blog written by someone named Tedo, a Filipino journalist currently based in Chicago, that is devoted to Rhodia notepads. Tedo posts random stories, artwork and photos from Rhodia lovers around the world. I always carry around a 3&amp;frasl;5 x 4.5 Rhodia notepad and traded in my Tufte graph paper for Rhodia a little over a year ago. If you&amp;rsquo;re one of us, check out Rhodia Drive and the flickr group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch paper for the mobile designer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sketch-paper-mobile-designer/</guid>
      <description>Erlend posted on the Artueel blog about a great idea they had for mobile designers&amp;#8212;a sketchpaper document you can print out (PDF and PSD formats available) so you can get your ideas on paper. They&amp;rsquo;ve created sketchpaper for the iPhone and the Nokia N95. Since we‘re all big fans of the iPhone and the mobile future in general, we want to help the mobile designer achieving his goals. For those who like to sketch the design/flow of their mobile app or website we present you: sketch paper for the iPhone and Nokia N95.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fine Art of Wireframes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/fine-art-wireframes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fine-art-wireframes/</guid>
      <description>On the Geniant blog, T.Scott Stromberg exposes his craft of wireframe sketching. I also spend most of my ideation time sketching. It&#39;s lovely to see other people&#39;s methods for getting ideas down. I love Stromberg&#39;s comments and comic book style.
This might sound kind of pathetic, but seeing the pens and paper he uses is the kind of thing I really geek out on. I love that he&#39;s pimping out the Behance dot grid pads.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>