<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rich text editor on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/rich-text-editor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rich text editor on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/rich-text-editor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Text Editor Task Creation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/evernote-text-editor-task-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/evernote-text-editor-task-creation/</guid>
      <description>Evernote, the unique note keeping desktop, mobile, and web-based application allows users to upload notes from images or PDFs or create them right in the software as one would any publishing system. The note creation editor features a simple rich text editor with one feature that is uncommon for web-based editors--a task checkbox. All this does is insert a checkbox wherever the insertion mark (cursor) is located, and while in edit mode, allows you the user to toggle between checked (done) and unchecked (to do).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnSugar Site Publishing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/onsugar-site-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/onsugar-site-publishing/</guid>
      <description>Sugar Inc. releases the OnSugar Blogging platform to let Sugar community members start their own sites. Based on the Drupal platform, OnSugar provides some very nice modifications to clean up and simplify the posting and content management interfaces provided by the popular open source CMS. What I like most about what they&#39;ve done with Drupal is the clean tabbed UI for content creation, the media embedding options for inserting images from Getty, ShopStyle, and Fashion week photos, and the excellent spread editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System One Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/system-one-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/system-one-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>System One is an enterprise content management platform that combines functionality of a wiki and CMS in a rich internet application environment. The article editor provides some interesting features and AJAX functionality, including a block/paragraph-level editor, drag and drop moving within an article, and related internal/external content suggestions.
1. The journal&#39;s multi-entry view.2. Clicking the link to create a new page displays an input to provide the page name, and shows suggestions for pages that are similarly named.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogger Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/blogger-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/blogger-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>The new Blogger Draft text editor shares some of the behaviors of the rich text editor in Gmail, and as commenter points out, uses the same icons used in Google Pages. Blogger and Pages use beveled buttons rather than using the more minimalist style of the borderless icons in Gmail. One might argue that these controls are actually more usable because the states of toggles and the affordances supplied by buttons and dropped down menus should be obvious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google have been doing some work getting some of their interfaces to be consistent with each other. GMail and Blogger now provide similar interface behaviors and controls, with slight differences. Other applications like Google Sites and Docs continue to have different controls.
Gmail and Blogger are among the simplest of these text editor interfaces, for good reason. In blogs and email, rich text formatting should be bare bones and out of the way as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Mail Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-mail-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-mail-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Mail&#39;s rich text editor in the composition form is clean and provides the core set of formatting options you&#39;d need. The implementation is simple and intuitive. A few things they do differently include: rolling some commonly visible controls into drop down menus, e.g. text alignment and list style blocks.
1. Font face selection and font size are in HTML form selects. 2. Font color selection. Highlight or background color uses the same color selection control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apture Text Editing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apture-text-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apture-text-editing/</guid>
      <description>The Apture service allows web site publishers to easily find and incorporate multimedia content from the web into their site. Apture requires one line of javascript code to work. The service embeds dynamic links in the page that allow users to preview content from the outside sites in AJAX layers over the page content. Publishers can choose to automatically generate links from certain sites, e.g. YouTube and Wikipedia. They can also create links by selecting text on the page and finding the content they want to embed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Sites Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google Sites, the new wiki application that is now part of Google Apps is a content management tool based on the JotSpot service acquired by Google. Sites retains the excellent rich text editor tools that JotSpot had. The formatting bar allows users to do the simple things you would expect from a word processor, such as making font changes and adding styles such as headings to text, insert lists, links, images, and table of contents.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
