<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Surface on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/microsoft-surface/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft Surface on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/microsoft-surface/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audi Car Configurator on Surface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/audi-car-configurator-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/audi-car-configurator-surface/</guid>
      <description>This is video showing the interaction design of a Surface interface to configure the Audi A4.
Audi A4 Car Configurator by Neue Digitale / Razorfish in collaboration with Realtime Technology AG. Showcased at this year’s IAA - the world’s leading automotive fair. The application allows multiple users to configure an Audi A4 simultaneously by changing the car&#39;s paint finishes, rims and by selecting and coloring style package components. The configured A4 is experienced in an immersive 3d environment, in which users can navigate seamlessly by zooming and panning using a multitouch-enabled interface</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC.com Microsoft Surface Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/msnbccom-microsoft-surface-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/msnbccom-microsoft-surface-videos/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve caught Chuck Todd using a desktop touch interface a few times on MSNBC to click through poll charts. While John King has been using a Perceptive Pixel-designed touch wall, Todd has been using a Microsoft Surface interface on a desktop. The device and manipulation of data on the screen looks very natural on this show, especially for the kind of information he&#39;s speaking to. I think whenever there&#39;s a lot of visual information to add to a story, this kind of an interface has potential to be very helpful and I look forward to seeing what they do at MSNBC and on other shows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
