<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Flex on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/flex/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Flex on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/flex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GestureWorks Open Source Multitouch Gesture Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</guid>
      <description>GestureWorks is a multitouch authoring environment for Flash and Flex that ships with a library of over 20 unique gestures. This gesture library is built upon an open source gesture framework, allowing developers to customize and extend the “gesture object” to create support for new gestures. The library is available for GestureWorks, and posters in PNG, PDF and AI format are also provided.
http://gestureworks.com/about/open-source-gesture-library/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anaara Media LLC</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/anaara-media-llc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/anaara-media-llc/</guid>
      <description>The website of RIA company Anaara Media LLC has an interesting flash interface which makes use of expanding cards to present its content.
http://anaara.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Tips for a Great Flex UX</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/6-tips-great-flex-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/6-tips-great-flex-ux/</guid>
      <description>Theresa Neil is writing a 6 part series of articles on designing great Adobe Flex/Air user experiences. The first 3 parts are up now.
After designing several large enterprise applications for diverse clients and industries, I’ve noticed some barriers to crafting a great experience in Flex. I think these barriers arise from the relative newness of the technology (and RIAs in general), the initial focus on development over design, and the confidence that Flex can provide a great UX out of the box.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>