<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ratings on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/ratings/</link><description>Recent content in ratings on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/ratings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>iTunes Ratings</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-ratings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-ratings/</guid><description>The iTunes Store allows customers to rate items and displays the average rating and total ratings below the product image. They use a disclosure arrow to allow customers to view a breakdown of ratings by number of stars.
1. Customers' average rating, and form select to add your own rating.2. Expanded ratings break down after clicking the disclosure triangle. http://www.apple.com/itunes/</description></item><item><title>Engadget Comment Voting</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/engadget-comment-voting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/engadget-comment-voting/</guid><description>Engadget's comment rating and karma system uses +1/-1 voting, so users can vote comments up or down. Votes below a certain threshold get dimmed out rather than hidden. When a vote is applied, the user's vote is registered, a message appears, and the voting controls are hidden. To the right, there's an exclamation mark to flag inappropriate comments, which are then immediately collapsed from view.
http://www.engadget.com/</description></item><item><title>YouTube Comment Rating</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-comment-rating/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-comment-rating/</guid><description>YouTube's comment rating controls allow users to vote a comment up or down. When user enters a down vote, the comment is collapsed from view. There is a link to the left of rating controls to report a comment as spam.
https://www.youtube.com/</description></item><item><title>Netflix Rate for Recommendations</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-rate-recommendations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-rate-recommendations/</guid><description>Netflix shows a module to signed in users at the top of their home page asking the user to rate recent returns. The module promises to give 2 recommendations immediately after they've rated. On sites like Flickr, the recommendation engine is perhaps one of the single best incentives for adding ratings. On a lot of sites, ratings give you nothing back. This is a good example to illustrate quickly why you'd want to add a rating, and would be particularly useful to demonstrate the value to new users.</description></item><item><title>RYZ Rating and Favoriting</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</guid><description>RYZ is a sneaker manufacturer that crowdsources the design of their product and shares the revenue with winners. Users download a template to create design and upload to their profile. Participants vote on the designs by giving ratings and winners receive $1000 and $1 for every pair sold. The site provides simple interfaces for both favoriting and rating entries.
1. The voting page.2. Clicking the star badge in the corner of the image adds to favorites.</description></item><item><title>The Filter Rating</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-rating/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-rating/</guid><description>The rating controls in The Filter provide a slider control with a 10 point scale. Each rating is accompanied by an English language equivalent, e.g. 0% on the negative side is "Never show me this again!" and 100% on the positive side is "A new kind of awesome." Middling ratings are "Not for me", "Average", and "This is good."
1. Ratings slider control.2. The Ratings module in the video player. More related items in carousel below.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn Museum Click! Rating</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/brooklyn-museum-click-rating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/brooklyn-museum-click-rating/</guid><description>The Brooklyn Museum's Click! show is a crowd-curated exhibition that accepted user submissions for photographs that reflect the theme, "The changing face of Brooklyn." Following the submission period, visitors are asked to help curate the photography show by evaluation submissions on their effectiveness at demonstrating the theme. The interface for evaluating photos steps the user through each entry and provides a slider control to rate the photo on a scle from most effective to least effective.</description></item><item><title>QUEEKY Ratings</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/queeky-ratings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/queeky-ratings/</guid><description>QUEEKY is a drawing community that allows users to draw pictures in their browsers using the site's flash application. Users can rate the drawings using a rating scale ranging from 1 (Hmmm) to 10 (A masterpiece!). Scores on the low side are color coded to a cool violet color and on the high side towards a hotter pink/fuschia.
1. Low rating2. High rating3. Full page http://www.queeky.com/</description></item><item><title>ibeatyou rating</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ibeatyou-rating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ibeatyou-rating/</guid><description>ibeatyou is a video portal that allows people to create challenges to compete on anything. Users either upload a video, record from webcam, or import from YouTube.
The rating system is a whimsical little widget for allowing a score from 1 to 5. The vote is indicated by a little blue man holding up a scrore card. They also provide a qualitative award, allowing users to give an award to the entry and name it anything they like.</description></item><item><title>Fancast Rating (Hulu Player)</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</guid><description>The Fancast experience for the Hulu video player provides a customized rating widget that differs from the straight-forward star rating on Hulu. Users select a text value that gets converted to stars.
1. Button in lower right prompts user to rate the video2. Clicking the button displays scale as text values3. Value selected by user is converted to star rating scale http://fancast.com</description></item><item><title>TED Ratings</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ted-ratings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ted-ratings/</guid><description>I was a bit confused the first time I saw this rating interface, and have to admit that I ignored it for months. The thing that threw me was the multiple checkboxes offered for each value. But I came back and realized that what this was doing was giving you a pre-defined set of tags which it was then using to create a filtering mechanism for the site. I appreciate that.</description></item></channel></rss>