<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>community on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in community on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>99u Conference Notes: Quirky Studio Visit with Ben Kaufman</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/99u-conference-notes-quirky-studio-visit-ben-kaufman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/99u-conference-notes-quirky-studio-visit-ben-kaufman/</guid>
      <description>A group of 99u attendees had a visit with Ben Kaufman, the CEO/founder of product development company Quirky, who gave us a look into how his company uses crowd-sourcing to deliver products. Here are some of my notes from that visit. More 99u notes to follow.
Kaufman got his start as an inventor in high school when he made a lanyard to hold an iPod shuffle. The company he started to ship this product later morphed into Mophie, the maker of the JuiceBox battery case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usabilla Discover</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</guid>
      <description>Usabilla Discover is like a mashup of Pinterest and LittleBigDetails, or maybe it&#39;s a social LittleSnapper. Whatever the pitch, it&#39;s pretty useful to share screenshots of interface and visual designs you like. Now to figure out how to get my over 2,000 screenshots into it.
Note: To get in during the beta, sign up here with code &amp;quot;KONIGI&amp;quot;, good for the first 200 who use the code.
http://discover.usabilla.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can now post Mockups to UX.StackExchange.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/you-can-now-post-mockups-uxstackexchangecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/you-can-now-post-mockups-uxstackexchangecom/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m pretty excited about the announcement we at Balsamiq were able to make jointly with the group at StackExchange today. The two groups have been working together to integrate Mockups into the UX StackExchange. You can now post Mockups wireframes with questions and answers to UX.StackExchange.com using the free integrated Mockups editor. I&#39;m really excited about this. One of the conversations Peldi and I had before I joined Balsamiq was about creating something I&#39;ve wanted to use for a long time--a site where you could upload wireframes to vet ideas, get feedback, and test concepts with other peer professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>visualizing.org</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/visualizingorg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/visualizingorg/</guid>
      <description>Visualizing.org looks like an exciting new community devoted to information design and sensemaking--making sense of complex issues through data and design. An excerpt from their about page describes the site:
It&#39;s a place to showcase work, get feedback, ensure that your work is seen by lots of people and gets used by teachers, journalists, and conference organizers to help educate the public about various world issues. Visualizing is also a free resource to search for data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Interface Stack Exchange</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-stack-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-stack-exchange/</guid>
      <description>The User Interface Stack Exchange is a free, community driven Q and A site for user interface researchers and experts. It was created through the open democratic process defined at Stack Exchange Area 51, part of the Stack Exchange Network and Stack Overflow. Help out by registering and contributing your expertise.
http://ui.stackexchange.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Feedback - Website Review Community</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback-website-review-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback-website-review-community/</guid>
      <description>Concept Feedback is a website review community with over 5,000 web designers and developers, marketers and entrepreneurs. Once a website is posted on Concept Feedback, members are invited to provide reviews. On average, a concept receives 12 or more unique reviews, while some can generate as many as 100. Because of the nature of the community, feedback can cover a variety of topics, including design, usability, content and strategy. Concept Feedback is best for getting design-related feedback from a wide audience and can be used at all stages of development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build It With Me Connects App Designers and Builders</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/build-it-me-connects-app-designers-and-builders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/build-it-me-connects-app-designers-and-builders/</guid>
      <description>Build It With Me is a free site that connects like-minded designers &amp;amp; developers with the same goal: create cool &amp;amp; useful apps.
Getting funding for your app idea is hard and often unrealistic. Most of the time you may just need to connect with a partner who has a skill set you lack to finish off your app. This is where Build It With Me is comes in, connecting you to those people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hitotoki</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/hitotoki/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/hitotoki/</guid>
      <description>Hitotoki is a literary project collecting stories tied to geographic locations. Nice hand drawn details and minimalist sensibility. Uses the connection to locales using Google Maps to navigate the story spaces on the home page.
http://hitotoki.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Exchange</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-exchange/</guid>
      <description>UX Exchange is a Q&amp;amp;A site for user experience professionals, modeled after the programming Q&amp;amp;A site Stack Overflow. Users post questions, reply with answers and vote questions and answers up and down.
http://uxexchange.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Wide Web Consortium (W3C)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/world-wide-web-consortium-w3c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/world-wide-web-consortium-w3c/</guid>
      <description>The W3C undergoes its first major redesign in years, simplifying its information architecture, adding visual polish. The header, sidebar, and icons are major improvements, and the addition of progressive disclosure behaviors simplify some of the rather lengthy lists.
http://www.w3.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtersage</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/filtersage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/filtersage/</guid>
      <description>Filtersage connects the present to the past. You can discover great movies and music or share your knowledge by making new connections. http://www.filtersage.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Designers: A community of practice for design &amp; user experience people in Open Source</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/open-source-designers-community-practice-design-user-experience-people-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/open-source-designers-community-practice-design-user-experience-people-open-source/</guid>
      <description>Leisa Reichelt has started a Ning community for designers contributing to open source projects. If you’re doing design &amp;amp; user experience work in an open source community, then chances are we have a lot in common – no matter what community we’re working in. We have some big challenges every day, but we also know that if we can overcome those challenges we can make a really big contribution to the sustainability and increased popularity of open source software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Feedback</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Concept Feedback.com is a free community where designers and developers can exchange feedback on design projects. Registered users have the ability to post marketing concepts for free. Concepts may include, but are not limited to, websites, logos, newsletters, landing pages, advertisements and videos. Reviewers can offer constructive feedback on each concept using a proprietary feedback tool. Feedback is automatically collected and archived for the user to help improve the final concept and get better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yay!everyday</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/yayeveryday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/yayeveryday/</guid>
      <description>yay!everyday is community inspiration gallery focussed on sharing images that showcase artists, designers, and their work. Love the random sort option, and the staggered placement of the gallery of images which feels like an installation of paintings on a gallery wall.
http://yayeveryday.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweetizen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</guid>
      <description>Tweetizen is a simple web-based tool designed to help you filter the daily influx of tweets, and easily embed twitter groups to your own website. http://www.tweetizen.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
