<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>radial menus on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/radial-menus/</link><description>Recent content in radial menus on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/radial-menus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pinterest Mobile Radial Menus</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-mobile-radial-menus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-mobile-radial-menus/</guid><description>&lt;p>Pinterest's mobile app displays a radial menu if you tap on an image. The menu items are for functions that are also available using the icons and buttons in the top of the UI for allowing you to pin, like, or send the image.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Radial Menu Tests in Firefox</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/radial-menu-tests-firefox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/radial-menu-tests-firefox/</guid><description>Testing of proof of concept prototypes of radial menus. The idea is to get users to try to select the same menu item repeatedly as the radial menu changes from state to state and capture participants feedback on usability of the interface.
http://jonoscript.wordpress.com/2008/10/28/pie-in-the-sky/</description></item><item><title>Adaptive Path Aurora Concept Video, Part 1</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</guid><description>Adaptive Path, as part of Mozilla Lab's concept video series, provides some suggestions for the possible future of the web experience with Aurora. This forward looking concept focuses on 4 high priority elements: context awareness, natural interaction, continuity, and multi-user applications.
Aurora (Part 1) from Adaptive Path on Vimeo. The scenario laid out is one in which one user starts an audio chat and screen sharing sesion with another user and we begin to see how users can find information from their history and share it and remix it with others in the session.</description></item><item><title>Songza Radial Menus</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/songza-radial-menus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/songza-radial-menus/</guid><description>You rarely see radial menus implemented on the web. Radial menus provide a branching interface from a single starting point. Songza uses this interface convention to provide a very interesting way of selecting from 4 categories of actions that can be performed on a single song: play, share, rate, playlist. These are categories of actions you typically get with audio and video media on web sites. The radial menu allows the designer to keep the display simple, so the user can focus on the lists of titles.</description></item></channel></rss>