<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inspiration on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/inspiration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Inspiration on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/inspiration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Usabilla Discover</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</guid>
      <description>Usabilla Discover is like a mashup of Pinterest and LittleBigDetails, or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a social LittleSnapper. Whatever the pitch, it&amp;rsquo;s pretty useful to share screenshots of interface and visual designs you like. Now to figure out how to get my over 2,000 screenshots into it.
Note: To get in during the beta, sign up here with code &amp;quot;KONIGI&amp;quot;, good for the first 200 who use the code.
http://discover.usabilla.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marian Bantjes: Intricate beauty by design on TED</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/marian-bantjes-intricate-beauty-design-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/marian-bantjes-intricate-beauty-design-ted/</guid>
      <description>Marian Bantjes gives a fantastic TED talk, where she discusses her work as a graphic artist living outside the mainstream of design thinking, thinking about ethereal qualities like bringing joy, invoking wonder, and inciting curiosity. This bit excited me:
The more I deal with the work as something of my own, as something that is personal, the more successful it is as something that is compelling, interesting, and sustaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful Minimal Websites</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/beautiful-minimal-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/beautiful-minimal-websites/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the 6 part collection of minimalist designs posted by Vandelay Design. Some sites are more minimalist than others. I tend to use that term loosely at times as well. But the predominant theme seems to be type as interface, minimal use of graphics (aside from a logo and the body content), few if any graphic treatments of navigation, and little to no use of texture and graphic effects, and liberal use of white space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yay!everyday</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/yayeveryday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/yayeveryday/</guid>
      <description>yay!everyday is community inspiration gallery focussed on sharing images that showcase artists, designers, and their work. Love the random sort option, and the staggered placement of the gallery of images which feels like an installation of paintings on a gallery wall.
http://yayeveryday.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milton Glaser on Shepard Fairey and Plagiarism</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/milton-glaser-shepard-fairey-and-plagiarism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/milton-glaser-shepard-fairey-and-plagiarism/</guid>
      <description>Print Magazine interviews Milton Glaser to discuss Shepard Fairey and the topic of appropriation and plagiarism. If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, Fairey is the graffiti artist responsible for such iconic imagery as the ubiquitous Andre OBEY tag and the Obama Hope image. Glaser had this to say, on the topic of copying other artists&amp;rsquo; work:
The process of looking back at the past is very accepted in our business—the difference is when you take something without adding anything to the conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motionographer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/motionographer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/motionographer/</guid>
      <description>Motionographer is a source of inspiration for filmmakers, animators and designers.
http://motionographer.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Design Book Covers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/100-design-book-covers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/100-design-book-covers/</guid>
      <description>visual evation posts pictures from 100 design books.
http://www.evasion.cc/blog/comments/100-design-books-covers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veerle&#39;s Inspiration series: Magazines</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/veerles-inspiration-series-magazines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/veerles-inspiration-series-magazines/</guid>
      <description>Veerle Pieters continues her excellent design inspiration series with screenshots from a handful of magazines, both digital and ezine.
http://veerle.duoh.com/blog/comments/inspiration_series_magazines/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future Of Apple Is In 1960s Braun</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/future-apple-1960s-braun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/future-apple-1960s-braun/</guid>
      <description>Gizmodo puts Dieter Rams&amp;rsquo; designs at Braun next to Jonathan Ives&amp;rsquo; designs at Apple.
10 principles of design according to Rams:
 Good design is innovative. Good design makes a product useful. Good design is aesthetic. Good design helps us to understand a product. Good design is unobtrusive. Good design is honest. Good design is durable. Good design is consequent to the last detail. Good design is concerned with the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>