<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>activism on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/activism/</link><description>Recent content in activism on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/activism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Re-nourish: Design Sustainably</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/re-nourish-design-sustainably/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/re-nourish-design-sustainably/</guid><description>Re-nourish.com is an independent online toolkit for sustainable graphic design.
By providing reliable, accessible sustainability tools untethered to commercial interests, we empower graphic designers to implement sustainable decision making in their day-to-day work. Our mission is nothing short of changing the industry, helping truly sustainable graphic design become what design is, not merely what it &amp;quot;could be.&amp;quot;
Check it out and learn how to change your business' impact on the earth.</description></item><item><title>The Feast Conference</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/feast-conference/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/feast-conference/</guid><description>I've registered to join the Feast Conference in New York City on Oct. 1.
The Feast Conference gathers the world's greatest innovators from across industries and society to empower, inspire and engage each other in creating world-shaking change. A creative look at the world's toughest problems, The Feast Conference presents the most innovative solutions, insights, and best practices as a catalyst toward action.
More than a conference, The Feast represents a bottom-up movement, so we're curating an audience as cross-disciplinary and diverse as our talks.</description></item></channel></rss>