<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq UX Template</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/balsamiq-ux-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/balsamiq-ux-template/</guid>
      <description>Made for UX designers This template is made for UI designers using Balsamiq Mockups that want to create polished, client-ready presentation decks. It includes a few example pages for basic UX document needs (journey maps, personas, wireframe pages), a Symbol Library for controls crafted in Konigi-style, and grid Symbols to keep your layout tight.
 Download for free 1. Download the template.
2. Duplicate it whenever you start a new project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Bit Heart</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/8-bit-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/8-bit-heart/</guid>
      <description>Need a heart card for your significant other?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Snippets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/text-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/text-snippets/</guid>
      <description>About This is a work in progress. I&#39;m copying over my commonly used text snippets and wireframes as I go.
People&#39;s Names, Sorted 10, First Name  Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   10, Last Name  Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun   Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun   20, First Name  Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   20, Last Name  Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun   Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun   Wireframe Symbols  Download Balsamiq BMML file</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchbooks: DIY Instructions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/sketchbooks-diy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/sketchbooks-diy/</guid>
      <description>This is a guide for binding your own sketchbooks. I offer it to you designers, developers, makers, and tinkerers out there who are looking for a way to physically connect to your practice of designing interfaces, or who maybe just want a fun and practical way to get your hands dirty.
I started making my own sketchbooks and pads a few years ago. At the time there weren&#39;t many options for interface sketching and storyboarding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Wireframe Cards</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/christmas-wireframe-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/christmas-wireframe-cards/</guid>
      <description>Need a holiday card for your nerdy design team. Then look no further, and don&#39;t let your Christmas procrastination get you down.
These postcard-sized Christmas wireframes were lovingly crafted in OmniGraffle. You can download the .graffle file to customize it and send around some holiday cheer or whatever. Santa suit up, nerds! Love,
Konigi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn Wireframe Birthday Card</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/unicorn-wireframe-birthday-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/unicorn-wireframe-birthday-card/</guid>
      <description>You never know when you&#39;ll need a last minute unicorn birthday card.
This postcard-sized wireframe was lovingly crafted in OmniGraffle, and you can download the .graffle file to make your own.
Love,
Teh uN1Cr0n5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protokit [Archived]</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/protokit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/protokit/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: Protokit is no longer being developed, but is still available for you to poke fun at.
Protokit was an experimental project to develop a toolkit for creating HTML prototypes. It uses the following open source libraries and plugins: Blueprint, jQuery, jQuery UI, jQuery Templates, and iXEdit. More information about the included libraries and their licensing agreements can be found in theREADME file.
Version 0.1 was the preliminary version and is very rough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Magnets (DIY Kit)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/wireframe-magnets-diy-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/wireframe-magnets-diy-kit/</guid>
      <description>About This DIY magnet template is based on the Konigi wireframe stencils and includes 3 sheets of elements that might be useful in whiteboard prototyping. Simply download and print the PDFs onto magnet sheets, optionally laminate them if you intend to use with dry-erase markers, and finally cut them out.
 Printing These sheets are made to print on magnetic sheets, and were designed and tested for use with Avery 3270 Printable Magnet Sheets for Inkjet Printers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule and Cost Summary Calculator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/schedule-and-cost-summary-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/schedule-and-cost-summary-calculator/</guid>
      <description>About this template This Cost Estimate and Scheduling spreadsheet provides a lightweight method for learning to estimate time to complete a web design project, and calculating cost for completion. The intended audience is individual freelancers or contractors who need to prepare proposals for potential clients. This may not be an ideal format for the calculation of project team estimates. The purpose of the document is to teach you to get acquainted with spreadsheets as tools for cost estimation, with the hopes that you will learn to use and modify it to suit your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils [Archived]</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</guid>
      <description>About This is a set of shapes for making wireframe in OmniGraffle 5 Pro or OmniGraffle 6 (Mac OS X). It consists of most of the basic elements you&#39;ll need to create user interface specifications.  No Installation Required! The stencils ship with OmniGraffle! Find them in the Software category. To download them anyway, get the file and open it, when it appears click the Install button.
 Download Download Version 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template [Archived]</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template/</guid>
      <description>Made for web designers OmniGraffle Pro (v. 5) template for interface design. Includes shared layers for basic UX document needs, e.g. title page, wireframes, storyboards. Grid with guides keeps your layout tight. Sized to work in 100% at 1:1 ratio in terms of pixels&amp;#8212;the wireframe is 950px wide 30px cols. To print, export to PDF and scale to fit. In presentation mode, you&#39;ll be showing true pixel dimensions.
 Installation 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph Paper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/graph-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/graph-paper/</guid>
      <description>About This 8.5 x 11 inch graph paper is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects. You&#39;ll find styles for wireframing user interfaces, and story boarding interaction. I&#39;ve been told that it&#39;s also used by animators and filmmakers. Enjoy.
 Scanning These cyan and gray grid pages are great for sketching, but also work well when producing high fidelity drawings. The boxes and grid lines of the cyan versions are non-photo blue, so you can easily remove them when scanned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
