<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>history on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/history/</link><description>Recent content in history on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>John M. Carroll on the History of HCI</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/john-m-carroll-history-hci/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/john-m-carroll-history-hci/</guid><description>John M. Carroll discusses the history of Human Computer Interaction on Interaction-Design.org.
Human-computer interaction (HCI) is an area of research and practice that emerged in the early 1980s, initially as a specialty area in computer science. HCI has expanded rapidly and steadily for three decades, attracting professionals from many other disciplines and incorporating diverse concepts and approaches. To a considerable extent, HCI now aggregates a collection of semi-distinct fields of research and practice in human-centered informatics.</description></item><item><title>The History &amp; Evolution of User Experience Design</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/history-evolution-user-experience-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/history-evolution-user-experience-design/</guid><description>On the Tea with Teresa podcast, Teresa Brazen interviews Adaptive Path's Peter Merholz to talk about the history and evolution of User Experience Design. User experience design is, at its core, a philosophy that products and services should be designed so that they are pleasurable and easy for people to use. While that might seem an obvious design approach, it's actually not the way many designers historically thought about making things.</description></item></channel></rss>