<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>zoomable user interface (zui) on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/zoomable-user-interface-zui/</link><description>Recent content in zoomable user interface (zui) on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/zoomable-user-interface-zui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unfold</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unfold/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unfold/</guid><description>The site for Norwegian studio Unfold has some interesting &amp;amp; unexpected layout with 45 degree angle text and blocks of color, and panning and sliding interface elements.
http://unfold.no/</description></item><item><title>BeerCamp</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/beercamp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/beercamp/</guid><description>Best zoomable user interface evah.
http://2011.beercamp.com/</description></item><item><title>Prezi: The zooming presentation editor</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/prezi-zooming-presentation-editor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/prezi-zooming-presentation-editor/</guid><description>Prezi is an interesting web app that allows users to create Flash-based Zoomable/Pannable presentations. The interface brings up a presentation editor with a keyboard command, and displays a radial menu for placing media objects, drawing paths for prev/next animation, etc. The finished presentation allows users to step through the "slides" as the canvas zooms and pans. It really might be a nice service for doing things like simple product screencasts, for instance, and hopefully the finished product will allow you to export your work for embedding on your site.</description></item><item><title>Hillcrest Labs Remote Control</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/hillcrest-labs-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hillcrest-labs-remote-control/</guid><description>Hillcrest Labs provides a vision of the pointing and navigating future with their demonstration of Freespace motion-controlled TV remote.
I came across the video demos of Hillcrest Labs' remote control via NewTeevee. The video above shows a demo at the Consumer Electronics Show last winter, but check the NewTeevee link for the more complete demo of their Freespace motion control technology (sadly they won't let me embed it here).</description></item><item><title>Adaptive Path Aurora Concept Video, Part 1</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</guid><description>Adaptive Path, as part of Mozilla Lab's concept video series, provides some suggestions for the possible future of the web experience with Aurora. This forward looking concept focuses on 4 high priority elements: context awareness, natural interaction, continuity, and multi-user applications.
Aurora (Part 1) from Adaptive Path on Vimeo. The scenario laid out is one in which one user starts an audio chat and screen sharing sesion with another user and we begin to see how users can find information from their history and share it and remix it with others in the session.</description></item></channel></rss>