<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>creativity on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/creativity/</link><description>Recent content in creativity on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:23:11 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Power of 100</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/power-of-100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:23:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/power-of-100/</guid><description>In this article I discuss how the 100x method gives you a way to use arbitrary structure to discipline yourself through the challenge of working towards a goal that may seem large at the onset, and to push you forward through what Seth Godin refers to in The Dip — that point in the project where you’re unsure whether to go on or quit.</description></item><item><title>99u Master Class: Irene Au on Mindfulness Techniques to Make You a Better Creative</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-master-class-irene-au-mindfulness-techniques-make-you-better-creative/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-master-class-irene-au-mindfulness-techniques-make-you-better-creative/</guid><description>Irene Au was a design and user experience leader at Google, Yahoo, and Netscape. She's now a partner at Khosla Ventures, and has been focussing on her yoga instruction in the past few years. She led a session at the 99u Conference to discuss mindfulness mediation techniques for creatives.
Au talked about different methods of mindfulness mediation practice. Mindfulness, in general, is a state of awareness or consciousness of the present moment.</description></item><item><title>Jack White on Constraints</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/jack-white-constraints/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/jack-white-constraints/</guid><description>Telling yourself, “Oh, you have all the time in the world, you have all the money in the world, you have all the colors in the palette you want, anything you want,” I mean, that just kills creativity.
&amp;#8212;Jack White
I was going through the parts I had highlighted in my Kindle version of Austin Kleon's book, Steal Like An Artist, and I keep thinking of how much I like this quote from musician Jack White, talking about using constraints to stay creative.</description></item><item><title>Bruce Springsteen on Creativity</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bruce-springsteen-creativity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bruce-springsteen-creativity/</guid><description>I'd like to talk about the one thing that's been consistent over the years—the genesis and power of creativity. ... It’s all about how you’re putting what you do together. The elements you’re using don’t matter. Purity of human expression and experience is not confined to guitars, to tubes, to turntables, to microchips. There’s no right way, no pure way of doing it—there’s just doing it.
From Bruce Springsteen's inspiring 2012 SXSW Keynote Speech.</description></item><item><title>Why Creative People Need to Be Eccentric</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/why-creative-people-need-be-eccentric/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/why-creative-people-need-be-eccentric/</guid><description>I love these two posts by Mark McGuiness on the 99% on why eccentricity and how daily routine helps trigger creativity.
He points out three characteristics of a hypnotic trigger:
Uniqueness - it should be something (or a combination of things) you don't associate with other activities, otherwise the effect will be diluted.
Emotional intensity - the kind you experience when you're really immersed in creative work.
Repetition - the more times you experience the unique trigger in association with the emotions, the stronger the association becomes.</description></item><item><title>The 10% Myth and How to Put Your Creative Process on Autopilot</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/10-myth-and-how-put-your-creative-process-autopilot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/10-myth-and-how-put-your-creative-process-autopilot/</guid><description>What if we could eliminate noise and give our brains space to do harder work or process different things?
The Costanza Principle There's a particularly funny episode of Seinfeld titled "The Abstinence," where George abstains from sex because his girlfriend has Mono, and strange things begin to happen to the serial underachiever. He appears to utilize more of his brain and becomes mentally sharp. He remembers where he left things years ago.</description></item><item><title>Bill Buxton on How to Keep Innovating</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-how-keep-innovating/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-how-keep-innovating/</guid><description>In BusinessWeek, Bill Buxton discusses how to keep innovating, with the main idea being that you can continue to cultivate creativity and innovation by finding new things that you have a passion for. He suggests that when you get good enough at a thing, you should find something else to be passionate about, and commit and throw yourself into learning how to do it. You'll be bad at it at first, but the experience of learning something new, no matter how bad you are at it at first, may affect your creativity in positive ways that you won't realize until you experience it.</description></item><item><title>Creative 30</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/creative-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/creative-30/</guid><description>VICE, Volvo, The Independent and Yahoo! have teamed up on a project called Creative 30 which aims to find and celebrate thirty of Britain’s most promising young creative people. Check out the video interviews that take a peek into the lives and process of the selected designers.
http://www.creative30.net/</description></item></channel></rss>