<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accordions on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/accordions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accordions on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/accordions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EffectiveUI Accordion Stacks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/effectiveui-accordion-stacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/effectiveui-accordion-stacks/</guid>
      <description>Effective UI has an interesting Flash UI for presenting menus on their home page using a stacked accordion. Upon landing on the home page, a series of stacked boxes are displayed with both a large descriptive heading of that section and shows the first mini-slide in that deck/stack to help you see what that section is about. Mousing over the first slide in the stack expands the stack to show the headings for the other nodes of content within it, and the user may now hover over the other items to view their descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Accordions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-accordions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-accordions/</guid>
      <description>Apple&#39;s accordion module provides a method for displaying a good deal of informational and promotional content without overwhelming the interface. The types of things that are displayed in these are accordions are usually supporting content, so the desire to use a design pattern that hides and shows these panels of content is useful. Only one panel is visible at a time, and hovering over or clicking a panel heading brings its content into view with a smooth slide transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Autos Carousel and Accordion Panel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-autos-carousel-and-accordion-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-autos-carousel-and-accordion-panel/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Autos has uses a nice hybrid design pattern for promoting the different categories of top cars selected by users. Situated in the right hand column, the arrows at the upper right allow the user to slide through the different lists. The details for the top car are shown in an exposed panel of the accordion, and the titles of the remaining 4 are displayed as well with large number to indicate order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nivea Download Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</guid>
      <description>The Nivea brand advertising site features a very wizard for determining the type of logo file you should download depending on how the logo will be used. The visitor will answer questions about the purpose, application, and size needed. At the end of the process, a file is given to download. The questions are very easy to answer, and stepping the user through this process eliminates having to sift through a longer list of file types to determine the logo that would best suit the user&#39;s application.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>