<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cohdoo Highlight: Voice recording iPhone app</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/cohdoo-highlight-voice-recording-iphone-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/cohdoo-highlight-voice-recording-iphone-app/</guid>
      <description>Cohdoo, the company that makes the iPhone whiteboard magnets that I&amp;rsquo;ve posted about have just released Highlight a nice iPhone app for voice recordings. It&amp;rsquo;s aimed at helping user researchers record interviews, and is just as useful for recording meetings and conference talks.
To start new sessions, press the New Recording button, and during the recording you can tap the huge green Mark Highlight button, which I could see being useful for marking new questions during interviews, or marking sections of conference talks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pear Note: Note taking utility for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/pear-note-note-taking-utility-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/pear-note-note-taking-utility-mac/</guid>
      <description>Pear Note from Useful Fruit Software is a powerful note-taking tool for Mac OS X. The application integrates text notes with audio and video you can record from interview sessions, meetings, etc.
The notes are time-marked to the video and slides that are being viewed during the recording, so you can click text from your notes, and the app will jump to that time in the recording so you can watch the video or see the slide that went with the note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Whiteboarding with Twiddla</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</guid>
      <description>Twiddla is an easy to use collaborative whiteboard service, but it&amp;rsquo;s really got the potential to be much more. The whiteboard lets you mark up websites and graphics, and even use a drag-drop library of interface elements for working on interface concepts collaboratively. You communicate with others in the meeting with the chat window, and you can also use built in audio-conferencing capabilities. Very impressive, and free. Would make sense for there to be options for private meetings as well as embedding the whiteboard into your CMS or intranet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>