<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tables on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/tables/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tables on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/tables/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DataTables (table plug-in for jQuery)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/datatables-table-plug-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/datatables-table-plug-jquery/</guid>
      <description>DataTables is a plug-in for the jQuery Javascript library. It is flexible tool, based upon the foundations of progressive enhancement, which will add advanced interaction controls to any HTML table. Key features:
  Variable length pagination  On-the-fly filtering  Multi-column sorting with data type detection  Smart handling of column widths  Display data from almost any data source  DOM, Javascript array, Ajax file and server-side processing (PHP, C#, Perl, Ruby, AIR, Gears etc)  Fully internationalisable  jQuery UI ThemeRoller support  Wide variety of plug-ins inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Undo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-undo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-undo/</guid>
      <description>Netflix offers an undo function in their Queue that allows users to undo a remove action. Users click an X icon to remove a movie from their queue, and the row is grayed out, showing an undo text link replacing the remove icon. The row persists until the user moves to a different page, so several removed rows may be visible if the user does repeated removes in one session. Upon return visits to the queue, the removed movies will be gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com TV Show Episode Details</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-com-tv-show-episode-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-com-tv-show-episode-details/</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#39;s Unbox service displays episodes of a TV show&#39;s season in a table listing. Each episode name is listed by title and air date, with a synopsis teaser, pricing information and a checkbox. On the left of each row is a plus (+) icon so the user can view the episode details. The row expands to show an image and the complete synopsis.
1. Episode listing table.2. Single episode expanded to show details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AideRSS Table Row Expansion</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</guid>
      <description>AideRSS is a service that scores and filters RSS feeds so that users can view the most active posts for a web site. Activity is based on number of comments, and posts to digg or del.icio.us. The feeds are displayed in a table, with hot or most active entries indicated by a higher rank and warmer color in the postrank column. A &#34;+ more&#34; icon allows the user to expand entry information within a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zebra Striping: Does it Really Help?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/zebra-striping-does-it-really-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/zebra-striping-does-it-really-help/</guid>
      <description>The conclusions in this A List Apart article about zebra striping, the method of using alternating row colors in tables, strike me as odd. My first reaction to the article was, &#34;Why do you need to study the usability of that technique?&#34; I wonder if the issue isn&#39;t so much a question of usability, but rather of aesthetic sensibility. Bad table row style without zebra striping can adversely affect readability as much as good zebra striping or horizontal rule style.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
