<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>product site on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/product-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in product site on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/product-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Colosseo Letterpress Poster Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/colosseo-letterpress-poster-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/colosseo-letterpress-poster-site/</guid>
      <description>Cameron Moll&#39;s gorgeous Colosseo poster reimagines the Roman Colloseum with type, and the elegant product site beautiful tells its story.
http://colosseotype.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShareFile.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sharefilecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sharefilecom/</guid>
      <description>http://www.sharefile.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NihongoUp</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nihongoup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nihongoup/</guid>
      <description>NihongoUp is a Japanese educational game &amp;amp; reviewing tool.
※ Learn hiragana and katakana in two weeks
※ Improve your kana IME reading speed
※ Review JLPT kanji and vocabulary in context
※ Learn to correctly use particles and counters
http://nihongoup.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuama:Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/kuamadesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/kuamadesign/</guid>
      <description>Web agency website with good look&amp;amp;feel, good CSS.
http://www.kuama.net</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LITAGO KU-KUNST</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</guid>
      <description>Cute use of sticker effects and vinyl toy illustration in this promotional site for a Norwegian milk product. Love the background and navigation menu on the bottom.
http://www.litago.no/kampanjer/kunst/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Cartel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/big-cartel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/big-cartel/</guid>
      <description>Shopping cart provider Big Cartel hosts simple, customizable ecommerce sites for independent creatives, e.g. artists and musicians. The company site sells the product by describing the service in terms of value, and by providing examples of other artist sites, and the design experience. I think the soft textured watercolor background in the header gives it a hand-crafted feel that&#39;s appropriate to this audience. I think emphasizing the sign up link slightly might be a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen Lifestyle Vehicles (UK)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/volkswagen-lifestyle-vehicles-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/volkswagen-lifestyle-vehicles-uk/</guid>
      <description>Love the soft texture of the water color background and the animated illustration that appears when you hover over the vehicles.
http://www.volkswagen-vans.co.uk/escape/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gatorade</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/gatorade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/gatorade/</guid>
      <description>The Gatorade site redesign accompanies the drink maker&#39;s rebranding and the bold type of the product names on every bottle. Every drink name is an active message about excelling in sports and the video loop that runs in the background of product and athlete pages suffuses the site with the imagery of athletes kicking ass. A product filter allows users to view by product name or nutritient.
http://www.gatorade.com/#/products/tiger</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erath Winery </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/erath-winery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/erath-winery/</guid>
      <description>From out of Oregon&#39;s Dundee Hills rolls a new web presence for its founding winery, those consummate Pinot masters who combine the &#34;Art of Pinot&#34; with the winemaker&#39;s pharmacological science to trample out the vintage where The Grapes Of Erath are stored at http://www.erath.com.
Visualize a glass of Fuqua or Niederberger&#39;s best, or, if you&#39;re feeling prime time, maybe a glass of pink from their Melrose vineyard, and enjoy their new website :).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Atrium</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/open-atrium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/open-atrium/</guid>
      <description>Simple product announcement page for Open Atrium, an open source intranet package powered by Drupal. The sidewards illustration seems to suggest, perhaps, a flourishing ecosystem turned on its head.
http://openatrium.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fever</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/fever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/fever/</guid>
      <description>Fever is a feed reading server product. The product site features a single-page design, with well-organized and clear product information at the top, and navigation anchors that scroll the page down. All of the features you need from the service&amp;#8212;purchasing info, account info, customer support&amp;#8212;are included dynamically in the single page, so once you&#39;ve purchased the product, for instance, your customer info is populated into the account area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palm Pre</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/palm-pre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/palm-pre/</guid>
      <description>Palm&#39;s Pre product page has a serious, polished look that I assume is targeted at a &#34;grown up,&#34; no-nonsense audience, judging by the business user scenarios in the video and the big kitchen counter backdrop. The smooth, rounded corners of the page&#39;s UI elements echo the pebble shape of the phone and the circular shapes of the Pre OS. I like the use of depth of field with the full bleed photo, the hover of the boxes on the right, the change in state when clicking the site search box, and the categorized features at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buddy Carr Skateboards</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/buddy-carr-skateboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/buddy-carr-skateboards/</guid>
      <description>The Buddy Carr Skateboards site showcases the limited edition design by Antonio Carusone with a minimalist design consistent with the designers typographic treatment of the skateboard graphics.
http://www.buddycarrskateboards.com/index.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LittleSnapper for iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/littlesnapper-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/littlesnapper-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Simple single page product site for LittleSnapper iPhone, an app that lets you snap, tag, and share photos. I love the how the screenshots and videos slide into the iphone image on the page when you click the buttons on the right. Brilliant idea.
http://www.realmacsoftware.com/littlesnapper/iphone/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iWantMyName</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/iwantmyname/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/iwantmyname/</guid>
      <description>iWantMyName is a service for international domain registration and management.
http://iwantmyname.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
