<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>management on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in management on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Kalbach on Jazz as a Model for the Way Businesses Work</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jim-kalbach-jazz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jim-kalbach-jazz/</guid>
      <description>Jim Kalbach talks about the improvisational model of Jazz as a metaphor for the way some businesses approach collaboration today. What was probably seen a few years ago as a radical way of structuring companies to organize around the work rather than using inflexible business units as boundaries, is now more commonplace.
To demonstrate what happens in the teamwork of a group of jazz performers, Kalbach assembled a group of musicians to perform a song they hadn&amp;rsquo;t played together before, and described how jazz performances &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; as a type of collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Change Effectively, Change Just One Thing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/change-effectively-change-just-one-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/change-effectively-change-just-one-thing/</guid>
      <description>Peter Bregman writes about how finding the simplest solution provides the most effective path to change. In his story he talks about how changing one thing, one habit or pattern of behavior, permitted him to be effective at losing weight. This simple strategy contrasts with the multitude of diet books that suggest entire regimine of change in order to lose weight.
It&#39;s a great tale that Bregman uses to illustrate how simplifying a process or dealing with a challenge can sometimes be most effectively handled by reducing it to its essence, and devoting 100% of energy on a singular action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
