<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comparison Tables on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/comparison-tables/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comparison Tables on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/comparison-tables/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Product Comparison Table</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/adobe-product-comparison-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/adobe-product-comparison-table/</guid>
      <description>Adobe&#39;s Creative Suite packages the company&#39;s graphics and motion products into families that can be purchased as a set. Because it can be difficult to determine which suite is right for the work you do, Adobe provides both a product comparison table with products and features listed in a chart, or a wizard questionnaire. 1. The standard product comparison table, showing suites along the top and included products prices in rows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp Product Comparison Table</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-product-comparison-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-product-comparison-table/</guid>
      <description>37 Signals&#39; product comparison for Basecamp provides a simple, side-by-side comparison of the features of each product category. They also try to help guide the customer to the plan that meets typical needs by featuring the Plus Plan in a larger box. Details for each feature are provided in a mouseover when hovering over the feature in the featured plan box. The mouseover is not provided on hover in the other boxes, but the feature description is the same, regardless of plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MYOB Product Comparison Table</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/myob-product-comparison-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/myob-product-comparison-table/</guid>
      <description>With only 2 accounting products, comparing Account Edge and First Edge should be simple. The product comparison page displays a feature comparison table in the right side of the page, and a user needs/persona based bullet list in the left to help prospective customers determine which product fits their needs.
 http://www.myob-us.com/compare_mac_products/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quicken Product Comparison Table and Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</guid>
      <description>When a software company&#39;s product family grows, it can be quite difficult for customers to figure out which product is right for their needs. Quicken is one of those examples where the number of products is overwhelming. They try to help customers with a product comparison table provides a basic checkbox chart of all product feature categories, with product names and prices along the top of the table, and rows of feature categories, with checkboxes to indicate which products match which features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Quotes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quotes/</guid>
      <description>The &#34;In Quotes&#34; project in Google Labs is an interesting attempt to leverage information from Google News to try to help people understand where public figures stand on topics and issues by extracting quotes. Google says &#34;Much of the published reporting about people is based on the interpretation of a journalist. Direct quotes, on the other hand, are concrete units of information that describe how newsmakers represent themselves.&#34;
The interface is pretty simple to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>