<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>software on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in software on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:18:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspect Ratio Calculators</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/aspect-ratio-calculators/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/aspect-ratio-calculators/</guid>
      <description>Aspect Ratio Calculators for web designers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frontify: Design review, documentation, and specification app</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</guid>
      <description>Frontify looks like an interesting SaaS product for design teams. It provides collaborative features for getting design feedback, creating specifications, documentation and style guides, and linking pages together.
The commenting and linking features are what you&#39;d expect, but what I was really impressed with are the measures, colors, and typography tools for generating style guides. Very nicely done. There are additional capabilities for code export &amp;amp; integration with their API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mockups 2.0: the Symbols release</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mockups-20-symbols-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mockups-20-symbols-release/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;ve release Mockups 2.0 at Balsamiq. The main feature in this release is the Symbols functionality. It allows you to reuse groups of controls in order to create templates, page masters, and libraries of re-usable components. This can be done globally for all of your projects, or locally within a single project. You can create symbols from the top down and the bottom up. There&#39;s some documentation for this somewhat advanced feature here: Working with Symbols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Sierra on Creating Awesome Users</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kathy-sierra-creating-awesome-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kathy-sierra-creating-awesome-users/</guid>
      <description>The model for sustaining customer loyalty is reverse engineering user awesomeness.
Peldi pointed me to a video of Kathy Sierra&#39;s presentation at Business of Software 09, where she talks about sustaining passionate and loyal customers. Positioning and generating sustainable relationships is not what you think it should be about. It&#39;s about user benefits, and not features--about how they feel about themselves in the context of what you provide them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MageConf</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/mageconf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/mageconf/</guid>
      <description>Site for open-source e-commerce conference in Kiev.
http://mageconf.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ImageOptim: PNG/JPEG/GIF optimizer for Mac OS X</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/imageoptim-pngjpeggif-optimizer-mac-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/imageoptim-pngjpeggif-optimizer-mac-os-x/</guid>
      <description>ImageOptim is a free Macintosh application that optimizes images so they take up less disk space and load faster. It finds the best compression parameters and by removing unnecessary comments and color profiles. It handles PNG, JPEG and GIF animations.
Via @chrismessina
http://imageoptim.pornel.net/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treejack - Information architecture testing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/treejack-information-architecture-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/treejack-information-architecture-testing/</guid>
      <description>Treejack is a tool to help you test the effectiveness of an information architecture.&amp;nbsp; Use it to find out which categories are strong, which labels need tweaking and what tasks people are struggling with.&amp;nbsp; Because you can upload an existing or proposed IA, and test with participants remotely, you get rapid feedback at a fraction of the cost of in-person testing.
Often, usability testing only reveals flaws with the interaction and interface elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Setup</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/setup/</guid>
      <description>The Setup does nerdy interviews to find out what people use to get stuff done. http://sam.brown.usesthis.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infomaki: Open Source Usability Testing Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/infomaki-open-source-usability-testing-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/infomaki-open-source-usability-testing-software/</guid>
      <description>Infomaki is a Ruby on Rails application developed by the New York Public Library as a way of rapidly testing alternate designs and navigation language with minimal disruption to users. NYPL are using it to power http://usability.nypl.org and test new designs for the main NYPL.org web site. More and documentation is available at the NYPL Labs blog, http://labs.nypl.org.
https://sourceforge.net/projects/infomaki/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axure for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/axure-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/axure-mac/</guid>
      <description>Axure started a blog to discuss progress on the MAxure, a Mac version of Axure RP. Nice.
http://www.axureformac.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAApps: UX Software Directory</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/iaapps-ux-software-directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/iaapps-ux-software-directory/</guid>
      <description>IAApps is a directory of usability, information architecture, and user experience design software.
http://www.iaapps.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silverback Usability Testing Software</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/silverback-usability-testing-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/silverback-usability-testing-software/</guid>
      <description>Silverback is a simple to use usability testing application that allows you to capture screen activity, record audio and video of the participant’s voice, add chapter markers on the fly, control recording with the remote, and export to Quicktime.
http://silverbackapp.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justinmind Prototyper</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/justinmind-prototyper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/justinmind-prototyper/</guid>
      <description>Justinmind Prototyper is a tool to design wireframes and run simulations for web, desktop and mobile applications. The product looks similar to Axure, and lets you define user interface elements using a drag and drop environment with component libraries, and attach actions to components. The prototypes allow you to map interactive behaviors to elements, define process logic and flow, and add functional specifications and annotations. Looks very full featured and offers the possibility of running a web server to deploy multiple prototypes that are viewable in a browser and allow users to comment on designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Software is Built: Interview with Liz Danzico</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-software-built-interview-liz-danzico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-software-built-interview-liz-danzico/</guid>
      <description>The Scott Swigart and Sean Campbell interview Liz Danico to discuss user experience on the How Software is Built blog. The lengthy conversation covers a wide array of topics including Liz&#39;s view of the differences in design process between typical clients with small teams and larger open source projects with communities of participants, design vision and leadership in open source software, and opinions about the acceptance with the direction that open source software has led users in terms of sharing data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xSort: Free card sorting application for Mac OS</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/xsort-free-card-sorting-application-mac-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/xsort-free-card-sorting-application-mac-os/</guid>
      <description>xSort is a card sorting application for researchers and information architects that want to get a better idea of their users&#39; mental models for any given application or task. The software is free and works on Mac OS X.
http://www.xsortapp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
