<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tools on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/categories/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tools on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:18:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/categories/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspect Ratio Calculators</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/aspect-ratio-calculators/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 10:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/aspect-ratio-calculators/</guid>
      <description>Aspect Ratio Calculators for web designers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principle for Mac: Animation and Prototyping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</guid>
      <description>Principle for Mac ($99) is a tool for designing animation, primarily for mobile devices. It provides an easy to use interface for prototyping interaction, transitions, or other animated elements in your interface.
You can design with text, rectangles (which can modified with border radius to make circles), or graphics created with other tools, and then hook up animations for actions like taps, scrolling, and drag, and use the drivers UI to connect those actions to drive other properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots Static Site Builder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 15:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</guid>
      <description>Roots is an open source static site compiler that can help take some of the work out of setting up your own build tasks using taskrunners like gulp or grunt. It runs in your terminal and requires minimal setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generator Directories</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/static-site-generator-directories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/static-site-generator-directories/</guid>
      <description>These are the 2 main directories listing generators that you can use to build a static site. Each offers a sortable lists to browse by user rating or language.
StaticGen - Lists the top Open Source static site generators only. Filter by language. Sort by rating, issues, forks, titles.
Static Site Generators - Lists Open Source and Commercial static site generators. Sort by rating, license, and language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astropad: Use iPad as Mac Graphics Tablet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/astropad-use-ipads-mac-graphics-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;video&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&#34;853&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ouwCHT3rGRY&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://astropad.com/&#34;&gt;AstroPad&lt;/a&gt; turns your iPad into a Mac graphics tablet, mirroring a section of your Mac&#39;s screen when connected via WiFi or USB. Once connected you can sketch/draw on the tablet with an iPad stylus or finger. It will operate pretty much like a Wacom graphics tablet when you&#39;re using a Desktop graphics app with a drawing tool like Pixelmator, Photoshop, or Sketchbook Pro. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAPERPROTO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/paperproto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/paperproto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://paperproto.com/&#34;&gt;PAPERPROTO&lt;/a&gt; is a 3D printable model to use for paper prototyping mobile applications, in the style of a &lt;a href=&#34;http://lifestyle.howstuffworks.com/crafts/seasonal/winter/theatre-activities-for-kids7.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;story scroll&lt;/a&gt;. You can download the file or buy the model for printing on demand directly from Shapeways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Check</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-check/</guid>
      <description>UX Check is a Google Chrome extension for reviewing web sites and apps against Jakob Neilsen&#39;s Usability Heuristics.
The tool opens the heuristics in a side panel next to the website you enter. You select a problem area on the screen, related to one of the usability heuristics and a callout appears for you to add notes and recommendations. When you&#39;re done a report is available with screenshots and your notes for each issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Accessibility Project</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/accessibility-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/accessibility-project/</guid>
      <description>The A11Y project is a community-driven effort to make web accessibility easier. They provide articles on best practices for doing front end development with accessibility in mind. The site includes an accessibility checklist, a pattern library for accessible widgets, and a list of resources for diving deeper into web accessibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Project Checklist</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ux-project-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ux-project-checklist/</guid>
      <description>This UX Checklist by Andrea Soverini&#39;s is a nice overview of potential UX-related tools and techniques that you could use for product design. It provides a layered visualization of a design process, like an extension of JJG&#39;s layers, with links to articles on the technique. Would make a good poster for a workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RemoteIE: Remote Testing for Internet Explorer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/remoteie-remote-testing-internet-explorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/remoteie-remote-testing-internet-explorer/</guid>
      <description>The Microsoft Remote Desktop app lets you use Azure RemoteApp to test your site on IE (on Windows 10 Technical Preview from anywhere). After you download the app for Mac, Windows iOS or Android, you can connect to their cloud-based version of IE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AniJS: Declarative handling library for CSS animations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</guid>
      <description>AniJS is a library for CSS animations that allows you to write simple statements for handling animation as key/value pairs in html data attributes. It feels very close to writing natural language statements, in a format that is a bit more familiar in code than writing sentences. A simple example contains IF, ON, DO, and TO pairs and would look like this: &amp;lt;input id=&#34;name&#34; type=&#34;text&#34; data-anijs=&#34;if: focus, do: wobble, to: p&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>uilang</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/uilang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/uilang/</guid>
      <description>uilang is a minimal, ui-focused programming language for web designers that handles click events, primarily for toggling classes and css display properties. I love the natural language approach to scripting in uilang. You just insert a statement in a code block like this and it works magically: &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;clicking on &#34;.try-it&#34; toggles class &#34;hidden&#34; on &#34;.info-box&#34;&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; You still have to write your CSS to handle things like effects, but that&#39;s a plus if you don&#39;t want or need someone else&#39;s implementation of those things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolio Emoticon for HipChat</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/coolio-emoticon-hipchat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/coolio-emoticon-hipchat/</guid>
      <description>It bothers me that Hipchat doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a (coolio) emoticon. How can they ship without one? Shameful.
I&amp;rsquo;ll forgive the oversight and provide one to fill the gap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq UX Template</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/balsamiq-ux-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/balsamiq-ux-template/</guid>
      <description>Made for UX designers This template is made for UI designers using Balsamiq Mockups that want to create polished, client-ready presentation decks. It includes a few example pages for basic UX document needs (journey maps, personas, wireframe pages), a Symbol Library for controls crafted in Konigi-style, and grid Symbols to keep your layout tight.
 Download for free 1. Download the template.
2. Duplicate it whenever you start a new project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balsamiq UX Template</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/balsamiq-ux-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/balsamiq-ux-template/</guid>
      <description>Made for UX designers This template is made for UI designers using Balsamiq Mockups that want to create polished, client-ready presentation decks. It includes a few example pages for basic UX document needs (journey maps, personas, wireframe pages), a Symbol Library for controls crafted in Konigi-style, and grid Symbols to keep your layout tight.
 Download for free 1. Download the template.
2. Duplicate it whenever you start a new project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
