<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of an Apple Email</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/anatomy-apple-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/anatomy-apple-email/</guid>
      <description>Peldi tipped me to this graphic deconstructing one of Apple&#39;s promotional emails.
http://www.flowtown.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2011/01/110110-FLOW-APPLE.png</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LITAGO KU-KUNST</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</guid>
      <description>Cute use of sticker effects and vinyl toy illustration in this promotional site for a Norwegian milk product. Love the background and navigation menu on the bottom.
http://www.litago.no/kampanjer/kunst/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept Feedback</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Concept Feedback.com is a free community where designers and developers can exchange feedback on design projects. Registered users have the ability to post marketing concepts for free. Concepts may include, but are not limited to, websites, logos, newsletters, landing pages, advertisements and videos. Reviewers can offer constructive feedback on each concept using a proprietary feedback tool. Feedback is automatically collected and archived for the user to help improve the final concept and get better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Discussion on User Experience Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/discussion-user-experience-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/discussion-user-experience-design/</guid>
      <description>I spoke with Russ Perry at the Phoenix Ad Blog to discuss what User Experience Design might mean to graphic designers and marketing professionals, especially those not involved in the design of sites and apps. I don&#39;t like getting caught up in the &#34;defining the damned thing&#34; discussions, but there you have it. Oh, and I mention Zappos, not because of their visual or interface design, per se, but about their relevance in terms of the holistic approach to user experience outside of the interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Direct Marketing and User Experience Are the Same</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-direct-marketing-and-user-experience-are-same/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-direct-marketing-and-user-experience-are-same/</guid>
      <description>Usability blogger, John S. Rhodes writes in Apogee that Direct Marketing and UX are the same, or at least share common goals and methodologies. This quote sums up these parallel ways of thinking and working:
There is a serious emphasis on testing and measurement. Metrics are the law. Success is based on tangible results: number of phone calls, number of and type of brochures requested, number of email address captured, number of comments made, number of web page views and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
