<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>html5 on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/html5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in html5 on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/html5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Web Designer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/google-web-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/google-web-designer/</guid>
      <description>Google Web Designer is design and development tools for creating interactive HTML5-based motion graphics. The tool looks like it&#39;s targeted at advertising creative. It provides templates for banner ads, which makes sense, but can be used for generating any canvas motion graphics. The default layouts are for DoubleClick and AdMob mobile ads.
Web Designer is a web application that&#39;s built with HTML5, and runs natively on your desktop. It provides support for text, images, videos, and even provides bezier drawing tools for creating shapes and 3d objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoSWS: HTML5 Video Player Comparison</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/videosws-html5-video-player-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/videosws-html5-video-player-comparison/</guid>
      <description>I like this &amp;quot;See What Sucks&amp;quot; table of HTML5 Video players, for comparing features of the video players like library dependencies, flash fallback, playlist and audio support. Starred products indicate the &amp;quot;Suck less than others&amp;quot; rating.
http://praegnanz.de/html5video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawscript: Generate vector code from Illustrator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/drawscript-generate-vector-code-illustrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/drawscript-generate-vector-code-illustrator/</guid>
      <description>Drawscript is an extension for Adobe Illustrator that generates graphics code from vector shapes in realtime. Generates OBJ-C, C++, JavaScript for HTML5 Canvas, Processing, Actionscript 3, JSON, and Raw bezier points.
http://drawscri.pt/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ai to Canvas Plug-In</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/ai-canvas-plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/ai-canvas-plug/</guid>
      <description>The Ai-&amp;gt;Canvas plug-in enables Adobe Illustrator to export vector and bitmap artwork directly to an HTML5 canvas element that can be rendered in a canvas-enabled browser. The plug-in provides drawing, animation and coding options such as events so that you can build interactive, well-designed canvas-based web apps.
http://visitmix.com/labs/ai2canvas/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 Boilerplate: A rock-solid default for HTML5</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/html5-boilerplate-rock-solid-default-html5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/html5-boilerplate-rock-solid-default-html5/</guid>
      <description>I stumbled on Paul Irish and Divya Manian&#39;s HTML5 Boilerplate after looking for a solution to fall back on a local jQuery library if Google&#39;s CDN ever went south, and reading about how to use this technique for WordPress. Ben Kutil also helped me undersand how the fallback technique works a little bit, and I tested and implemented on Balsamiq&#39;s site.
HTML5 Boilerplate is not a library, but a template and set of awesome examples for how to get started integrating HTML 5 into your sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sencha Touch HTML5 Mobile App Framework</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</guid>
      <description>Sencha Touch looks like an excellent toolkit for delivering HTML 5/CSS 3 mobile experiences. Check out these demos your mobile device to give it a test run: GeoCongress (makes use of geolocation), Solitaire (drag and drop and flip animations), Kiva (provides iPad popover controls).
Sencha Touch allows you to develop web apps that look and feel native on Apple iOS and Google Android touchscreen devices. It&#39;s built specifically to leverage HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript and makes use of HTML5 to deliver components like audio and video, as well as a localStorage proxy for saving data offline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTF is HTML5 (Infographic)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wtf-html5-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wtf-html5-infographic/</guid>
      <description>I found this graph explaining HTML 5 features via @obxdesignworks. Succinctly describes the major features enabled by HTML 5 that you need to be aware of: Canvas and video elements, offline storage and geolocation. The graph below shows a snapshot of current support and intent to support in web browsers. Shows that IE is well behind the field in terms of readiness as we speak, but IE 9 intends to support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When can I use... HTML5, CSS3, etc.</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</guid>
      <description>Can I Use provides compatibility tables for features in HTML5, CSS3, SVG and other upcoming web technologies.
http://caniuse.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SublimeVideo HTML 5 Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sublimevideo-html-5-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sublimevideo-html-5-video-player/</guid>
      <description>SublimeVideo is an HTML5 video player with full screen play and scrubbing controls. Because it&#39;s HTML5, the controls may be styled and no plugins are required. Presently supports Safari, Chrome, and IE with Chromeframe installed. Firefox support forthcoming. Will be available for free for non-commercial use.
Via @dandean
http://jilion.com/sublime/video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Rotation with CSS</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/text-rotation-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/text-rotation-css/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Snook shows a CSS technique for text rotation, which is supported in Webkit browsers, Firefox 3.5+, and IE 5.5+. Should be useful for ideas the little rotated year displays in the demo, but for me this would also be incredibly useful in dense angled headings for tables.
http://snook.ca/archives/html_and_css/css-text-rotation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernizr: Use CSS3 and HTML5 Now</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/modernizr-use-css3-and-html5-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/modernizr-use-css3-and-html5-now/</guid>
      <description>Modernizr is a JavaScript library that essentially allows you to use conditionals (if-statements) in your CSS for the availability of CSS3 and HTML5, while still maintaining a fine level of control over older browsers that may not yet support these new technologies.
http://www.modernizr.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
