<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>expand-collapse transitions on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/expand-collapse-transitions/</link><description>Recent content in expand-collapse transitions on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/expand-collapse-transitions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quicken Product Comparison Table and Wizard</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</guid><description>When a software company's product family grows, it can be quite difficult for customers to figure out which product is right for their needs. Quicken is one of those examples where the number of products is overwhelming. They try to help customers with a product comparison table provides a basic checkbox chart of all product feature categories, with product names and prices along the top of the table, and rows of feature categories, with checkboxes to indicate which products match which features.</description></item><item><title>Apple Support Email Button</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-support-email-button/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-support-email-button/</guid><description>The Apple Support site features a very simple "email this page" button in the upper right of the screen along with other tools like print and call support. The email widget starts out as an envelope icon. When clicked, the icon slides to the left and an input appears with a "To" label and a "Send" button. The user simply enters the recipients address and presses send. An AJAX progress spinner appears briefly, then a confirmation message, and the form collapses back to the icon.</description></item><item><title>WordPress Layout Customization</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wordpress-layout-customization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wordpress-layout-customization/</guid><description>WordPress added some excellent layout customization options on administration screens in version 2.7. The most obvious change comes in the form of the Screen Options tab, which expands a settings panel that let's the admin hide or show parts of the UI being viewed, and saves those settings for the user immediately. The UI also provides a drag and drop behavior to re-arrange modules. When hovering over a module heading, the icon turns into a full hand and lets the user move modules up or down in the column, or between columns.</description></item><item><title>Pano Logic Expanding Call to Action</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pano-logic-expanding-call-action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pano-logic-expanding-call-action/</guid><description>Pano Logic sells a simple network PC. Their product site features a large graphic of the product, and 3 simple informational modules at the bottom to find out more about the product, read reviews and press, and watch a demo webinar. The modules expand when the user hovers over each box. There isn't much information added, except for a call to action that tells the user a little more about what they'll see if they click the link.</description></item><item><title>Amazon.com TV Show Episode Details</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-com-tv-show-episode-details/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-com-tv-show-episode-details/</guid><description>Amazon's Unbox service displays episodes of a TV show's season in a table listing. Each episode name is listed by title and air date, with a synopsis teaser, pricing information and a checkbox. On the left of each row is a plus (+) icon so the user can view the episode details. The row expands to show an image and the complete synopsis.
1. Episode listing table.2. Single episode expanded to show details.</description></item><item><title>AideRSS Table Row Expansion</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</guid><description>AideRSS is a service that scores and filters RSS feeds so that users can view the most active posts for a web site. Activity is based on number of comments, and posts to digg or del.icio.us. The feeds are displayed in a table, with hot or most active entries indicated by a higher rank and warmer color in the postrank column. A "+ more" icon allows the user to expand entry information within a row.</description></item><item><title>Last.fm Feedback</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-feedback/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-feedback/</guid><description>The feedback and bug reporting interface that Last.fm is using during its beta for the redesigned site provides a simple way to report problems and tell the company what you like. During the beta, a temporary, persistent yellow navigation bar is placed at the top of the page with links to info about the beta program, notices for known issues, and an option to leave feedback. Clicking leave feedback expands the yellow bar to show feedback options.</description></item><item><title>VIRB Feedback and Bug Reporting</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virb-feedback-and-bug-reporting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virb-feedback-and-bug-reporting/</guid><description>VIRB's bug reporting link in the page footer allows signed in users to report bugs or send other feedback quickly and simply. Clicking the "Report a bug" expands the footer to display feedback options.
1. &amp;quot;Report a Bug&amp;quot; link in footer.2. Expanded bug reporting and suggestion interface form expands in the footer. http://virb.com/</description></item><item><title>OfficeMax Faceted Search Results</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-faceted-search-results/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-faceted-search-results/</guid><description>OfficeMax search provides faceted filtering of results using controls in a left sidebar. Facets such as category, brand, and price show 5 terms per facet, allow the user to expand to see more terms if any, add and remove facet selections in any order. A breadcrumb trail is also provided to show the selections made, and can be used to clear all selections at once by clicking on the first term in the trail.</description></item><item><title>Flickr Sharing</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-sharing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-sharing/</guid><description>Flickr have added a sharing interface for their photos and videos. Presumably this is because of the introduction of videos into the ecosystem. The interface is provided via an unobtrusive link that uses AJAX to display contextual menus when clicked.
Prior to the introduction of this interface, users had to go to click the "All Sizes" link to find URLs for the item.
1. &amp;quot;Share This&amp;quot; button appears to the right of photo or video title.</description></item><item><title>Nivea Download Wizard</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</guid><description>The Nivea brand advertising site features a very wizard for determining the type of logo file you should download depending on how the logo will be used. The visitor will answer questions about the purpose, application, and size needed. At the end of the process, a file is given to download. The questions are very easy to answer, and stepping the user through this process eliminates having to sift through a longer list of file types to determine the logo that would best suit the user's application.</description></item><item><title>Indeed Faceted Navigation</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/indeed-faceted-navigation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/indeed-faceted-navigation/</guid><description>Job search engine Indeed offers faceted search filtering in their results. Facets include useful filtering criteria such as job title, salary range estimate, company, location, and job type. Filters beneath any facet may be selected at any point while viewing the results, and removed in an ad-hoc manner regardless of the order selected. Users may also remove all filtering to return to original results.
1. Search interface.2. Search results with filters on left column which can be hidden/collapsed.</description></item><item><title>Gawker Media Video Comments</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gawker-media-video-comments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gawker-media-video-comments/</guid><description>Gawker Media's weblogs provide a simple method for including YouTube videos in comments. The example shown here is from the Consumerist blog. Users find a video in YouTube, copy and paste the permalink URL into their comment on the blog, and the video is embedded into their published comment. This method of transcluding content is popular in wikis, but the implementation usually involves using a special syntax. Gawker's method of using translating the permalink is dead simple.</description></item><item><title>AOL Music Desktop Video Widget</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aol-music-desktop-video-widget/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aol-music-desktop-video-widget/</guid><description>AOL's Desktop Widget is standalone video player (Adobe AIR application) that runs on the user's computer. The video player allows users to browse and watch the top 100 AOL Music Videos without having to access their web site. The player provides typical functions including playlisting, favoriting, sending to friend, embedding.
1. Video player on the left. On the right are mosaic of headshots to browse artists and search box.2. Playlist mode.</description></item><item><title>Fancast Rating (Hulu Player)</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</guid><description>The Fancast experience for the Hulu video player provides a customized rating widget that differs from the straight-forward star rating on Hulu. Users select a text value that gets converted to stars.
1. Button in lower right prompts user to rate the video2. Clicking the button displays scale as text values3. Value selected by user is converted to star rating scale http://fancast.com</description></item></channel></rss>