<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Registration on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/registration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Registration on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/registration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp Form Focus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-form-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-form-focus/</guid>
      <description>This is a cute interaction for the input focus and data validation on Basecamp&#39;s registration form. The smiling character illustration on the left points out which steps are in focus. When an invalid value is entered, the character makes a concerned face and the pointing hand stays fixed on the highlighted input.
The illustrations on the site do a great job of making you feel like this isn&#39;t &amp;quot;business as usual,&amp;quot; which is the reason for switching to Basecamp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geeklist Sign Up Password Strength</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/geeklist-sign-password-strength/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/geeklist-sign-password-strength/</guid>
      <description>Geeklist&#39;s sign up form tells you how secure your password is by indicating how long it would take to crack. Sounds much more understandable and convincing than the typical weak/strong message.
1. A really strong password.2. A dictionary word is weak. 3. Better, but still weak. The messaging may be convincing enough to get users to think about their choice.
https://geekli.st/signup</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moof Login and Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moof-login-and-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moof-login-and-registration/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m sure some might dislike the use of the bottom-border inputs here, but I&#39;m a big fan of fill-in-the-blank forms and the conversational copy used in this login and registration form on this social music site.
 http://moof.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin.com Header</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</guid>
      <description>The Virgin.com redesign sports a header that provides a boatload of functionality using mega fly out menus: locale selection, micro-site navigation, registration, login, and newsletter signup. I like that they make these options readily available wherever you are on the site. The longer drop downs like the registration form, for example, seem a little long for users on smaller screens, e.g. netbooks. 1. The global navigation bar provides mega drop downs with sub-nodes and links to their subsidiary companies that provide products and services under each category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aardvark Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</guid>
      <description>The registration process on Aardvark provides a modal dialog that uses some nice content previews, content filtering, and progressive disclosure to guide the new user through the form. 1. Clicking sign up button from an invitation opens modal dialog with basic information form. A preview area updates your info as you fill out the form.2. The birthday input filters and corrects date format. City/State shows suggestions. (The one in yellow is a browser auto-completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huffduffer Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/huffduffer-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/huffduffer-registration/</guid>
      <description>Huffduffer, a hybrid bookmarking/podcast service features a whimsical inline registration form that&#39;s formatted in sentences with blank areas that the user fills out with their name, password, etc. Kind of a fun, unexpected way to format the form. Reminds me of the kinds of forms you&#39;d fill out by hand in days of old, which goes with the retro style of the site.
Via SwissMiss.
 http://huffduffer.com/signup/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnSugar Site Publishing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/onsugar-site-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/onsugar-site-publishing/</guid>
      <description>Sugar Inc. releases the OnSugar Blogging platform to let Sugar community members start their own sites. Based on the Drupal platform, OnSugar provides some very nice modifications to clean up and simplify the posting and content management interfaces provided by the popular open source CMS. What I like most about what they&#39;ve done with Drupal is the clean tabbed UI for content creation, the media embedding options for inserting images from Getty, ShopStyle, and Fashion week photos, and the excellent spread editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolspotters User Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/coolspotters-user-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/coolspotters-user-registration/</guid>
      <description>Coolspotters user registration form does input validation and shows an icon in the right side of the input for valid or invalid values, and displays error message text to the right of the input. Simple.
1. Checking user name and displaying error.2. Validated input. http://coolspotters.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Registration and Login</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-registration-and-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-registration-and-login/</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#39;s login and registration screen is the standard by which other login screens are measured. The simple flow consists of: 1) entering your email address, and 2) entering your password. If you are a new customer, simply select the new customer radio and the follow up screens provide the registration flow.
1. Enter your email address, if you&#39;re not registered, select &amp;quot;New customer,&amp;quot; otherwise log in2. Enter registration info https://amazon.com/gp/sign-in.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-registration/</guid>
      <description>Starting off from Basecamp&#39;s sign up page, you pick your plan option, then fill out their form. The form is clean and simple. Inputs and labels are aligned well and there is a logical chunking of sections of the form. I like the simple hairlines between chunks in the top area.
One of the nicest things about this entire experience is the starting point where you select your plan. The user may return to this page at any point to upgrade, downgrade or cancel their plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-registration/</guid>
      <description>A quick and simple registration form that&#39;s compressed into a small area. The labels could be right-aligned for better readability in that 2 column format and the submit button could be aligned left with the inputs to really clean this up.
 https://google.com/accounts/NewAccount?service=mail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-registration/</guid>
      <description>Simple registration form. No captcha in this form, although that could change when they get out of private beta. Having to click the check button seems unnecessary. A javascript check on blur would be better. This form might benefit from a little chunking, e.g. simple hairlines between some fields.  http://hulu.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration at Netflix is a multi-page funnel. Form fields are laid out very well, and the flow is pretty simple considering the huge amount of text that surrounds the form. After entering your info, you can begin entering your genre preferences or search for videos to start adding to your queue. 1. Enter email address and password2. Select plan option3. Enter name and shipping info4. Enter payment info http://netflix.com/Register</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photobucket Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photobucket-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photobucket-registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration couldn&#39;t be simpler. 3 fields: enter a username and password twice and you&#39;re done. No captchas. Oops, is that screenname unavailable, well let&#39;s get alerted right away before you go on. Nice.
1. Enter username, AJAX error check and suggestions if username unavailable2. Enter password http://photobucket.com/register.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-registration/</guid>
      <description>We happened to catch the Yahoo! registration pages when they were being redesigned in 2007. The first version was captured in November 2007 and the second is the prior version. The redesigned version is subtle, but really improves the user&#39;s flow through the form. It compresses the vertical height of the form and uses more conversational labels.
1. Registration screen2. Old registration screen prior to Fall 2007 https://edit.yahoo.com/registration</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>