<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ideas on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/ideas/</link><description>Recent content in ideas on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/ideas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Give it five minutes</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/give-it-five-minutes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/give-it-five-minutes/</guid><description>I'm certainly no stranger to being opinionated and argumentative. I've put my foot in my mouth a few times by pushing back on others' ideas, and am well aware that being quick to react can be detrimental. The older I get, the more I realize how little I know and how much more time I need to spend thinking after listening, before I open my mouth or start to type to respond.</description></item><item><title>Where Good Ideas Come From, by Steven Johnson</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/where-good-ideas-come-steven-johnson/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/where-good-ideas-come-steven-johnson/</guid><description>Chance favors the connected mind.
I just picked up Steven Berlin Johnson's Where Good Ideas Come From after watching this sketch-note summarization of the ideas in the book.
I became a fan of Steven's after reading the New Yorker article "Watching TV Makes you Smarter" and his book, Everything Bad is Good for You. This one looks like it will be an interesting read. I'm hoping it's full of stories of long drawn out infancy of ideas, and the collisions and connections that make ideas succeed.</description></item><item><title>9 experiences for 2009</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/9-experiences-2009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/9-experiences-2009/</guid><description>Brandon Schauer gives us 9 ideas for experiences whose time has come--the idea being that these are things we can do to create or extend the experience with our businesses because the timing is right. With luck, execution of any of these ideas can turn into real value for businesses and their customers.
http://www.adaptivepath.com/blog/2009/01/05/9-experiences-for-2009/</description></item><item><title>67 Thoughts About Design</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/67-thoughts-about-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/67-thoughts-about-design/</guid><description>Tom Peters does a brain dump of the main ideas he's discussed about design in the past 15 years. In his list, he drops some thoughts that simply reflect the era of the present and past 15 years, and in others he provides nuggets of wisdom. Here's a sampling.
Everybody's doin' it Small things are often (usually?) more important than big things.
"It" is about the way every individual conducts himself or herself.</description></item></channel></rss>