<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>information architecture on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/information-architecture/</link><description>Recent content in information architecture on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/information-architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ASIS&amp;T Bulletin: IA Issue (Oct/Nov 2012)</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/asist-bulletin-ia-issue-octnov-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/asist-bulletin-ia-issue-octnov-2012/</guid><description>The IA Issue of ASIS&amp;amp;T Journal is out, edited by Thomas Haller. Here's a listing of articles in this issue. Information Architecture in the Age of Complexity, by Andrea Resmini The Architecture of Information, by Martyn Dade-Robertson Optimizing Websites in the Post Panda World, by Marianne Sweeny A Metaphor for Content Strategy, by Carrie Hane Dennison How to Start Sketchnoting, by Veronica Erb A Conversation with Eric Reiss, Author of Usable Usability: Simple Steps for Making Stuff Better, by Thom Haller Get more info about this issue of the Bulletin or Download the PDF.</description></item><item><title>Edistorm</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/edistorm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/edistorm/</guid><description>Edistorm looks like an interesting tool for collaborative brainstorming. Group brainstorming sticky note boards (storms) can be set up with a background template, e.g. 5 up, SWOT, venn diagrams, etc. You place colored sticky notes with text, organize however you want, you can add +1 votes using a voting system, and add comments to notes. There's some kind of recomendations feature that will suggest new topics, which I guess might only work well with certain content types.</description></item><item><title>Explain IA: Win 1K</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/explain-ia-win-1k/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/explain-ia-win-1k/</guid><description>Explain IA is a contest created by the Information Architecture Institute to find the explanation of information architecture. Will be interesting to see what people come up with. I'd especially like to see the explanation that explains IA in layman's terms in a way that my non-techie mother could understand.
What is it? Why is it important? What does it mean to you? Some folks may offer a definition in 140 characters or less, while others will use this opportunity to tell a story (using text, pictures, audio, and/or video) about their relationship to IA.</description></item><item><title>The UX of moving house: Real Estate Site Review</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-moving-house-real-estate-site-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-moving-house-real-estate-site-review/</guid><description>Martin Belam recently underwent the process of finding a house using real estate agency sites and has documented his observations. His notes are in a 2 part series looking first at site search and information architecture and following up with a review of results displays.
http://www.currybet.net/cbet_blog/2010/01/ux_moving_house_1.php</description></item><item><title>Journal of Information Architecture, Issue 2</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/journal-information-architecture-issue-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/journal-information-architecture-issue-2/</guid><description>Issue 2 Volume 1, Fall 2009, of the Journal of Information Architecture is now available. Includes the following articles.
Byström, Pharo &amp;amp; Resmini Editorial: Open 24/7
Stefano Bussolon Card Sorting, Category Validity, and Contextual Navigation
Brigitte Kaltenbacher From Prediction to Emergence
David Walczyk &amp;amp; Cedomir Kovacev Mediation as Message
Read Issue 2 of the Journal of IA.
http://journalofia.org/volume1/issue2/</description></item><item><title>Treejack - Information architecture testing</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/treejack-information-architecture-testing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/treejack-information-architecture-testing/</guid><description>Treejack is a tool to help you test the effectiveness of an information architecture.&amp;nbsp; Use it to find out which categories are strong, which labels need tweaking and what tasks people are struggling with.&amp;nbsp; Because you can upload an existing or proposed IA, and test with participants remotely, you get rapid feedback at a fraction of the cost of in-person testing.
Often, usability testing only reveals flaws with the interaction and interface elements.</description></item><item><title>Content Templates to the Rescue</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/content-templates-rescue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/content-templates-rescue/</guid><description>Erin Kissane writes about using content templates "... to help speed up the information-collection process, improve consistency across the website, and make the editing process easier and more orderly" in A List Apart.
The ideal situation is to have a content strategist, perhaps a technical writer, who can provide the guidance for auditing and organizing information, and add some rigor to the writing process. The absence of a content strategist on a project necessitates at least dedicating one person to this task.</description></item><item><title>The Life Cycle of a Wireframe</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/life-cycle-wireframe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/life-cycle-wireframe/</guid><description>Nick Finck's Puget Sound SIGCHI lecture on the Lifecycle of the Wireframe discusses Nick's IA process. My overall strategy for IA is 3 step process; understanding the problem (note: not merely identifying the problem but really understanding it), find a solution (there may be more than one solution, but there is often only one right solution), and present the solution (a large part of your job as a IA is presenting your work so the client can understand the results).</description></item><item><title>Dan Klyn interview with Richard Saul Wurman</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/dan-klyn-interview-richard-saul-wurman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/dan-klyn-interview-richard-saul-wurman/</guid><description>IA instructor and author of the forthcoming book "Now That I See It" interviewed Richard Saul Wurman to discuss architecture and design, IA roots in library and information work, and the work of making the complex clear.
One thing that I latched onto is Wurman's contention that his success working with the design of information systems and structures comes as a result of acknowledging his ignorance. "Grasp your life as an ignorant person,"</description></item><item><title>Is Information Architecture Dying?</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/information-architecture-dying/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/information-architecture-dying/</guid><description>Anthony Viviano at Organic asks if Information Architecture is dead, continuing the discussions about the inclusiveness and expanding scope of IA vis-a-vis UX, and hopping on the question about interaction design being a dead end job. Clearly, he doesn't think the practice and craft of IA is dead, just as the craft of Interaction Design is clearly alive. But the role is changing, and while the navel gazing gets resoundingly loud around defining things, the definition of the shifting roles and responsibilities in the field is meaningful.</description></item><item><title>Journal of Information Architecture</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/journal-information-architecture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/journal-information-architecture/</guid><description>The Journal of Information Architecture is a peer-reviewed scholarly journal, published by the REG-iA (Research and Education Group in Information Architecture), an IAI (Information Architecture Institute) international volunteer initiative started by Andrea Resmini. Its aim is to facilitate the systematic development of the scientific body of knowledge in the field of information architecture. The long term goal of the journal is to serve as a forum for new research and sharing of good ideas and case studies that are useful to the field's researchers, practitioners, students, and all other interested parties.</description></item><item><title>Complete Beginner's Guide to Information Architecture</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/complete-beginners-guide-information-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/complete-beginners-guide-information-architecture/</guid><description>For those new to Information Architecture and the role of the IA, UX Booth has written an introduction to the field and role, by taking a look at how some noteworthy IAs have defined the discipline, and looking at some of the work that is typical of our craft. It can be confusing to understand the role of the IA, because in many cases, IA encompasses more than what is defined in this primer.</description></item><item><title>Fear of the High Fidelity Wireframe</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/fear-high-fidelity-wireframe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/fear-high-fidelity-wireframe/</guid><description>In Twitter today, I posted a message that I need to resist putting rounded corners on boxes in wireframes. Then I got a few replies essentially saying that stylized elements shouldn't be in wireframes. Context is everything. Taken out of context, it is very difficult to possibly critique a specific design technique without knowing the how and why you're using it. Because of that 140 character constraint in Twitter, I didn't really explain that this rounded corner example came from my hybrid high-fidelity wireframing and visual design document I was working on.</description></item><item><title>iTunes Nomenclature needs a refresh</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/itunes-nomenclature-needs-refresh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/itunes-nomenclature-needs-refresh/</guid><description>Or maybe we're just comfortable with the mix in of apps and music? No, not me. Artist and Album are certainly just wrong. Don't know how they can make that legacy labeling generic across music/movie/application. Creator instead of artist, perhaps. And just leave album blank for apps and movies. Album doesn't serve a purpose for apps does it? The link doesn't appear to work.
http://www.flickr.com/photos/jibbajabba/2980855655/</description></item><item><title>The what, when and why of wireframes</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/what-when-and-why-wireframes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/what-when-and-why-wireframes/</guid><description>James Kelway's article on wireframes in the User Pathways blog summarizes what the different types are, what their purpose is, who the audience for their use are, and how they are typically implemented. There are several nice illustrations in this article for those that need to explain what they are.
http://userpathways.com/2008/06/26/the-what-when-and-why-of-wireframes/</description></item></channel></rss>