<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fun on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fun on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dedesign the Web 2</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dedesign-web-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dedesign-web-2/</guid>
      <description>Head to Dedesign the Web and play name that website using wireframes. Courtesy of Designation.
http://dedesigntheweb.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Bit Heart</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/8-bit-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/8-bit-heart/</guid>
      <description>Much Need a heart card for your significant other or kid who loves games? I made a heart for you to cut out. Here you go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Bit Heart</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/8-bit-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/8-bit-heart/</guid>
      <description>Need a heart card for your significant other?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Wireframe Cards</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/christmas-wireframe-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/christmas-wireframe-cards/</guid>
      <description>Need a holiday card for your nerdy design team. Then look no further, and don&#39;t let your Christmas procrastination get you down.
These postcard-sized Christmas wireframes were lovingly crafted in OmniGraffle. You can download the .graffle file to customize it and send around some holiday cheer or whatever. Santa suit up, nerds! Love,
Konigi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can you guess what this is?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/can-you-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/can-you-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>So I&#39;m working on this hand drawn font and looking at characters with diacritics is having a weird effect on me. While working on it, the รถ character reminded me of something from my childhood and I had to remake it in type.
So if you can guess what this is by @ing me on Twitter or in G+ if we follow each other there, I&#39;ll give you a floppy disk notebook from my stash, and a few sketch pads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn Wireframe Birthday Card</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/unicorn-wireframe-birthday-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/unicorn-wireframe-birthday-card/</guid>
      <description>You never know when you&#39;ll need a last minute unicorn birthday card.
This postcard-sized wireframe was lovingly crafted in OmniGraffle, and you can download the .graffle file to make your own.
Love,
Teh uN1Cr0n5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the kittens...</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/save-kittens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/save-kittens/</guid>
      <description>Mark Goetz makes a plea to save the baby kittens. Because every time you make a powerpoint, Edward Tufte kills a kitten... and David Byrne does a happy dance.
I love how the cats run off the side of the canvas. Oh, and how no one in that meeting is paying attention... Awesome.
http://markandrewgoetz.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/tufte-wallpaper.png</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Menu for iSquint</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/help-menu-isquint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/help-menu-isquint/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a bit too busy to blog seriously yet, having just gotten back from my vacation. In the meantime, enjoy this help menu I discovered when opening iSquint, an app that I found in my Applications folder, and only launched to see what it was before I AppZapped it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dom Goodrum</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</guid>
      <description>Portfolio showcasing the favourite projects of designer Dom Goodrum.
http://www.domgoodrum.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Newsinator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/merry-newsinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/merry-newsinator/</guid>
      <description>So this year my company plaid decided to create a tool to help people save time around the holidays. It&#39;s called the Merry Newsinator and it generates a customized personal newsletter in about 3 minutes. Anyways hope you like it and would love to see you post it. I have included one we did for santa claus below! Happy Holidays!
http://merrynewsinator.com/2lc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter &#43; Wow</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/flutter-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/flutter-wow/</guid>
      <description>I like the prominent header, and the fun use of illustration on this site, especially in the header and footer. The grass overlapping tabs, and the whimsical footer tunnels are great.
http://flutterandwow.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone is all Fun and Games</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-all-fun-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-all-fun-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Fred Beecher wrote the excellent article &#34;The iPhone is Not Easy to Use: A New Direction for User Experience&#34; on Johnny Holland to talk about why the iPhone is not easy to use (at first), and why it changes the game for user experience designers. The examples illustrate how gestural interfaces are hidden, and lack the affordances of physical buttons. But the real story here is how the iPhone brings one thing to the experience that is more important than usability&amp;#8212;fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FatCow</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/fatcow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/fatcow/</guid>
      <description>Love the nutritional information panel on the right of this promo landing page. It&#39;s ashame they don&#39;t use a fun graphic like this on the regular home page.
http://www.fatcow.com/fatcow/special-promo.bml#ic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teoskaffa.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teoskaffacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teoskaffacom/</guid>
      <description>Teo Skaffa&#39;s fun portfolio is like a tribute to 8 bit game consoles. Huge pixelated text and pointers, dinging mouseovers that make you half expect coins to pop out of links, and a keyboard navigation make this site a pleasure for NES nostalgists.
http://www.teoskaffa.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LITAGO KU-KUNST</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</guid>
      <description>Cute use of sticker effects and vinyl toy illustration in this promotional site for a Norwegian milk product. Love the background and navigation menu on the bottom.
http://www.litago.no/kampanjer/kunst/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
