<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>input devices on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/input-devices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in input devices on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/input-devices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buxton Collection</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/buxton-collection/</guid>
      <description>Bill Buxton has been collecting input and interactive devices whose design struck him as interesting, useful, or important. In the process, he has assembled a great collection spanning over 30 years of the history of pen computing, pointing devices, touch technologies, as well as an illustration of the nature of how new technologies emerge.
The collection can be browsed in HTML or via the PivotViewer Silverlight interface. PivotViewer provides a richer experience with faceted filtering, search, and hypertext links for metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swype Text Input for Screens</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/swype-text-input-screens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/swype-text-input-screens/</guid>
      <description>CNet reports on Swype, a new keyboard technology for touch screens created by the inventory of the T9 keyboard technology for numeric keypads. Swype lets the user drag their finger across the screen, touching each of the letters in the words they want to enter, and predictive software selects the word they wanted. This could be a great tool to the improve the typing experience on the iPhone, which I find pretty awful compared to a hardware keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
