<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>flash on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/flash/</link><description>Recent content in flash on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/flash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GestureWorks Open Source Multitouch Gesture Library</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</guid><description>GestureWorks is a multitouch authoring environment for Flash and Flex that ships with a library of over 20 unique gestures. This gesture library is built upon an open source gesture framework, allowing developers to customize and extend the “gesture object” to create support for new gestures. The library is available for GestureWorks, and posters in PNG, PDF and AI format are also provided.
http://gestureworks.com/about/open-source-gesture-library/</description></item><item><title>Sugagloss</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sugagloss/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sugagloss/</guid><description>Sugagloss, a top end retailer of exclusive adult accessories, underwear and gifts.
Built completely in Flash around a massively enhanced Magento backend, it behaves like a designer shoppers dream – and yet with it’s HTML progressive build methodology it ticks all SEO best practice requirements – whilst never for a moment compromising it’s user centric, highly engaging environment.
http://www.sugagloss.co.uk</description></item><item><title>By the People: the Election of Barack Obama</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/people-election-barack-obama/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/people-election-barack-obama/</guid><description>Promoting the documentary &amp;quot;By The People: The Election of Barack Obama&amp;quot;, this site uses full screen flash and full-screen scaling images to get across some of the passion of the actual campaign.
http://www.myobamadvd.com</description></item><item><title>Webgriffe</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/webgriffe/</guid><description>The portfolio site of the Webgriffe does an excellent job highlighting the work of a web agency with interests in both the fashion and design trends. The site immerse the user in a business catwalk video on the background. The studio worked hard to realize a SEO friendly dinamic flash site with deep linking navigation and high attention to usability.
http://www.webgriffe.com</description></item><item><title>Joe</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/joe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/joe/</guid><description>The whimsical sketched interface of Joe Davis' design portfolio.
http://www.joedavis.co.uk/</description></item><item><title>Petra Quilitz</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/petra-quilitz/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/petra-quilitz/</guid><description>This is one perhaps one of the most attractive portfolios I've seen for an Info. Arch./Interaction Designer. Love the use of photography to highlight the nice large deliverables tacked on the walls. Great stuff.
http://www.petraquilitz.com/</description></item><item><title>LITAGO KU-KUNST</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</guid><description>Cute use of sticker effects and vinyl toy illustration in this promotional site for a Norwegian milk product. Love the background and navigation menu on the bottom.
http://www.litago.no/kampanjer/kunst/</description></item><item><title>Redub Designs a Better Online Magazine</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/redub-designs-better-online-magazine/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/redub-designs-better-online-magazine/</guid><description>I came across Redub's "Don't Make Me Scroll" presentation embedded above, which looks at the current offering of magazine readers which are modeled after print layouts, are difficult to read, SEO-unfriendly, and which rarely use the full capabilities provided by web browsers, e.g. multi-media. Or they're modeled largely after blogs with articles are long and scrolling, are limited by the possibilities of HTML/CSS, and have layouts that aren't differentiated from blogs and which pale in comparison to the layout in the printed version of the original magazine article.</description></item><item><title>Sick City Club</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sick-city-club/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sick-city-club/</guid><description>Sick City Club are a new band hotly tipped for 2009 by UK's Radio One. The new site was designed and built by Zaum &amp;amp; Brown. It's a full flash build powered by an xml cms. The design was inspired by traveling around a city, always being on the go. The sites most prominent feature is the bands new video playing as the background.
http://www.sickcityclub.net</description></item><item><title>Capacity</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/capacity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/capacity/</guid><description>Love the animated effect when mousing over the 3d logo. Simple grid and nice use of expand/collapse transitions in places.
http://www.capacity.tv/</description></item><item><title>Gatorade</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/gatorade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/gatorade/</guid><description>The Gatorade site redesign accompanies the drink maker's rebranding and the bold type of the product names on every bottle. Every drink name is an active message about excelling in sports and the video loop that runs in the background of product and athlete pages suffuses the site with the imagery of athletes kicking ass. A product filter allows users to view by product name or nutritient.
http://www.gatorade.com/#/products/tiger</description></item><item><title>Multitouch Barcelona</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/multitouch-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/multitouch-barcelona/</guid><description>The clever, whimsy of falling balls that drop into the content boxes as the page loads, and bounce up and down as you scroll make the Multitouch Barcelona site an unexpected and enjoyable experience.
http://www.multitouch-barcelona.com/</description></item><item><title>Use It Better: Usability Testing Service for Flash Sites</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/use-it-better-usability-testing-service-flash-sites/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/use-it-better-usability-testing-service-flash-sites/</guid><description>Use It Better is an online tool for recording user sessions for testing &amp;amp; analysing user experience and usability on Adobe Flash websites.
http://www.useitbetter.com/</description></item><item><title>Free Flash Catalyst Tutorials on Lynda.com</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/free-flash-catalyst-tutorials-lyndacom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/free-flash-catalyst-tutorials-lyndacom/</guid><description>Lynda.com has free introductory tutorials for the Flash Catalyst beta, screencasted by Mordy Golding.
http://www.lynda.com/home/DisplayCourse.aspx?lpk2=778</description></item><item><title>sex:female</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sexfemale/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sexfemale/</guid><description>Bold photography in Lena Vazhenina's portfolio. Moving through the photos isn't the most intuitive thing though--you have to click and drag horizontally. But gorgeous presentation.
http://sexfemale.cc/</description></item></channel></rss>