<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>quality assurance on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/quality-assurance/</link><description>Recent content in quality assurance on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/quality-assurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sauce Labs: Cloud-Based Cross-Browser Testing</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/saucelabs-cloud-based-cross-browser-testing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/saucelabs-cloud-based-cross-browser-testing/</guid><description>Sauce Labs provides browser testing services for front end development and quality assurance. Their Scout service lets you test your public or private web app in any browser via a VM that's run in the cloud. Enter a URL to test, select an OS and browser, and a virtual machine runs in the web page so you can test in that configuration on demand. Scout can record and save screenshots and video of every session, and they can can be shared, embedded etc.</description></item><item><title>BrowserStack: Cross-Browser Testing Tool</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/browserstack-cross-browser-testing-tool/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/browserstack-cross-browser-testing-tool/</guid><description>Browserstack allows you to stop relying on screenshot web apps or using multiple virtual machines to do your testing. The service gives you remote, web-based, VNC screen sharing using the web browser you choose, so you can test your web sites and apps in real time rather than relying on static screen comparisons.
Enter a URL to test, and select a target browser in the version of your choosing and screen resolution.</description></item><item><title>Guide to CSS support in email clients</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/guide-css-support-email-clients/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/guide-css-support-email-clients/</guid><description>Campaign Monitor provides a table showing the level of CSS support in the 23 different email clients they test, and covers all the popular applications across desktop, web and mobile email. The web-based version of the guide focusses on the 10 most popular email clients on the market, and they provide a complete report on all 23 email clients in PDF format.
http://www.campaignmonitor.com/css/</description></item><item><title>IETester: Testing Multiple IE Versions</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/ietester-testing-multiple-ie-versions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/ietester-testing-multiple-ie-versions/</guid><description>IETester is a free WebBrowser that allows you to have the rendering and javascript engines of IE8 beta 1, IE7 IE 6 and IE5.5 on Vista and XP, as well as the installed IE in the same process. Thanks to Chad for the tip.
http://www.my-debugbar.com/wiki/IETester/HomePage</description></item><item><title>Install multiple versions of IE on your PC</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/install-multiple-versions-ie-your-pc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/install-multiple-versions-ie-your-pc/</guid><description>The Multiple IE Installer is a must have resource for front end developers. I had to configure a new computer for myself because of a recent job change, so that meant installing all of my design/development tools again. On my new MacBook Pro, I run VMWare and just ran Tredosoft's Multiple IE Installer for Windows XP. On an XP machine with IE7 (you must upgrade to IE7 before running this), the application will allow you to select versions of IE 3, 4, 5, and 6 to install.</description></item><item><title>Litmus: Test your email and website designs</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/litmus-test-your-email-and-website-designs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/litmus-test-your-email-and-website-designs/</guid><description>Litmus provides testing of web sites and email messages across all browser and email platforms for a fee.
http://litmusapp.com/</description></item></channel></rss>