<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Modal Dialogs on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/modal-dialogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Modal Dialogs on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/modal-dialogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Delete Timer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-delete-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-delete-timer/</guid>
      <description>YouTube puts up 2 speed bumps when you try to delete a video from the video manager. This technique slows down the user about to peform a destructive action, and protects them from inadvertently deleting content.
1. Selecting Delete action shows dialog confirming action.2. A second confirmation dialog requires confirmation, but the Delete button is disabled until the countdown timer runs out.
https://www.youtube.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons, Revised</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</guid>
      <description>We covered Shelfari&#39;s hybrid button in their list views of bookshelf items. That example showed a single push button with an attached icon for drop down menu. The single button allowed for the use of a default behavior, while the drop down arrow allowed for the display of other options for the item. The drop down menu allowed users to make multiple selections, i.e. using checkbox behaviors, rather than just select one value in the drop down list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aardvark Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</guid>
      <description>The registration process on Aardvark provides a modal dialog that uses some nice content previews, content filtering, and progressive disclosure to guide the new user through the form. 1. Clicking sign up button from an invitation opens modal dialog with basic information form. A preview area updates your info as you fill out the form.2. The birthday input filters and corrects date format. City/State shows suggestions. (The one in yellow is a browser auto-completion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>