<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>animation on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/animation/</link><description>Recent content in animation on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 09:46:19 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/animation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>gifmuse.io</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/gifmuse-io/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 09:46:19 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/gifmuse-io/</guid><description>A museum of animated gifs.</description></item><item><title>Principle for Mac: Animation and Prototyping</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</guid><description>Principle for Mac ($99) is a tool for designing animation, primarily for mobile devices. It provides an easy to use interface for prototyping interaction, transitions, or other animated elements in your interface.
You can design with text, rectangles (which can modified with border radius to make circles), or graphics created with other tools, and then hook up animations for actions like taps, scrolling, and drag, and use the drivers UI to connect those actions to drive other properties.</description></item><item><title>Tumblr Fave Animation</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</guid><description>This is a small animation of the heart/broken heart that is shown when favoriting or unfaving a Tumblr post in the mobile app.
Screencast / Video https://www.tumblr.com/</description></item><item><title>AniJS: Declarative handling library for CSS animations</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</guid><description>AniJS is a library for CSS animations that allows you to write simple statements for handling animation as key/value pairs in html data attributes. It feels very close to writing natural language statements, in a format that is a bit more familiar in code than writing sentences. A simple example contains IF, ON, DO, and TO pairs and would look like this: &amp;lt;input id="name" type="text" data-anijs="if: focus, do: wobble, to: p"</description></item><item><title>UI Animations</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ui-animations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ui-animations/</guid><description>This is a collection of videos of UI animations (mostly Apple) curated by @gardaud.
http://ui-animations.tumblr.com/</description></item><item><title>Google Web Designer</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/google-web-designer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/google-web-designer/</guid><description>Google Web Designer is design and development tools for creating interactive HTML5-based motion graphics. The tool looks like it's targeted at advertising creative. It provides templates for banner ads, which makes sense, but can be used for generating any canvas motion graphics. The default layouts are for DoubleClick and AdMob mobile ads.
Web Designer is a web application that's built with HTML5, and runs natively on your desktop. It provides support for text, images, videos, and even provides bezier drawing tools for creating shapes and 3d objects.</description></item><item><title>SIX UX: Transition and animation gallery</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/six-ux-transition-and-animation-gallery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/six-ux-transition-and-animation-gallery/</guid><description>SIX UX is a gallery of transitions and animations shown as 6 second videos. Andreas Popp combined Vine app videos with tumblr to showcase otherwise ephemeral movements found around the web. Low fi and awesome. Check it.
http://sixux.com/</description></item><item><title>Meaningful Transitions: A collection of transition patterns</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/meaningful-transitions-collection-transition-patterns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/meaningful-transitions-collection-transition-patterns/</guid><description>Meaningful Transitions is the thesis project of Johannes Tonollo, an interface design student at the FH Potsdam, Germany. Johannes wrote his Thesis on &amp;quot;Transitions in the User Interface,&amp;quot; in which he analyzed how motion in the user interface can be a helpful extension to static elements to enhance the user experience.
The collection of transitions is clustered into 6 different categories: Orientation, Spatial Extension, Awaking Controls (Awakening?), Highlight, Feedback, and Feedforward.</description></item><item><title>Jane Austin &amp; Chris Neale on Sketch Prototypes</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/jane-austin-chris-neale-sketch-prototypes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/jane-austin-chris-neale-sketch-prototypes/</guid><description>The paper prototype is generally used as a design tool and even usability testing tool, but the folks at IG Index have figured out a creative way to use sketches and paper prototypes as a communication tool in place of wireframes for demonstrating interaction to development teams. Martin Belam posted video from UX London 09 of Jane Austin, Chris Neale and Frances Eida discussing this simple method of taking wireframe/storyboard sketches or paper prototypes, and creating stop-motion animation to demonstrate interface.</description></item><item><title>Joe</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/joe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/joe/</guid><description>The whimsical sketched interface of Joe Davis' design portfolio.
http://www.joedavis.co.uk/</description></item><item><title>Tori's Eye</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/toris-eye/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/toris-eye/</guid><description>This is pretty cool. Origami birds carrying tweets while the sun rises on papercraft scenery. All done with jquery.
http://toriseye.quodis.com/#konigi</description></item><item><title>Motionographer</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/motionographer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/motionographer/</guid><description>Motionographer is a source of inspiration for filmmakers, animators and designers.
http://motionographer.com/</description></item><item><title>Back of the Napkin</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/back-napkin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/back-napkin/</guid><description>I can't think of a more appropriate site for a cute hand drawn interface than for The Back of the Napkin book site. This is a great book for anyone who wants to expand their tools for business thinking. Dan Roam provides a friendly approach and simple formula to using drawing to collect, analyze, and communicate problems and ideas, and you don't need to be good at drawing to do it.</description></item><item><title>Using the Storyboard Paper for Stop Motion Animation</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/using-storyboard-paper-stop-motion-animation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/using-storyboard-paper-stop-motion-animation/</guid><description>My son got his hands on the storyboard paper and started sketching a stop motion animation sequence in the cells. He just started his second session in a stop motion class. This is one of the things I used our printed graph paper for, but because that was printed in black/gray on our laser printer, I had a hard time knocking out the grid lines mixed in with his drawings.</description></item><item><title>CGART: Video and Motion Graphics Showcase</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/cgart-video-and-motion-graphics-showcase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/cgart-video-and-motion-graphics-showcase/</guid><description>CGART is an excellent new showcase that curates motion work covering the following areas: Motion Design, Animation, CG Animation, Cinematography, Special Effects, Interesting Advertising, Music Videos, Making of Videos, Movie Trailers, Motion Experiments.
http://cgart.com/</description></item></channel></rss>