<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>advertising on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/advertising/</link><description>Recent content in advertising on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/advertising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MTV Networks: Which video ads work best?</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/mtv-networks-which-video-ads-work-best/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mtv-networks-which-video-ads-work-best/</guid><description>CNet reports on an MTV Networks survey on the effectiveness of their video advertising formats. "Project Inform," the MTV survey, found that a five-second-long "pre-roll" ad in advance of the clip, combined with ten seconds of a semi-transparent ad unit that takes up the lower third of the video (and starts about ten seconds in), makes up "both the most effective and the most audience-friendly ad product for short-form online video,"</description></item><item><title>Concept Feedback</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/concept-feedback/</guid><description>Concept Feedback.com is a free community where designers and developers can exchange feedback on design projects. Registered users have the ability to post marketing concepts for free. Concepts may include, but are not limited to, websites, logos, newsletters, landing pages, advertisements and videos. Reviewers can offer constructive feedback on each concept using a proprietary feedback tool. Feedback is automatically collected and archived for the user to help improve the final concept and get better results.</description></item><item><title>BooneOakley</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/booneoakley/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/booneoakley/</guid><description>Ad agencies are outdoing each other in terms of clever uses of social media. BooneOakley's new web site is actually a series of YouTube videos with links placed via annotations into the videos to connect all of what we might traditionally think of as sections. What they create is something like a network of hypertext connections to hold together a concept of site&amp;#8212;hacked together boundaries that create space within another larger space.</description></item><item><title>Twix.com</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/twixcom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/twixcom/</guid><description>Man, the candy advertising biz sure spends a lot on creative work. While not as unexpected as the Skittles site, the interactive storytelling on Twix.com takes you through a scenario where you get to play a guy trying and lying to pick up a girl at a party by helping him make strategic decisions at each Twix moment. Guess 18-30-ish guys are their target demographic. Clever use of interactive video and a humorous story to keep you engaged on the site for more than a few seconds.</description></item><item><title>Skittles</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/skittles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/skittles/</guid><description>Stealing a page out of Modernista's book, Skittles launches a site that uses social networking and media sites as its backdrop. Like the Modernista site, the effect is unexpected and attention getting. Choosing Twitter for this experiment was pretty gutsy. Whereas they could have more control over what goes on their YouTube and Facebook pages, the sentiment on Twitter isn't all too positive. You can check the live feed of Skittles tweets at Newstrendz, a new social trends site.</description></item><item><title>Playground Contextual Banner Ad</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/playground-contextual-banner-ad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/playground-contextual-banner-ad/</guid><description>Swedish agency Akestam Holst has created a contextual banner ad for retailer Playground Stores that selects an appropriate jacket for you depending on the weather where in your location. The demo seems hard coded, but is kind of neat. Would be really weird if they could figure out my gender and favorite colors.
Via Creativity
http://www.dallassthlm.com/playground/playground.html</description></item><item><title>Pomegranate</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/pomegranate/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/pomegranate/</guid><description>This one seems out of left field. A clever advertising campaign for the all in one device you want, but can never have. Explore a little while, and you'll discover what you can have instead (check out the first link first).
http://76.74.186.145/</description></item><item><title>Sprint Now Widgets</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/sprint-now-widgets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sprint-now-widgets/</guid><description>Sprint's widgetopia is a clever Flash site advertising their mobile broadband card.
http://now.sprint.com/widget/</description></item><item><title>Warioland Ad on YouTube</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/warioland-ad-youtube/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/warioland-ad-youtube/</guid><description>This is one of the cleverest web ads I've ever seen. May even trump the Apple ad units that talk to each other.
https://www.youtube.com/experiencewii</description></item><item><title>LongTail Video</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/longtail-video/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/longtail-video/</guid><description>Jeroen "JW" Wijering, developer who brought us the JW FLV Media Player has launched the LongTail Video venture. The company provides a the Video Player with ad serving pre-roll, post-roll, and mid-roll options.
http://www.longtailvideo.com/</description></item><item><title>Adtunes.com</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/adtunes-com/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adtunes-com/</guid><description>Adtunes is a portal for finding music from TV commercials, film trailers, TV show and film soundtracks, and video games. I've used the forums on this site several times to track down the creators of music in TV commercials.
http://adtunes.com/</description></item><item><title>REC: Immersive Movie Ad</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/rec-immersive-movie-ad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rec-immersive-movie-ad/</guid><description>The REC movie site is one of the most immersive Flash video interactive pieces I've seen in a long time. The site puts you into the movie as though you are watching video captured from an observer who is actually in the scene. There's a qality to the video and the storytelling here that feels very reminiscent of the Blair Witch Project, and here it is an equally successful vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Placement on a Page: The Missing Ad Metric</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/placement-page-missing-ad-metric/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/placement-page-missing-ad-metric/</guid><description>Paidcontent reports on a study conducted by MarketingSherpa on advertising bechmarks, which showed the effect of online ad placement in relation to the fold.
According to the report, most individuals don‘t see most ads served to them—especially ads served below the fold. Despite this result, media delivery reports rarely include information on whether, or what percentage of, a media buy was served above or below the fold. On the chart below, the bottom of the blue area represents the percent of total viewers who see an ad; the top represents the percent of total viewers who scroll to a point where the ad is visible on their screen.</description></item><item><title>Fanta</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/fanta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/fanta/</guid><description>http://www.fanta.co.uk/</description></item><item><title>Mexico Via Pacifico</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/mexico-pacifico/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/mexico-pacifico/</guid><description>http://mexicoviapacifico.com/</description></item></channel></rss>