<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crowdsourcing on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/crowdsourcing/</link><description>Recent content in crowdsourcing on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/crowdsourcing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NYPL Labs Infomaki: A lightweight usability testing service</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/nypl-labs-infomaki-lightweight-usability-testing-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/nypl-labs-infomaki-lightweight-usability-testing-service/</guid><description>The New York Public Library Labs has begun testing a light usability testing system to supplement their formal tests, inspired by the Five Second Test method which was devised by Jared Spool and turned into a service by the guys at mayhem(method). The service, nicknamed Infomaki (info roll?), combines the type of service 5 second test provides, as well as allowing single question surveys for checking on things like simple labeling issues, which you might have tested using card sorting.</description></item><item><title>NO!SPEC vs. crowdSPRING Debate at 37signals</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/nospec-vs-crowdspring-debate-37signals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/nospec-vs-crowdspring-debate-37signals/</guid><description>37 signals gave the soapbox to crowdSPRING to justify the crowdsourcing and spec work platform and the debate ensued. I got through about half of the long rant, then half of the comments, and called it a day. I've already chimed in about my opinion for crowdSPRING. I believe there is a place for this market, and if small businesses will support it with dollars, then it will continue to exist.</description></item><item><title>Drupal.org crowd wireframing</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/drupal-org-crowd-wireframing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/drupal-org-crowd-wireframing/</guid><description>Leisa Reichelt starts up some participatory design by getting Drupal contributors to sketch suggestions for things they'd like to see change on Drupal.org.
http://www.disambiguity.com/drupalorg-come-wireframe-with-me/</description></item><item><title>Cymbolism, Words &amp; Colors</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/cymbolism-words-colors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/cymbolism-words-colors/</guid><description>"Cymbolism is a new website that attempts to quantify the association between colors and words, making it simple for designers to choose the best colors for the desired emotional effect."
http://www.cymbolism.com/</description></item><item><title>RYZ Rating and Favoriting</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</guid><description>RYZ is a sneaker manufacturer that crowdsources the design of their product and shares the revenue with winners. Users download a template to create design and upload to their profile. Participants vote on the designs by giving ratings and winners receive $1000 and $1 for every pair sold. The site provides simple interfaces for both favoriting and rating entries.
1. The voting page.2. Clicking the star badge in the corner of the image adds to favorites.</description></item><item><title>NameThis: Crowdsourced Project Naming</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/namethis-crowdsourced-project-naming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/namethis-crowdsourced-project-naming/</guid><description>NameThis is an innovative new crowdsourced community that uses the wisdom of crowds to name products and services. Companies or individuals who are looking to name something pay $99 to request help in naming the thing. Participants provide suggestions and vote or invest a stake in the suggestions that have been posted. Kluster's robots decide which is best, and participants get paid back when they've invested in the winner. You can find out more about how it works.</description></item><item><title>Crowdsourced Color Explorer</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/crowdsourced-color-explorer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/crowdsourced-color-explorer/</guid><description>I have to admit, that this crowdsourced color explorer is one of the coolest ideas I've seen in, oh, the last few weeks. On the Dolores blog, Brendan explains how Mechanical Turk was used to present a set of random colors to participants in an exercise designed to observe how people name colors. The project was inspired by the World Color Survey. The result was the color explorer, aka "</description></item><item><title>brand and celeb tags</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/brand-and-celeb-tags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/brand-and-celeb-tags/</guid><description>Noah Brier's celeb tags and brand tags sites is a crowdsourced tagging game that asks participants to tag a brand or celebrity and then see how others have tagged the brand or celeb. The game can be played in reverse as well, by viewing a tag cloud and trying to guess what the brand or celeb is.
I tried to take screenshots, but the celebrities' tag results were full of nonsensical tags.</description></item><item><title>Users around the world translate Facebook for free</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/users-around-world-translate-facebook-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/users-around-world-translate-facebook-free/</guid><description>Facebook is tapping its international user community to help translate it's interface, namely the copy for its guidelines, into nearly the 2 dozen languages that represent the community's market outside the US. The localization effort is a massive crowdsourcing task that has been both criticized and lauded. The critics often point to the unpredictability and inconsistency of translations. Proponents of the effort applaud the boldness at utilizing an already eager community to contribute to making the application better for users in other non English-speaking countries.</description></item><item><title>Crowdsourcing The Library of Congress</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/crowdsourcing-library-congress/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/crowdsourcing-library-congress/</guid><description>The Library of Congress has maded 2 of its collections of historical photographs available on Flickr. The goal is to get users to tag and comment on the photos, as well as help provide identifying information. It's very interesting to see such a large and old institution embracing open social collaboration like this. When I was in school, the idea of user supplied freetagging was pretty seen as an edge-case activity even for things like private databases.</description></item></channel></rss>