<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>collaboration on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/collaboration/</link><description>Recent content in collaboration on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Relay.io Design Sharing via Slack</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/relay-io-design-sharing-via-slack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/relay-io-design-sharing-via-slack/</guid><description>Relay looks like it&amp;rsquo;ll be a nice design communication tool for teams using Slack. Capture screens directly from Adobe CC, Sketch, Chrome, or anything else on your screen and it&amp;rsquo;ll be ready for critique in Slack, with comments and annotation.
(Hatip Leon)</description></item><item><title>Frontify: Design review, documentation, and specification app</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</guid><description>Frontify looks like an interesting SaaS product for design teams. It provides collaborative features for getting design feedback, creating specifications, documentation and style guides, and linking pages together.
The commenting and linking features are what you'd expect, but what I was really impressed with are the measures, colors, and typography tools for generating style guides. Very nicely done. There are additional capabilities for code export &amp;amp; integration with their API.</description></item><item><title>Call Recorder for Skype</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/call-recorder-skype/</guid><description>ecamm's Call Recorder for Mac captures audio and video to save Skype calls as QuickTime movies. Useful for user interviews or screensharing sessions.
Thanks to Thomas @vanderwal for the tip
http://www.ecamm.com/mac/callrecorder/</description></item><item><title>IPEVO Ziggi Review</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/ipevo-ziggi-review/</guid><description>Have you ever done the dance of holding a sketch up to your computer's webcam or taken pictures of them with your iPhone to email to yourself or to colleagues? I've done that sort of thing for all of the years that I've worked remotely on design and development teams, because scanners get tired real fast. Frustrated with this process, I had largely given up, until a few months ago when I was looking for tools to share work on paper between students and teachers.</description></item><item><title>Draftboard: Design Review Tool</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/draftboard-design-review-tool/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/draftboard-design-review-tool/</guid><description>Draftboard is a wireframe and visual design review web app for capturing design reviews of your work.
http://www.draftboardapp.com</description></item><item><title>A wireframe kit for Google Drawings</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/wireframe-kit-google-drawings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/wireframe-kit-google-drawings/</guid><description>Morten Just created wireframe templates using the new drawing tools available for Google Docs. The illustration tools in Docs gives you basic shapes you need to create UI elements that can be combined and grouped to create components. The biggest advantage is that since it's document authoring in the Docs cloud, you can do collaborative editing.
For what it's worth, I don't think this is ideal, but it is interesting because of the online collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Team Whiteboarding with Twiddla</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</guid><description>Twiddla is an easy to use collaborative whiteboard service, but it's really got the potential to be much more. The whiteboard lets you mark up websites and graphics, and even use a drag-drop library of interface elements for working on interface concepts collaboratively. You communicate with others in the meeting with the chat window, and you can also use built in audio-conferencing capabilities. Very impressive, and free. Would make sense for there to be options for private meetings as well as embedding the whiteboard into your CMS or intranet.</description></item><item><title>Software Tool Design: Design by Sketching</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/software-tool-design-design-sketching/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/software-tool-design-design-sketching/</guid><description>The second part of Stephen Chambers' series on designing the ANTS Profiler tool, a .NET code profiler, discusses how a team leader challenged a group to really work collaboratively on developing the concept for the tool's interface by taking away computers and requiring that the team work with only paper, whiteboards, pencils, and markers.
James, the team leader had just read Bill Buxton's Sketching the User Experience and wanted to try to get his engineers to rally around the idea that everyone can participate in this ideation phase, and no one needed any specific skill to propose and sketch ideas.</description></item><item><title>Protonotes: HTML prototyping collaboration tool</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/protonotes-html-prototyping-collaboration-tool/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/protonotes-html-prototyping-collaboration-tool/</guid><description>Protonotes provides a service to allow teams to add notes directly onto html prototypes. Check out the video below for a demo. After you register the confirmation email provides a few snippets of javascript to put into your html prototypes to insert a menubar over the top of your site. The menubar provides controls for creating notes and can be configured to be unobtrusive. http://www.protonotes.com/</description></item><item><title>Sumopaint.com beta - Image Editing in the Browser</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/sumopaintcom-beta-image-editing-browser/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sumopaintcom-beta-image-editing-browser/</guid><description>Sumopaint, by Snap Group Ltd is looking to be a really slick Flash-based online graphics creation and editing tool. It has a very complete list of functionalities with shapes, brushes, layers, text editing, filters, and many of the features you'd expect from Photoshop or (ack) GIMP. Users can share images for community editing, create and view versions, and add comments. This looks like it might turn out to be an excellent resource for those looking at doing things like shared whiteboarding and prototyping without the real-time editing.</description></item><item><title>CollabFinder</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/collabfinder/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/collabfinder/</guid><description>CollabFinder is a new community to find and communicate with other designers and developers with the goal of collaborating on future projects. Great and simple idea that could turn out to be a very useful connector. http://collabfinder.com/</description></item><item><title>ProofHQ</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/proofhq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/proofhq/</guid><description>ProofHQ is a collaborative tool for reviewing creative projects such as photography and graphic design. The tool allows you to upload anything from a PDFs, PSDs, and JPGs to Word and PowerPoint files up to 75 MB. The functionality is a bit like a mashup of Flickr and Skitch. It allows users to annotate, mark up, and comment on the work. The art can be embedded into a web site with the provided embed code.</description></item><item><title>Backboard</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/backboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/backboard/</guid><description>Backboard is a very simple collaboration service that allows teams to upload images (e.g. schematics, design comps, and screenshots) to a web page and elicit feedback from team members. http://getbackboard.com/</description></item><item><title>TextFlow</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/textflow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/textflow/</guid><description>TextFlow is a new parallel document editing application and service that allows multiple users to work on a document simultaneously. The service should appeal to people who use the Track Changes feature of Microsoft Word. TextFlow lets users edit documents, and instantly see the changes suggested. One person can review the changes and apply them. The difference between this service and something like Google Docs or working in a wiki, is that the changes are indicated visually, rather than having to go through the diff displays in revision history.</description></item><item><title>Denning and Yaholkovsky on Real Collaboration</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/denning-and-yaholkovsky-real-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/denning-and-yaholkovsky-real-collaboration/</guid><description>Thomas Van Der Wal Personal provides a brief synopsis of "Getting to "we"", an article in Communications of the ACM (Volume 51, Issue 4 - April 2008). According to Thomas:
Peter Denning and Peter Yaholkovsky break down the tools needed for various knowledge needs into four categories: 1) Information sharing; 2) Coordination; 3) Cooperation; and Collaboration.
The article apparently discusses the misunderstanding of the term collaboration, and when it is an appropriate practice.</description></item></channel></rss>