<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>software as a service (saas) on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/software-as-a-service-saas/</link><description>Recent content in software as a service (saas) on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/software-as-a-service-saas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>280 Slides - Create &amp; Share Presentations Online</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/280-slides-create-share-presentations-online/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/280-slides-create-share-presentations-online/</guid><description>280 Slides is a service that lets you create presentations online in a Keynote-like interface, and then share them, download them to PowerPoint, and present them online.
http://280slides.com/</description></item><item><title>TextFlow</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/textflow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/textflow/</guid><description>TextFlow is a new parallel document editing application and service that allows multiple users to work on a document simultaneously. The service should appeal to people who use the Track Changes feature of Microsoft Word. TextFlow lets users edit documents, and instantly see the changes suggested. One person can review the changes and apply them. The difference between this service and something like Google Docs or working in a wiki, is that the changes are indicated visually, rather than having to go through the diff displays in revision history.</description></item><item><title>readbag personal bookmarking</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/readbag-personal-bookmarking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/readbag-personal-bookmarking/</guid><description>readbag is one of those incredibly simple and well-implemented services that puts a subtle but useful twist on a product in an already crowded space. The readbag bookmarking service (it's actually a Google App Engine application) provides the functionality to do one thing very well--bookmark pages that you want to read for later.
Now you might argue that you can use any social bookmarking service to do this, or something like Evernote.</description></item><item><title>FontStruct: User Generated Fonts</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/fontstruct-user-generated-fonts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/fontstruct-user-generated-fonts/</guid><description>Font retailer, FontShop are launching FontStruct a free font-building tool that lets users create fonts via an online font editor using geometrical shapes, which are arranged in a grid pattern, like tiles or bricks. TrueType fonts are generated for use on Mac or PC. Users can keep fonts to themselves or share them with the community. All fonts are free to download. http://fontstruct.fontshop.com/</description></item><item><title>MoFuse: Hosted Mobile Website Service</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/mofuse-hosted-mobile-website-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mofuse-hosted-mobile-website-service/</guid><description>MoFuse is a service that allows site owners to provide a .mobi experience for their existing sites. The service allows you simply plug an RSS feed url into your account settings for a new site, and delivers a mobile formatted version of that feed. They also provide the ability to publish as an iPhone app, using the IUI interface, which you can experience on Google and FaceBook mobile sites. The service also allows you to create static pages, and customize the colors of the UI.</description></item></channel></rss>