<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fish Eye Lens on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/fish-eye-lens/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fish Eye Lens on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/fish-eye-lens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Lives Here Glossary</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ed-lives-here-glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ed-lives-here-glossary/</guid>
      <description>Paper manufacturer NewPage provides the Ed Lives Here site, a useful resource with information about paper, printing, and design. One of the features of this site is a glossary of printing terms. The glossary provides categorized sub-glossaries, as well as the typical a-z index of terms, and a search input. Browsing through the glossary is facilitated by the A-Z links, which use a fish eye lens to bring focus to a section of the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Path Aurora Concept Video, Part 1</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/adaptive-path-aurora-concept-video-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Adaptive Path, as part of Mozilla Lab&#39;s concept video series, provides some suggestions for the possible future of the web experience with Aurora. This forward looking concept focuses on 4 high priority elements: context awareness, natural interaction, continuity, and multi-user applications.
Aurora (Part 1) from Adaptive Path on Vimeo. The scenario laid out is one in which one user starts an audio chat and screen sharing sesion with another user and we begin to see how users can find information from their history and share it and remix it with others in the session.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>