<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>photography on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in photography on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exclusive Reels</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/exclusive-reels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/exclusive-reels/</guid>
      <description>The team over at mediumrare (www.mrare.ca) are proud to launch their latest site - Exclusive Reels.
http://www.exclusivereels.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By the People: the Election of Barack Obama</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/people-election-barack-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/people-election-barack-obama/</guid>
      <description>Promoting the documentary &amp;quot;By The People: The Election of Barack Obama&amp;quot;, this site uses full screen flash and full-screen scaling images to get across some of the passion of the actual campaign.
http://www.myobamadvd.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>robertogadotti.it</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/robertogadottiit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/robertogadottiit/</guid>
      <description>a new vers ready for 2010
I gave more importance to the emotional impact that usability.
http://www.robertogadotti.it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonterra Trattoria</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/bonterra-trattoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/bonterra-trattoria/</guid>
      <description>Mediumrare just launched the redesign of a Calgary Restaurant called Bonterra. Check out the food gallery for pure awesomeness.
http://bonterra.ca</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petra Quilitz</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/petra-quilitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/petra-quilitz/</guid>
      <description>This is one perhaps one of the most attractive portfolios I&#39;ve seen for an Info. Arch./Interaction Designer. Love the use of photography to highlight the nice large deliverables tacked on the walls. Great stuff.
http://www.petraquilitz.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palm Pre</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/palm-pre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/palm-pre/</guid>
      <description>Palm&#39;s Pre product page has a serious, polished look that I assume is targeted at a &#34;grown up,&#34; no-nonsense audience, judging by the business user scenarios in the video and the big kitchen counter backdrop. The smooth, rounded corners of the page&#39;s UI elements echo the pebble shape of the phone and the circular shapes of the Pre OS. I like the use of depth of field with the full bleed photo, the hover of the boxes on the right, the change in state when clicking the site search box, and the categorized features at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yay!everyday</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/yayeveryday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/yayeveryday/</guid>
      <description>yay!everyday is community inspiration gallery focussed on sharing images that showcase artists, designers, and their work. Love the random sort option, and the staggered placement of the gallery of images which feels like an installation of paintings on a gallery wall.
http://yayeveryday.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sex:female</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sexfemale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sexfemale/</guid>
      <description>Bold photography in Lena Vazhenina&#39;s portfolio. Moving through the photos isn&#39;t the most intuitive thing though--you have to click and drag horizontally. But gorgeous presentation.
http://sexfemale.cc/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixmac - royalty-free pictures &amp; illustrations, photos &amp; stock images</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/pixmac-royalty-free-pictures-illustrations-photos-stock-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/pixmac-royalty-free-pictures-illustrations-photos-stock-images/</guid>
      <description>Over 3 millions of professional royalty-free photos of about anything are available online through the PIXMAC microstock photobank (www.pixmac.com). Press, graphic designers or bloggers can order photographs they need.
The customers can browse the photos by keywords, or they can use the unique database of fresh, daily updated royalty-free celebrity photos.
Although Pixmac sell the photos cheaply, it pays the authors well thanks to the size of the global Internet market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprocket House</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sprocket-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sprocket-house/</guid>
      <description>Design for Web &amp;amp; Print
http://sprockethouse.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Yale Illumination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/greg-yale-illumination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/greg-yale-illumination/</guid>
      <description>New site for New York lighting company Greg Yale Illumination. Designed and developed by Knowawall.
http://www.gregyale.com/www/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Wink (studio aw)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/alex-wink-studio-aw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/alex-wink-studio-aw/</guid>
      <description>http://www.studioaw.com.br</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BARREL</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/barrel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/barrel/</guid>
      <description>Barrel is a design studio in NYC with a clean, minimalist site. Love the logo, the non-nonsense grid, and the product photos.
http://www.barrelny.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daisy Balloon</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/daisy-balloon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/daisy-balloon/</guid>
      <description>Daisy is an artist that does incredible things with balloons. The site presently shows some amazing dresses fabricated with the long balloons you&#39;d usually only see in the form of little animals, but Daisy elevates the art to design amazing clothing that could be called haute couture. I could easily imagine these things being made out of a less ephemeral material and being worn, albeit a bit uncomfortably.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DestroyFlickr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/destroyflickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/destroyflickr/</guid>
      <description>Tina pointed to DestroyFlickr, an excellent AIR application for viewing Flickr photos.
DestroyFlickr explores alternative methods for viewing and sharing Flickr content. Its user interface provides an environment that benefits photos rather than hindering them. With the ability to look at a photo on a dark, neutral background, you can view it without the interference of a brighter surrounding. By using workspaces and canvases, DestroyFlickr is able to retain a constant history of where you have navigated, offering the ability to revisit an area without the need to reload the entire page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
