<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>css 3 on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/css-3/</link><description>Recent content in css 3 on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/css-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Animate.css: Plug-and-play CSS animation stylesheet</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/animatecss-plug-and-play-css-animation-stylesheet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/animatecss-plug-and-play-css-animation-stylesheet/</guid><description>animate.css is a stylesheet created by Dan Eden for doing common, cross-browser css3 animations for things like transitions for emphasis. To use them in your project, simply add add the stylesheet and link, add a class to an element, or call the animation yourself in your CSS file.
http://daneden.me/animate/</description></item><item><title>Sencha Touch HTML5 Mobile App Framework</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</guid><description>Sencha Touch looks like an excellent toolkit for delivering HTML 5/CSS 3 mobile experiences. Check out these demos your mobile device to give it a test run: GeoCongress (makes use of geolocation), Solitaire (drag and drop and flip animations), Kiva (provides iPad popover controls).
Sencha Touch allows you to develop web apps that look and feel native on Apple iOS and Google Android touchscreen devices. It's built specifically to leverage HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript and makes use of HTML5 to deliver components like audio and video, as well as a localStorage proxy for saving data offline.</description></item><item><title>When can I use... HTML5, CSS3, etc.</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</guid><description>Can I Use provides compatibility tables for features in HTML5, CSS3, SVG and other upcoming web technologies.
http://caniuse.com/</description></item></channel></rss>