<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>writing on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/writing/</link><description>Recent content in writing on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:35:31 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What do you do?</title><link>https://konigi.com/writing/004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:35:31 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/writing/004/</guid><description>I saw him sitting on a rock in the dust with his face in his hands, trying to stifle the sounds behind them. He&amp;rsquo;s a grown man in a muscle shirt and leather cowboy hat. His shoulders were shuddering. He was crying. Bawling, really. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only one.
Looking around me, outside the ornate building, I began to take in more of the people gathered here. Some were in small groups and others alone.</description></item><item><title>POTD: J.K. Rowlings Plot Spreadsheet for Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/potd-jk-rowling%e2%80%99s-plot-spreadsheet-%e2%80%98harry-potter-and-order-phoenix%e2%80%99/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/potd-jk-rowling%e2%80%99s-plot-spreadsheet-%e2%80%98harry-potter-and-order-phoenix%e2%80%99/</guid><description>Love this post on /Film showing a few artifacts from J.K. Rowling's creative process. Rowling uses spreadsheets she draws by making grid lines on plain paper, creating columns to outline a book's plot along a timeline, with months progressing downward. The initial columns contains a title and blurb about the plot, and further columns contain info about sub-plots. The excerpt below describes this in detail:
Rowling outlines each chapter in detail including which month of the school year it takes place in, the title and the plot.</description></item><item><title>Content Templates to the Rescue</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/content-templates-rescue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/content-templates-rescue/</guid><description>Erin Kissane writes about using content templates "... to help speed up the information-collection process, improve consistency across the website, and make the editing process easier and more orderly" in A List Apart.
The ideal situation is to have a content strategist, perhaps a technical writer, who can provide the guidance for auditing and organizing information, and add some rigor to the writing process. The absence of a content strategist on a project necessitates at least dedicating one person to this task.</description></item><item><title>Writing Microcopy</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/writing-microcopy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/writing-microcopy/</guid><description>Joshua Porter writes about the use of microcopy to create confidence and alleviate concerns in customers about the actions they take on your site. Ironically, the smallest bits of copy, microcopy, can have the biggest impact. ... Microcopy is small yet powerful copy. It’s fast, light, and deadly. It’s a short sentence, a phrase, a few words. A single word. It’s the small copy that has the biggest impact. Don’t judge it on its size…judge it on its effectiveness.</description></item><item><title>The Language We Use</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/language-we-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/language-we-use/</guid><description>In "The language we use," David Malouf discusses how ideas about user interaction can become so ingrained in what we are familiar with, that our language begins to reflect that familiarity. That can lead to a natural tendency to explain away interaction without thought to what it means to the design of a thing. In this case a student describes the change of context in a sketch presentation by using the word "</description></item><item><title>Designing by Writing</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/designing-writing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/designing-writing/</guid><description>I love what tiny gigantic has written in this great short post about designing by writing (or the non-iterative design process). I agree wholeheartedly, although I think of writing as part of design to be accretive and/or iterative. A few choice bits from the entry:
[W]hen someone asks you why you used green, or why you included that crumpled-paper background, or why there’s a bird in the logo, you’re gonna need to know.</description></item><item><title>Going Slow</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/going-slow/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/going-slow/</guid><description>The New York Times fashion section article, "Blogging at a Snail's Pace" discusses slow blogging, a near Ludd-like movement against the practice of posting quick and in high volume. It's like slow food versus fast food. Slow bloggers discard the belief that webloggers need to post often, because the reflectiveness of thought and quality of writing suffer. When comparing the slow versus fast differences, Barbara Ganley, a blogger who writes from Vermont had this to say.</description></item><item><title>David Pogue on Tech Terms to Avoid</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/david-pogue-tech-terms-avoid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/david-pogue-tech-terms-avoid/</guid><description>David Pogue offers some suggestions the selection of non-jargony words when writing/speaking about technology. Most of these I agree with. Here's a few: * Enable. Who on earth says, "Enable the GPS function"? Only user-manual writers and computer-book authors. Say "Turn on GPS" instead.
* Support. I don't mean "support" as in "tech support," although even that term is a corporate creepy cop-out (it means "help line"). No, I mean the verb, as in, "</description></item><item><title>Economist.com Editorial Style Guide</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/economist-com-editorial-style-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/economist-com-editorial-style-guide/</guid><description>The Economist, the magazine and news site, provides access to the excellent editorial style guide that every journalist for the company is given. The book, written by John Grimond, is also available for purchase in the printed book form.
http://www.economist.com/research/styleguide/</description></item></channel></rss>