<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>game on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in game on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LITAGO KU-KUNST</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/litago-ku-kunst/</guid>
      <description>Cute use of sticker effects and vinyl toy illustration in this promotional site for a Norwegian milk product. Love the background and navigation menu on the bottom.
http://www.litago.no/kampanjer/kunst/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LittleBigPlanet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/littlebigplanet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/littlebigplanet/</guid>
      <description>The art direction on the LittleBigPlanet site is fabulous and fun as hell. The rich flash experience takes the idea of the DIY game building experience and literally brings that to life. There are corrugated box platforms held up by rope strung on on eyelets, hand drawn video controls, skateboards rolling to and fro as the platforms oscillate, and the little animated rag boy character flopping around as you navigate the space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wario Land: Shake It!</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/wario-land-shake-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/wario-land-shake-it/</guid>
      <description>The promo site for the new Wario Land Wii game takes you into the world of the big garlicky brute as he stomps through the screen, shaking the interface up, much as he did with the YouTube promo. The big gimmick with this site is that you have to shake objects in the interface to navigate from section to section. The rest of the site makes use of a hunt for objects to keep you engaged as you explore the story and game play features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Superest</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/superest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/superest/</guid>
      <description>http://www.thesuperest.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
