<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>physical computing on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/physical-computing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in physical computing on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/physical-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudwash: Washing machine prototype by Berg</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cloudwash-washing-machine-prototype-berg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cloudwash-washing-machine-prototype-berg/</guid>
      <description>I love Berg&#39;s demo of their Cloudwash smart washing machine concept. The company created the prototype to demonstrate how a smart networked appliance might be better designed. The video provides an excellent walkthrough of their design process.
They simplify the face, which consisted of many controls for dedicated functions, reducing that to &#34;high value functions&#34; only. More functionality is accessible via a smart phone app, which also integrates the device with services such as warranty and supplies management and purchasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Mornings: Physical Computing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/creative-mornings-physical-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/creative-mornings-physical-computing/</guid>
      <description>At today&#39;s excellent Creative Mornings on physical computing, Zach Klein and Casey Pugh from Vimeo talked about tinkering with Arduino, an open-source electronics prototyping platform. They showed some simple circuit controls using the LEDs and Processing, and then demoed a Daft Punk helmet they created with LEDs, that could then be controlled/drawn on via a Flash UI. Neat stuff. Later, I got to talk to Carl, a freelance developer/interaction designer who turned me onto NYC Resistor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
