<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nonprofit on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/nonprofit/</link><description>Recent content in nonprofit on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/nonprofit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>World Wide Web Consortium (W3C)</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/world-wide-web-consortium-w3c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/world-wide-web-consortium-w3c/</guid><description>The W3C undergoes its first major redesign in years, simplifying its information architecture, adding visual polish. The header, sidebar, and icons are major improvements, and the addition of progressive disclosure behaviors simplify some of the rather lengthy lists.
http://www.w3.org/</description></item><item><title>Park Avenue Armory</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/park-avenue-armory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/park-avenue-armory/</guid><description>The site for the Park Ave Armory, a non-profit venue for the arts in New York City is a clean, modern looking site with a simple 2-3 column grid that makes minimal use of graphics and presents information simply. There's small change in the logo and heading colors to add some variety and the navigation is clear.
http://www.armoryonpark.org/</description></item><item><title>GOOD</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/good/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/good/</guid><description>GOOD is a collaborative project that produces a print magazine, website, videos, and events that focus on the greater good and moving the world forward, e.g. towards social and environmental improvement. They donate 100% of contributions for the magazine to one of the non profit orgs they support.
The site is utterly readable and clean, and utilizes a blog format with excellent filtering abilities. I like the layout of the entries on the main pages, which look sort of like index cards laid out across a desk.</description></item><item><title>Design Can Change</title><link>http://konigi.com/designs/design-can-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/designs/design-can-change/</guid><description>Design Can Change is a site created by designers at smashLab to provoke the community to start thinking and acting towards sustainable practices. The message of the site is delivered simply and elegantly. Succinct lead copy is accompanied by appropriate infographics, illustration, and stunning photography. Most importantly, the campaign effectively uses storytelling to communicate the issue emphatically and create connection with the audience so they may make the same pledge.</description></item></channel></rss>