<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Breadcrumbs on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/breadcrumbs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Breadcrumbs on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/breadcrumbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Profoto Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Profoto&#39;s take on the breadcrumb combines expanded menus for each branch to provide a drill-down method for navigating siblings, aunts, great-aunts, etc. It basically exposes the hierarchy of siblings at each level, and it&#39;s really most useful when you&#39;ve navigated deep into a hierarchy. It can get a little weird when you use these, because you have to remember that you&#39;re viewing siblings in the branch you&#39;re exposing. If you look at the last screenshot for the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zappos Search Results Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</guid>
      <description>The Zappos&#39; search engine provides a nice results filtering interfaces that presents the user with facets for refining their search. The user can click on the terms at the top of the search results page to narrow the set, and a breadcrumb trail shows the selections they&#39;ve made. Each term in the breadcrumb provides a checkbox to remove any one of those selections and broaden their search.
1. Users run a search using the site&#39;s global search box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompareNetworks jQuery&#39;d Bread Crumb</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/comparenetworks-jqueryd-bread-crumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/comparenetworks-jqueryd-bread-crumb/</guid>
      <description>The JQuery&amp;rsquo;d Breadcrumb is an odd breadcrumb interface that collapses all nodes in the branch upon page load, and then expands to show each node the user mouses over. Their explanation:
This collapsible breadcrumb was developed to deal with deeply nested, verbosely named pages. Rather than limit the amount of elements shown on the sever side, we decided to go with a client side solution for usability and SEO reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wowhead Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Wowhead is a database of World of Warcraft information. The database provides a hierarchical subject taxonomy to describe items, and presents that hierarchy in the breadcrumbs for the item. When the user hovers ofer a branch in the breadcrumb trail, a drop down menu is displayed to show the node siblings and drill down to children. 1. Single entry view (database record).2. Hovering over the current entry&#39;s parent category (Daggers) to view siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Breadcrumb Tab</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo&#39;s hybrid tab/breadcrumb navigation is one of my favorite approaches to global and local navigation. This navigation interface answers a few nagging questions that an interface designer might ask. &#34;How do I present the user with an interface that provides focus on the area they&#39;ve navigated to, while providing a path back or to other main areas of interest?&#34;
What&#39;s interesting here is that they provide a row of primary navigation tabs at the top level, and replace that with a hybrid tab/breadcrumb once the user makes the decision to drill down.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>