<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>promotional content on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/promotional-content/</link><description>Recent content in promotional content on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/promotional-content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hulu 3 Up Carousel</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-3-carousel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-3-carousel/</guid><description>Hulu's new 3-up carousel is being utilized in the site's channels sections to offer a promotional space that takes up less screen height than their 1 up carousel, allowing the display of 3 promo items. This is very similar to the horizontal scrolling Cover Flow module in use on Apple.com interior pages.
1. First set of channels. Scroll bar below allows the user to view more.2. Second set of channels. Hovering over a channel reveals it's name and an &amp;quot;explore&amp;quot; button to jump to it.</description></item><item><title>CBS Navigation</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/cbs-navigation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/cbs-navigation/</guid><description>The CBS site features a drop down menu that spans the entire width of the layout when the user hovers over shows. Wide drop downs are not unusual, and for a time appeared on the Amazon.com site when they experiencing the growth of their departments. On CBS, this type of interface is used to display as many of the network's shows as it can, segmenting them by airing time and format.</description></item><item><title>hulu Carousel</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-carousel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-carousel/</guid><description>Hulu provides an interesting carousel for the promotion of content on their home page. They use a large stage that spans the entire width of the browser window and shows one promoted piece of content at a time. Left/Right arrows allow the user to page through the promos, and a representation of the promos as mini-screens (small multiples) at the bottom of the stage allows the user to see what number they're looking at, among the total promos.</description></item></channel></rss>