<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wizards on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/wizards/</link><description>Recent content in wizards on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/wizards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adobe Product Comparison Table</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/adobe-product-comparison-table/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/adobe-product-comparison-table/</guid><description>Adobe's Creative Suite packages the company's graphics and motion products into families that can be purchased as a set. Because it can be difficult to determine which suite is right for the work you do, Adobe provides both a product comparison table with products and features listed in a chart, or a wizard questionnaire. 1. The standard product comparison table, showing suites along the top and included products prices in rows.</description></item><item><title>Quicken Product Comparison Table and Wizard</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</guid><description>When a software company's product family grows, it can be quite difficult for customers to figure out which product is right for their needs. Quicken is one of those examples where the number of products is overwhelming. They try to help customers with a product comparison table provides a basic checkbox chart of all product feature categories, with product names and prices along the top of the table, and rows of feature categories, with checkboxes to indicate which products match which features.</description></item><item><title>Nivea Download Wizard</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</guid><description>The Nivea brand advertising site features a very wizard for determining the type of logo file you should download depending on how the logo will be used. The visitor will answer questions about the purpose, application, and size needed. At the end of the process, a file is given to download. The questions are very easy to answer, and stepping the user through this process eliminates having to sift through a longer list of file types to determine the logo that would best suit the user's application.</description></item><item><title>Vote Chooser Wizard</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/vote-chooser-wizard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/vote-chooser-wizard/</guid><description>A friend sent me the link to VoteChooser to remind people before the primary to vote. The site consists of a single page wizard that asks you 10 questions about where you stand on political issues. The results page shows how your position aligns with those of presidential candidates in an attempt to help the undecided discover who might be the best person to vote for.
I hesitated at posting this with my results, because I don't want to make a political statement, but its useful to see how this simple questionnaire is very effective at helping to do a simple research task like figuring out what candidates stand for.</description></item></channel></rss>