<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>design reviews on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/design-reviews/</link><description>Recent content in design reviews on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/design-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frontify: Design review, documentation, and specification app</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/frontify-design-review-documentation-and-specification-app/</guid><description>Frontify looks like an interesting SaaS product for design teams. It provides collaborative features for getting design feedback, creating specifications, documentation and style guides, and linking pages together.
The commenting and linking features are what you'd expect, but what I was really impressed with are the measures, colors, and typography tools for generating style guides. Very nicely done. There are additional capabilities for code export &amp;amp; integration with their API.</description></item><item><title>Draftboard: Design Review Tool</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/draftboard-design-review-tool/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/draftboard-design-review-tool/</guid><description>Draftboard is a wireframe and visual design review web app for capturing design reviews of your work.
http://www.draftboardapp.com</description></item><item><title>ProofHQ</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/proofhq/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/proofhq/</guid><description>ProofHQ is a collaborative tool for reviewing creative projects such as photography and graphic design. The tool allows you to upload anything from a PDFs, PSDs, and JPGs to Word and PowerPoint files up to 75 MB. The functionality is a bit like a mashup of Flickr and Skitch. It allows users to annotate, mark up, and comment on the work. The art can be embedded into a web site with the provided embed code.</description></item></channel></rss>