<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:23:11 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Power of 100</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/power-of-100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:23:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/power-of-100/</guid><description>Leveraging the power of discipline, consistency and compounding in your creative work.</description></item><item><title>Rule 7</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/rule-7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:36:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rule-7/</guid><description>My favorite Sister Corita Kent Rule</description></item><item><title>gifmuse.io</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/gifmuse-io/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 09:46:19 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/gifmuse-io/</guid><description>A museum of animated gifs.</description></item><item><title>Sketch Zine</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-zine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 11:15:21 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketch-zine/</guid><description>A little zine made form my UI Sketching talk.</description></item><item><title>Skillshare Course on Rapid Wireframing</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 11:17:22 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</guid><description>I published a free course for Balsamiq users on Skillshare. The course, Rapid Wireframing: Finding the Right Product Design, is designed for those new to Balsamiq, but also features some demonstration of new features like Quick Draw (using the mouse to block out wireframe zones) and Alternates (creating alternate versions of screens). If you&amp;rsquo;re a veteran user, you may be interested in checking that out, and updating to the latest version to take advantage of these useful new ways of working on projects.</description></item><item><title>5.25 Inch Floppy Sketchbook Is Back</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 12:06:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/5-25-inch-floppy-sketchbook-is-back/</guid><description>Remember these? From 2009-2010 I these sketchbooks for a while, using a 5.25&amp;rdquo; floppy disk as a notebook cover. I kind of missed them, so I made a limited number in blank and grid paper.
It’s a wirebound 5.25 inch square sketchbook with about 120-130 pages (60-65 sheets) of 70 pound white vellum paper, hand-crafted by me in my home North of the SF Bay. You can buy a book with blank sheets or one printed with 1cm grid in warm gray ink.</description></item><item><title>Creating Polished Wireframes in Balsamiq</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/creating-polished-wireframes-balsamiq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/creating-polished-wireframes-balsamiq/</guid><description>For Balsamiq users or anyone that bemoans handwritten fonts and sketchy wireframes, I wrote an article to show how to create polished wireframes in Balsamiq on our UX blog. It shows how to use the wireframe skin with a few base controls, and techniques to achieve a minimalist aesthetic. It&amp;rsquo;s meant for those who need to create client-ready deliverables, or for when the sketchy-skin gets in the way of communicating your ideas.</description></item><item><title>Jim Kalbach on Jazz as a Model for the Way Businesses Work</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/jim-kalbach-jazz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jim-kalbach-jazz/</guid><description>Jim Kalbach talks about the improvisational model of Jazz as a metaphor for the way some businesses approach collaboration today. What was probably seen a few years ago as a radical way of structuring companies to organize around the work rather than using inflexible business units as boundaries, is now more commonplace.
To demonstrate what happens in the teamwork of a group of jazz performers, Kalbach assembled a group of musicians to perform a song they hadn&amp;rsquo;t played together before, and described how jazz performances &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; as a type of collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Hello Hugo: Konigi is now a Static Site</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/hello-hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/hello-hugo/</guid><description>After many years of being a Drupal user, from version 2 when I started iaslash.org to version 6 on this site, I&amp;rsquo;ve made the move from PHP/MySQL blog to full on static site. Here&amp;rsquo;s why and how I did it.
Choosing Static Site Generators In the past few years, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken a few sites backwards from Drupal and WordPress into the age of static sites. In many ways, it feels like going back to the beginning of my career, when I used Perl and Shell scripts to generate sites in my first job, and later to more sophisticated site generation using MovableType as a middle man.</description></item><item><title>Code.org Program for K-5</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/codeorg-program-k-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/codeorg-program-k-5/</guid><description>Code.org now has an elementary school program (Kindergarden - 5th grade), and Code Studio for the program looks like its modeled after the free MIT Scratch app, a visual tool that we used with our first son to introduce computer science fundamentals a few years ago. Good stuff.</description></item><item><title>Aral Balkan: I, Simulation</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/aral-balkan-i-simulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/aral-balkan-i-simulation/</guid><description>Aral Balkan’s “I, Simulation” talk about the current state of privacy and freedom in software and services is one the best presentations I’ve watched this year. Balkan talks about business models that focus on user data, and what that can mean to your "privacy." Watch the talk below, given at Open Exchange in Munich, Germany. The information you hand over using service providers like Facebook (think also Messenger, Whatsapp, Instagram) and Google (think also Gmail, Hangouts, Android Devices, Drive, Nest, Dropcam, and Fiber) is already being used to create simulations of you, and he likens this use to spyware.</description></item><item><title>Dedesign the Web 2</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/dedesign-web-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dedesign-web-2/</guid><description>Head to Dedesign the Web and play name that website using wireframes. Courtesy of Designation.
http://dedesigntheweb.com/</description></item><item><title>Des Traynor: Product Strategy is About Saying No</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/des-traynor-product-strategy-about-saying-no/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/des-traynor-product-strategy-about-saying-no/</guid><description>The devil runs UX workshops for idle hands, and he comes up with bad features. This is Des Traynor's lightning talk at Business of Software in 2013. He did an extended version of this in 2014, but the pecha kucha version gets to the heart of the topic. http://vimeo.com/81544164</description></item><item><title>Coolio Emoticon for HipChat</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/coolio-emoticon-hipchat/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/coolio-emoticon-hipchat/</guid><description>It bothers me that Hipchat doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a (coolio) emoticon. How can they ship without one? Shameful.
I&amp;rsquo;ll forgive the oversight and provide one to fill the gap.</description></item><item><title>Experimenting with the IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</guid><description>I got an IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard System ($149 retail price) to demo and did a first little experiment. The product consists of a video sensor and interactive pen. You have to have a projector as well. Here's a super rough demo I made for my team at Balsamiq to show how it would work using Balsamiq Mockups.
While the demo is pretty rough given the 15 minutes I gave myself to set up and record with my phone, it's pretty interesting to consider the possibilities for whiteboarding with wireframing software, if you're so inclined.</description></item></channel></rss>