<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ecommerce on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/ecommerce/</link><description>Recent content in ecommerce on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/ecommerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sugagloss</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sugagloss/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sugagloss/</guid><description>Sugagloss, a top end retailer of exclusive adult accessories, underwear and gifts.
Built completely in Flash around a massively enhanced Magento backend, it behaves like a designer shoppers dream – and yet with it’s HTML progressive build methodology it ticks all SEO best practice requirements – whilst never for a moment compromising it’s user centric, highly engaging environment.
http://www.sugagloss.co.uk</description></item><item><title>Teez</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teez/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teez/</guid><description>A t-shirt store design re-think
http://teez.com.ua</description></item><item><title>The Apple Store's Checkout Form Redesign</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/apple-stores-checkout-form-redesign/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/apple-stores-checkout-form-redesign/</guid><description>I finally made some time to read through Luke Wroblewski's excellent review of the changes in the Apple store's redesigned checkout form. According to Wroblewski, &amp;quot;...retail sales data shows that Mac sales were up 21% year-over-year in the months of October and November. So it's interesting to note that Apple's primary online sales channel (Web-based checkout) was redesigned during this time.
I wasn't surprised that the single page checkout form is an improvement over the paged version.</description></item><item><title>Happy Webbies</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/happy-webbies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/happy-webbies/</guid><description>Desktops and shirts for web designers. The messages hold the world of lesser designers and developers in contempt, but the illustration is great.
http://www.happywebbies.com/</description></item><item><title>Big Cartel</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/big-cartel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/big-cartel/</guid><description>Shopping cart provider Big Cartel hosts simple, customizable ecommerce sites for independent creatives, e.g. artists and musicians. The company site sells the product by describing the service in terms of value, and by providing examples of other artist sites, and the design experience. I think the soft textured watercolor background in the header gives it a hand-crafted feel that's appropriate to this audience. I think emphasizing the sign up link slightly might be a good idea.</description></item><item><title>Republic Bike</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/republic-bike/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/republic-bike/</guid><description>Republic Bike assembles custom bicycles based on shared design. The build feature on the bike configurator lets you choose among a few "curated" color combinations for components. I like the big heading type and the illustration and table of the bike product page. Via @edfladung
http://www.republicbike.com</description></item><item><title>howies</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/howies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/howies/</guid><description>My friend Carl told me about howies a while ago, but I only recently had a look back. They're a clothing and accessories company that aims at providing products with materials and construction that are meant to last and can be handed down to others for reuse. What I like most is how they use storytelling to provide a picture about materials in their products and their handmedown idea, which is communicated in its own mini site.</description></item><item><title>Hidden Secrets of the Amazon Shopping Cart</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/hidden-secrets-amazon-shopping-cart/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/hidden-secrets-amazon-shopping-cart/</guid><description>I'm just seeing for the first time Bryan Eisenberg's GrokDotCom article from Feb 2008 on the evolution of Amazon's shopping cart. It's a great article that makes observations about Amazon's tweaking and testing of their shopping cart buttons over the years. I put all of his screenshots together in the image above.
http://www.grokdotcom.com/2008/02/26/amazon-shopping-cart/</description></item><item><title>Versions</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/versions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/versions/</guid><description>Versions is a Mac Subversion Client (SVN). The home page groups the layout into 3 sections, providing the product overview and value statement, a diagram of how it works, and the full feature and functionality list. It does this all in one page, without the fuss of transitions to view them--just scroll. There are only 2 other pages of significance here. A support page that provides search and a listing of recent support issues via Google Groups, and the shopping cart page.</description></item><item><title>Nike Store</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/nike-store/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/nike-store/</guid><description>Nike's online retail presence is a Flash application that sticks with the glossy stage of the rest of the Nike product sites. The Nike Store provides faceted browsing powered by Endeca on the backend, so the experience of finding the gear particular to your needs is among the best of any online retailer. http://nike.com/index.jhtml#l=nikestore,home&amp;re=US&amp;co=US&amp;la=EN</description></item></channel></rss>