<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>innovation on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in innovation on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How might we...</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-might-we/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-might-we/</guid>
      <description>We know that starting with why is important to product design, but what comes next? &#34;How&#34; would definitely come soon after. But there are many ways to propose how to begin exploring possibilities. The 99u points to a number of questions to ask before starting a project, and how language matters. They refer to Warren Berger&#39;s article in the Harvard Business Review about one of the questions top innovators ask when confronted with a design challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin on the Importance of Domain Knowledge</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/seth-godin-importance-domain-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/seth-godin-importance-domain-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin&#39;s blog often talks about where successful ideas come from, and in this post talks about bypassing the need to make huge leaps in innovation by synthesizing what we know and have learned from history, using Palm as the cautionary tale.
It&#39;s not enough to be aware of the domain you&#39;re working in, you need to understand it. Noticing things and being curious about how they work is the single most common trait I see in creative people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Nominated as InJo Pick for Conference on Innovation Journalism</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-nominated-injo-pick-ij-7-seventh-conference-innovation-journalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-nominated-injo-pick-ij-7-seventh-conference-innovation-journalism/</guid>
      <description>Last week I got a surprising call from Roman Pixell, Fellow in the Innovation Journalism Fellowship Program at Stanford. The InJo program at Stanford is focused on journalism covering innovation processes and ecosystems.
I&#39;m honored to have been nominated for the InJo Pick alongside the well respected journalists in this year&#39;s selection, and will be attending the InJo 7 conference in Palo Alto, participating in a round table on June 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The iPad is a Toy</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-toy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ipad-toy/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Apple said Monday that it sold more than 300,000 iPads on the day of its launch, ushering in a new era of people buying things to find out what they are.&#34; -- Seth Meyer for Weekend Update on SNL.
 I knew that it would be much more like an iPod Touch than a Mac netbook. But what I didn&#39;t know until I &#34;found out what it really was,&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User-Centered Innovation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-centered-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-centered-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Roberto Verganti&#39;s article in HBR, &amp;quot;User-Centered Innovation Is Not Sustainable,&amp;quot; discusses how focussing on what user&#39;s say they want isn&#39;t a strategy for innovation. Not news to you, but his take looks at what that means regarding innovation from a sustainability perspective. I found it thought-provoking in other ways as well. The main idea is this. Forward-looking designers and business or policy decision makers may have a greater role and influence regarding designing sustainability products than customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside IDEO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/inside-ideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/inside-ideo/</guid>
      <description>Design Observer points to the 1999 ABC Nightline program that took an inside look at IDEO. How does the process of designing a better product work? To show you, Nightline went to Palo Alto, CA to the designers at IDEO, and gave them the toughest problem we could think of. Take something old and familiar like the shopping cart and completely redesign it in just five days.
IDEO&#39;s unique brand of brainstorming is called &#39;&#39;Deep Dive,&#39;&#39; a sort of total immersion into the problem at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Buxton on How to Keep Innovating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-how-keep-innovating/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bill-buxton-how-keep-innovating/</guid>
      <description>In BusinessWeek, Bill Buxton discusses how to keep innovating, with the main idea being that you can continue to cultivate creativity and innovation by finding new things that you have a passion for. He suggests that when you get good enough at a thing, you should find something else to be passionate about, and commit and throw yourself into learning how to do it. You&#39;ll be bad at it at first, but the experience of learning something new, no matter how bad you are at it at first, may affect your creativity in positive ways that you won&#39;t realize until you experience it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paula Scher gets serious at TED</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/paula-scher-gets-serious-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/paula-scher-gets-serious-ted/</guid>
      <description>Fantastic TED video of Paula Scher looking back at her career for those moments where she was able to devote time and effort to serious play and create wonderful work, and contrasting it with the unfortunate moments when the serious becomes solemn. I love how this retrospective observation of her career brings her to conclude that the best of times for her as a designer is when she comes into a project with no grounding or bearing--those times where lack of history or reference point allows that kind of play to emerge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clover Innovates the Coffee Maker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/clover-innovates-coffee-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/clover-innovates-coffee-maker/</guid>
      <description>The $11,000 Clover Coffee Maker brews one cup of coffee at a time using a method similar to a French Press, but with the ability to customize water volume and temperature per cup. The machine is programmable and has a network connection, so the machine can use brewing parameters for specific roasts. Check the video below for the Clover in action.  According to Wired Magazine, Howard Schultz, the founder of Starbucks described the coffee by saying, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Zappos Pays New Employees to Quit</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/why-zappos-pays-new-employees-quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/why-zappos-pays-new-employees-quit/</guid>
      <description>The stories of Zappos&#39; commitment to superior customer service has become nearly legendary. From regular upgrades to next day delivery at no cost to the story of a customer service reps delivery of flowers to a customer whos mother passed away. Now, in Harvard Business Online, Bill Taylor tells of Zappos&#39; unusual customer training program. Zappos offers new employees a $1000 offer to quit after a 4 week training session. The idea behind this tactic is that by weeding out people who take the offer, they keep the ones who will be committed to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Contextual User Interfaces</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/rise-contextual-user-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/rise-contextual-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>In Alex Iskold&#39;s article, The Rise of Contextual User Interfaces, the writer and CEO of software company AdaptiveBlue talks about the rise of contextual interfaces on the desktop an in the services we use on the web.
He points out the failing of choice over context in the old paradigm of UI design. Standardization of UI elements (tabs, combo boxes, etc.) was meant as a way to keep users from having to learn how to use an interface.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
