<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>balsamiq on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/balsamiq/</link><description>Recent content in balsamiq on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 11:17:22 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/balsamiq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Skillshare Course on Rapid Wireframing</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 11:17:22 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</guid><description>I published a free course for Balsamiq users on Skillshare. The course, Rapid Wireframing: Finding the Right Product Design, is designed for those new to Balsamiq, but also features some demonstration of new features like Quick Draw (using the mouse to block out wireframe zones) and Alternates (creating alternate versions of screens). If you&amp;rsquo;re a veteran user, you may be interested in checking that out, and updating to the latest version to take advantage of these useful new ways of working on projects.</description></item><item><title>Creating Polished Wireframes in Balsamiq</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/creating-polished-wireframes-balsamiq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/creating-polished-wireframes-balsamiq/</guid><description>For Balsamiq users or anyone that bemoans handwritten fonts and sketchy wireframes, I wrote an article to show how to create polished wireframes in Balsamiq on our UX blog. It shows how to use the wireframe skin with a few base controls, and techniques to achieve a minimalist aesthetic. It&amp;rsquo;s meant for those who need to create client-ready deliverables, or for when the sketchy-skin gets in the way of communicating your ideas.</description></item><item><title>Balsamiq UX Template</title><link>http://konigi.com/tools/balsamiq-ux-template/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/tools/balsamiq-ux-template/</guid><description>Made for UX designers This template is made for UI designers using Balsamiq Mockups that want to create polished, client-ready presentation decks. It includes a few example pages for basic UX document needs (journey maps, personas, wireframe pages), a Symbol Library for controls crafted in Konigi-style, and grid Symbols to keep your layout tight.
Download for free 1. Download the template.
2. Duplicate it whenever you start a new project.</description></item></channel></rss>