<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>whiteboards on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/whiteboards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in whiteboards on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/whiteboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimenting with the IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</guid>
      <description>I got an IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard System ($149 retail price) to demo and did a first little experiment. The product consists of a video sensor and interactive pen. You have to have a projector as well. Here&#39;s a super rough demo I made for my team at Balsamiq to show how it would work using Balsamiq Mockups.
 While the demo is pretty rough given the 15 minutes I gave myself to set up and record with my phone, it&#39;s pretty interesting to consider the possibilities for whiteboarding with wireframing software, if you&#39;re so inclined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Whiteboarding with Twiddla</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</guid>
      <description>Twiddla is an easy to use collaborative whiteboard service, but it&#39;s really got the potential to be much more. The whiteboard lets you mark up websites and graphics, and even use a drag-drop library of interface elements for working on interface concepts collaboratively. You communicate with others in the meeting with the chat window, and you can also use built in audio-conferencing capabilities. Very impressive, and free. Would make sense for there to be options for private meetings as well as embedding the whiteboard into your CMS or intranet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low-Cost Multi-point Interactive Whiteboards Using the Wiimote</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/low-cost-multi-point-interactive-whiteboards-using-wiimote/</guid>
      <description>Researcher provides another Wii Remote hack, this time to help business users create interactive whiteboards on the cheap.
 You might remember the incredible Wiimote hacks by by Johnny Chung Lee, who gave us head tracking demo for desktop VR displays. Lee, a PhD student in the Human-Computer Interaction Institute at Carnegie Mellon University is back with some more useful Wiimote hacks, this time to turn any surface into an interactive whiteboard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
