<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Login on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/login/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Login on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/login/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moof Login and Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moof-login-and-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moof-login-and-registration/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m sure some might dislike the use of the bottom-border inputs here, but I&#39;m a big fan of fill-in-the-blank forms and the conversational copy used in this login and registration form on this social music site.
 http://moof.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin.com Header</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</guid>
      <description>The Virgin.com redesign sports a header that provides a boatload of functionality using mega fly out menus: locale selection, micro-site navigation, registration, login, and newsletter signup. I like that they make these options readily available wherever you are on the site. The longer drop downs like the registration form, for example, seem a little long for users on smaller screens, e.g. netbooks. 1. The global navigation bar provides mega drop downs with sub-nodes and links to their subsidiary companies that provide products and services under each category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Login Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/100-login-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/100-login-forms/</guid>
      <description>Design Reviver collects and captures a massive set of 100 login forms.
http://designreviver.com/inspiration/100-sites-with-outstanding-login-forms/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise 2.0 Conference Inline Login Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/enterprise-2-0-conference-inline-login-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/enterprise-2-0-conference-inline-login-form/</guid>
      <description>The Enterprise 2.0 Conference site, which is run on Jive Clearspace, provides an inline form for logging into the site. Clicking the Login link in the header replaces the header content with a form where inputs and labels are displayed in a single row.
1. Header global navigation with login link.2. Clicking login link replaces the navigation bar with the inline login form. http://community.e2conf.com/index.jspa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Inline Login Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/konigi-inline-login-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/konigi-inline-login-form/</guid>
      <description>Seems strange to feature this site here, but I&#39;m building up a set of this inline form design convention. Konigi provides an unobtrusive control for logging in via the user&#39;s site login/password or Open ID login in a utility navigation area. Clicking one of these log in links allows the user to enter their credentials without navigating to a form on a separate page.
1. Header with login options in utility nav on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Hour Work Week Login Screen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/4-hour-work-week-login-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/4-hour-work-week-login-screen/</guid>
      <description>The clever login screen for Tim Ferris&#39; book site uses words from the book or audiobook as the password for entering restricted areas of its resources section.
 http://fourhourworkweek.com/wms/login/login.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Registration and Login</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-registration-and-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-registration-and-login/</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#39;s login and registration screen is the standard by which other login screens are measured. The simple flow consists of: 1) entering your email address, and 2) entering your password. If you are a new customer, simply select the new customer radio and the follow up screens provide the registration flow.
1. Enter your email address, if you&#39;re not registered, select &amp;quot;New customer,&amp;quot; otherwise log in2. Enter registration info https://amazon.com/gp/sign-in.html</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>