<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>announcement on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/announcement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in announcement on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/announcement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael to Join Balsamiq</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/michael-join-balsamiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/michael-join-balsamiq/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be big.
I&#39;ve been keeping a secret for a few months, that I&#39;m finally able to share with my friends and colleagues who follow Konigi. Today I&#39;ll be bringing my love of interface design to the small team at Balsamiq. I will be joining Peldi, Val, Marco, Luis, Mariah, and Malcolm, my new family at the company that introduced software and web designers to the fun and easy way to create quick, sketch-style wireframes with Balsamiq Mockups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Site is Back and Server Moved</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-site-back-and-server-moved/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-site-back-and-server-moved/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for the downtime. Konigi went down for most of the day yesterday because a spike in traffic and number of database requests caused the databases to be taken offline. With our web host&#39;s help, we&#39;ve moved Konigi to a virtual private server, and now we&#39;re able to run our own database rather than share database resources and limit the number of requests we can make. These are all good problems, and the growing pains are to be expected I suppose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for 2009</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/thank-you-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/thank-you-2009/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to take a moment before I start the New Year&#39;s reveling with my family to thank all of you for the past year.
It&#39;s been a great second year discussing and learning with all of you via Konigi. I&#39;ve connected with so many awesome UX designers by posting my thoughts and experiments on the site, meeting up in the NYC area at social gatherings and conferences, and in the exchange of little tweets here and there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi DIY Wireframe Magnets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-diy-wireframe-magnets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-diy-wireframe-magnets/</guid>
      <description>The Konigi DIY Wireframe Magnet Kit is based on the wireframe stencils and includes 3 sheets of elements that might be useful in whiteboard prototyping. Simply download and print the PDFs onto magnet sheets. They were designed and tested for use with Avery 3270 Printable Magnet Sheets for Inkjet Printers. Lamination is also recommended so they&#39;re usable with dry-erase markers. Enjoy!
//konigi.com/tools/wireframe-magnets-diy-kit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe Icons Updated (v. 1.2)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-icons-updated-v-12/</guid>
      <description>The wireframe icons have been updated to add a bunch of new icons and crop the PNGs to 16 x 16 px. Still recession priced at $10, with lifetime free upgrades. If you own this set, go to your account page and click the &#34;Files&#34; link.
New icons: home, currency symbols, light bulb, hour glass, bell, rubber stamp, text tool, drawing tool, layout, calculator, medal, ribbon, puzzle piece/plugin, key, asterisk/new, wand/wizard, music, exit, pagination arrows, mobile phone, iPhone, happy face, and sad face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Wants to Grow</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-wants-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-wants-grow/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m going to be tearing things up a little while Konigi gets a clue about what it is. I started playing with this blog in Nov 07 as a more organized way of doing my visual design and user interface design sets on Flickr, and think it&#39;s still going well. But over time I&#39;ve found myself drawn to re-blogging and writing the occasional essay, reminding me of my first try at blogging when I did iaslash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You may now login with email instead of username</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/you-may-now-login-email-instead-username/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/you-may-now-login-email-instead-username/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to @lorenbaxter&#39;s suggestion, I&#39;ve enabled logging in with email rather than username if you prefer. Luckily Drupal&#39;s logintoboggan module allows admins to offer this option, as well as offering registration and signup without the roundtrip to email. Sweet. Thanks for making my life easier, Drupal.
This should help ease the experience of finding your file downloads as well if you bought stencils or icons form the store. It also brings me around to re-implementing some of the features I put in in Feb-March last year and then took out, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Notebook for Konigi Friends at SXSW Wireframe Talk</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/free-notebook-konigi-friends-sxsw-wireframe-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/free-notebook-konigi-friends-sxsw-wireframe-talk/</guid>
      <description>So I&#39;ve made some 8.5 in. by 5.25 in. graph paper notebooks because I wanted something a little more functional than what I was using for sketching. They&#39;re basically a mini version of the wireframe grid I use, with markers for 1/3s and 1/4s, but without the gutters. I&#39;ve been working with a prototype of this for a few months now and have a bunch of these ready to put up for sale, but haven&#39;t been rushing to do it, mostly because I made them for myself and selling stuff like notebooks isn&#39;t profitable until you get into selling large quantities, and unfortunately I haven&#39;t the time to market the pads and books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Updated (Version 2.1)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-version-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template-updated-version-21/</guid>
      <description>The OmniGraffle UX Template for interface and interaction designers has been updated to version 2.1. Included in this release are major alignment, grid, and layout changes. Added guides for 24 column grid with vertical and horizontal gutters on wireframes. Added appropriate guides to all templates that necessitated alignment guides. Added small wireframe and iPhone templates. Download it here.
//konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-ux-template</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi on Twitter and Facebook</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-twitter-and-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-twitter-and-facebook/</guid>
      <description>It seems it&#39;s time to start spilling out some of the meta-discussion in my head--the monologue I guess--about what I&#39;m doing here on Konigi. So I started to post announcements and thoughts about what I&#39;m working on with a Konigi Twitter account.
Basically, I feel like I want to separate Konigi-specific postings from my regular Twitter stream so I can update interested readers via that account, as well as post more work in progress commentary, observations, and announcements related strictly to Konigi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays from Konigi</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/happy-holidays-konigi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/happy-holidays-konigi/</guid>
      <description>I just wanted to take a moment to thank everyone who took some time out of their busy days to read Konigi this year, to provide their feedback and commentary, to download my tools, to buy notepads, and to help me keep a dialogue going with you, my new and old design and development friends. This has been a very rewarding first year playing with this blog, and I feel light years away from those years spent doing iaslash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Notepads Should Be Available Next Week</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-notepads-should-be-available-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-notepads-should-be-available-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Konigi Notepad inventory will be arriving next week. We&#39;ll have the wireframe paper, storyboard paper, and a few new designs for designers who don&#39;t need all the fuss of the big title boxes--minimalists like me! Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Graph Paper Notepad Preview</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-notepad-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/konigi-graph-paper-notepad-preview/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m happy to announce that Konigi will soon be offering several products for creatives. I&#39;ve posted some photos I took quickly of the first set below. Better photos will come when the shopping cart is set up.
The first round of gear will include wireframe and storyboard notepads. Each of these pads include 50 sheets at 8 1/2 x 11 inches on white 70# paper, glued on the left side. The ink is a non-photo blue (cyan) so that the grid lines and any sketch lines made in non-photo blue pencil can be knocked out when scanned and processed in graphics software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Faceted Browsing on Konigi</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-faceted-browsing-konigi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-faceted-browsing-konigi/</guid>
      <description>About 10 years ago I participated in the daily indexing of news articles as part of my job designing a digital library. During graduate study for the MLS my concentration was actually on information retrieval and classification, so I was interested in doing the job and understanding the content in order to know how to make it useful to users. Customers would get this information via the web site, by email, and in newsletters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back From a Break</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/back-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/back-break/</guid>
      <description>So, I pretty much took the week off from blogging because I was having a little bit of a creative block this week after finishing off a project and starting a new one. I also had a little bit of a let down after seeking out an estimate to create custom notebooks with my graph paper. Of course, I wanted to do a really high quality book, with a scored cover like the Rhodia, but the quote came in so high that I got really discouraged.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
