<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prototyping on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/prototyping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prototyping on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 11:17:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/prototyping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillshare Course on Rapid Wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 11:17:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</guid>
      <description>I published a free course for Balsamiq users on Skillshare. The course, Rapid Wireframing: Finding the Right Product Design, is designed for those new to Balsamiq, but also features some demonstration of new features like Quick Draw (using the mouse to block out wireframe zones) and Alternates (creating alternate versions of screens). If you&amp;rsquo;re a veteran user, you may be interested in checking that out, and updating to the latest version to take advantage of these useful new ways of working on projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principle for Mac: Animation and Prototyping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 10:31:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/principle-mac/</guid>
      <description>Principle for Mac ($99) is a tool for designing animation, primarily for mobile devices. It provides an easy to use interface for prototyping interaction, transitions, or other animated elements in your interface.
You can design with text, rectangles (which can modified with border radius to make circles), or graphics created with other tools, and then hook up animations for actions like taps, scrolling, and drag, and use the drivers UI to connect those actions to drive other properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots Static Site Builder</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 15:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/roots/</guid>
      <description>Roots is an open source static site compiler that can help take some of the work out of setting up your own build tasks using taskrunners like gulp or grunt. It runs in your terminal and requires minimal setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AniJS: Declarative handling library for CSS animations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</guid>
      <description>AniJS is a library for CSS animations that allows you to write simple statements for handling animation as key/value pairs in html data attributes. It feels very close to writing natural language statements, in a format that is a bit more familiar in code than writing sentences. A simple example contains IF, ON, DO, and TO pairs and would look like this: &amp;lt;input id=&#34;name&#34; type=&#34;text&#34; data-anijs=&#34;if: focus, do: wobble, to: p&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>uilang</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/uilang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/uilang/</guid>
      <description>uilang is a minimal, ui-focused programming language for web designers that handles click events, primarily for toggling classes and css display properties. I love the natural language approach to scripting in uilang. You just insert a statement in a code block like this and it works magically: &amp;lt;code&amp;gt;clicking on &#34;.try-it&#34; toggles class &#34;hidden&#34; on &#34;.info-box&#34;&amp;lt;/code&amp;gt; You still have to write your CSS to handle things like effects, but that&#39;s a plus if you don&#39;t want or need someone else&#39;s implementation of those things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudwash: Washing machine prototype by Berg</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cloudwash-washing-machine-prototype-berg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cloudwash-washing-machine-prototype-berg/</guid>
      <description>I love Berg&#39;s demo of their Cloudwash smart washing machine concept. The company created the prototype to demonstrate how a smart networked appliance might be better designed. The video provides an excellent walkthrough of their design process.
They simplify the face, which consisted of many controls for dedicated functions, reducing that to &#34;high value functions&#34; only. More functionality is accessible via a smart phone app, which also integrates the device with services such as warranty and supplies management and purchasing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origami: Design prototyping with Quartz Composer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/origami-design-prototyping-quartz-composer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/origami-design-prototyping-quartz-composer/</guid>
      <description>Origami is a free toolkit created by the Facebook Design team for Quartz Composer, the visual programming tool that&#39;s available with the Apple XCode development environment. Origami provides patches that can be added to your Quartz Composer library, to create interactive prototypes without programming. Quartz composer&#39;s UI allows you connect patches with wires (or tubes, if you&#39;re familiar with that metaphor) to perform tasks or set behaviors and properties.
Jay Thrash&#39;s video explains how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precomposed Touch Gestures</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</guid>
      <description>Aureus Wade&#39;s Precomposed Touch Gestures are a set of touch-device gestures available as QuickTime animations for use in product demos or presentations. They&#39;ll work in your video editor, and Photoshop.
http://areuswade.com/precomposed-touch-gestures/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protosketch</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/protosketch/</guid>
      <description>Protosketch is a new free app for iOS from UI Stencils to convert sketches to interactive prototypes. The app is made to work with their sketch pads and stencils. Sketch your screens, add them to the app, define hot areas for links, select link destinations, and prototype.
https://protosketch.uistencils.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixture</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/mixture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/mixture/</guid>
      <description>Mixture is a rapid prototyping and static site generation tool for Mac and Windows. It works with the Liquid templating system, supports includes and smart paths, handles HAML and SASS comilation, CSS and JS minification, and provides a simple model system for global and custom data, and supports access to form and query data in their request model. It can produce static HTML that you can push to a hosting service, and allows use of your own domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hammer for Mac</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/hammer-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/hammer-mac/</guid>
      <description>Hammer is a static web site builder for the Mac that lets you build out sites quickly with no server side requirements.
Hammer does includes without PHP, compiles Coffeescript to JS, SASS/SCSS to CSS, has an auto-refresh feature for never having to reload the browser, and provides some simple to use helpers. Since it knows about all of the files in your projects, you just reference names and it knows how to build out paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redacted Font</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/redacted-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/redacted-font/</guid>
      <description>Christian Naths&#39; Redacted is a set of fonts released under SIL Open Font license with block and scribbled font faces. Main difference between Redacted and BLOKK (which the font is copies/is inspired by) is that Redacted uses smaller widths so your text blocks won&#39;t end up wider than your normal font setting.
Git it for free.
https://github.com/christiannaths/Redacted-Font/blob/master/README.md</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tapotype Transition Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/tapotype-transition-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/tapotype-transition-library/</guid>
      <description>Tapotype is a reference library of transitions for mobile prototypes created by Gene Lu using Fireworks and the TAP platform, a framework for iOS prototyping developed by UNITiD. Gene provides tutorials on building prototypes with Tapotype and TAP, and shows how to integrate InDesign and its documenting capabilities into your Fireworks/Tap prototyping workflow.
http://tapotype.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Snippets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/text-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/text-snippets/</guid>
      <description>About This is a work in progress. I&#39;m copying over my commonly used text snippets and wireframes as I go.
People&#39;s Names, Sorted 10, First Name  Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   10, Last Name  Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun   Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun    20, First Name  Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   20, Last Name  Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun   Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun      Wireframe Symbols  Download Balsamiq BMML file</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Snippets</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/tools/text-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/tools/text-snippets/</guid>
      <description>About This is a work in progress. I&#39;m copying over my commonly used text snippets and wireframes as I go.
People&#39;s Names, Sorted 10, First Name  Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   10, Last Name  Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun   Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun   20, First Name  Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun   20, Last Name  Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun   Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun   Wireframe Symbols  Download Balsamiq BMML file</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
