<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferences and Events</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/articles/conferences-and-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/articles/conferences-and-events/</guid>
      <description>All UX Design Development   The 99U New York, NY monitor  ACM SIGCHI Conference  monitor  Adaptive Path UX Intensive Workshop    Ampersand Brighton, UK; New York, NY monitor  Beyond Tellerand Düsseldorf, Germany monitor  Big Design Conference Dallas, TX   Brooklyn Beta Brooklyn, NY   Build Belfast, Northern Ireland monitor  Business of Software Boston, MA monitor  Chicago Camps Chicago, IL   Circles Grapevine, TX monitor  ConvergeSE Columbia, SC monitor  ConveyUX Seattle, WA   Cooper Workshops San Francisco, CA   dConstruct Brighton, UK monitor  Delight Portland, OR monitor  Euro IA Summit    An Event Apart  monitor  eyeo Minneapolis, MN monitor  ffwd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming 2012-2013 UX Conferences</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/upcoming-2012-2013-ux-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/upcoming-2012-2013-ux-conferences/</guid>
      <description>The 2012-2013 conference calendar is lining up and I&#39;ve been starting to track the upcoming events as tickets start to go on sale. I&#39;ve omitted those that are already sold out. Here&#39;s what&#39;s looking interesting on my radar, listed in date order. Am sure I&#39;m missing quite a few. This is a good start.  Lean UX Denver
Denver, CO, Sep 20-21, 2012 fluxible
Kitchener, Ontario, Sep 22–23, 2012 Euro IA Summit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asbury Agile 2012 Conference</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/asbury-agile-2012-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/asbury-agile-2012-conference/</guid>
      <description>Asbury Agile has launched the site for their second conference, which takes place in Asbury Park, the The Boss&amp;rsquo; stomping grounds, on October 3, 2012. I&amp;rsquo;m honored to be one of the guest speakers, to give a talk on interface sketching. There&amp;rsquo;ll be an awesome cast of speakers including Chris Ackermann, Matt Bango, Brad Frost, Sasha Laundy, Kenneth Reitz, Tomer Sharon, Rob Spectre, Srjdjan Strbanovic. Early bird tickets are now available (save $50).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketchnotes 2009 &amp; 2010: A book by Eva-Lotta Lamm</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchnotes-2009-2010-book-eva-lotta-lamm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sketchnotes-2009-2010-book-eva-lotta-lamm/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty incredible. Eva-Lotta Lamm&amp;rsquo;s self-published book contains 2 years&amp;rsquo; worth of illustrated sketchnotes from dozens of UX / Design events and conferences, featuring talks from over 100 speakers and panelists.
Some of the events covered in the book are UXweek 2009, d.construct 2010, Flash on the Beach 2010, UXcamp Europe 2010, offf 2010, UXcamp London, Internet Week Europe 2010, various London IA events and RSA talks.
The book contains notes from talks by Edward Tufte, Scott McCloud, Jesse James Garrett, Ryan Singer, Tim Berners-Lee, Stephen Fry, Dave Gray, Whitney Hess, Stephen Anderson, Andy Budd, Richard Rutter, Eric Reiss, Giles Colborne, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BeerCamp</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/beercamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/beercamp/</guid>
      <description>Best zoomable user interface evah.
http://2011.beercamp.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction10: How to Design an Experience for Experience Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction10-how-design-experience-experience-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction10-how-design-experience-experience-designers/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Bove writes for Fast Company about how she and Bill DeRouchey designed the conference experience in &amp;quot;Interaction10: How to Design an Experience for Experience Designers.&amp;quot; It&amp;rsquo; a great behind the scenes look at how they observed the event the year prior, and thought about every aspect of the attendee experience and designed the IXD10 event to create a service that caters to what&amp;rsquo;s important to the conference-goer at every point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX People: Conference Showcasing Britain&#39;s Talent</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-people-conference-showcasing-britains-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-people-conference-showcasing-britains-talent/</guid>
      <description>UX People is a conference showcasing Britain&amp;rsquo;s talent and achievements in User Experience Design.
Come to learn...
A place to exchange ideas and unveil excellence, UX People is a non-profit making event that celebrates the UK’s place at the forefront of the field. User experience experts from some of the country’s biggest organisations will be giving stimulating talks, leading in-depth workshops and sharing industry insights.
Come to teach...
UX People is committed to helping the rising stars of Britain become the world-class speakers of tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Lx: User Experience Lisbon</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-lx-user-experience-lisbon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-lx-user-experience-lisbon/</guid>
      <description>UX Lx, User Experience Lisbon, is set to take place in Lisbon Portugal next May 12 to 14. Nice time for a trip to Portugal. Speakers include Jared Spool, Luke Wroblewski, Dan Saffer, Peter Merholz, Donna Spencer, Brian Fling, Bill Scott, and Dana Chisnell.
http://www.ux-lx.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mobileHCI 2009 Proceedings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/mobilehci-2009-proceedings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/mobilehci-2009-proceedings/</guid>
      <description>The full text of the proceedings of MobileHCI09, the 11th International Conference on Human-Computer Interaction with Mobile Devices and Services is available online. The event, which covers mobile and wearable computing devices and services took place September, 2009 at the University of Bonn in Germany.
http://mobilehci.uni-siegen.de/mhci2009.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction 10 Registration Open</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-10-registration-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-10-registration-open/</guid>
      <description>Registration for Interaction 10 is open. Early bird pricing ends November 30th. Interaction 10 is held at SCAD, Savannah College of Art and Design on Feb 4-7, 2010 in Savannah, Georgia. Keynote speakers are Paola Antonelli, Bill Moggridge, Nathan Shedroff, Ezio Manzini, Jon Kolko, Dan Hill.
http://interaction.ixda.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Drop Shadow Talks, Berlin</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/drop-shadow-talks-berlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/drop-shadow-talks-berlin/</guid>
      <description>This is interesting. This season, Berliner Technische Kunsthochschule Hochschule für Gestaltung (FH) is putting on a series of lectures in Berlin centering on topics related to the drop shadow and 3D visual elements in graphic design.
The Drop Shadow Talks reply to current developments on the visually enriched layer for machine interaction. In the shades of evening lectures the Drop Shadow Talks will present art and projects inﬂuenced and inspired by the baroque graphical user interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holland Festival Program Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</guid>
      <description>The Holland Festival provides a program browser/calendar that provides an AJAX interface for viewing over 3 weeks of events in a grid. Drop down menus are provided to narrow or expand by genre, locale and route. A single toggle highlights featured events. And a sliding selector, which can be dragged to move the range left and right and with handles to narrow or expand the window, allows you to filter the days to be shown in the grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Santa Maria: The Influence of Print Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/jason-santa-maria-influence-print-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/jason-santa-maria-influence-print-design/</guid>
      <description>SVA Dot Dot Dot Lectures: Jason Santa Maria from MFA Interaction Design on Vimeo.
 In SVA&amp;rsquo;s Dot Dot Dot lecture series, Jason Santa Maria talks about the role of print design in influencing design on the web, and how visual designers might bring the same level of attention to designing online content with the same rigor and attention to visual meaning.
http://vimeo.com/4394152</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 99% Conference</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/99-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/99-conference/</guid>
      <description>Behance&amp;rsquo;s 99 Percent Conference bills itself as one &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;that focuses less on inspiration, and more on how idea generation and organization come together to make ideas happen.&amp;rdquo; Not suprisingly, they have one of the best looking conference sites to set the stage, showcasing the speakers and event. The treatment of the slash motif morphing into the trapezoids repeated throughout the site in the photography is cool. I like the dark bold color treatment and the clean hierarchy in tables, forms, and text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tap is the New Click</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/tap-new-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/tap-new-click/</guid>
      <description>NYC IxDA - Tap is the New Click - Dan Saffer from Interaction Design Association on Vimeo. Dan Saffer gave a fantastic NYC IXDA presentation, Tap Is the New Click, discussing the rise of touch interfaces, their place and adoption in society, and the role of the interaction designer in designing these direct manipulation interfaces. Every IA and IXD needs to watch this. A summary of the talk below:
Even though the technology has been around for decades, only now are we starting to see mass production and adoption of touchscreen and gestural devices for the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IxDA Interaction 09 | Vancouver</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ixda-interaction-09-vancouver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ixda-interaction-09-vancouver/</guid>
      <description>IxDA&amp;rsquo;s second annual conference, Interaction &amp;lsquo;09|vancouver is coming up from Feb 5-8.
Interaction 09|vancouver will be held from February 5-8, 2009 in stunning Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, in conjunction with Simon Fraser University&amp;rsquo;s School of Interactive Arts and Technology and the Faculty of Business Administration. Join several hundred Interaction Designers from around the world as we address the design of interactive systems of all types: applications (web and desktop), mobile, consumer electronics, digitally enhanced environments, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX London</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ux-london/</guid>
      <description>UX London is a three-day event for user experience designers that combines a day of inspirational conference with four half days of practical, in-depth, hands-on workshops, all presented by some of the biggest names in the industry. Speakers include Don Norman, Leisa Reichelt, Dan Saffer, Luke Wroblewski, Jared Spool, Jeff Veen, Eric Reiss, and Peter Merholz. If I were in Europe I&amp;rsquo;d definitely want to be there.
http://uxlondon.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Mornings: Physical Computing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/creative-mornings-physical-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/creative-mornings-physical-computing/</guid>
      <description>At today&amp;rsquo;s excellent Creative Mornings on physical computing, Zach Klein and Casey Pugh from Vimeo talked about tinkering with Arduino, an open-source electronics prototyping platform. They showed some simple circuit controls using the LEDs and Processing, and then demoed a Daft Punk helmet they created with LEDs, that could then be controlled/drawn on via a Flash UI. Neat stuff. Later, I got to talk to Carl, a freelance developer/interaction designer who turned me onto NYC Resistor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Werchter 2008</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/rock-werchter-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/rock-werchter-2008/</guid>
      <description>http://www.rockwerchter.be/RW2008/site/index.asp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seed Conference 2008</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/seed-conference-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/seed-conference-2008/</guid>
      <description>http://www.seedconference.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hatch Happy Easter</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/hatch-happy-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/hatch-happy-easter/</guid>
      <description>http://www.hatchsf.com/easter/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pangea Day</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/pangea-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/pangea-day/</guid>
      <description>http://www.pangeaday.org/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>