<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>social networks on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/social-networks/</link><description>Recent content in social networks on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/social-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Usabilla Discover</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/usabilla-discover/</guid><description>Usabilla Discover is like a mashup of Pinterest and LittleBigDetails, or maybe it's a social LittleSnapper. Whatever the pitch, it's pretty useful to share screenshots of interface and visual designs you like. Now to figure out how to get my over 2,000 screenshots into it.
Note: To get in during the beta, sign up here with code &amp;quot;KONIGI&amp;quot;, good for the first 200 who use the code.
http://discover.usabilla.com/</description></item><item><title>Being Without Chasing: The Grateful Dead vs. The Top 40</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/being-without-chasing-grateful-dead-vs-top-40/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/being-without-chasing-grateful-dead-vs-top-40/</guid><description>Seth Godin's blog entry, &amp;quot;The Grateful Dead and the Top 40,&amp;quot; looks at a band that only ever had 1 &amp;quot;hit record,&amp;quot; but who were very succesful at what they did. They may have not hit the Top 40 more than once, but one thing is true, they knew themselves as artists, and were true to that.
In terms of chart success, Elton John is probably the polar opposite of The Grateful Dead.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn Museum: 1stfans, a socially-networked museum membership</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/brooklyn-museum-1stfans-socially-networked-museum-membership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/brooklyn-museum-1stfans-socially-networked-museum-membership/</guid><description>The Brooklyn Museum continues its exploration and extension of Museum services by offering 1stfans a socially-networked museum membership. Members pay a smaller $20 membership fee and get access to special events where they can mingle with other 1stfans members, may skip lines at film events, and get alerts via flickr, facebook, and twitter. The museum also recently added a crowd-sourced art work tagging interface that allows users to describe work in the collection using free tags, and has utilized Flickr for over a year now to promote events.</description></item><item><title>MySpace Redesign</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/myspace-redesign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/myspace-redesign/</guid><description>TechCrunch has screenshots of the MySpace redesign that launches next week. Adaptive Path were involved in the design and IA process.
Los Angeles based social network MySpace, which has 115 million monthly visitors worldwide (Comscore, April 2008), will be launching a redesign of its site next week. The first phase of the project, internally called “MySpace 2.0,” will launch on Wednesday June 18.
The changes affect five major areas of the service: homepage, navigation, profile editor, search and the MySpaceTV Flash player.</description></item></channel></rss>