<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>microsites on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/microsites/</link><description>Recent content in microsites on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/microsites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Virgin.com Header</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</guid><description>The Virgin.com redesign sports a header that provides a boatload of functionality using mega fly out menus: locale selection, micro-site navigation, registration, login, and newsletter signup. I like that they make these options readily available wherever you are on the site. The longer drop downs like the registration form, for example, seem a little long for users on smaller screens, e.g. netbooks. 1. The global navigation bar provides mega drop downs with sub-nodes and links to their subsidiary companies that provide products and services under each category.</description></item><item><title>EA Microsite Navigation</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ea-microsite-navigation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ea-microsite-navigation/</guid><description>Game maker EA provides access to their network of microsites from EA.com and offers cross-site navigation via a toolbar that is positioned at the bottom or top of each site. I like the design of the navigation on the main site and the Sports sites. But the navigation is inconsistent in position, visual design, and behavior from site to site. The Pogo site doesn't have a micro-site navigator at all, so ironically, you have to "</description></item><item><title>Nike Microsite Navigation</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-microsite-navigation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-microsite-navigation/</guid><description>Nike.com's main site provides entry to a host of micro-sites for each sport or product family, but a consistent navigation model is provided across all microsites. A primary navigation widget is provided in the Nike Swoosh button, which reveals a list of a few of the most popular microsite destinations. A "More" link epxands the list to show all of the microsites.
1. Users click the Nike Swoosh logo to navigate across the Nike space to other microsites.</description></item></channel></rss>