<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>video players on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/video-players/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video players on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/video-players/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Video Hero</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-video-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-video-hero/</guid>
      <description>Nike has been using a video player as hero graphic in the main Nike.com site. The player features large buttons for play controls and link to microsite (the button with the right angle quotes), star rating, playhead, low/high resolution and bandwidth switcher, a time elapse countdown, volume bars, and save/share options.
 http://www.nike.com/nikeos/p/nike/en_US/?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formula 1 Video Bandwidth Profiler</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/formula-1-video-bandwidth-profiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/formula-1-video-bandwidth-profiler/</guid>
      <description>Formula 1&#39;s Video site provides a bandwidth profiler before display their video player. After checking your bandwidth availability, the app suggests a resolution and quality that will give you the best experience.
1. User selects the video they wish to view.2. App assesses available bandwidth.3. App provides report of bandwidth and resolution, and suggests the option that will provide the best experience.4. Grade 2 video player. http://www.formula1.com/video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/msnbc-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/msnbc-video-player/</guid>
      <description>MSNBC&#39;s video player loads in a pop up window with the video player on the right, and a left sidebar showing navigation options to browse by playlist, category, or show. The video player itself provide a barebones set of controls for pause/play, previous/next, volume, mailto link, and embed code. A square ad unit hides the left sidebar pre-roll and is replaced by a small persistent ad unit sitting below the player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancast Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-video-player/</guid>
      <description>The Fancast has a simple video player interface with typical features. No advanced features like clipping (although it does allow sharing scenes) and the features it does have are not available in full screen mode. Additionally, accessing any of those features, e.g. sharing and embedding, pauses playback. I like the simplicity of the design, but the video player could reach some parity in terms of functionality with what video users are becoming accustomed to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNET TV Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnet-tv-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnet-tv-video-player/</guid>
      <description>CNET TV provides a video player that showcases their large library of content including product reviews, news coverage, and special reports. The main page of CNET TV features the video player in the center stage, with a short list of featured (hot) content flanking the left side, and a playlist on the right showing the currently playing video. The player controls are simple and easy to use, but at full screen, the controls a little soft and blurry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TheWB.com Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thewb-com-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thewb-com-video-player/</guid>
      <description>The WB brings its video site to the masses of OC and Friends fans and adds another network portal into the mix with Hulu. In terms of visual appearances and the high level navigation (IA), TheWB.com feels like the polar opposite in sensibility to Hulu&#39;s pared down appearances and very usable directory structure and show pages. On Hulu, once you arrive at a show page, everything you can watch whether it be a full episode or clip, is neatly organized and presented on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Unbox Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-unbox-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-unbox-video-player/</guid>
      <description>Unbox is Amazon.com&#39;s Movie and TV Show store, which offers downloadable videos that may be played on a user&#39;s PC, TiVo, or portable media player. The Unbox video player provides a &#34;Shop&#34; browser, a carousel of poster images for viewing top selling and renting movies and TV shows. Sadly, you have to make your purchase via the Amazon.com web site, and can&#39;t purchase directly from the player. You also cannot browse videos by genre in the player&#39;s Shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Media Annotation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-media-annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-media-annotation/</guid>
      <description>YouTube have added media annotation controls that allow users to add comment bubbles, note boxes, and links (within YouTube only) to their own videos. YouTube is not the first to add media annotations or commenting features like this, but the addition of this feature may mean we&#39;ll see more if it on video portals. The feature is similar to the video annotation that Bubbleply does. Viewers are not allowed to add annotations to other users&#39; media as is done on Flickr and iminlikewithyou.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ibeatyou rating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ibeatyou-rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ibeatyou-rating/</guid>
      <description>ibeatyou is a video portal that allows people to create challenges to compete on anything. Users either upload a video, record from webcam, or import from YouTube.
The rating system is a whimsical little widget for allowing a score from 1 to 5. The vote is indicated by a little blue man holding up a scrore card. They also provide a qualitative award, allowing users to give an award to the entry and name it anything they like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howcast Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/howcast-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/howcast-video-player/</guid>
      <description>Howcast is a web video site founded by veterans of Google and YouTube, to &#34;bring together the personality of user-generated content with the quality of a professional video studio.&#34; The videos produced by the site bring a higher standard of quality than Google and YouTube, and offer interesting features such as chapter markers and time-marked notes called &#34;steps&#34; in Howcast parlance. The content is targetted at information seekers of how to, tutorial, and DIY instructional video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MotionBox Video Player Clipping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</guid>
      <description>Motionbox provides a nice interface for creating clips of videos they host. Along with Hulu, Motionbox is among the first to introduce the idea of clipping portions of web video. However, Motionbox outshines Hulu in terms of usability. Clipping is a simple operation that mimics the video selection paradigm users have become comfortable with on video editing software. And unlike Hulu, Motionbox provides instant feedback about where the start and end markers lie, by moving the video playhead with the position of the markers as you adjust the clip size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOL Music Desktop Video Widget</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aol-music-desktop-video-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aol-music-desktop-video-widget/</guid>
      <description>AOL&#39;s Desktop Widget is standalone video player (Adobe AIR application) that runs on the user&#39;s computer. The video player allows users to browse and watch the top 100 AOL Music Videos without having to access their web site. The player provides typical functions including playlisting, favoriting, sending to friend, embedding.
1. Video player on the left. On the right are mosaic of headshots to browse artists and search box.2. Playlist mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancast Rating (Hulu Player)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</guid>
      <description>The Fancast experience for the Hulu video player provides a customized rating widget that differs from the straight-forward star rating on Hulu. Users select a text value that gets converted to stars.
1. Button in lower right prompts user to rate the video2. Clicking the button displays scale as text values3. Value selected by user is converted to star rating scale http://fancast.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TED Ratings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ted-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ted-ratings/</guid>
      <description>I was a bit confused the first time I saw this rating interface, and have to admit that I ignored it for months. The thing that threw me was the multiple checkboxes offered for each value. But I came back and realized that what this was doing was giving you a pre-defined set of tags which it was then using to create a filtering mechanism for the site. I appreciate that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Explore Related Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-explore-related-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-explore-related-videos/</guid>
      <description>YouTube&#39;s exploring functionality in the full-screen video player allows users to directed exploration of related videos.
1) Clicking the explore button in the lower left brings up related videos visualization, which is sort of like a digraph that looks like a constellation of stars. 2) Circles in the center are videos. Hover over one circle expands to show you other videos related to that one, forming a cluster. Click a circle to watch a video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
