<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>messaging on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/messaging/</link><description>Recent content in messaging on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/messaging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twitter Confirmations</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/twitter-confirmations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/twitter-confirmations/</guid><description>Twitter provides a subtle, unobtrusive notification messages, e.g. when a direct message is sent. The confirmation appears as a layer with a white background over the top of the page, covering the page header, and unfortunately, not providing a more obvious "Close" link to dismiss the message. The message can be easily dismissed by clicking anywhere in the div, but that's not readily apparent.
1. Direct message interface.2. Confirmation that direct message has been sent appears as layer over the top of the page.</description></item><item><title>thesixtyone alerts</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thesixtyone-alerts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thesixtyone-alerts/</guid><description>Music community site thesixtyone uses unobtrusive growl-like panels in the bottom right corner of the page for system alerts and messaging. Like growl or iminlikewithyou, these messages appear briefly and fade out. The effect is subtle and might be easily missed, but the addition of an ambient "pop" earcon (alert sound) tells you to look for the message. Nicely done.
1. System alerts appear in the bottom right corner, with accompanying alert sounds.</description></item><item><title>Facebook Form Auto-completion</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/facebook-form-auto-completion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/facebook-form-auto-completion/</guid><description>Facebook's address auto-completion in the compose message form is one of the best examples of auto-completion behavior in a form. The interaction very closely mimics what you would expect to happen in the To field of email applications like Apple Mail and Outlook.
1. Cursor is in the To: field. Contextual help displayed below input.2. Typing characters in the input invokes person/recipient auto-completion suggestions. 3. Selecting a person from auto-completion suggestions, entering a comma, or clicking enter displays the selected recipient in a block.</description></item></channel></rss>