<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>file management on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/file-management/</link><description>Recent content in file management on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/file-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SugarSync Creating and Moving Items</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-creating-and-moving-items/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-creating-and-moving-items/</guid><description>SugarSync's web-based document management application allows users to manage files that are kept on their computers. The interactions for creating and moving folders use an identical design pattern for placing items in a directory on the file system. This is similar to the Save As behavior in operating systems such as the Mac Finder and Windows Explorer, which will let users navigate to a disk drive, and then drill down deeply into a directory location.</description></item><item><title>SugarSync Uploading Files</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-uploading-files/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-uploading-files/</guid><description>SugarSync's upload file behavior uses a customized interface that is not typical. Instead of using the browser behavior for handling file uploads using &amp;lt;input type="file"&amp;gt;, which typically provides an input and browse button in Firefox and Internet Explorer, SugarSync uses a single button to invoke the file browsing window, and then displays the file's name in HTML. To be fair, Safari provides a slicker interface for file uploads, which doesn't display an input, but only a button, and then shows the file name next to the button when a file is found.</description></item></channel></rss>