<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>notebooks on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/notebooks/</link><description>Recent content in notebooks on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/notebooks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wireframe Sketch Book Now Available</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-sketch-book-now-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-sketch-book-now-available/</guid><description>The sketch book is finally available in the store. It's a small 8.25 x 5.5 inch wirebound book that lays flat, has a 24 x 24 grid with note block on the front (landscape orientation) and 48 x 24 grid on the back (landscape or portrait). Includes 50 perforated sheets (100 pages) printed in non-photo blue ink, and an interior flap on the back cover. For the first set sold, I'm also including a Zebra 0.</description></item><item><title>Free Notebook for Konigi Friends at SXSW Wireframe Talk</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/free-notebook-konigi-friends-sxsw-wireframe-talk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/free-notebook-konigi-friends-sxsw-wireframe-talk/</guid><description>So I've made some 8.5 in. by 5.25 in. graph paper notebooks because I wanted something a little more functional than what I was using for sketching. They're basically a mini version of the wireframe grid I use, with markers for 1/3s and 1/4s, but without the gutters. I've been working with a prototype of this for a few months now and have a bunch of these ready to put up for sale, but haven't been rushing to do it, mostly because I made them for myself and selling stuff like notebooks isn't profitable until you get into selling large quantities, and unfortunately I haven't the time to market the pads and books.</description></item><item><title>Trying Out Notebooks Has Become an Obsession</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/trying-out-notebooks-has-become-obsession/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/trying-out-notebooks-has-become-obsession/</guid><description>Here's a collection of notebooks that are in heavy rotation now, and the last Rhodia I used before I started making my own. Click through for notes. View the photo in flickr for notes about the ones in this picture.
//konigi.com/</description></item><item><title>What do you look for in a sketch notebook?</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/what-do-you-look-sketch-notebook/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/what-do-you-look-sketch-notebook/</guid><description>It's getting kind of old skool over here in the home office. I haven't yet gotten around to talking about why I'm spending time on notepads and notebooks, and just how I use these things. But I'm going to post an article describing just that. This photo is just a teaser to let you know that I'm still working away at this sketch paper stuff because it's an itch that just won't go away.</description></item><item><title>Creating Handcrafted Notebooks</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/creating-handcrafted-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/creating-handcrafted-notebooks/</guid><description>This is my first case bound book notebook. I took a one day workshop at the Center for Book Arts to continue pursuing my obsession with notebooks. It is half filled with Bienfang 8x8 to the inch graph paper and the other half is Borden and Riley bleed proof paper. The section of papers is stitched into a text block that is drilled on left side to create this landscape orientation.</description></item><item><title>Get To The Point Bookmarks</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/get-point-bookmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/get-point-bookmarks/</guid><description>Seems like someone has come up with a better solution for marking my note and sketch pages in my Moleskines. Dog eared pages never suited me, and the colored tabs I get at MUJI and the occasional PostIt note are OK. But I love the idea of these magnetic page markers from Folio because it means I won't need to buy anymore sticky tabs from the stationery store. And the little pointed arrows are pretty useful for pointing out lines of interest in books too.</description></item><item><title>My Mobile Sketch Rig: Pilot Couleur Mini Pencils and Moleskine</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/my-mobile-sketch-rig-pilot-couleur-mini-pencils-and-moleskine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/my-mobile-sketch-rig-pilot-couleur-mini-pencils-and-moleskine/</guid><description>I'm a big fan of Pilot and Pentel mechanical pencils. At home I use the larger Pentels, but when I'm out, I carry around the small red Pilot Couleur above attached to my small Moleskine. Ideas often come when I'm away from the desk so I feel like I always have to have pencil and paper wherever I go. The Pilots have a rubberized coating, hold 0.5mm leads, and hide an eraser under the push button.</description></item><item><title>Moleskine Soft Cover Notebooks</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/moleskine-soft-cover-notebooks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/moleskine-soft-cover-notebooks/</guid><description>I got my hands on the new soft cover Moleskine notebooks. The faux cover feels like a luxurious thin leather, and is soft, but sturdy.
http://www.moleskine.com/eng/_interni/catalogo/Cat_int/catalogo_notebooks.htm</description></item><item><title>To All the Notebooks I've Ever Loved Before</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/all-notebooks-ive-ever-loved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/all-notebooks-ive-ever-loved/</guid><description>I recently talked to someone about the graph/grid paper books I've acquired over the years which have become a central part of my process. This is a listing of those pads, and a telling of their virtues. Rhodia This is my workhorse. At first I didn't get why so many designers carried these around, until I got my hands on one. To me the Rhodias are an all-around notepad for in office or outside use.</description></item><item><title>Rhodia Drive</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/rhodia-drive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/rhodia-drive/</guid><description>Rhodia Drive is a fantastic blog written by someone named Tedo, a Filipino journalist currently based in Chicago, that is devoted to Rhodia notepads. Tedo posts random stories, artwork and photos from Rhodia lovers around the world. I always carry around a 3/5 x 4.5 Rhodia notepad and traded in my Tufte graph paper for Rhodia a little over a year ago. If you're one of us, check out Rhodia Drive and the flickr group.</description></item></channel></rss>