<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>drag and drop on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/drag-and-drop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in drag and drop on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/drag-and-drop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slavery Footprint Form: Drag to Select</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</guid>
      <description>The Slavery Footprint website allows consumers to visualize how their consumption habits are connected to modern-day slavery.
They use a set of forms in a wizard-like survey to come up with an estimate of the number of slaves that are impacted by your behavior.
This section of the survey asks the user to drag the icons for items that describe the kind of house and car they own or rent into a drop area in the home above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Layout Customization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wordpress-layout-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wordpress-layout-customization/</guid>
      <description>WordPress added some excellent layout customization options on administration screens in version 2.7. The most obvious change comes in the form of the Screen Options tab, which expands a settings panel that let&#39;s the admin hide or show parts of the UI being viewed, and saves those settings for the user immediately. The UI also provides a drag and drop behavior to re-arrange modules. When hovering over a module heading, the icon turns into a full hand and lets the user move modules up or down in the column, or between columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Media Annotation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-media-annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-media-annotation/</guid>
      <description>YouTube have added media annotation controls that allow users to add comment bubbles, note boxes, and links (within YouTube only) to their own videos. YouTube is not the first to add media annotations or commenting features like this, but the addition of this feature may mean we&#39;ll see more if it on video portals. The feature is similar to the video annotation that Bubbleply does. Viewers are not allowed to add annotations to other users&#39; media as is done on Flickr and iminlikewithyou.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
