<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>css on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/css/</link>
    <description>Recent content in css on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 12:47:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/css/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RGBA feColorMatrix</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/rgba-fecolormatrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 12:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/rgba-fecolormatrix/</guid>
      <description>An SVG filter that changes colors based on a transformation matrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AniJS: Declarative handling library for CSS animations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/anijs-declarative-handling-library-css-animations/</guid>
      <description>AniJS is a library for CSS animations that allows you to write simple statements for handling animation as key/value pairs in html data attributes. It feels very close to writing natural language statements, in a format that is a bit more familiar in code than writing sentences. A simple example contains IF, ON, DO, and TO pairs and would look like this: &amp;lt;input id=&#34;name&#34; type=&#34;text&#34; data-anijs=&#34;if: focus, do: wobble, to: p&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap, from Twitter</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/bootstrap-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/bootstrap-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Bootstrap is a free, simple, and flexible HTML, CSS (Less Framework), and Javascript (jQuery) for popular user interface components and interactions created by the devs at Twitter.
http://twitter.github.com/bootstrap/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InstaCSS: CSS Documentation Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/instacss-css-documentation-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/instacss-css-documentation-search/</guid>
      <description>Using InstaCSS is a much easier way to look up CSS docs than Googling. Enter a CSS property in the search box, and the panel below dynamically shows matching properties. Simple. If you&#39;re a Mac user, it seems to me like it would be useful tucked into a Fluid menu item like this. Via Think Vitamin Newsletter
http://instacss.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animate.css: Plug-and-play CSS animation stylesheet</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/animatecss-plug-and-play-css-animation-stylesheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/animatecss-plug-and-play-css-animation-stylesheet/</guid>
      <description>animate.css is a stylesheet created by Dan Eden for doing common, cross-browser css3 animations for things like transitions for emphasis. To use them in your project, simply add add the stylesheet and link, add a class to an element, or call the animation yourself in your CSS file.
http://daneden.me/animate/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 Boilerplate: A rock-solid default for HTML5</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/html5-boilerplate-rock-solid-default-html5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/html5-boilerplate-rock-solid-default-html5/</guid>
      <description>I stumbled on Paul Irish and Divya Manian&#39;s HTML5 Boilerplate after looking for a solution to fall back on a local jQuery library if Google&#39;s CDN ever went south, and reading about how to use this technique for WordPress. Ben Kutil also helped me undersand how the fallback technique works a little bit, and I tested and implemented on Balsamiq&#39;s site.
HTML5 Boilerplate is not a library, but a template and set of awesome examples for how to get started integrating HTML 5 into your sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ProCSSor: CSS Prettifier</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/procssor-css-prettifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/procssor-css-prettifier/</guid>
      <description>ProCSSor is a tool to format your CSS to be readable. Paste, specify URL, or upload file, and then select your options and ProCSSor outputs a cleaned up version of your stylesheet.
http://www.procssor.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sencha Touch HTML5 Mobile App Framework</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/sencha-touch-html5-mobile-app-framework/</guid>
      <description>Sencha Touch looks like an excellent toolkit for delivering HTML 5/CSS 3 mobile experiences. Check out these demos your mobile device to give it a test run: GeoCongress (makes use of geolocation), Solitaire (drag and drop and flip animations), Kiva (provides iPad popover controls).
Sencha Touch allows you to develop web apps that look and feel native on Apple iOS and Google Android touchscreen devices. It&#39;s built specifically to leverage HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript and makes use of HTML5 to deliver components like audio and video, as well as a localStorage proxy for saving data offline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Grid Overlay with CSS and JQuery</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/quick-grid-overlay-css-and-jquery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/quick-grid-overlay-css-and-jquery/</guid>
      <description>Griddy is a simple JQuery plugin that overlays a customizable grid over any element.
http://devgrow.com/griddy/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When can I use... HTML5, CSS3, etc.</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/when-can-i-use-html5-css3-etc/</guid>
      <description>Can I Use provides compatibility tables for features in HTML5, CSS3, SVG and other upcoming web technologies.
http://caniuse.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only Two Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/only-two-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/only-two-designers/</guid>
      <description>http://www.only2designers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design, the web, and craft</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/design-web-and-craft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/design-web-and-craft/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a little late on getting to this one, but wanted to post before I forgot because it is a great topic for early and mid-career web designers. Matt (emenel) reacted to Mark Boulton&#39;s thoughts about whether or not designers needed to know html.
Matt summarizes what he believes:
As a designer there is a continuum you travel over the course of your career. It starts with making - crafting objects in your selected medium - and progresses through a point where you internalize your craft and can design without making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShareFile.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sharefilecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sharefilecom/</guid>
      <description>http://www.sharefile.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LESS: Simple CSS variables and more</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/less-simple-css-variables-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/less-simple-css-variables-and-more/</guid>
      <description>The LESS Ruby gem compiles LESS code into CSS. LESS extends CSS with variables, mixins, operations, and extended rules, and uses existing CSS syntax. You simply rename your .css files as .less files and compile with a plugin or a simple app like LESS.app for the Mac.
http://lesscss.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brosho - Design CSS in the browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/brosho-design-css-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/brosho-design-css-browser/</guid>
      <description>This plugin allows you to reduce the amount of time spent switching between browser windows. With this jquery plugin included on a page, you&#39;ll be able to select individual elements and write css code for it right in your browser. Changes are updated on the fly, so you can see your style changes as you write them.
The CSS generated by your edits can then be generated and copy-pasted into your stylesheet file for minor edits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
