<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sample deliverables on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/sample-deliverables/</link><description>Recent content in sample deliverables on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/sample-deliverables/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MOObileFrames</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/moobileframes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/moobileframes/</guid><description>MOObileFrames is a collection of mobile sketches and wireframes curated by Hannah Milan.
http://moobileframes.tumblr.com/page/1</description></item><item><title>Sarah Sampsel on Designing The Washington Post for iPad</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/sarah-sampsel-designing-washington-post-ipad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/sarah-sampsel-designing-washington-post-ipad/</guid><description>Sarah Sampsel wrote about designing the Washington Post iPad app, in 2 entries describing a little bit about the process. The first entry describes the types of interaction, visual design, and brand issues she had to consider when designing for the device. The second shows a few wireframes of the evolution of the home screen design.
Would have been lovely to also see some of the sketches, but it's awesome that Sarah shared not just final wireframes, but a series of wireframes showing the iterations.</description></item><item><title>Better Gmail Client Wireframe</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</guid><description>I posted on Twitter about how frustrating it can be to have to use email. With every day that I use Twitter via Twhirl I become less and less interested in using email. So I moaned to my Twitter peeps about the pain I feel. Some people wanted to know what I wanted, so I responded with the ideal flow, using Mac OS X's Growl alerting app as the starting point:</description></item></channel></rss>