<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Editor on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/video-editor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Editor on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/video-editor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MotionBox Video Player Clipping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</guid>
      <description>Motionbox provides a nice interface for creating clips of videos they host. Along with Hulu, Motionbox is among the first to introduce the idea of clipping portions of web video. However, Motionbox outshines Hulu in terms of usability. Clipping is a simple operation that mimics the video selection paradigm users have become comfortable with on video editing software. And unlike Hulu, Motionbox provides instant feedback about where the start and end markers lie, by moving the video playhead with the position of the markers as you adjust the clip size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaltura Video Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kaltura-video-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kaltura-video-editor/</guid>
      <description>Kaltura&#39;s Flash / Flex video editor mimicks a full-featured video editor like iMovie. The company&#39;s product allows its users to add video to a collaboratively created work. The editor features nearly all of the features you would expect from a video editor, but delivers the entire interface via the web. Features include organizing clips from a media library, adding titles, transitions, and special effects, and adding and controlling soundtrack and volume.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>