<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>favorites on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/favorites/</link><description>Recent content in favorites on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/favorites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tumblr Fave Animation</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</guid><description>This is a small animation of the heart/broken heart that is shown when favoriting or unfaving a Tumblr post in the mobile app.
Screencast / Video https://www.tumblr.com/</description></item><item><title>New York Times Article Clipping</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-times-article-clipping/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-times-article-clipping/</guid><description>The New York Times' Times File Service allows users to save news items for reading later. Users click an Folder icon in the article tools adjacent to the article. When they navigate to their Times File, they see their list of shaved articles, with options for tagging, describing, and sharing the article via email. A nice feature of the Tiles File can be found under the Most Popular tab, where the most saved articles can be copied into your own library.</description></item><item><title>RYZ Rating and Favoriting</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</guid><description>RYZ is a sneaker manufacturer that crowdsources the design of their product and shares the revenue with winners. Users download a template to create design and upload to their profile. Participants vote on the designs by giving ratings and winners receive $1000 and $1 for every pair sold. The site provides simple interfaces for both favoriting and rating entries.
1. The voting page.2. Clicking the star badge in the corner of the image adds to favorites.</description></item><item><title>Daylife Favoriting</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-favoriting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-favoriting/</guid><description>Daylife provides an excellent mechanism for favoriting. The news portal, which is published to demonstrate the company's news delivery product, provides a simple method for saving favorites that uses a star icon. The site classifies articles into topics which are simply terms describing a subject matter, person, or company/organization. Users see star icons when they hover over a link to a topic or a story. Starring the link adds the topic or story to their "</description></item></channel></rss>