<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mega drop down menus on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/mega-drop-down-menus/</link><description>Recent content in mega drop down menus on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/mega-drop-down-menus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Daylife Drop Down Menus</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</guid><description>Daylife's drop down menu in global navigation that provides a wide ribbon to show both navigation to secondary levels and to show teaser content, e.g. the Latest News menu shows top level news categories as well as recent articles in each category. News sites like Daylife and NewsVine have been coming up with interesting ways of changing user's expectations of what can exist in global navigation. In some cases, the labels and categories for what appear in global navigation suggest a shifting information architecture that is based on what's interesting now or what people have been reading.</description></item><item><title>Google Analytics Drop Down Menus</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-drop-down-menus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-drop-down-menus/</guid><description>I'm a fan of the drop down menus that span a wide area, e.g. the main body or full page, in order to show a wider range of options rather showing fewer in a vertical drop down and forcing navigation through a fly-out tree. This convention is showing up mostly in global navigation, and with the introduction of Microsoft's Ribbon, we can expect to see more of it.
Google shows buttons with down arrows to indicate that clicking one of those controls will show expanded options in-screen, a la the drop down menu.</description></item><item><title>Hulu Channel Drop Down Menu</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</guid><description>Hulu's drop down menu for channels stretches to the width of the design and provides a multi-column grid of channels. This method of running a drop down or flyout menu left-to-right rather than top-to-bottom allows interface designers to present longer lists of options without worrying about what appears in relation to the fold, and forcing scroll on longer lists.
http://www.hulu.com/</description></item><item><title>CBS Navigation</title><link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cbs-navigation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cbs-navigation/</guid><description>The CBS site features a drop down menu that spans the entire width of the layout when the user hovers over shows. Wide drop downs are not unusual, and for a time appeared on the Amazon.com site when they experiencing the growth of their departments. On CBS, this type of interface is used to display as many of the network's shows as it can, segmenting them by airing time and format.</description></item></channel></rss>