<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Navigation on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/navigation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Navigation on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/navigation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigation Patterns for Responsive Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/navigation-patterns-responsive-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/navigation-patterns-responsive-design/</guid>
      <description>I like Brad Frost&amp;rsquo;s examples for handling both complex navigation and simple navigation needs on responsive designs.
Via Leisa IAI Members
http://bradfrostweb.com/blog/web/complex-navigation-patterns-for-responsive-design/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Lists</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/elastic-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/elastic-lists/</guid>
      <description>Elastic Lists is an open source project from Moritz Stefaner that allows you to create a faceted browsing interface for navigating large, multi-dimensional info spaces with just a few clicks, never letting you run into situations with zero results. Elastic Lists is an Apache licensed, AS3 project for use in Flash CS4 or Flex.
http://moritz.stefaner.eu/projects/elastic-lists/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Heroes Killed Cowboys</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/my-heroes-killed-cowboys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/my-heroes-killed-cowboys/</guid>
      <description>Cornwall based club night with a passion for cutting edge electronic dance music, design and making people want to dance. Jac The Disco are residents, whilst many top DJ&amp;rsquo;s and live bands make their south west debut with us. Soon to host in London. An eye on the future.
http://www.myheroeskilledcowboys.co.uk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dom Goodrum</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</guid>
      <description>Portfolio showcasing the favourite projects of designer Dom Goodrum.
http://www.domgoodrum.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teez</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teez/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teez/</guid>
      <description>A t-shirt store design re-think
http://teez.com.ua</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xocolatl - Stunning chocolate shop website design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/xocolatl-stunning-chocolate-shop-website-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/xocolatl-stunning-chocolate-shop-website-design/</guid>
      <description>A beautifully designed eCommerce website showcasing this boutique chocolate shop. http://www.xocolatl.co.nz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBBLEWOOD Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/bubblewood-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/bubblewood-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Interesting bubble/cloud of links make up the front page of this retail site.  Screencast / Video
http://www.bubblewood.com/index_fr.htm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Shaw</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/andy-shaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/andy-shaw/</guid>
      <description>Taking a portfolio site to the bare essentials. Links to the latest work &amp;amp; contact options.
http://andyshaw.me</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin.com Header</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</guid>
      <description>The Virgin.com redesign sports a header that provides a boatload of functionality using mega fly out menus: locale selection, micro-site navigation, registration, login, and newsletter signup. I like that they make these options readily available wherever you are on the site. The longer drop downs like the registration form, for example, seem a little long for users on smaller screens, e.g. netbooks. 1. The global navigation bar provides mega drop downs with sub-nodes and links to their subsidiary companies that provide products and services under each category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EA Microsite Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ea-microsite-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ea-microsite-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Game maker EA provides access to their network of microsites from EA.com and offers cross-site navigation via a toolbar that is positioned at the bottom or top of each site. I like the design of the navigation on the main site and the Sports sites. But the navigation is inconsistent in position, visual design, and behavior from site to site. The Pogo site doesn&#39;t have a micro-site navigator at all, so ironically, you have to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Microsite Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-microsite-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-microsite-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Nike.com&#39;s main site provides entry to a host of micro-sites for each sport or product family, but a consistent navigation model is provided across all microsites. A primary navigation widget is provided in the Nike Swoosh button, which reveals a list of a few of the most popular microsite destinations. A &#34;More&#34; link epxands the list to show all of the microsites.
1. Users click the Nike Swoosh logo to navigate across the Nike space to other microsites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atomic Floyd - The New State of Sound</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/atomic-floyd-new-state-sound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/atomic-floyd-new-state-sound/</guid>
      <description>Online presence and shop for high end head phone manufactorer Atomic Floyd. Special attention was put into the html focus defocus of the navigation. By Story Worldwide.
http://www.atomicfloyd.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duchy Originals</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/duchy-originals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/duchy-originals/</guid>
      <description>http://www.duchyoriginals.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>inezborges</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/inezborges/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/inezborges/</guid>
      <description>inezborges, is a graphic and designer web working on Oporto. Specializing in Web and Print Design, she creates clean, engaging, and functional websites.
Nowadays, she spends most of her free time in researching web design technologies. She´s working in the internet industry, focusing on web design as well as user interface design, web 2.0.
http://www.inezborges.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serial Cut</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/serial-cut/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/serial-cut/</guid>
      <description>Slick portfolio from Serial Cut has a single-page feel, using full page background images and quick transitions without Flash.
http://www.serialcut.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for Faceted Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</guid>
      <description>Stephanie Lemieux discusses issues to consider when designing faceted navigation interfaces for search in the latest UIE newsletter.
Faceted search is a very popular and powerful solution when done well; it allows users to deconstruct a large set of results into bite-size pieces and navigate based on what’s important to them. But faceted search by itself is not necessarily going to make your users lives easier. You need to understand your users’ mental models (how they seek information), test your assumptions about how they will interpret your terms and categories and spend time refining your approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Reed Web Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/jason-reed-web-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/jason-reed-web-design/</guid>
      <description>I like this simple, one-page portfolio. Uses accordions to switch between sections and tabs within accordion panels to navigate sub-sections. The hand-drawn arrows are a nice touch.
http://www.jasonreedwebdesign.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profoto Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Profoto&#39;s take on the breadcrumb combines expanded menus for each branch to provide a drill-down method for navigating siblings, aunts, great-aunts, etc. It basically exposes the hierarchy of siblings at each level, and it&#39;s really most useful when you&#39;ve navigated deep into a hierarchy. It can get a little weird when you use these, because you have to remember that you&#39;re viewing siblings in the branch you&#39;re exposing. If you look at the last screenshot for the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweetizen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</guid>
      <description>Tweetizen is a simple web-based tool designed to help you filter the daily influx of tweets, and easily embed twitter groups to your own website. http://www.tweetizen.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anaara Media LLC</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/anaara-media-llc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/anaara-media-llc/</guid>
      <description>The website of RIA company Anaara Media LLC has an interesting flash interface which makes use of expanding cards to present its content.
http://anaara.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Yale Illumination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/greg-yale-illumination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/greg-yale-illumination/</guid>
      <description>New site for New York lighting company Greg Yale Illumination. Designed and developed by Knowawall.
http://www.gregyale.com/www/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EffectiveUI Accordion Stacks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/effectiveui-accordion-stacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/effectiveui-accordion-stacks/</guid>
      <description>Effective UI has an interesting Flash UI for presenting menus on their home page using a stacked accordion. Upon landing on the home page, a series of stacked boxes are displayed with both a large descriptive heading of that section and shows the first mini-slide in that deck/stack to help you see what that section is about. Mousing over the first slide in the stack expands the stack to show the headings for the other nodes of content within it, and the user may now hover over the other items to view their descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTunes Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-pagination/</guid>
      <description>The iTunes Store has 3 different pagination controls it uses in different places. The most common method for paging through a series of items is to show a carousel on the main pages, with prev/next arrow icons to shuffle through sets of 3-4. On special featured modules with larger poster image thumbnails they use coverflow with their hybrid scrollbar which has arrows that increment one item at a time, or allow you to scroll to move through larger increments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Multi Level Navigation Menu Techniques</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/10-multi-level-navigation-menu-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/10-multi-level-navigation-menu-techniques/</guid>
      <description>devSnippets collects 10 examples of multi-level navigation menus using Javascript libraries and CSS, and adds a little annotation about the methods and how they effects are accomplished. Via @nourayehia
http://devsnippets.com/reviews/10-brilliant-multi-level-navigation-menu-techniques.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wowhead Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Wowhead is a database of World of Warcraft information. The database provides a hierarchical subject taxonomy to describe items, and presents that hierarchy in the breadcrumbs for the item. When the user hovers ofer a branch in the breadcrumb trail, a drop down menu is displayed to show the node siblings and drill down to children. 1. Single entry view (database record).2. Hovering over the current entry&#39;s parent category (Daggers) to view siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>120 Horizontal Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/120-horizontal-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/120-horizontal-menus/</guid>
      <description>CSS Tea collects screenshots of 120 global navigation bars.
http://www.csstea.com/css-gallery-news-and-resources/264-120-excellent-examples-of-css-horizantal-menu.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daylife Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Daylife&#39;s drop down menu in global navigation that provides a wide ribbon to show both navigation to secondary levels and to show teaser content, e.g. the Latest News menu shows top level news categories as well as recent articles in each category. News sites like Daylife and NewsVine have been coming up with interesting ways of changing user&#39;s expectations of what can exist in global navigation. In some cases, the labels and categories for what appear in global navigation suggest a shifting information architecture that is based on what&#39;s interesting now or what people have been reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Breadcrumb Tab</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo&#39;s hybrid tab/breadcrumb navigation is one of my favorite approaches to global and local navigation. This navigation interface answers a few nagging questions that an interface designer might ask. &#34;How do I present the user with an interface that provides focus on the area they&#39;ve navigated to, while providing a path back or to other main areas of interest?&#34;
What&#39;s interesting here is that they provide a row of primary navigation tabs at the top level, and replace that with a hybrid tab/breadcrumb once the user makes the decision to drill down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Channel Drop Down Menu</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</guid>
      <description>Hulu&#39;s drop down menu for channels stretches to the width of the design and provides a multi-column grid of channels. This method of running a drop down or flyout menu left-to-right rather than top-to-bottom allows interface designers to present longer lists of options without worrying about what appears in relation to the fold, and forcing scroll on longer lists.
 http://www.hulu.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IKEA Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ikea-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ikea-navigation/</guid>
      <description>IKEA&#39;s navigation menus feature a simple navigation bar on the top of the layout. The most important entry points are shown as is a button for new items. A drop down menu at right for the rest of the top level entry points. Within each section, tree navigation interfaces are provided for browsing more deeply within the section.
1. Home page.2. &amp;quot;Living Room&amp;quot; selected in the global navigation. Local navigation appears in the left sidebar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Falling Leaves Concept UI for iPhone</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/falling-leaves-concept-ui-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/falling-leaves-concept-ui-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Not sure if the user on Vimeo who posted this is THE Woz, but he or she posted this concept user interface for an iPhone menu application that looks very interesting. The video opens with a UI that displays falling media that appear like little square stamps dropping like leaves to a desktop with contacts, photos, videos, etc. on the face of the leaves. The user can apparently pick up one of the pieces, and if it&amp;rsquo;s a video for example, start playing that video in the UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sesame Street</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/sesame-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/sesame-street/</guid>
      <description>The Sesame Workshop and PBS produce excellent Flash sites for kids. Among my favorites are the Sesame Street and Arthur sites. The recent redesign of the Sesame Street site adds new navigation options, a more YouTube-like video section, and most notably, user profiles. The best of the new features is the ability to add favorites to &amp;ldquo;Your Street,&amp;rdquo; a user profile page that uses your favorites to display a start page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Faceted Browsing on Konigi</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-faceted-browsing-konigi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-faceted-browsing-konigi/</guid>
      <description>About 10 years ago I participated in the daily indexing of news articles as part of my job designing a digital library. During graduate study for the MLS my concentration was actually on information retrieval and classification, so I was interested in doing the job and understanding the content in order to know how to make it useful to users. Customers would get this information via the web site, by email, and in newsletters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN.com Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnn-com-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnn-com-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The CNN News portal provides a very dense global navigation header that&#39;s got quite a bit going on, but succeeds in drawing out the main entry points for news, featured or promoted points of interest, language/edition preference setting, search, and even a sticky alert area for late breaking news. It even borrows the idea of hot topics navigation per section from Newsvine, which allows for a more variable set of local navigation based on what&#39;s happening now, rather than on a rigid top-down IA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/delicious-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/delicious-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The redesigned del.icio.us site provides drop down navigation to signed in users. Clicking the navigation label jumps to that section, or click the arrow to drill down in that section. They provide separators in the drop-down to chunk up the navigation options. There&#39;s some inconsistency in the treatment of selected sections. The blue background of the nav link on Home implies selected color. But if you click the links in the global nav, the blue background on Home remains on Home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL TELEVISION</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/national-television/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/national-television/</guid>
      <description>National Television is a video and film production studio in California. It&amp;rsquo;s portfolio site is among the best examples of the use of bold typography as the primary element that defines both the form and interface. The look is clean and undeniably confident.
http://www.natl.tv/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schematic</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/schematic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/schematic/</guid>
      <description>Schematic is a large agency with 6 offices in locations including Los Angeles, New York, and London. They provide a host of services including strategy, creative, marketing, user experience and technology. It&amp;rsquo;s portfolio shows how a company site can be at once slick and easy to use. It&amp;rsquo;s easily on my list of favorites and is one of the nicest portfolios to look at. What I like about this site, besides the very clean visual design, is that it provides a very usable example of a zoomable user interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daisy Balloon</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/daisy-balloon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/daisy-balloon/</guid>
      <description>Daisy is an artist that does incredible things with balloons. The site presently shows some amazing dresses fabricated with the long balloons you&amp;rsquo;d usually only see in the form of little animals, but Daisy elevates the art to design amazing clothing that could be called haute couture. I could easily imagine these things being made out of a less ephemeral material and being worn, albeit a bit uncomfortably.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO TRY</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</guid>
      <description>Yugo Nakamura and the Simone Inc. crew are serving up some sick Flash once again for Uniqlo. This time, the mini site is devoted to women&amp;rsquo;s bras. The mood is cheerful as happy electronic strings accompany the dizzying array of women&amp;rsquo;s headshots spinning and combining to create patterns in 3D space. Click on a picture to reveal the details (in Japanese) of one of the women&amp;rsquo;s age, height, and bra size, or use the pop up menus to filter the set down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/buffalo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/buffalo/</guid>
      <description>Buffalo&amp;rsquo;s site is simple on the surface, with very few pages. What I like most are the transitions when you click to view their work. AJAX is used to display work in-page, similar to the functionality of a lightbox, but doing away with transitions typically indicated by graying out the background. This version displays the portfolio panel with a close icon. They also use AJAX to toggle visibility, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACTGRM</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/actgrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/actgrm/</guid>
      <description>Flash sites with minimalist layouts and huge navigation links are all the rage. But that&amp;rsquo;s cool, because I rarely see one that I don&amp;rsquo;t like. The colorful cool orbs bubbling in the background give me a warm fuzzy feeling&amp;ndash;it&amp;rsquo;s like having a clear lava lamp lightbox to drop photos onto. Love it.
http://www.actgrm.com/index.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enigmind</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/enigmind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/enigmind/</guid>
      <description>Engimind is a design agency in Bogota, Columbia. Their flash site has a clean, modern, and mechanical feel, and features some unique navigation tools that allow users to click links, or use their keyboard entirely to move select sections and scroll through their portfolio. http://www.enigmind.com/#/NEWS/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservation International Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/conservation-international-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/conservation-international-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Conservation International site provides an interesting take on the flyout or drop down global navigation bar. The site uses single, short action words set in very large type to indicate what you can do and name the sections of the site: Discover, Learn, Explore, Act, Give. These are nice pathfinder-type labels. When the user hovers over a links, the label expands to provide a phrase. For example, Learn becomes &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tork Revolution Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tork-revolution-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tork-revolution-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Tork Revolution site features a Flash global/local navigation system that appears conventional on the surface, but positions the navigation elements in unconventional places on the page, using size, position, and color to indicate hierarchy.
1. The home page.2. Clicking, Foodservice, one of the main entry points in the global nav pulls that word out of the nav and re-positions it at the top of the page.3. Following a link to a sub-page, we are now viewing &amp;quot;Foodservice &amp; Kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARTINESSS</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/martinesss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/martinesss/</guid>
      <description>http://www.chichov.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TON LO BIANCO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/ton-lo-bianco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/ton-lo-bianco/</guid>
      <description>http://www.tonlobianco.com.br/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viking Penguin Book Club</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/viking-penguin-book-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/viking-penguin-book-club/</guid>
      <description>http://www.vpbookclub.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>maker&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/makers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/makers/</guid>
      <description>http://makers.jp/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>standardimage</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/standardimage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/standardimage/</guid>
      <description>standardimage provides an interesting single page, scrolling interface. The global navigation persists in a fixed position in the left of the page, and clicking on any of these links scrolls the user to that area of the page. You can just as easily scroll with the scroll bar as well. In some areas, you can pan horizontally, e.g. to see more images in the portfolio of work.
http://www.standardimage.jp/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwittEarth: Another globe interface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/twittearth-another-globe-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/twittearth-another-globe-interface/</guid>
      <description>TwittEarth is another spinning earth globe interface for displaying geolocalized information that&#39;s similar to the Yahoo Newsglobe and wii news channel interfaces. I don&#39;t care much for viewing the public twitter feed, so it&#39;s not very interesting to me. I&#39;m still trying to imagine the context that makes these interfaces practical for everyday use. The place where it makes most sense to me is in the 10 foot experience, as with the wii news channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Interface Implementations of Faceted Browsing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-implementations-faceted-browsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-implementations-faceted-browsing/</guid>
      <description>Mike Padilla offers up a description of facets and their use on web sites for browsing and filtering. He defines the types of interactions or behaviors that are typically found on sites with faceted browsing, describes what happens in terms of the system when you apply filters, and shows some examples of faceted browsing in use on sites including my favorite, Nike.com.
http://www.digital-web.com/articles/user_interface_implementations_of_faceted_browsing/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dasai</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dasai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dasai/</guid>
      <description>http://www.dasai.es/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Werchter 2008</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/rock-werchter-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/rock-werchter-2008/</guid>
      <description>http://www.rockwerchter.be/RW2008/site/index.asp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VaryWell</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/varywell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/varywell/</guid>
      <description>VaryWell is the portfolio of Seattle, Washington designers Ryan and Jason Hickner. The Hickners work on in web sites, interactive displays, and interesting hardware projects including a very cool LED light color mixer. Their portfolio is a nice demonstration of the the Flash Papervision tools. Selecting a project presents a stack of media that are unshuffled and spread around the screen, much as you would spread a set of slides on a lightbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letters &amp; Numbers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/letters-numbers-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/letters-numbers-0/</guid>
      <description>http://www.letters-numbers.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polk</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/polk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/polk/</guid>
      <description>http://www.polkdesign.net/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wards Exchange</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/wards-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/wards-exchange/</guid>
      <description>http://www.wards-exchange.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publicis &amp; Hal Riney Webcam Gesture Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/publicis-hal-riney-webcam-gesture-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/publicis-hal-riney-webcam-gesture-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Publicis and Hal Riney site attempts to innovate navigation by replacing mouse input by detecting gestures the user makes against their webcam. Once the Flash file embeds your webcam video into the lower right corner of the page, a body outline is superimposed, and hot spots in the North-South-East-West quandrants are ghosted on the screen to show where you should hold or swipe your hand to navigate. Unfortunately the video ended up eating up resources on my machine to the point that the load times were painfully slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Chart: Reinventing Color from 1950 to Today</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/color-chart-reinventing-color-1950-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/color-chart-reinventing-color-1950-today/</guid>
      <description>http://www.moma.org/exhibitions/2008/colorchart/flashsite/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katja Schweiker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/katja-schweiker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/katja-schweiker/</guid>
      <description>http://www.katjaschweiker.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorola - Public Safety Solutions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/motorola-public-safety-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/motorola-public-safety-solutions/</guid>
      <description>http://business.motorola.com/publicsafety/secondnature/site.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>viaduct</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/viaduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/viaduct/</guid>
      <description>http://www.viaduct.co.uk/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SectionSeven Inc.</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sectionseven-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sectionseven-inc/</guid>
      <description>http://www.sectionseven.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B_CUBE</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/b-cube/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/b-cube/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of zoomable user interfaces. When they&amp;rsquo;re done simply and elegantly, the experience of navigating through a ZUI site is sheer pleasure. You never lose a sense of where you are, and the whole of the site is near by. On small, manageable sites where the number of sections is not very wide or deep, the zooming paradigm works very well. Danka Studio, which creates sophisticated, interactive navigation on its Flash sites has achieved that with the site created for French architecture firm B-CUBE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julie Bayard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/julie-bayard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/julie-bayard/</guid>
      <description>http://www.juliebayard.fr/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design and the Elastic Mind</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/design-and-elastic-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/design-and-elastic-mind/</guid>
      <description>http://www.moma.org/exhibitions/2008/elasticmind/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JLERN DESIGN</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/jlern-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/jlern-design/</guid>
      <description>http://jlern.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STUDIOS architecture</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/studios-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/studios-architecture/</guid>
      <description>http://www.studiosarchitecture.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SF/PM</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sf-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/sf-pm/</guid>
      <description>http://www.sf-pm.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKIO NISHIYAMA : HAIR STYLIST</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/akio-nishiyama-hair-stylist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/akio-nishiyama-hair-stylist/</guid>
      <description>http://www.akionishiyama.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alberto Oviedo Photography</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/alberto-oviedo-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/alberto-oviedo-photography/</guid>
      <description>http://oviedofoto.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analogue</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/analogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/analogue/</guid>
      <description>http://www.analogue.ca/main.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DESUDESU</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/desudesu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/desudesu/</guid>
      <description>http://www.desudesu.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucuma</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/lucuma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/lucuma/</guid>
      <description>http://lucuma.com.ar/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOJESS</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nojess/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nojess/</guid>
      <description>http://www.nojess.net/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are VI - Vivid Image London</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/we-are-vi-vivid-image-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/we-are-vi-vivid-image-london/</guid>
      <description>http://www.wearevi.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>another graphic design portfolio</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/another-graphic-design-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/another-graphic-design-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>http://anotherwebsite.net/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drykorn</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/drykorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/drykorn/</guid>
      <description>With a tagline like &amp;ldquo;for beautiful people,&amp;rdquo; your web site better beautiful too. Drykorn totally delivers on that promise. There are very few sites I gush over, but every time I come back to this site I want to just wrap myself up in it. Each season the design takes on a new texture, in line with the colors and fabrics of their garments. The design showcased here is for Spring/Summer &amp;lsquo;08, and its appropriately light, but summery fabric background is still as rich and textured as the dark woolen background they sported in the Winter look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Nike Store provides an excellent faceted navigation for narrowing product listings by sensible facets including gender, product type, sport, color, and price. The site skins the faceted classification tool provided by Endeca, which allows the user to select a product attribute of interest under any facet, and continually provides feedback about the attributes in other facets that can be used to narrow your choice of products down. Nike&#39;s Flash-based implementation is appropriate and useful, and ranks among the best examples of faceted navigation you will find on either commercial or academic databases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Hulu provides a nice faceted approach for browsing clips and episodes.
1. Filtering navigation in left sidebar2. All facets exposed; &amp;quot;Clip&amp;quot; selected under Type facet3. &amp;quot;Comedy&amp;quot; selected under genre facet; Selecting &amp;quot;show more&amp;quot; expands to show other choices under facet4. &amp;quot;NBC&amp;quot; selected under Source facet http://hulu.com/videos/views/thumbs/all/clip/all/all/today/1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firstborn</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/firstborn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/firstborn/</guid>
      <description>Design and technology consultancy with offices in New York and Los Angeles. A very usable Flash experience with simple, but sexy navigation, clean URLs, selectable text and flexible sorting features on list/gallery pages. The 11&amp;frasl;2007 redesign is much bolder than the previous design (the white bg). An instant classic.
http://firstbornmultimedia.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viget Labs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/viget-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/viget-labs/</guid>
      <description>Design agency with offices in VA and NC. Superb interactions to transition from page to page make this site feel like it&amp;rsquo;s done in Flash, but it&amp;rsquo;s all javascript using JQuery. Looks like it&amp;rsquo;s mostly all in done in 1 XHTML page with a few AJAX calls for the dynamic stuff like jobs. Lovely colors and art direction make this site feel warm and human.
http://teamviget.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>