<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Touch User Interface</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/touch-user-interface/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/touch-user-interface/</guid><description>I just discovered Touch User Interface, a blog that reports regularly on touch interface projects, and provides links to resources related to designing for touch screen interfaces.
http://www.touchuserinterface.com/</description></item><item><title>J.BradfordDillon</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/jbradforddillon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/jbradforddillon/</guid><description>An information dense layout resembling a tabloid design. I like the table of contents on the right side, and the footer content.
http://jbradforddillon.com/</description></item><item><title>Minimalissimo</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/minimalissimo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/minimalissimo/</guid><description>Minimalissimo practices what they preach. They blog about all type of minimalist design, and their own design is really just that: minimalist.
Their pagination design is also pretty sweet.
http://minimalissimo.com</description></item><item><title>Bill C. English</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/bill-c-english/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/bill-c-english/</guid><description>Online portfolio and journal of UI and web designer Bill C. English.
http://billcenglish.com</description></item><item><title>Bad Ass Ideas</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/bad-ass-ideas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/bad-ass-ideas/</guid><description>Samantha Warren's blog and portfolio is features some great layered graphics in the trompe l'oeil header and footer and some lovely type. I like the paper textures, the subtle shadows and little 3D effects, the nice treatment of the search box, and the general feeling of dynamism created by the asymmetry of the header/footer and layering, balanced by the strong alignment in the body. Nice stuff.
http://badassideas.com/</description></item><item><title>Lovely Package</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/lovely-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/lovely-package/</guid><description>Simple, minimalist look for a package design weblog.
http://lovelypackage.com/</description></item><item><title>Unstoppable Robot Ninja</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unstoppable-robot-ninja/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unstoppable-robot-ninja/</guid><description>This is a bad-ass looking weblog with a very cool header. Big type and ample white space sets up a very clear visual hierarchy and makes it easy to read, and a strong center alignment of header/footer elements directs the eye. I love the big illustrated robot head in the header (kind of expecting it to wink at me) and the character photos in the footer. I also like the way the global navigation shifts so that the center link is whatever section you're viewing, which makes that centered look and directs your eyes downwards.</description></item><item><title>darrenalawi.com</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/darrenalawicom/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/darrenalawicom/</guid><description>Different approach to a blog &amp;amp; portfolio design, built on Wordpress.
http://www.darrenalawi.com</description></item><item><title>TypeNeu</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/typeneu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/typeneu/</guid><description>TypeNeue is a typography blog that uses Suprb's Grid A Liciouis theme for WordPress to give it that dense multi-column layout. Entries are ordered reverse chronologically, but unlike typical columnar layouts, the entries are read from left to right first, then top to bottom, so the lines of demarcation are staggered. This creates a unexpectedness and less ordered feeling to the layout, but gives the design the ability to put more content into the screen above the fold.</description></item><item><title>UX Booth: Free Website Usability Testing Reviews &amp; UX Blog</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-booth-free-website-usability-testing-reviews-ux-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ux-booth-free-website-usability-testing-reviews-ux-blog/</guid><description>The UX Booth is a group that writes about User Experience, and offers free Website Usability Reviews that all designers and developers can benefit from.
Via Digital Web
http://www.uxbooth.com/</description></item><item><title>The CANADIAN DESIGN RESOURCE</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/canadian-design-resource/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/canadian-design-resource/</guid><description>The Canadian Design Resource is a blog that showcases work from Canadian designers covering a wide range of disciplines.
Thanks DesignNotes.
http://www.canadiandesignresource.ca/officialgallery/index.php</description></item><item><title>Jason Santa Maria</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/jason-santa-maria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/jason-santa-maria/</guid><description>Brooklyn visual designer Jason Santa Maria redesigns his site with a more flexible system that will allow him to adapt the design of each entry to suit the content. He notes that this is a redefined focus on art direction, and a magazine approach to content publishing outside of the typical confines of a CMS templating system.
I liked previous site design, and its reference to physical print. But I find that while the new visual style might refer back to the feeling of print, this visual style is more appealing to me as a someone who tends to be drawn to modern design.</description></item><item><title>inspireUX - words to inspire user experience designers</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/inspireux-words-inspire-user-experience-designers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/inspireux-words-inspire-user-experience-designers/</guid><description>inspireUX is a blog that posts quotes to inspire user experience designers (whether they be visual designers, information architects, interaction designers, etc.). The quotes are formatted to be printed on 4x6" index cards, so you can keep them close at hand when inspiration is needed.
http://www.inspireux.com/</description></item><item><title>Wunderbloc</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/wunderbloc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/wunderbloc/</guid><description>http://www.wunderbloc.com/</description></item><item><title>Astheria</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/astheria/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/astheria/</guid><description>http://astheria.com</description></item></channel></rss>