<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>principles on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/principles/</link><description>Recent content in principles on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/principles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Ten Commandments Of User Experience</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/ten-commandments-user-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ten-commandments-user-experience/</guid><description>View more presentations from Nick Finck. Nick Finck and Raina Van Cleave's presentation slides from the SXSWi talk are up. Here's a summary:
User experiences are your everyday experiences—anything from operating a car, to making a pot of coffee, to ordering a pair of shoes online. User experience is the result of your interactions with a product or service, specifically how it’s delivered and its related artifacts according to the design.</description></item><item><title>Google Design Principles</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/google-design-principles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/google-design-principles/</guid><description>Luke Wroblewski summarizes the fundamental principles that guide Google in designing user experiences, as told by John Wiley in a WritersUA presentation.
Useful: focus on people -their lives, their work, their dreams. Fast: every millisecond counts Simple: simplicity is powerful. Engaging: engage beginners and attract experts. Innovative: dare to be innovative. Universal: design for the world. Profitable: plan for today's and tomorrow's business. Beautiful: delight the eye without distracting the mind.</description></item><item><title>Shneiderman's Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/shneidermans-eight-golden-rules-interface-design/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/shneidermans-eight-golden-rules-interface-design/</guid><description>Ben Shneiderman's Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design are user interface design rules described in Designing the User Interface: Strategies for Effective Human-Computer Interaction. Shneiderman proposed this collection of principles that are derived heuristically from experience and applicable in most interactive systems after being properly refined, extended, and interpreted.
To improve the usability of an application it is important to have a well designed interface and these "Eight Golden Rules of Interface Design"</description></item></channel></rss>