<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>top stories on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/top-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in top stories on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/top-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.fm Top Content Charts Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-top-content-charts-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-top-content-charts-module/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm&#39;s top artists and top songs content module appears on user profiles. The module shows a list of top content, with options in tabs to change time slice. The content module also provides options to modify settings and embed the content on an external blog or social network site.
1. Default tab, showing last 7 days of top artists with Last.fm&#39;s signature bar chart for number of plays. 2. Last 6 months tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IHT Top Stories Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iht-top-stories-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iht-top-stories-module/</guid>
      <description>The International Herald Tribune site has, in my opinion, been the site that set the bar for clean, minimalist newspaper web sites since John Weir worked on the design circa 2000/2001. The evolution of the site has continued to stick to Weir&#39;s minimalist visual style, although his innovative DHTML column and clipping behaviors are gone.
The top stories content module is an interface element that is a common feature in news sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsweek Top 10 Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/newsweek-top-10-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/newsweek-top-10-module/</guid>
      <description>Newsweek uses Clearspring&#39;s Flash widgets to display top read and emailed stories as a content delivery module in a sidebar. This module is like most top story modules provided on news sites, e.g. NY Times, but the interesting features are the ability to adjust the range of stories by time (notice the nice slider control) and to embed the module as a widget. While this module is implemented as Flash, there is no reason it can&#39;t be done as XHTML and Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
