<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>errors on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/errors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in errors on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/errors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>404 Error Pages, One More Time</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/404-error-pages-one-more-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/404-error-pages-one-more-time/</guid>
      <description>Smashing Magazine expound upon what makes a well designed 404 page in their latest design gallery which features 50 examples. Inspired by the gallery, I made a more useful 404 for Konigi as well.
http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2009/01/29/404-error-pages-one-more-time/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Input Masks in Forms</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/input-masks-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/input-masks-forms/</guid>
      <description>Luke Wroblewski pointed to Josh Bush&#39;s Masked Input Plugin for JQuery. Luke writes that the plugin &#34;integrate(s) formatting cues directly into an input field to help signal how to correctly answer a question. These formatting instructions are automatically included in an input and cannot be removed by a user. More importantly, a user cannot enter other non-valid characters into the input field. Check out the demo at Masked Input Plugin.&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Fail Safe When You Can Poka-yoke?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/why-fail-safe-when-you-can-poka-yoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/why-fail-safe-when-you-can-poka-yoke/</guid>
      <description>Poka-Yoke is a Japanese word for &#34;fail-safing&#34; that I just came across and suspect might be entering my UI vocabulary soon. The entry from Wikipedia:
Poka-yoke (IPA: [poka joke]) is a Japanese term that means &#34;fail-safing&#34;, &#34;Foolproof&#34; or &#34;mistake-proofing&#34; — avoiding (yokeru) inadvertent errors (poka)) is a behavior-shaping constraint, or a method of preventing errors by putting limits on how an operation can be performed in order to force the correct completion of the operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Loses Users&#39; Email Notification Settings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-loses-users-email-notification-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/facebook-loses-users-email-notification-settings/</guid>
      <description>I got this in my email from Facebook. Unfortunately, the settings that control which email notifications get sent to you were lost. We&#39;re sorry for the inconvenience.
 Wow. Really? I agree with what M. David Peterson had to say about the issue. Sounds like they&#39;ve got some inexperienced engineers running the show. If this had been a web service with critical data that wasn&#39;t backed up, people would be pretty pissed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
