<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>drop-down menus on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/drop-down-menus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in drop-down menus on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/drop-down-menus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fever Progressive Disclosure</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fever-progressive-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fever-progressive-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>The Fever RSS news reader provides some useful progressive disclosure/enhancement behaviors that hide features until they are needed. Many of the primary features are also provided as keyboard shortcuts. The resulting experience provides a subtle and minimalist aesthetic without compromising features.
1. The initial view of the app shows groups of items and the pages linking to them. The main navigator is shown in left sidebar.2. Selecting a category (&amp;quot;UX&amp;quot; in this example) displays a second column for browsing feeds in that category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin.com Header</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</guid>
      <description>The Virgin.com redesign sports a header that provides a boatload of functionality using mega fly out menus: locale selection, micro-site navigation, registration, login, and newsletter signup. I like that they make these options readily available wherever you are on the site. The longer drop downs like the registration form, for example, seem a little long for users on smaller screens, e.g. netbooks. 1. The global navigation bar provides mega drop downs with sub-nodes and links to their subsidiary companies that provide products and services under each category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holland Festival Program Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</guid>
      <description>The Holland Festival provides a program browser/calendar that provides an AJAX interface for viewing over 3 weeks of events in a grid. Drop down menus are provided to narrow or expand by genre, locale and route. A single toggle highlights featured events. And a sliding selector, which can be dragged to move the range left and right and with handles to narrow or expand the window, allows you to filter the days to be shown in the grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoMA Exhibition/Collection Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moma-exhibitioncollection-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moma-exhibitioncollection-browser/</guid>
      <description>MoMA&#39;s exhibition and collection browser provides faceted drill-down of the museum collection&#39;s image library using a mega drop-down menu. Each facet provides the ability to select multiple terms, so the user may select multiple authors, departments or decades, for instance. Executing the search displays the narrowed set of results in an image gallery that can be toggled thumbnail, slideshow, list, and single artist views. Sorting options and image matte colors may also be selected by the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profoto Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Profoto&#39;s take on the breadcrumb combines expanded menus for each branch to provide a drill-down method for navigating siblings, aunts, great-aunts, etc. It basically exposes the hierarchy of siblings at each level, and it&#39;s really most useful when you&#39;ve navigated deep into a hierarchy. It can get a little weird when you use these, because you have to remember that you&#39;re viewing siblings in the branch you&#39;re exposing. If you look at the last screenshot for the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Life Magazine Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/best-life-magazine-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/best-life-magazine-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Best Life Magazine&#39;s global navigation uses drop-down menus to provide both sub-section navigation where applicable, and teasers of content in sections, using a multi-column lists and showing a featured article with a thumbnail. Thanks to Fritz for the pointer.
1. Subscribe drop down shows print and online subscription options.2. Teasers of latest and featured content within a section. http://bestlifeonline.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/target-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/target-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Target&#39;s global navigation features wide, multi-column drop-down menus that stretch to the full width of the page layout. The columns in the drop down show hierarchical lists of product/section contents using font weight and indentation, and additionally allow the company to promote special events.
1. Drop down for the &amp;quot;Women&amp;quot; section shows a multi-column hierarchical list of all product sub-categories.2. The &amp;quot;See All&amp;quot; menu item allows the site to show other product categories that aren&#39;t being featured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons, Revised</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</guid>
      <description>We covered Shelfari&#39;s hybrid button in their list views of bookshelf items. That example showed a single push button with an attached icon for drop down menu. The single button allowed for the use of a default behavior, while the drop down arrow allowed for the display of other options for the item. The drop down menu allowed users to make multiple selections, i.e. using checkbox behaviors, rather than just select one value in the drop down list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Move and Label Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-move-and-label-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-move-and-label-menus/</guid>
      <description>Google modified the labeling (tagging) menus in Gmail to add a Move option to co-exist with the prior Label drop down menu. The Move menu allows the user to move an email to a single label and then archives it, removing it from the Inbox. The Label menu allows the user to add multiple labels to the email, but does not archive it. Both menus offer a label search input with auto-completion, as well as options to create new or manage existing labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Shelfari has a clever hybrid button/drop down menu to display actions on books. The button label shows the current status of the item, e.g. on my shelf, add to my shelf. When the user hovers over a button of a book that&#39;s not in your shelf, the label changes to &#34;Add to I&#39;ve Read&#34;. Clicking the drop down arrow shows other options for the book with shelf actions in the top half (I plan to read, I&#39;m reading now, I&#39;ve read), and the bottom half shows other attributes of your book (Favorite, I own, Wish list).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wowhead Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Wowhead is a database of World of Warcraft information. The database provides a hierarchical subject taxonomy to describe items, and presents that hierarchy in the breadcrumbs for the item. When the user hovers ofer a branch in the breadcrumb trail, a drop down menu is displayed to show the node siblings and drill down to children. 1. Single entry view (database record).2. Hovering over the current entry&#39;s parent category (Daggers) to view siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daylife Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Daylife&#39;s drop down menu in global navigation that provides a wide ribbon to show both navigation to secondary levels and to show teaser content, e.g. the Latest News menu shows top level news categories as well as recent articles in each category. News sites like Daylife and NewsVine have been coming up with interesting ways of changing user&#39;s expectations of what can exist in global navigation. In some cases, the labels and categories for what appear in global navigation suggest a shifting information architecture that is based on what&#39;s interesting now or what people have been reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a fan of the drop down menus that span a wide area, e.g. the main body or full page, in order to show a wider range of options rather showing fewer in a vertical drop down and forcing navigation through a fly-out tree. This convention is showing up mostly in global navigation, and with the introduction of Microsoft&#39;s Ribbon, we can expect to see more of it.
Google shows buttons with down arrows to indicate that clicking one of those controls will show expanded options in-screen, a la the drop down menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Quotes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quotes/</guid>
      <description>The &#34;In Quotes&#34; project in Google Labs is an interesting attempt to leverage information from Google News to try to help people understand where public figures stand on topics and issues by extracting quotes. Google says &#34;Much of the published reporting about people is based on the interpretation of a journalist. Direct quotes, on the other hand, are concrete units of information that describe how newsmakers represent themselves.&#34;
The interface is pretty simple to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Channel Drop Down Menu</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</guid>
      <description>Hulu&#39;s drop down menu for channels stretches to the width of the design and provides a multi-column grid of channels. This method of running a drop down or flyout menu left-to-right rather than top-to-bottom allows interface designers to present longer lists of options without worrying about what appears in relation to the fold, and forcing scroll on longer lists.
 http://www.hulu.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
