<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unexpected on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/unexpected/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unexpected on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/unexpected/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unfold</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unfold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unfold/</guid>
      <description>The site for Norwegian studio Unfold has some interesting &amp;amp; unexpected layout with 45 degree angle text and blocks of color, and panning and sliding interface elements.
http://unfold.no/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bond Art &#43; Science</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/bond-art-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/bond-art-science/</guid>
      <description>The new site for Bond Art + Science mimics an instant messaging window session where Bond are talking to you directly as a potential client. Messages scroll up from the bottom in a canned discussion, almost as if viewing someone&#39;s previous IM session. The device would have been very clever if it was actually functioning as a chat bot. This site manages to do one thing very well&amp;#8212;it gets your attention because the presentation is unexpected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IDEO</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/ideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/ideo/</guid>
      <description>The redesigned IDEO site has been sitting in a browser tab for a few weeks now because it just felt like one of those things I needed to mull over before writing about. It&#39;s one of the few sites this year that just took me by surprise. In short, the deep treasure trove of content unleashed in this redesign is a huge departure from the tightly constrained and minimalist prior design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO TRY</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</guid>
      <description>Yugo Nakamura and the Simone Inc. crew are serving up some sick Flash once again for Uniqlo. This time, the mini site is devoted to women&#39;s bras. The mood is cheerful as happy electronic strings accompany the dizzying array of women&#39;s headshots spinning and combining to create patterns in 3D space. Click on a picture to reveal the details (in Japanese) of one of the women&#39;s age, height, and bra size, or use the pop up menus to filter the set down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernista</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/modernista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/modernista/</guid>
      <description>Modernista delivers one of the most unexpected agency portfolios by using UGC tools to display their content. Their site is sort of an un-site. Once you arrive at their domain, a smallish red navigation widget that&#39;s 50px x 80px displays in the upper left of the screen. The rest of the screen is taken over by an 100% x 100% iframe showing their Wikipedia page.
For the most part, the red widget is the only bit of the Modernista identity you see in their experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
