<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing Enjoyable User Interfaces: Lessons learned from computer games</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-enjoyable-user-interfaces-lessons-learned-computer-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-enjoyable-user-interfaces-lessons-learned-computer-games/</guid>
      <description>I find inspiration in the literature that examines games and play as factors in creating delightful and engaging experiences. I like to think of how this applies to products outside of the video gaming industry. I&#39;ve had Thomas Malone&#39;s 1981 paper, &#34;Heuristics for Designing Enjoyable Interfaces: Lessons from computer games&#34; on my desk for a while. I finally got around to reading it and found some interesting ideas that resonated with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Wright on Game Play and Education</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/will-wright-game-play-and-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/will-wright-game-play-and-education/</guid>
      <description>Will Wright&amp;rsquo;s talk at the Summit on Science, Entertainment, and Education looks at how game play can be relevant to education. These are my notes from this talk.
How we process information Our basic model for processing and acting on data that we receive in the world looks something like this:
- Behavior
- Models (Predictive) ↑
- Schema (Abstractions) ↑
- Metaphors (Patterns) ↑
- Examples (Data) ↑</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playful Design Book Site</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/playful-design-book-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/playful-design-book-site/</guid>
      <description>Rosenfeld Media have a book site and Ning community up for John Ferrara&amp;rsquo;s forthcoming book, Playful Design: Creating Game Expderiences in Everyday Interfaces.
Game design is a sibling discipline to software and Web design, but they&#39;re siblings that grew up in different houses. They have much more in common than their perceived distinction typically suggests, and user experience practitioners can realize enormous benefit by exploiting the solutions that games have found to the real problems of design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Things Video Games Can Teach Us About Web Usability</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/6-things-video-games-can-teach-us-about-web-usability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/6-things-video-games-can-teach-us-about-web-usability/</guid>
      <description>Mark Riggan makes some interesting observations about design strategies and techniques used in video games that keep the experience usable, and suggests how these ideas apply to designing for the web.
http://www.atlanticbt.com/blog/6-things-video-games-can-teach-us-about-web-usability/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone is all Fun and Games</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-all-fun-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iphone-all-fun-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Fred Beecher wrote the excellent article &amp;ldquo;The iPhone is Not Easy to Use: A New Direction for User Experience&amp;rdquo; on Johnny Holland to talk about why the iPhone is not easy to use (at first), and why it changes the game for user experience designers. The examples illustrate how gestural interfaces are hidden, and lack the affordances of physical buttons. But the real story here is how the iPhone brings one thing to the experience that is more important than usability&amp;#8212;fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teoskaffa.com</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teoskaffacom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/teoskaffacom/</guid>
      <description>Teo Skaffa&amp;rsquo;s fun portfolio is like a tribute to 8 bit game consoles. Huge pixelated text and pointers, dinging mouseovers that make you half expect coins to pop out of links, and a keyboard navigation make this site a pleasure for NES nostalgists.
http://www.teoskaffa.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRID In-Game Motion Graphics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/grid-game-motion-graphics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/grid-game-motion-graphics/</guid>
      <description>Motionographer has some cool video of the in-game menus and motion graphics in RACE DRIVER GRID video game from Codemasters.
http://motionographer.com/2008/06/30/real-time-motion-graphics-grid/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Xbox Experience</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-xbox-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-xbox-experience/</guid>
      <description>Kotaku reports on the New Xbox Experience, which does away with the Blade interface, and replaces with a remote-control type UI with cover-flow-like browsability. We&amp;rsquo;ll have to see what the reception will be for this. Xbox are integrating Netflix soon, and may be hoping to simplify the experience for a wider audience. I found the Blade UI to be pretty interesting the few times I got to use it.
http://kotaku.com/5025143/the-new-xbox-experience-just-the-facts-and-maybe-some-conjecture</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CamSpace Webcam Game Controller</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/camspace-webcam-game-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/camspace-webcam-game-controller/</guid>
      <description>Camspace is pretty slick. The people at CamTrax are demoing the PC camera-based interface. At first blush, I thought it similar to the gimicky Eye Toy games, but this is much better. CamTrax is a software-based technology that enables the tracking of hand-held objects in real time, with high reliability. What you see in the demo is that the software recognizes the hand-held objects and effectively turns them into pointers and other controls that can be used to act on the simple end as a cursor, and on the more sophisticated end as a game controller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Out And Play</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/get-out-and-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/get-out-and-play/</guid>
      <description>The Nokia ngage Get Out and Play site features some fun stop motion animation, a sick Breakout game using people, and the game Snake played out as an animation of 1,000 people. This is brilliant. Don&#39;t miss it.
http://www.get-out-and-play.com/index.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Network to release casual multiplayer game</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/cartoon-network-release-casual-multiplayer-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/cartoon-network-release-casual-multiplayer-game/</guid>
      <description>Cartoon Network are building a new online gaming community that hopes to challenge the model of the Massively Multiplayer Online Game (MMOG) with FusionFall, a game that leverages a community of players, but doesn&#39;t require the long term buildup of skillsets and earned resources. We&#39;re not building a game for hardcore gamers who will spend 60-plus hours a week here. If you think of those as hour-long dramas on TV, we want to be the half-hour sitcom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Superest: Who is the superest hero of them all?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/superest-who-superest-hero-them-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/superest-who-superest-hero-them-all/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the idea The Superest, a game/blog that features drawings of superheroes. The Superest is a continually running game of My Team, Your Team. The rules are simple:
Player 1 draws a character with a power. Player 2 then draws a character whose power cancels the power of that previous character. Repeat.
 To experience the fun in order, start at the first hero.
http://www.thesuperest.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineer Unlocks Wii&#39;s Hidden Potential</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/engineer-unlocks-wiis-hidden-potential/</guid>
      <description>CNET reports on Johnny Chung Lee&amp;rsquo;s interaction experiments with the Wii Remote. Lee, a Phd student at Carnegie Melon, does a quick demo of head tracking for VR displays and multi point interaction using the wii remote. His experiments describe with incredible clarity how the wii remote fundamentally works and how the remote might be exploited to do much more than point at single points on the screen and control them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>