<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>interaction on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/interaction/</link><description>Recent content in interaction on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/interaction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Multi-touch Interactions on the Apple iPad</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/new-multi-touch-interactions-apple-ipad/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/new-multi-touch-interactions-apple-ipad/</guid><description>Craig Villamor and Luke Wroblewski summarize the new interactions we'll be seeing in the iPad.
During Apple's 90 minute unveiling of the iPad this week, a lot of new multi-touch interactions were shown off. But they went by fast. So as a service to digital product designers everywhere, we took the time to extract 8 minutes of new user interface demos from the iPad keynote. Now you can quickly just catch the UI in action on Apple's new native iPad and iWork applications.</description></item><item><title>About the close tab behaviour in Google Chrome</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/about-close-tab-behaviour-google-chrome/</guid><description>Basil Safwat does a very thorough comparison of the the tabs in Mac Safari and Chrome, pointing out the subtleties in the close button positioning and behavior. While Mac close icons are on the left by convention, Chrome positions them to the right of the tab and keeps them visible, while Safari positions them to the left and only displays the close icon on hover. I initially had to relearn the close button position because Firefox also places them on the right.</description></item><item><title>Product Planner - View and Create User Flows, Viral Loops, and More.</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/product-planner-view-and-create-user-flows-viral-loops-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/product-planner-view-and-create-user-flows-viral-loops-and-more/</guid><description>Product Planner is one an brilliant idea. Deconstruct the user flow of web sites, illustrate the flow with annotated screenshot flowcharts, allow users to copy the flow and reuse on the site. Like Konigi, this does a great job of capturing examples of alternative approaches to interaction, showcases them for you to compare, and allows you to select the best examples to learn from and inform you of approaches you may not have thought of.</description></item></channel></rss>