<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visualization on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/visualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Visualization on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Koblin: Artfully visualizing our humanity</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/aaron-koblin-artfully-visualizing-our-humanity/</guid>
      <description>From Aaron Koblin&amp;rsquo;s TED presentation:
&amp;ldquo;Artist Aaron Koblin takes vast amounts of data &amp;ndash; and at times vast numbers of people &amp;ndash; and weaves them into stunning visualizations. From elegant lines tracing airline flights to landscapes of cell phone data, from a Johnny Cash video assembled from crowd-sourced drawings to the &amp;ldquo;Wilderness Downtown&amp;rdquo; video that customizes for the user, his works brilliantly explore how modern technology can make us more human.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chartbeat dashboard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/chartbeat-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/chartbeat-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Slick real time data visualization in the dashboard of web analytics service chartbeat. http://chartbeat.com/dashboard/?url=avc.com&amp;k=317a25eccba186e0f6b558f45214c0e7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information Architects Web Trend Map 4</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/information-architects-web-trend-map-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/information-architects-web-trend-map-4/</guid>
      <description>Information Architects, Japan, post their 4th Web Trends map. They&amp;rsquo;ll only be printing 1,000 copies.
http://informationarchitects.jp/web-trend-map-4-final-beta/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post/Evri Related Content Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/washington-postevri-related-content-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/washington-postevri-related-content-module/</guid>
      <description>The Washington Post uses a related content widget created by Evri that indexes content using person, place, and thing (subject) facets and allows the Post to display a list of related content beneath news. The widget, which is actually a bit of SVG/VML and JavaScript, provides a small visualization of topics in the article, and allows the user to do some filtering of the related content. Navigating to topic pages provides a complete filtering view for exploring and narrowing related content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NY Times Visualization Lab</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ny-times-visualization-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ny-times-visualization-lab/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times teams up with IBM&amp;rsquo;s Many Eyes project to provide word visualizations of data in the Vizlab.
http://vizlab.nytimes.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Periodic Table of Visualization Methods</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/periodic-table-visualization-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/periodic-table-visualization-methods/</guid>
      <description>This is a neat table listing and categorizing visualization methods from the folks at Visual Literacy
http://www.visual-literacy.org/periodic_table/periodic_table.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAYTUM</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/daytum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/daytum/</guid>
      <description>Daytum comes to us from the data obsessed minds of visual designers, Nick Felton and Ryan Case. Felton is the creator of the Feltron personal annual report that we Tufte/stats junkies love and Case is the creative director working on the social media experience at Sling Media. DAYTUM is a wonderful evolution of the personal annual report, bringing obsessive loggers a place to count whatever comes to mind and visualize that data beautifully in the personal and community space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everymoment Now News Visualization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/everymoment-now-news-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/everymoment-now-news-visualization/</guid>
      <description>everymomentnow is a beautiful news visualization site designed and developed by Craig Mod. The idea is to provide a sense of volume and correlation between keywords within a given subject area. The current incarnation focuses on Obama/McCain in the news. The clean, minimalist interface allows the user to visualize spikes in news article occurrences for each keyword a the highest level. You choose a single focal point using a keyword (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AideRSS Table Row Expansion</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</guid>
      <description>AideRSS is a service that scores and filters RSS feeds so that users can view the most active posts for a web site. Activity is based on number of comments, and posts to digg or del.icio.us. The feeds are displayed in a table, with hot or most active entries indicated by a higher rank and warmer color in the postrank column. A &#34;+ more&#34; icon allows the user to expand entry information within a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNIQLO TRY</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/uniqlo-try/</guid>
      <description>Yugo Nakamura and the Simone Inc. crew are serving up some sick Flash once again for Uniqlo. This time, the mini site is devoted to women&amp;rsquo;s bras. The mood is cheerful as happy electronic strings accompany the dizzying array of women&amp;rsquo;s headshots spinning and combining to create patterns in 3D space. Click on a picture to reveal the details (in Japanese) of one of the women&amp;rsquo;s age, height, and bra size, or use the pop up menus to filter the set down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization Sites</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/data-visualization-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/data-visualization-sites/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for resources related to data visualization, look no further than the lists on these 2 great resources:  Random Etc.&amp;rsquo;s list of 20 resources Meryl.net&amp;rsquo;s list of 175 resources 
http://meryl.net/2008/01/22/175-data-and-information-visualization-examples-and-resources/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Builder National Disgruntledness Index</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/career-builder-national-disgruntledness-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/career-builder-national-disgruntledness-index/</guid>
      <description>http://www.careerbuilder.com/ngi/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! NewsGlobe vs. Wii News Channel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-newsglobe-vs-wii-news-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/yahoo-newsglobe-vs-wii-news-channel/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! launched the News Globe, which shows the top news stories of the day using a rotatable globe for navigation. The stories are depicted as red blocks stacked over geographic regions of the globe, with taller stacks indicating more stories. By default the interface will autoplay through the top stories, spinning the globe to get from story to story. Clicking a link to a news article jetisons you out of this otherworldly view of earth, and into text land on a separate page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Explore Related Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-explore-related-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-explore-related-videos/</guid>
      <description>YouTube&#39;s exploring functionality in the full-screen video player allows users to directed exploration of related videos.
1) Clicking the explore button in the lower left brings up related videos visualization, which is sort of like a digraph that looks like a constellation of stars. 2) Circles in the center are videos. Hover over one circle expands to show you other videos related to that one, forming a cluster. Click a circle to watch a video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>