<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>questionnaires on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/questionnaires/</link>
    <description>Recent content in questionnaires on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/questionnaires/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quicken Product Comparison Table and Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</guid>
      <description>When a software company&#39;s product family grows, it can be quite difficult for customers to figure out which product is right for their needs. Quicken is one of those examples where the number of products is overwhelming. They try to help customers with a product comparison table provides a basic checkbox chart of all product feature categories, with product names and prices along the top of the table, and rows of feature categories, with checkboxes to indicate which products match which features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Science Research Service Launches</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/crowd-science-research-service-launches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/crowd-science-research-service-launches/</guid>
      <description>Crowd Science is a new comer among user research services that allow you to prompt small sets of users to participate in questionnaires while they&#39;re browsing your site.
Crowd Science Demographics is a new analytics service that builds detailed reports on the demographics and attitudes of website audiences. By surveying a small number visitors with carefully constructed questionnaires, Crowd Science Demographics is able to build comprehensive audience profiles that give publishers a deep understanding of their audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote Chooser Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/vote-chooser-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/vote-chooser-wizard/</guid>
      <description>A friend sent me the link to VoteChooser to remind people before the primary to vote. The site consists of a single page wizard that asks you 10 questions about where you stand on political issues. The results page shows how your position aligns with those of presidential candidates in an attempt to help the undecided discover who might be the best person to vote for.
I hesitated at posting this with my results, because I don&#39;t want to make a political statement, but its useful to see how this simple questionnaire is very effective at helping to do a simple research task like figuring out what candidates stand for.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
