<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enjoyment on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/enjoyment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enjoyment on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/enjoyment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing Enjoyable User Interfaces: Lessons learned from computer games</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-enjoyable-user-interfaces-lessons-learned-computer-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-enjoyable-user-interfaces-lessons-learned-computer-games/</guid>
      <description>I find inspiration in the literature that examines games and play as factors in creating delightful and engaging experiences. I like to think of how this applies to products outside of the video gaming industry. I&#39;ve had Thomas Malone&#39;s 1981 paper, &#34;Heuristics for Designing Enjoyable Interfaces: Lessons from computer games&#34; on my desk for a while. I finally got around to reading it and found some interesting ideas that resonated with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicker Studio&#39;s Jennifer Bove on how to design enjoyment</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/kicker-studios-jennifer-bove-how-design-enjoyment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/kicker-studios-jennifer-bove-how-design-enjoyment/</guid>
      <description>Jennifer Bove, principal at Kicker Studio, writes about the ways interaction designers can make design more about people and less about technology--designing behaviors that are defined from the point of view of humans, and designed to elicit emotion, make products and services more enjoyable and easier to use. Bove writes about the subtle things that can reference human connection, whether it is the language presented in system messages, the logic behind system behaviors that reflects human thought and desire, or subtle cues and movement that feels organic This is an excellent read that picks up the thread in Don Norman&#39;s Emotional Design, and Dave Malouf&#39;s recent writing about moving beyond function towards enjoyment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>