<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dummy text on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/dummy-text/</link><description>Recent content in dummy text on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/dummy-text/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Text Snippets</title><link>https://konigi.com/tools/text-snippets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/tools/text-snippets/</guid><description>About This is a work in progress. I'm copying over my commonly used text snippets and wireframes as I go.
People's Names, Sorted 10, First Name Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun Andrew Lincoln Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun 10, Last Name Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Steven Yeun 20, First Name Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun Adam Minarovich Andrew Lincoln Andrew Rothenberg Chandler Riggs Danai Gurira David Morrissey Emma Bell Irone Singleton Jeffrey DeMunn Jeryl Prescott-Sales Jon Bernthal Lauren Cohan Laurie Holden Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Michael Rooker Norman Reedus Sarah Callies Steven Yeun 20, Last Name Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun Emma Bell Jon Bernthal Sarah Callies Lauren Cohan Jeffrey DeMunn Danai Gurira Laurie Holden Andrew Lincoln Madison Lintz Melissa McBride Adam Minarovich David Morrissey Jeryl Prescott-Sales Norman Reedus Chandler Riggs Michael Rooker Andrew Rothenberg Irone Singleton Steven Yeun Wireframe Symbols Download Balsamiq BMML file</description></item><item><title>Blind Text Generator</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/blind-text-generator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/blind-text-generator/</guid><description>I prefer not to use dummy text, because creating wireframes and comps that reflect how they will really look and function is what people pay me for, and is a sign of a lazy IA/IXD. Plus it can be really enjoyable to write real fake copy. Having said that, I have to admit to being the lazy IA from time to timeand have gone to gone to lipsum.com to generate dummy text.</description></item></channel></rss>