<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>screen resolution on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/screen-resolution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in screen resolution on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/screen-resolution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Screensiz.es</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/screensizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/screensizes/</guid>
      <description>screensiz.es displays a table of screen specifications including resolution and pixel density for popular devices and monitors currently on the market.
Via Swissmiss
http://screensiz.es/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine Res Tool</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/fine-res-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/fine-res-tool/</guid>
      <description>The folks at FINE Design created a browser-based tool for seeing how your web site measures up at different screen resolutions.
To use it, simply enter a full URL of your choosing. Up pops that location superimposed with a draggable set of rulers (x and y axis) configurable in center/left/and right alignment. These rulers allow you to view that site as it would be seen at different resolutions. So you can get a sense for what other eyeballs experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Browser Size</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/google-browser-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/google-browser-size/</guid>
      <description>Google Browser Size is a visualization of browser window sizes for web sites. Enter a URL into the app, and the page is displayed behind an overlay showing the percentage of browser users who are able to view the visible portion, based on their browser&#39;s available viewport size, and their display&#39;s screen resolution. For example, the &amp;quot;90%&amp;quot; contour means that 90% of people visiting the site have their browser window open to at least this size or larger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Methodologie Browser Size Test</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/methodologie-browser-size-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/methodologie-browser-size-test/</guid>
      <description>Mmmmm, grids. Methodologie uses stats from The Counter to display the screen resolutions supported by users&#39; computers in their 10/2008 numbers.
http://www.methodologie.com/sizer/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Resolution Statistics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/screen-resolution-statistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/screen-resolution-statistics/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to researching user&#39;s screen resolution, I&#39;m a strong believer that vertical positioning matters most when considering key issues such as location of identifying elements like site name and h1-type headings, and elements that satisfy business rules such as ad location. The B&amp;amp;A article, &#34;Blasting the Myth of the Fold&#34; addresses this issue well, and I&#39;m in agreement that &#34;the fold&#34; matters little if the above issues are dealt with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
