<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>calendars on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/calendars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in calendars on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/calendars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Holland Festival Program Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</guid>
      <description>The Holland Festival provides a program browser/calendar that provides an AJAX interface for viewing over 3 weeks of events in a grid. Drop down menus are provided to narrow or expand by genre, locale and route. A single toggle highlights featured events. And a sliding selector, which can be dragged to move the range left and right and with handles to narrow or expand the window, allows you to filter the days to be shown in the grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics Date Selector</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-date-selector/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-date-selector/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics offers one of the most sophisticated date selectors for data filtering that I&#39;ve seen. The interface allows you to filter reports to a single day by clicking one square in a 3 month range. To select a date range, you click the start input, click a day, and do the same for the end date range. Or you can enter dates in the text inputs.
The timeline control allows you to visualize the volume of visitor activity as vertical bars, and adjust the date range by pulling slider handles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MobileMe Calendar Date Selector</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mobileme-calendar-date-selector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mobileme-calendar-date-selector/</guid>
      <description>The date selection controls in MobileMe Calendar mimic the date selection segmented control in iCal. However, the control bar adds an additional drop-down menu for actions like creating events, and jumping to a specific date. The interface is simple. The addition of the action menu makes the functions from the iCal menu bar accessible without having to add to the web-based calendar interface.
1. The full calendar interface.2. The action menu expanded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-calendar/</guid>
      <description>Where Google Search gave us syntax for doing all kinds of advanced searching, Google Calendar goes a more natural route. When Calendar was released, it introduced a lot of people to the idea of the natural language command line for the web via the &#34;Quick Add&#34; feature. Via a simple form input, you enter basic event info, e.g. &#34;Lunch with Judy on Thusday at 1pm.&#34; The event is quickly added, and you click the event title in the calendar to edit the details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presdo Calendaring</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/presdo-calendaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/presdo-calendaring/</guid>
      <description>Presdo is a calendaring service that uses a simple form input as the command line for entering natural language commands for events. To use, enter event statements as with Google Calendar. It is always assumed that you are the subject&amp;#8212;the WHO. You just have to fill in the rest of the WHAT, WITH WHOM, and WHERE parts of the statement, e.g. &#34;Have lunch with Judy on Thursday at 1pm.&#34; Once you&#39;ve submitted the basic event info, you&#39;re presented with a more complete UI for entering event details, and this is where the service far surpasses Google&#39;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is Good</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</guid>
      <description>When Is Good is a tool that does one thing&amp;#8212;helps a group of people choose the time for their next meeting or event. One person starts by clicking (or clicking and dragging down) all the times that they are available on a calendar grid that shows 2 1/2 weeks of time slots. When Is Good then provides a link to circulate to participants, who see the proposed times and click on when they are free.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
