<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>modern on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/modern/</link><description>Recent content in modern on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/modern/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Design Hotels</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/design-hotels/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/design-hotels/</guid><description>Love the bold use of white text reversed on black everywhere on this site, including the forms. http://www.designhotels.com/home</description></item><item><title>Park Avenue Armory</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/park-avenue-armory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/park-avenue-armory/</guid><description>The site for the Park Ave Armory, a non-profit venue for the arts in New York City is a clean, modern looking site with a simple 2-3 column grid that makes minimal use of graphics and presents information simply. There's small change in the logo and heading colors to add some variety and the navigation is clear.
http://www.armoryonpark.org/</description></item><item><title>Fancast</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/fancast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/fancast/</guid><description>The slight redesign of the surface on Fancast is a lovely updating that comes along with the site's latest release and new inventory of video content. The presentation layer is sporting the clean and glossy look of white boxes with pale drop shadows that I'm fond of, as well as using soft white bevels with enough restraint to look good without going over the top. The overall look is softer, and might slightly reference the minimalist Hulu, but clearly outsexes that site.</description></item><item><title>Museum of Arts and Design</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/museum-arts-and-design/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/museum-arts-and-design/</guid><description>My first impression when landing on the MAD Museum site is that there is a sense dynamic tension between the huge decorative shapes that make up the bold MAD logo and the clean layout, whose grid and the solid blocks of type and photos feel very modern. There is an appropriate feeling in that tension that works well to characterize a museum like this, that houses objects of such a wide range of styles and periods.</description></item><item><title>Jason Santa Maria</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/jason-santa-maria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/jason-santa-maria/</guid><description>Brooklyn visual designer Jason Santa Maria redesigns his site with a more flexible system that will allow him to adapt the design of each entry to suit the content. He notes that this is a redefined focus on art direction, and a magazine approach to content publishing outside of the typical confines of a CMS templating system.
I liked previous site design, and its reference to physical print. But I find that while the new visual style might refer back to the feeling of print, this visual style is more appealing to me as a someone who tends to be drawn to modern design.</description></item></channel></rss>