<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 16:16:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design Basics</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/graphic-design-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 16:16:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/graphic-design-basics/</guid>
      <description>Designers Ellen Lupton and Jennifer Cole Phillips, authors of the book Graphic Design, The New Basics&amp;nbsp; and Directors of the MFA Program at Maryland Institute College of Art offer a free 35 minute Skillshare course walking through 5 basic principles of graphic design. The course is a quick primer on design principles suited to various visual design projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skillshare Course on Rapid Wireframing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 11:17:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/skillshare-rapid-wireframing-course/</guid>
      <description>I published a free course for Balsamiq users on Skillshare. The course, Rapid Wireframing: Finding the Right Product Design, is designed for those new to Balsamiq, but also features some demonstration of new features like Quick Draw (using the mouse to block out wireframe zones) and Alternates (creating alternate versions of screens). If you&amp;rsquo;re a veteran user, you may be interested in checking that out, and updating to the latest version to take advantage of these useful new ways of working on projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code.org Program for K-5</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/codeorg-program-k-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/codeorg-program-k-5/</guid>
      <description>Code.org now has an elementary school program (Kindergarden - 5th grade), and Code Studio for the program looks like its modeled after the free MIT Scratch app, a visual tool that we used with our first son to introduce computer science fundamentals a few years ago. Good stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do you call...</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-do-you-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-do-you-call/</guid>
      <description>After repeatedly using a pattern of term + description to describe something, I wondered if other people in my Twitter-sphere used the same or similar language to describe a common artifact. My question started:
I was wondering if people used different terms to describe either drawings made in software or on paper that describe a screen view at a high level of abstraction that uses only lines and labels.
 Accompanied by this screenshot: It&#39;s interesting to learn that we use so many terms to describe essentially the same thing, although some of the confusion in this discussion might be with understanding what I meant by my question:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin on the Importance of Domain Knowledge</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/seth-godin-importance-domain-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/seth-godin-importance-domain-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin&#39;s blog often talks about where successful ideas come from, and in this post talks about bypassing the need to make huge leaps in innovation by synthesizing what we know and have learned from history, using Palm as the cautionary tale.
It&#39;s not enough to be aware of the domain you&#39;re working in, you need to understand it. Noticing things and being curious about how they work is the single most common trait I see in creative people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUGE Launches UX School for International Design Talent</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/huge-launches-ux-school-international-design-talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/huge-launches-ux-school-international-design-talent/</guid>
      <description>Huge has announced HUGE UX School, a graduate program for design talent interested in pursuing careers in User Experience.
Ten students, selected from hundreds of international applicants, will join HUGE’s UX team in New York, where they will receive three months of hands-on training and learn the fundamentals of UX design.
HUGE started the school to help prepare design professionals for successful careers in interaction design and to find and cultivate industry talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Wright on Game Play and Education</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/will-wright-game-play-and-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/will-wright-game-play-and-education/</guid>
      <description>Will Wright&amp;rsquo;s talk at the Summit on Science, Entertainment, and Education looks at how game play can be relevant to education. These are my notes from this talk.
How we process information Our basic model for processing and acting on data that we receive in the world looks something like this:
- Behavior
- Models (Predictive) ↑
- Schema (Abstractions) ↑
- Metaphors (Patterns) ↑
- Examples (Data) ↑</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NihongoUp</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nihongoup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/designs/submissions/nihongoup/</guid>
      <description>NihongoUp is a Japanese educational game &amp;amp; reviewing tool.
※ Learn hiragana and katakana in two weeks
※ Improve your kana IME reading speed
※ Review JLPT kanji and vocabulary in context
※ Learn to correctly use particles and counters
http://nihongoup.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So you&#39;re thinking about becoming a designer?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/so-youre-thinking-about-becoming-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/so-youre-thinking-about-becoming-designer/</guid>
      <description>Liz Danzico sought out the advice of digital designers and designer conspirers to ask them to respond to the following statement:
So you’re thinking about becoming a designer? If I could tell you only one thing about going into the field, my advice would be ___________ .
 The suggestions ranged from the philosophical to the pragmatic. Below are the ones that resounded with me. Focus on empathy and understanding problems  Being empathetic helps designers create things that move people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Design Reading Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-reading-recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/interaction-design-reading-recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Requested Reading Recommendations from the School of Visual Arts, MFA in Interaction Design program.
Upon the request of readers, we asked faculty to recommend books for an interaction design reading list. These could be landmark texts, underdogs, or critical reads, or stepping stones to other fields. The following is what resulted from our request, comprising in part: a sneak preview of what will be assigned in courses; what some consider to be cornerstone interaction design texts; and what some consider important connections to other fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Experience/Rosenfeld Media Webinars</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/smart-experiencerosenfeld-media-webinars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/smart-experiencerosenfeld-media-webinars/</guid>
      <description>Rosenfeld Media and Smart Experience begin their webinar series. Registration is open now for the 2 opening sessions with Luke Wroblewski and Indi Young.
http://www.rosenfeldmedia.com/webinars/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing New MFA in Interaction Design</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-new-mfa-interaction-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-new-mfa-interaction-design/</guid>
      <description>Liz Danzico announces the MFA program in Interaction Design at SVA in New York City, which she is to chair. Today, the School of Visual Arts in New York City is unveiling a project we’ve been working on for some time: a new Master of Fine Arts in Interaction Design, a program to launch in Fall of 2009. The program was jointly concepted by Steven Heller, co-founder (with Lita Talarico) of the renowned MFA Designer as Author program, and me over the last several months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>60&#43; Killer Open Courseware Collections for Web Designers</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/60-killer-open-courseware-collections-web-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/60-killer-open-courseware-collections-web-designers/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Hupp points us to over 60 free university courses available as podcasts/webcasts. The subject matter covers a broad range of topics of interest to web designers ranging from design theory to Internet culture.
Via SwissMiss</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>