<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gestures on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/gestures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gestures on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/gestures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Precomposed Touch Gestures</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/precomposed-touch-gestures/</guid>
      <description>Aureus Wade&#39;s Precomposed Touch Gestures are a set of touch-device gestures available as QuickTime animations for use in product demos or presentations. They&#39;ll work in your video editor, and Photoshop.
http://areuswade.com/precomposed-touch-gestures/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Multitouch Gesture Library and Illustrations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/open-source-multitouch-gesture-library-and-illustrations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/open-source-multitouch-gesture-library-and-illustrations/</guid>
      <description>GestureWorks, a multitouch framework for Flash, have published their our free gesture icon set, available to use and reuse under a CC license. You can download vector and raster versions, as well as a poster with all 200+ icons. They&#39;re also available on flickr as part of their educational project, Open Exhibits.
http://gestureworks.com/features/open-source-gestures/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touch Notation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/touch-notation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/touch-notation/</guid>
      <description>Touch Notation is a simple annotation system created by Matt Gemmell for documenting multi-touch gestures. It&#39;s an incredibly simple system when compared to the more literal annotation symbols that use hands, because the symbology can be quickly rendered in sketches as well as being used in wireframing libraries.
The Touch Notation page provides PSD, AI, and OmniGraffle templates. I&#39;ve additionally created a Balsamiq Mockups version of the system on Mockups To Go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GestureWorks Open Source Multitouch Gesture Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gestureworks-open-source-multitouch-gesture-library/</guid>
      <description>GestureWorks is a multitouch authoring environment for Flash and Flex that ships with a library of over 20 unique gestures. This gesture library is built upon an open source gesture framework, allowing developers to customize and extend the “gesture object” to create support for new gestures. The library is available for GestureWorks, and posters in PNG, PDF and AI format are also provided.
http://gestureworks.com/about/open-source-gesture-library/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gesturecons: Multi-Touch Icons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gesturecons-multi-touch-icons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gesturecons-multi-touch-icons/</guid>
      <description>Gesture icons created for wireframing touch interfaces. High resolution multi-touch vector icons, scalable and alterable (.pdf, .ai, .eps file types.) Free for personal use, and commercial licenses are available.
http://gesturecons.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kicker Studio: Touchscreen Stencils</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/kicker-studio-touchscreen-stencils/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/kicker-studio-touchscreen-stencils/</guid>
      <description>Gesture stencils based on drawings Rachel Glaves did for the book, &amp;quot;Designing Gestural Interfaces,&amp;quot; suitable for using in documentation. The drawings are of hands performing common touchscreen gestures like tap, slide, point, drag, pinch, and spread. Available in OmniGraffle, Illustrator, Photoshop, Fireworks and SVG formats.
http://www.kickerstudio.com/blog/2008/12/touchscreen-stencils/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BiDi Screen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/bidi-screen/</guid>
      <description>BiDi Screen was demonstrated at SIGGRAPH Asia this year. It is a thin, depth-sensing LCD for 3D interaction using light fields.
The BiDi Screen is an example of a new type of I/O device that possesses the ability to both capture images and display them. This thin, bidirectional screen extends the latest trend in LCD devices, which has seen the incorporation of photo-diodes into every display pixel. Using a novel optical masking technique developed at the Media Lab, the BiDi Screen can capture lightfield-like quantities, unlocking a wide array of applications from 3-D gesture interaction with CE devices, to seamless video communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Gestures Pattern Library</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-gestures-pattern-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/interactive-gestures-pattern-library/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Gestures Pattern Library is a promising looking wiki that collects gestural interface information and patterns, such as found on such devices as the iPhone and Wii.
http://www.interactivegestures.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Mobile Concept Video</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</guid>
      <description>Firefox Mobile Concept Video from Aza Raskin on Vimeo. Aza Raskin demonstrates a touch interface concept for a Firefox Mobile browser. The mocked up prototype includes features including spatial browsing of browser tabs, and touch gestures for summoning application menus.
http://azarask.in/blog/post/firefox-mobile-concept-video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publicis &amp; Hal Riney Webcam Gesture Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/publicis-hal-riney-webcam-gesture-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/publicis-hal-riney-webcam-gesture-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Publicis and Hal Riney site attempts to innovate navigation by replacing mouse input by detecting gestures the user makes against their webcam. Once the Flash file embeds your webcam video into the lower right corner of the page, a body outline is superimposed, and hot spots in the North-South-East-West quandrants are ghosted on the screen to show where you should hold or swipe your hand to navigate. Unfortunately the video ended up eating up resources on my machine to the point that the load times were painfully slow.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
