<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>use cases on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/use-cases/</link><description>Recent content in use cases on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/use-cases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Articulating Your Preferred Use Case</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/articulating-your-preferred-use-case/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/articulating-your-preferred-use-case/</guid><description>I like how Seth Godin states everything so clearly. Usually it's a pithy piece of advice about how to do the right thing, do right by your product, and thereby do right for the market by serving the right users with the product they want, and forgetting about trying to serve everyone else.
Here's one thought about really knowing your use case and putting it out front for the market to see, and letting it guide your conversation.</description></item><item><title>Gifting Feature at Nintendo</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/gifting-feature-nintendo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/gifting-feature-nintendo/</guid><description>Nintendo provides excellent illustrations to describe the gifting process on the Wii, using storyboards. The gifting page shows a table of contents at the top, for each use case: sending, receiving, confirmation, and faq. Clicking one of the use cases jumps the user down to the storyboard illustrating steps to complete each case. It's a simple, very clear, and visual. I wish every support site worked that way. Thanks to Boon Sheridan for the tip.</description></item><item><title>Cockburn's Basic Use Case Template</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/cockburns-basic-use-case-template/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/cockburns-basic-use-case-template/</guid><description>Just discovering that Dr. Alistair Cockburn, whose Writing Effective Use Cases book got me through many a project, has a wiki. On the wiki he offers some great resources like the basic use case templates. If you don't have the book, this is a pretty good substitute for understanding use case writing.
http://alistair.cockburn.us/index.php/Basic_use_case_template</description></item></channel></rss>