<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>social networking on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/social-networking/</link><description>Recent content in social networking on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/social-networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WhiteHouse 2.0</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/whitehouse-20/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/whitehouse-20/</guid><description>This selection of screens showcases the different social networking and video sites that the Whitehouse has set up. It's interesting to see how much continuity and consistency they're able to achieve given the design constraints imposed by the sites. Perhaps they're given the unique layout options Networks get on YouTube channels. But they couldn't do much with the Facebook page. The MySpace implementation is particularly impressive as an example of site skinning.</description></item><item><title>thesixytone</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/thesixytone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/thesixytone/</guid><description>Hard to believe that independent music sites continue to find ways to create social experiences around listening to music in the wake of huge, established communities like last.fm scrobbling and one to one experiences like muxtape playlist sharing. thesixtyone brings band and listener contribution together by letting musicians upload music, while listeners surface the tracks that deserve attention. It's a nice minimal design that focuses on the experience of playing the new and popular music people are listening to and favoriting.</description></item><item><title>Skittles</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/skittles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/skittles/</guid><description>Stealing a page out of Modernista's book, Skittles launches a site that uses social networking and media sites as its backdrop. Like the Modernista site, the effect is unexpected and attention getting. Choosing Twitter for this experiment was pretty gutsy. Whereas they could have more control over what goes on their YouTube and Facebook pages, the sentiment on Twitter isn't all too positive. You can check the live feed of Skittles tweets at Newstrendz, a new social trends site.</description></item><item><title>The Filter</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/filter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/filter/</guid><description>The Filter is an portal that aggregates music, TV, and video content. The project was started by Peter Gabriel and is looking to get amass a community of users who are willing to rate content so they can provide recommendations back to the community.
The site is looking to be a comprehensive consumer experience for all media, and essentially is pulling content from various sources and providing a single interface for adding recommendations and usage metadata to that content within the confines of this community.</description></item><item><title>Designer Pages</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/designer-pages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/designer-pages/</guid><description>http://www.designerpages.com</description></item></channel></rss>