<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Storyboards on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/storyboards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Storyboards on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/storyboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridley Scott Demystifies the Art of Storyboarding</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/ridley-scott-demystifies-art-storyboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/ridley-scott-demystifies-art-storyboarding/</guid>
      <description>Ridley Scott, director of Alien and Blade Runner, talks about the importance of fast thumbnail sketching and storyboards in helping him make movies. Scott discusses how storyboards help him capture the imagery of scenes, and how talking through storyboards prepare the creative team by establishing a direction for what they intend to create. Read more at the article on Open Culture.
Via Ian Smile.
http://www.openculture.com/2012/05/ridley_scott_demystifies_the_art_of_storyboarding.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhotoSketch Storyboard Application</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/photosketch-storyboard-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/photosketch-storyboard-application/</guid>
      <description>PhotoSketch is an online tool created by five students from Tsinghua University in China and the National University of Singapore. It creates storyboards from sketches by finding &amp;amp; stitching background images &amp;amp; item layers.
We present a system that composes a realistic picture from a simple freehand sketch annotated with text labels. The composed picture is generated by seamlessly stitching several photographs in agreement
with the sketch and text labels; these are found by searching the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireframe and Storyboard Notepads are Back: Now sold via Amazon</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-and-storyboard-notepads-are-back-now-sold-amazon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/wireframe-and-storyboard-notepads-are-back-now-sold-amazon/</guid>
      <description>The Wireframe and Storyboard notepads have been reprinted and are now selling exclusively via Amazon.com. The good news is, now that you ordered via Amazon, your order may qualify for Free Super Saver Shipping, and may be combined with other Amazon purchases in your cart. So if you spend $25 at Amazon, even by combining your purchase with other qualified products fulfilled via Amazon, your shipping will be free. Yay, you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Gmail Client Wireframe</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-gmail-client-wireframe/</guid>
      <description>I posted on Twitter about how frustrating it can be to have to use email. With every day that I use Twitter via Twhirl I become less and less interested in using email. So I moaned to my Twitter peeps about the pain I feel. Some people wanted to know what I wanted, so I responded with the ideal flow, using Mac OS X&amp;rsquo;s Growl alerting app as the starting point:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using the Storyboard Paper for Stop Motion Animation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/using-storyboard-paper-stop-motion-animation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/using-storyboard-paper-stop-motion-animation/</guid>
      <description>My son got his hands on the storyboard paper and started sketching a stop motion animation sequence in the cells. He just started his second session in a stop motion class. This is one of the things I used our printed graph paper for, but because that was printed in black/gray on our laser printer, I had a hard time knocking out the grid lines mixed in with his drawings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Konigi Store</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-konigi-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/announcing-konigi-store/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to announce the first of a series of products that I&amp;rsquo;m producing for creatives involved in design for the screen. The first 2 products are graph paper notepads formatted for user interface design and design of time-related sequences.
The Wireframe Graph Paper Notepad is made for visual designers, interaction designers, and information architects designing for the screen. The notepad has 50 sheets at 8 1&amp;frasl;2 x 11 inches on white 70# paper, glued on the left side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle UX Template Update</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-ux-template/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve updated the OmniGraffle web design template formerly hosted on my blog at urlgreyhot. The new UX template is now formatted for OmniGraffle Pro version 5. In this template you&amp;rsquo;ll find shared layers (masters) for a title page, wireframe, wireframe/storyboard hybrid, simple storyboard, and storyboard with notes. Guides and adherence to a regular grid make it easy to use. The doc is sized so you can work at 100%, and print at 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OmniGraffle Web Design Template Updated</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-web-design-template-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-web-design-template-updated/</guid>
      <description>I updated the OmniGraffle Web Design Template.
This web design template is for people who do wireframes and storyboards. The template was created for OmniGraffle Professional provides the basic layout for a design deliverable including the following master canvases: document title, section title, wireframe (portrait and landscape), storyboard, and blank. The wireframes were created at 950px wide with guides following the Blueprint CSS Grid system. Wireframes also have 2 small hairline marks around the 600px point to mark the approximate fold.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>