<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blog on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in blog on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:23:11 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Power of 100</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/power-of-100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:23:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/power-of-100/</guid><description>Leveraging the power of discipline, consistency and compounding in your creative work.</description></item><item><title>Rule 7</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/rule-7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:36:53 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/rule-7/</guid><description>My favorite Sister Corita Kent Rule</description></item><item><title>Creating Polished Wireframes in Balsamiq</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/creating-polished-wireframes-balsamiq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/creating-polished-wireframes-balsamiq/</guid><description>For Balsamiq users or anyone that bemoans handwritten fonts and sketchy wireframes, I wrote an article to show how to create polished wireframes in Balsamiq on our UX blog. It shows how to use the wireframe skin with a few base controls, and techniques to achieve a minimalist aesthetic. It&amp;rsquo;s meant for those who need to create client-ready deliverables, or for when the sketchy-skin gets in the way of communicating your ideas.</description></item><item><title>Jim Kalbach on Jazz as a Model for the Way Businesses Work</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/jim-kalbach-jazz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/jim-kalbach-jazz/</guid><description>Jim Kalbach talks about the improvisational model of Jazz as a metaphor for the way some businesses approach collaboration today. What was probably seen a few years ago as a radical way of structuring companies to organize around the work rather than using inflexible business units as boundaries, is now more commonplace.
To demonstrate what happens in the teamwork of a group of jazz performers, Kalbach assembled a group of musicians to perform a song they hadn&amp;rsquo;t played together before, and described how jazz performances &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; as a type of collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Hello Hugo: Konigi is now a Static Site</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/hello-hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/hello-hugo/</guid><description>After many years of being a Drupal user, from version 2 when I started iaslash.org to version 6 on this site, I&amp;rsquo;ve made the move from PHP/MySQL blog to full on static site. Here&amp;rsquo;s why and how I did it.
Choosing Static Site Generators In the past few years, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken a few sites backwards from Drupal and WordPress into the age of static sites. In many ways, it feels like going back to the beginning of my career, when I used Perl and Shell scripts to generate sites in my first job, and later to more sophisticated site generation using MovableType as a middle man.</description></item><item><title>Code.org Program for K-5</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/codeorg-program-k-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/codeorg-program-k-5/</guid><description>Code.org now has an elementary school program (Kindergarden - 5th grade), and Code Studio for the program looks like its modeled after the free MIT Scratch app, a visual tool that we used with our first son to introduce computer science fundamentals a few years ago. Good stuff.</description></item><item><title>Aral Balkan: I, Simulation</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/aral-balkan-i-simulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/aral-balkan-i-simulation/</guid><description>Aral Balkan’s “I, Simulation” talk about the current state of privacy and freedom in software and services is one the best presentations I’ve watched this year. Balkan talks about business models that focus on user data, and what that can mean to your "privacy." Watch the talk below, given at Open Exchange in Munich, Germany. The information you hand over using service providers like Facebook (think also Messenger, Whatsapp, Instagram) and Google (think also Gmail, Hangouts, Android Devices, Drive, Nest, Dropcam, and Fiber) is already being used to create simulations of you, and he likens this use to spyware.</description></item><item><title>Dedesign the Web 2</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/dedesign-web-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/dedesign-web-2/</guid><description>Head to Dedesign the Web and play name that website using wireframes. Courtesy of Designation.
http://dedesigntheweb.com/</description></item><item><title>Des Traynor: Product Strategy is About Saying No</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/des-traynor-product-strategy-about-saying-no/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/des-traynor-product-strategy-about-saying-no/</guid><description>The devil runs UX workshops for idle hands, and he comes up with bad features. This is Des Traynor's lightning talk at Business of Software in 2013. He did an extended version of this in 2014, but the pecha kucha version gets to the heart of the topic. http://vimeo.com/81544164</description></item><item><title>Experimenting with the IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/experimenting-ipevo-interactive-whiteboard/</guid><description>I got an IPEVO Interactive Whiteboard System ($149 retail price) to demo and did a first little experiment. The product consists of a video sensor and interactive pen. You have to have a projector as well. Here's a super rough demo I made for my team at Balsamiq to show how it would work using Balsamiq Mockups.
While the demo is pretty rough given the 15 minutes I gave myself to set up and record with my phone, it's pretty interesting to consider the possibilities for whiteboarding with wireframing software, if you're so inclined.</description></item><item><title>What If DJ Controllers Had Built In Screens?</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/what-if-dj-controllers-had-built-screens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/what-if-dj-controllers-had-built-screens/</guid><description>This is a cool design challenge that showed up on DJ Tech Tools' blog to mock up DJ controllers. DJ gear vendor Numark is reported to be releasing a controller with a screen. That's kind of interesting, because it could potentially let digital DJs that use them close their computer screen and focus on performing.
While there are CDJs that already have color LCDs to preview deck track information, midi controllers are largely comprised of faders, buttons, knobs, toggle switches, jog wheels, and touch sensitive strips.</description></item><item><title>UI / UX Design Interviews on Medium</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/ui-ux-design-interviews-medium/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/ui-ux-design-interviews-medium/</guid><description>Frank Rapacciuolo is writing a series of Interviews of User Interface &amp;amp; User Experience Designers in a collection at Medium. In the interviews he asks people about their background, what they tell people they do, what a typical work day looks like, and gets opinions on several UX topics including the impact of design on society and where they stand on jumping directly into visual design.
Read the interviews at Medium.</description></item><item><title>99u Master Class: Irene Au on Mindfulness Techniques to Make You a Better Creative</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-master-class-irene-au-mindfulness-techniques-make-you-better-creative/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-master-class-irene-au-mindfulness-techniques-make-you-better-creative/</guid><description>Irene Au was a design and user experience leader at Google, Yahoo, and Netscape. She's now a partner at Khosla Ventures, and has been focussing on her yoga instruction in the past few years. She led a session at the 99u Conference to discuss mindfulness mediation techniques for creatives.
Au talked about different methods of mindfulness mediation practice. Mindfulness, in general, is a state of awareness or consciousness of the present moment.</description></item><item><title>99u Conference Notes: The Way We Work</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-conference-notes-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-conference-notes-way-we-work/</guid><description>These is part 1 of my notes from day 1 of the 99u, which began with some great talks about how we work. I'll post part 2 for the talks on how we lead in a later entry.
This set of talks featured Joshua Klein talking about the power of networks, Sarah Lewis talking about the importance of personal space, and Wendy MacNaughton talking about the power of listening.
Joshua Klein Joshua Klein is a hacker/technologist.</description></item><item><title>99u Conference Notes: Quirky Studio Visit with Ben Kaufman</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-conference-notes-quirky-studio-visit-ben-kaufman/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/99u-conference-notes-quirky-studio-visit-ben-kaufman/</guid><description>A group of 99u attendees had a visit with Ben Kaufman, the CEO/founder of product development company Quirky, who gave us a look into how his company uses crowd-sourcing to deliver products. Here are some of my notes from that visit. More 99u notes to follow.
Kaufman got his start as an inventor in high school when he made a lanyard to hold an iPod shuffle. The company he started to ship this product later morphed into Mophie, the maker of the JuiceBox battery case.</description></item></channel></rss>