<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Local Navigation on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/local-navigation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Local Navigation on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/local-navigation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Breadcrumb Tab</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo&#39;s hybrid tab/breadcrumb navigation is one of my favorite approaches to global and local navigation. This navigation interface answers a few nagging questions that an interface designer might ask. &#34;How do I present the user with an interface that provides focus on the area they&#39;ve navigated to, while providing a path back or to other main areas of interest?&#34;
What&#39;s interesting here is that they provide a row of primary navigation tabs at the top level, and replace that with a hybrid tab/breadcrumb once the user makes the decision to drill down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IKEA Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ikea-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ikea-navigation/</guid>
      <description>IKEA&#39;s navigation menus feature a simple navigation bar on the top of the layout. The most important entry points are shown as is a button for new items. A drop down menu at right for the rest of the top level entry points. Within each section, tree navigation interfaces are provided for browsing more deeply within the section.
1. Home page.2. &amp;quot;Living Room&amp;quot; selected in the global navigation. Local navigation appears in the left sidebar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN.com Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnn-com-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnn-com-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The CNN News portal provides a very dense global navigation header that&#39;s got quite a bit going on, but succeeds in drawing out the main entry points for news, featured or promoted points of interest, language/edition preference setting, search, and even a sticky alert area for late breaking news. It even borrows the idea of hot topics navigation per section from Newsvine, which allows for a more variable set of local navigation based on what&#39;s happening now, rather than on a rigid top-down IA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tork Revolution Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tork-revolution-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tork-revolution-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Tork Revolution site features a Flash global/local navigation system that appears conventional on the surface, but positions the navigation elements in unconventional places on the page, using size, position, and color to indicate hierarchy.
1. The home page.2. Clicking, Foodservice, one of the main entry points in the global nav pulls that word out of the nav and re-positions it at the top of the page.3. Following a link to a sub-page, we are now viewing &amp;quot;Foodservice &amp; Kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>