<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>embedding on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/embedding/</link><description>Recent content in embedding on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/embedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Filter Embedding Media in Comments</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-embedding-media-comments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-embedding-media-comments/</guid><description>The Wall feature of user profiles in The Filter allows users to create entries with recommendations as embedded content. Users enter their comment and search for anything from an artist to a track to find content to recommend. The selected content is embedded in the comment to be played in the media player.
The interface is similar to those provided in the MTV recommendations app on Facebook and the Video embedding control in Gawker Media comments.</description></item><item><title>Last.fm Top Content Charts Module</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-top-content-charts-module/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-top-content-charts-module/</guid><description>Last.fm's top artists and top songs content module appears on user profiles. The module shows a list of top content, with options in tabs to change time slice. The content module also provides options to modify settings and embed the content on an external blog or social network site.
1. Default tab, showing last 7 days of top artists with Last.fm's signature bar chart for number of plays. 2. Last 6 months tab.</description></item><item><title>Gawker Media Video Comments</title><link>https://konigi.com/interfaces/gawker-media-video-comments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/interfaces/gawker-media-video-comments/</guid><description>Gawker Media's weblogs provide a simple method for including YouTube videos in comments. The example shown here is from the Consumerist blog. Users find a video in YouTube, copy and paste the permalink URL into their comment on the blog, and the video is embedded into their published comment. This method of transcluding content is popular in wikis, but the implementation usually involves using a special syntax. Gawker's method of using translating the permalink is dead simple.</description></item></channel></rss>