<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>communication on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in communication on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Give it five minutes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/give-it-five-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/give-it-five-minutes/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m certainly no stranger to being opinionated and argumentative. I&#39;ve put my foot in my mouth a few times by pushing back on others&#39; ideas, and am well aware that being quick to react can be detrimental. The older I get, the more I realize how little I know and how much more time I need to spend thinking after listening, before I open my mouth or start to type to respond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dogs on Design: Danzico and Lucy</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/dogs-design-danzico-and-lucy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dogs-design-danzico-and-lucy/</guid>
      <description>Core77&#39;s Sarah Cox wrote a lovely article after talking with Liz Danzico about her thoughts on interaction design, life with her dog Lucy and communicating simply and humanly. Below is her summary of what dogs can teach us about interaction design.
1. It&#39;s important to know who is in charge. Just like training a pet, a designer need to establish a rapport with clients that mixes trust and expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shades of Grey: Wireframes as Thinking Device</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/shades-grey-wireframes-thinking-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/shades-grey-wireframes-thinking-device/</guid>
      <description>Will Evans writes for UX Mag about his process for creating wireframes, or more precisely how he uses wireframes for ideation and problem solving. Will breaks his design process into three phases: divergence, transformation, and convergence.
This seems similar to a common theme I come across when designers talk about their process--framing/ideating, reframing/ideating, selection/refining. Buxton also refers to this, citing Stuart Pugh&#39;s idea by illustrating the expanding/contracting nature of a designer&#39;s concept selection, which I find easy to map to sketching-wireframing as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabble Client for Yammer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/links/gabble-client-yammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/links/gabble-client-yammer/</guid>
      <description>Gabble is a native Mac OS X client for Yammer, the micro-messaging application for companies.
http://erikhinterbichler.com/software/gabble/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
