<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>drag to select on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/drag-to-select/</link>
    <description>Recent content in drag to select on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/drag-to-select/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slavery Footprint Form: Drag to Select</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</guid>
      <description>The Slavery Footprint website allows consumers to visualize how their consumption habits are connected to modern-day slavery.
They use a set of forms in a wizard-like survey to come up with an estimate of the number of slaves that are impacted by your behavior.
This section of the survey asks the user to drag the icons for items that describe the kind of house and car they own or rent into a drop area in the home above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is Good</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</guid>
      <description>When Is Good is a tool that does one thing&amp;#8212;helps a group of people choose the time for their next meeting or event. One person starts by clicking (or clicking and dragging down) all the times that they are available on a calendar grid that shows 2 1/2 weeks of time slots. When Is Good then provides a link to circulate to participants, who see the proposed times and click on when they are free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QUEEKY Ratings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/queeky-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/queeky-ratings/</guid>
      <description>QUEEKY is a drawing community that allows users to draw pictures in their browsers using the site&#39;s flash application. Users can rate the drawings using a rating scale ranging from 1 (Hmmm) to 10 (A masterpiece!). Scores on the low side are color coded to a cool violet color and on the high side towards a hotter pink/fuschia.
1. Low rating2. High rating3. Full page http://www.queeky.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MotionBox Video Player Clipping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</guid>
      <description>Motionbox provides a nice interface for creating clips of videos they host. Along with Hulu, Motionbox is among the first to introduce the idea of clipping portions of web video. However, Motionbox outshines Hulu in terms of usability. Clipping is a simple operation that mimics the video selection paradigm users have become comfortable with on video editing software. And unlike Hulu, Motionbox provides instant feedback about where the start and end markers lie, by moving the video playhead with the position of the markers as you adjust the clip size.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
