<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bold on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/bold/</link><description>Recent content in bold on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/bold/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unfold</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unfold/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/unfold/</guid><description>The site for Norwegian studio Unfold has some interesting &amp;amp; unexpected layout with 45 degree angle text and blocks of color, and panning and sliding interface elements.
http://unfold.no/</description></item><item><title>Dom Goodrum</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/dom-goodrum/</guid><description>Portfolio showcasing the favourite projects of designer Dom Goodrum.
http://www.domgoodrum.com</description></item><item><title>By the People: the Election of Barack Obama</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/people-election-barack-obama/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/people-election-barack-obama/</guid><description>Promoting the documentary &amp;quot;By The People: The Election of Barack Obama&amp;quot;, this site uses full screen flash and full-screen scaling images to get across some of the passion of the actual campaign.
http://www.myobamadvd.com</description></item><item><title>whnwlnd</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/whnwlnd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/whnwlnd/</guid><description>Bold type (fantastic use of Cufon) and a great looking portfolio of UX work from this Los Angeles studio.
http://www.whenweland.com/</description></item><item><title>Gatorade</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/gatorade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/gatorade/</guid><description>The Gatorade site redesign accompanies the drink maker's rebranding and the bold type of the product names on every bottle. Every drink name is an active message about excelling in sports and the video loop that runs in the background of product and athlete pages suffuses the site with the imagery of athletes kicking ass. A product filter allows users to view by product name or nutritient.
http://www.gatorade.com/#/products/tiger</description></item><item><title>WebWork Design Studio Collection</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/webwork-design-studio-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/webwork-design-studio-collection/</guid><description>Randjelovic Milos's portfolio really can't be capture very well in screenshots, so you should check out the site to experience the perfect transitions between pages. Beautiful bold type and simple presentation.
http://www.webwork-studio.org/</description></item><item><title>Tweetizen</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/tweetizen/</guid><description>Tweetizen is a simple web-based tool designed to help you filter the daily influx of tweets, and easily embed twitter groups to your own website. http://www.tweetizen.com/</description></item><item><title>IDEO</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/ideo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/ideo/</guid><description>The redesigned IDEO site has been sitting in a browser tab for a few weeks now because it just felt like one of those things I needed to mull over before writing about. It's one of the few sites this year that just took me by surprise. In short, the deep treasure trove of content unleashed in this redesign is a huge departure from the tightly constrained and minimalist prior design.</description></item><item><title>The Heads of State</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/heads-state/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/heads-state/</guid><description>The Heads of State are a 2 person design studio in Brooklyn and Seattle. Their recently redesigned site showcases the strong portfolio of print work on projects including book covers, magazine illustrations, and corporate identity. I love the simple, powerful covers on the Rosenfeld Media books, and after diving into their site, I think I'd love even more to hire them in the future.
https://www.theheadsofstate.com/</description></item><item><title>256TM</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/256tm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/256tm/</guid><description>What could be more appropriate for a font foundry than to use its own large, capitalized type as the focus, form, and interface for the design. 25TM is modern, minimalist, and makes its statement firmly&amp;#8212;type is the message, period.
http://www.256tm.com/</description></item><item><title>NATIONAL TELEVISION</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/national-television/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/national-television/</guid><description>National Television is a video and film production studio in California. It's portfolio site is among the best examples of the use of bold typography as the primary element that defines both the form and interface. The look is clean and undeniably confident.
http://www.natl.tv/</description></item><item><title>The Show</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/show/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/show/</guid><description>Big bold typography that functions as navigation, full screen photography that functions as backdrop, a simple message, and a lasting product that does justice to live music performances and the people who love them.
http://www.theshowlive.com/</description></item><item><title>Daisy Balloon</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/daisy-balloon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/submissions/daisy-balloon/</guid><description>Daisy is an artist that does incredible things with balloons. The site presently shows some amazing dresses fabricated with the long balloons you'd usually only see in the form of little animals, but Daisy elevates the art to design amazing clothing that could be called haute couture. I could easily imagine these things being made out of a less ephemeral material and being worn, albeit a bit uncomfortably.</description></item><item><title>Jason Santa Maria</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/jason-santa-maria/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/jason-santa-maria/</guid><description>Brooklyn visual designer Jason Santa Maria redesigns his site with a more flexible system that will allow him to adapt the design of each entry to suit the content. He notes that this is a redefined focus on art direction, and a magazine approach to content publishing outside of the typical confines of a CMS templating system.
I liked previous site design, and its reference to physical print. But I find that while the new visual style might refer back to the feeling of print, this visual style is more appealing to me as a someone who tends to be drawn to modern design.</description></item><item><title>SOFAMADE</title><link>https://konigi.com/designs/sofamade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/designs/sofamade/</guid><description>SOFAMADE are a design and development shop in Arlington, Texas. What I liked about their site most was the bold front page colors and intro paragraph with inline links and the wide 2 and 3 column grids that varied from page to page. The layout of the text-heavy Approach page and the Portfolio pages is clean and easy to read, although I thought the Approach pages did a better job at indicating the hierarchy of page elements.</description></item></channel></rss>