<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>faceted navigation on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/faceted-navigation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in faceted navigation on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/faceted-navigation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beatport Pro Music Store</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/beatport-pro-music-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/beatport-pro-music-store/</guid>
      <description>Beatport&#39;s Pro app for the Mac offers a shopping experience that&#39;s tailored for the way DJs shop for music. The app lets users analyze their music (tracks, sounds, and playlists) to prepare sets and add music to their playlists. Here are some of the elements of the version 2 interface related to shopping in the app.
Beatport comes close to the experience of shopping in a record store, breaking down music into genres and sub-genres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoMA Exhibition/Collection Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moma-exhibitioncollection-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moma-exhibitioncollection-browser/</guid>
      <description>MoMA&#39;s exhibition and collection browser provides faceted drill-down of the museum collection&#39;s image library using a mega drop-down menu. Each facet provides the ability to select multiple terms, so the user may select multiple authors, departments or decades, for instance. Executing the search displays the narrowed set of results in an image gallery that can be toggled thumbnail, slideshow, list, and single artist views. Sorting options and image matte colors may also be selected by the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for Faceted Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/designing-faceted-search/</guid>
      <description>Stephanie Lemieux discusses issues to consider when designing faceted navigation interfaces for search in the latest UIE newsletter.
Faceted search is a very popular and powerful solution when done well; it allows users to deconstruct a large set of results into bite-size pieces and navigate based on what’s important to them. But faceted search by itself is not necessarily going to make your users lives easier. You need to understand your users’ mental models (how they seek information), test your assumptions about how they will interpret your terms and categories and spend time refining your approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post/Evri Related Content Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/washington-postevri-related-content-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/washington-postevri-related-content-module/</guid>
      <description>The Washington Post uses a related content widget created by Evri that indexes content using person, place, and thing (subject) facets and allows the Post to display a list of related content beneath news. The widget, which is actually a bit of SVG/VML and JavaScript, provides a small visualization of topics in the article, and allows the user to do some filtering of the related content. Navigating to topic pages provides a complete filtering view for exploring and narrowing related content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zappos Search Results Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</guid>
      <description>The Zappos&#39; search engine provides a nice results filtering interfaces that presents the user with facets for refining their search. The user can click on the terms at the top of the search results page to narrow the set, and a breadcrumb trail shows the selections they&#39;ve made. Each term in the breadcrumb provides a checkbox to remove any one of those selections and broaden their search.
1. Users run a search using the site&#39;s global search box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FanSnap Search Results Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fansnap-search-results-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fansnap-search-results-filtering/</guid>
      <description>FanSnap is an event ticket search site that provides faceted results filtering. Users simply enter an upcoming event, and FanSnap returns a list of available tickets from vendors like StubHub, provides filtering by price, seating area, and ticket vendor. If a venue diagram is available seats are overlaid over the venue&#39;s seating chart. Users can sort and star/favorite available tickets in their &#34;short list&#34;, and then click a link to purchase the tickets at the ticket vendor&#39;s site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Faceted Browsing on Konigi</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/better-faceted-browsing-konigi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/better-faceted-browsing-konigi/</guid>
      <description>About 10 years ago I participated in the daily indexing of news articles as part of my job designing a digital library. During graduate study for the MLS my concentration was actually on information retrieval and classification, so I was interested in doing the job and understanding the content in order to know how to make it useful to users. Customers would get this information via the web site, by email, and in newsletters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OfficeMax Faceted Search Results</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-faceted-search-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-faceted-search-results/</guid>
      <description>OfficeMax search provides faceted filtering of results using controls in a left sidebar. Facets such as category, brand, and price show 5 terms per facet, allow the user to expand to see more terms if any, add and remove facet selections in any order. A breadcrumb trail is also provided to show the selections made, and can be used to clear all selections at once by clicking on the first term in the trail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Interface Implementations of Faceted Browsing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-implementations-faceted-browsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/user-interface-implementations-faceted-browsing/</guid>
      <description>Mike Padilla offers up a description of facets and their use on web sites for browsing and filtering. He defines the types of interactions or behaviors that are typically found on sites with faceted browsing, describes what happens in terms of the system when you apply filters, and shows some examples of faceted browsing in use on sites including my favorite, Nike.com.
http://www.digital-web.com/articles/user_interface_implementations_of_faceted_browsing/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indeed Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/indeed-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/indeed-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Job search engine Indeed offers faceted search filtering in their results. Facets include useful filtering criteria such as job title, salary range estimate, company, location, and job type. Filters beneath any facet may be selected at any point while viewing the results, and removed in an ad-hoc manner regardless of the order selected. Users may also remove all filtering to return to original results.
1. Search interface.2. Search results with filters on left column which can be hidden/collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kayak Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kayak-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kayak-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Kayak provided one of the earliest examples of using AJAX to provide data filtering controls and live refinement or filtering of results. Their slider controls remain one of the best examples of how AJAX can be used to make filtering visual and intuitive. Sliders allow users to narrow down search criteria including flight duration, takeoff/landing time, and price. 1. Default filtering controls.2. Search results page.3. Search results after adjusting search filters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roost Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/roost-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/roost-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Roost is a real estate search engine that provides full MLS listings. Their AJAX search refining filters are very similar to those provided by Kayak&#39;s travel search. The slider controls provide a visual method for narrowing down search criteria and results are updated immediately.
1. Default filtering controls.2. Search results page.3. Search results after adjusting search filters. http://roost.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Nike Store provides an excellent faceted navigation for narrowing product listings by sensible facets including gender, product type, sport, color, and price. The site skins the faceted classification tool provided by Endeca, which allows the user to select a product attribute of interest under any facet, and continually provides feedback about the attributes in other facets that can be used to narrow your choice of products down. Nike&#39;s Flash-based implementation is appropriate and useful, and ranks among the best examples of faceted navigation you will find on either commercial or academic databases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Hulu provides a nice faceted approach for browsing clips and episodes.
1. Filtering navigation in left sidebar2. All facets exposed; &amp;quot;Clip&amp;quot; selected under Type facet3. &amp;quot;Comedy&amp;quot; selected under genre facet; Selecting &amp;quot;show more&amp;quot; expands to show other choices under facet4. &amp;quot;NBC&amp;quot; selected under Source facet http://hulu.com/videos/views/thumbs/all/clip/all/all/today/1</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
