<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interface on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/categories/interface/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interface on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://konigi.com/categories/interface/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest Mobile Radial Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-mobile-radial-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-mobile-radial-menus/</guid>
      <description>Pinterest&#39;s mobile app displays a radial menu if you tap on an image. The menu items are for functions that are also available using the icons and buttons in the top of the UI for allowing you to pin, like, or send the image.
Screencast / Video http://www.pinterest.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest Tag Search and Suggestions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-tag-search-and-suggestions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-tag-search-and-suggestions/</guid>
      <description>Pinterest&#39;s search feature shows tag and board suggestions in the auto-completion list. Select terms/tags to display, and a horizontal list (accordion) of correlating tags to refine or narrow your your search are displayed below the search box.
Screencast / Video
http://www.pinterest.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Fave Animation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tumblr-fave-animation/</guid>
      <description>This is a small animation of the heart/broken heart that is shown when favoriting or unfaving a Tumblr post in the mobile app.
Screencast / Video
https://www.tumblr.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mention Call To Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mention-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mention-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Mention.com&#39;s Success Stories section uses this great phrase to introduce the Proof in the drip pan at the bottom of the page.
&amp;quot;They also started with a free trial.&amp;quot; Short and persuasive copy that makes an otherwise common CTA more compelling.
1. Intro text, subdued company logos for the proof (so as not to compete with the CTA), and bold red call to action button to create your first alert and start a free trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cotton Bureau Off-Canvas Checkout</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cotton-bureau-canvas-checkout/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cotton-bureau-canvas-checkout/</guid>
      <description>Cotton Bureau uses the off-canvas pattern to slide steps of the checkout flow into the screen from the right, as the product page and previous steps slide off screen to the left.
I like how this implies the forward movement through the checkout process a bit better than the cart workflows that use vertically arranged collapsing panels.
1. Product page.2. After adding product to cart, the cart panel slides in from right, and product panel slides off canvas to left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beatport Pro Music Store</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/beatport-pro-music-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/beatport-pro-music-store/</guid>
      <description>Beatport&#39;s Pro app for the Mac offers a shopping experience that&#39;s tailored for the way DJs shop for music. The app lets users analyze their music (tracks, sounds, and playlists) to prepare sets and add music to their playlists. Here are some of the elements of the version 2 interface related to shopping in the app.
Beatport comes close to the experience of shopping in a record store, breaking down music into genres and sub-genres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp Form Focus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-form-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-form-focus/</guid>
      <description>This is a cute interaction for the input focus and data validation on Basecamp&#39;s registration form. The smiling character illustration on the left points out which steps are in focus. When an invalid value is entered, the character makes a concerned face and the pointing hand stays fixed on the highlighted input.
The illustrations on the site do a great job of making you feel like this isn&#39;t &amp;quot;business as usual,&amp;quot; which is the reason for switching to Basecamp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geeklist Sign Up Password Strength</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/geeklist-sign-password-strength/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/geeklist-sign-password-strength/</guid>
      <description>Geeklist&#39;s sign up form tells you how secure your password is by indicating how long it would take to crack. Sounds much more understandable and convincing than the typical weak/strong message.
1. A really strong password.2. A dictionary word is weak. 3. Better, but still weak. The messaging may be convincing enough to get users to think about their choice.
https://geekli.st/signup</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Delete Timer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-delete-timer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-delete-timer/</guid>
      <description>YouTube puts up 2 speed bumps when you try to delete a video from the video manager. This technique slows down the user about to peform a destructive action, and protects them from inadvertently deleting content.
1. Selecting Delete action shows dialog confirming action.2. A second confirmation dialog requires confirmation, but the Delete button is disabled until the countdown timer runs out.
https://www.youtube.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Wine Agency Date Picker</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/la-wine-agency-date-picker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/la-wine-agency-date-picker/</guid>
      <description>I like the design of the La Wine Agency site. The beautiful large type on the off-white paper reminds me of letterpress cards.
One thing I loved immediately was the age gate, which asks you when you were born so you can get through to shop for wine.
Not only is the big text for the month/day/year picker friendly, but that goofy headlines and &amp;quot;When were you last born?&amp;quot; copy is hilarious, if you catch the joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinterest Switches</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-switches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pinterest-switches/</guid>
      <description>Sure you can use a checkbox to enter binary values in a form, but Pinterest goes the hi-fi route and instead uses sexy switches, a la iOS controls, in their email settings form.

http://pinterest.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zerply Email Notifications Settings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zerply-email-notifications-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zerply-email-notifications-settings/</guid>
      <description>Simple things appeal to me. I like the simplicity of being able to usubscribe immediately. Zerply goes the extra mile and not only gives me options to never get email notifications via links in the notification itself, but also to change the frequency of updates. Nice.
1. Email notification from Zerply.2. Update frequency settings in the bottom. Click and you&amp;rsquo;re done.
http://zerply.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photojojo Captcha</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photojojo-captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photojojo-captcha/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I know you hate captchas and they&#39;re riddled with problems. Why do it if you don&#39;t have to? But if you do it, at least make it a brainless action like this.
1. Click to answer the captcha challenge.
http://photojojo.com/contact/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slavery Footprint Form: Drag to Select</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-drag-select/</guid>
      <description>The Slavery Footprint website allows consumers to visualize how their consumption habits are connected to modern-day slavery.
They use a set of forms in a wizard-like survey to come up with an estimate of the number of slaves that are impacted by your behavior.
This section of the survey asks the user to drag the icons for items that describe the kind of house and car they own or rent into a drop area in the home above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slavery Footprint Form: Sliders</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-sliders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/slavery-footprint-form-sliders/</guid>
      <description>The Slavery Footprint website allows consumers to visualize how their consumption habits are connected to modern-day slavery.
They use a set of forms in a wizard-like survey to come up with an estimate of the number of slaves that are impacted by your behavior.
The forms use large controls and clear visual feedback using illustrations. Each step of the form is a full screen shown in linear progression.
1. Select male or female child to add.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroku Price Estimator</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/heroku-price-estimator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/heroku-price-estimator/</guid>
      <description>The price estimator for web application hosting provider Heroku uses sliders and switches to generate a price for your plan. Select the number of process and database options and the cost estimate updates dynamically.

http://www.heroku.com/pricing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrivals, Cultured Code Development Status</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/arrivals-cultured-code-development-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/arrivals-cultured-code-development-status/</guid>
      <description>I love this idea. Cultured Code shows the development status on their projects as a flight arrivals display.

http://culturedcode.com/status/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelley Blue Book Mad Libs Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kelley-blue-book-mad-libs-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kelley-blue-book-mad-libs-form/</guid>
      <description>The Kelley Blue Book features Mad Libs-style inline form elements for its contact form. The contact form, which was previously displayed with right-aligned labels adjacent to to left aligned fields, is now displayed as an inline form with &amp;quot;fill in the blanks&amp;quot; style prompts for input.

http://www.kbb.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUBBLEWOOD Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/bubblewood-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/bubblewood-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Interesting bubble/cloud of links make up the front page of this retail site.  Screencast / Video
http://www.bubblewood.com/index_fr.htm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebMynd Header and Footer</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/webmynd-header-and-footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/webmynd-header-and-footer/</guid>
      <description>The Webmynd site features some clever scrolling behaviors, slowly spinning the &#34;easier, beautiful...&#34; text and fading out the header and footer as you reach the edges of the page.
Screencast / Video http://webmynd.com/html/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moof Login and Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moof-login-and-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moof-login-and-registration/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m sure some might dislike the use of the bottom-border inputs here, but I&#39;m a big fan of fill-in-the-blank forms and the conversational copy used in this login and registration form on this social music site.
 http://moof.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panic Shopping Cart</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/panic-shopping-cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/panic-shopping-cart/</guid>
      <description>Panic, the Mac software company that makes Coda and Transmit, has an apparel store with fun shopping cart behaviors that mimic the Mac&#39;s dock. The apparel store shows t-shirt listings, and a little cart dock at the bottom of the page that invites visitors to drag t-shirts down into it to add to cart. Clicking and dragging shows the ghosted t-shirt moving with the cursor until it snaps into the dock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JS-Kit ECHO Commenting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/js-kit-echo-commenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/js-kit-echo-commenting/</guid>
      <description>JS-Kit&#39;s ECHO is a service that can be embedded in CMS as a replacement for commenting, and provides a real-time stream of diggs, tweets, comments. The interface, at first blush, looks a bit like an email composition form, with From, To, and Body Fields. Selecting the From drop down menu shows options for logging in your identity via JS-Kit or a third party social networking API. The To: field adds &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTunes First Time User Welcome Messages</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-first-time-user-welcome-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-first-time-user-welcome-messages/</guid>
      <description>First time users of iTunes are presented with instruction screens for adding media to their library. The simple instruction panels provide links to buy media or to watch video tutorials showing how to purchase, import, and use the software.
1. First time user panel for Music with links to download or import media, and watch tutorials.2. First time user panel for TV Shows.3. Tutorial video from Help app that appears when user clicks the &amp;quot;Watch the tutorial&amp;quot; links in first time user panels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kontain Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kontain-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kontain-search/</guid>
      <description>Kontain is a social media site for sharing photos, video, and music. The site provides a large, simple search form at the top of most aggregate pages, and a pared down version of the search form in the upper right corner of single asset pages. A pull down menu to the right of the search input displays options for searching everything, or restricting to media types, users, or just updates. The options are displayed as circles, and should function as radios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Magazine Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-magazine-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-magazine-search/</guid>
      <description>New York Magazine provides a site search form in the header with options to limit the scope of search, and features advanced filtering options on results page. The results page is simple on the surface, but provides powerful filtering options in the sidebar. The search strategy is shown with actions for removing terms from the search or clear all.
I found some of the behaviors on filtering options to be inconsistent with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iStockphoto Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/istockphoto-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/istockphoto-search/</guid>
      <description>iStockphoto takes a rather approach to search that offers plenty of options. When the user is logged out, they&#39;re presented with a search form on the front page with options that appear when the input is in focus. The user may then select typical options, e.g. size under photos, number of credits under illustration, format for video. On the results page, a simpler search form is displayed at the top of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fever Progressive Disclosure</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fever-progressive-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fever-progressive-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>The Fever RSS news reader provides some useful progressive disclosure/enhancement behaviors that hide features until they are needed. Many of the primary features are also provided as keyboard shortcuts. The resulting experience provides a subtle and minimalist aesthetic without compromising features.
1. The initial view of the app shows groups of items and the pages linking to them. The main navigator is shown in left sidebar.2. Selecting a category (&amp;quot;UX&amp;quot; in this example) displays a second column for browsing feeds in that category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin.com Header</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virgincom-header/</guid>
      <description>The Virgin.com redesign sports a header that provides a boatload of functionality using mega fly out menus: locale selection, micro-site navigation, registration, login, and newsletter signup. I like that they make these options readily available wherever you are on the site. The longer drop downs like the registration form, for example, seem a little long for users on smaller screens, e.g. netbooks. 1. The global navigation bar provides mega drop downs with sub-nodes and links to their subsidiary companies that provide products and services under each category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holland Festival Program Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/holland-festival-program-browser/</guid>
      <description>The Holland Festival provides a program browser/calendar that provides an AJAX interface for viewing over 3 weeks of events in a grid. Drop down menus are provided to narrow or expand by genre, locale and route. A single toggle highlights featured events. And a sliding selector, which can be dragged to move the range left and right and with handles to narrow or expand the window, allows you to filter the days to be shown in the grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EA Microsite Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ea-microsite-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ea-microsite-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Game maker EA provides access to their network of microsites from EA.com and offers cross-site navigation via a toolbar that is positioned at the bottom or top of each site. I like the design of the navigation on the main site and the Sports sites. But the navigation is inconsistent in position, visual design, and behavior from site to site. The Pogo site doesn&#39;t have a micro-site navigator at all, so ironically, you have to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Microsite Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-microsite-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-microsite-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Nike.com&#39;s main site provides entry to a host of micro-sites for each sport or product family, but a consistent navigation model is provided across all microsites. A primary navigation widget is provided in the Nike Swoosh button, which reveals a list of a few of the most popular microsite destinations. A &#34;More&#34; link epxands the list to show all of the microsites.
1. Users click the Nike Swoosh logo to navigate across the Nike space to other microsites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Video Hero</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-video-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-video-hero/</guid>
      <description>Nike has been using a video player as hero graphic in the main Nike.com site. The player features large buttons for play controls and link to microsite (the button with the right angle quotes), star rating, playhead, low/high resolution and bandwidth switcher, a time elapse countdown, volume bars, and save/share options.
 http://www.nike.com/nikeos/p/nike/en_US/?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layar: Mobile Augmented Reality browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/layar-mobile-augmented-reality-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/layar-mobile-augmented-reality-browser/</guid>
      <description>Layar is an augmented reality application for Android phones which uses location information and the phones camera to show what is around the user by displaying real time digital information on top of reality. The video shows the browser being used to scan buildings and overlay real estate information to find out which houses are for sale.
Screencast / Video http://layar.eu/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MoMA Exhibition/Collection Browser</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moma-exhibitioncollection-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moma-exhibitioncollection-browser/</guid>
      <description>MoMA&#39;s exhibition and collection browser provides faceted drill-down of the museum collection&#39;s image library using a mega drop-down menu. Each facet provides the ability to select multiple terms, so the user may select multiple authors, departments or decades, for instance. Executing the search displays the narrowed set of results in an image gallery that can be toggled thumbnail, slideshow, list, and single artist views. Sorting options and image matte colors may also be selected by the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formula 1 Video Bandwidth Profiler</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/formula-1-video-bandwidth-profiler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/formula-1-video-bandwidth-profiler/</guid>
      <description>Formula 1&#39;s Video site provides a bandwidth profiler before display their video player. After checking your bandwidth availability, the app suggests a resolution and quality that will give you the best experience.
1. User selects the video they wish to view.2. App assesses available bandwidth.3. App provides report of bandwidth and resolution, and suggests the option that will provide the best experience.4. Grade 2 video player. http://www.formula1.com/video/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profoto Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/profoto-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Profoto&#39;s take on the breadcrumb combines expanded menus for each branch to provide a drill-down method for navigating siblings, aunts, great-aunts, etc. It basically exposes the hierarchy of siblings at each level, and it&#39;s really most useful when you&#39;ve navigated deep into a hierarchy. It can get a little weird when you use these, because you have to remember that you&#39;re viewing siblings in the branch you&#39;re exposing. If you look at the last screenshot for the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Product Comparison Table</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/adobe-product-comparison-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/adobe-product-comparison-table/</guid>
      <description>Adobe&#39;s Creative Suite packages the company&#39;s graphics and motion products into families that can be purchased as a set. Because it can be difficult to determine which suite is right for the work you do, Adobe provides both a product comparison table with products and features listed in a chart, or a wizard questionnaire. 1. The standard product comparison table, showing suites along the top and included products prices in rows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp Product Comparison Table</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-product-comparison-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-product-comparison-table/</guid>
      <description>37 Signals&#39; product comparison for Basecamp provides a simple, side-by-side comparison of the features of each product category. They also try to help guide the customer to the plan that meets typical needs by featuring the Plus Plan in a larger box. Details for each feature are provided in a mouseover when hovering over the feature in the featured plan box. The mouseover is not provided on hover in the other boxes, but the feature description is the same, regardless of plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Life Magazine Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/best-life-magazine-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/best-life-magazine-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Best Life Magazine&#39;s global navigation uses drop-down menus to provide both sub-section navigation where applicable, and teasers of content in sections, using a multi-column lists and showing a featured article with a thumbnail. Thanks to Fritz for the pointer.
1. Subscribe drop down shows print and online subscription options.2. Teasers of latest and featured content within a section. http://bestlifeonline.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction-Design.org Tickmark Captcha</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/interaction-designorg-tickmark-captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/interaction-designorg-tickmark-captcha/</guid>
      <description>The captcha on Interaction-Design.org, which requires a verification of tickmarks sum.
 http://www.interaction-design.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MYOB Product Comparison Table</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/myob-product-comparison-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/myob-product-comparison-table/</guid>
      <description>With only 2 accounting products, comparing Account Edge and First Edge should be simple. The product comparison page displays a feature comparison table in the right side of the page, and a user needs/persona based bullet list in the left to help prospective customers determine which product fits their needs.
 http://www.myob-us.com/compare_mac_products/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quicken Product Comparison Table and Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicken-product-comparison-table-and-wizard/</guid>
      <description>When a software company&#39;s product family grows, it can be quite difficult for customers to figure out which product is right for their needs. Quicken is one of those examples where the number of products is overwhelming. They try to help customers with a product comparison table provides a basic checkbox chart of all product feature categories, with product names and prices along the top of the table, and rows of feature categories, with checkboxes to indicate which products match which features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Target Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/target-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/target-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Target&#39;s global navigation features wide, multi-column drop-down menus that stretch to the full width of the page layout. The columns in the drop down show hierarchical lists of product/section contents using font weight and indentation, and additionally allow the company to promote special events.
1. Drop down for the &amp;quot;Women&amp;quot; section shows a multi-column hierarchical list of all product sub-categories.2. The &amp;quot;See All&amp;quot; menu item allows the site to show other product categories that aren&#39;t being featured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Confirmations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/twitter-confirmations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/twitter-confirmations/</guid>
      <description>Twitter provides a subtle, unobtrusive notification messages, e.g. when a direct message is sent. The confirmation appears as a layer with a white background over the top of the page, covering the page header, and unfortunately, not providing a more obvious &#34;Close&#34; link to dismiss the message. The message can be easily dismissed by clicking anywhere in the div, but that&#39;s not readily apparent.
1. Direct message interface.2. Confirmation that direct message has been sent appears as layer over the top of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Support Email Button</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-support-email-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-support-email-button/</guid>
      <description>The Apple Support site features a very simple &#34;email this page&#34; button in the upper right of the screen along with other tools like print and call support. The email widget starts out as an envelope icon. When clicked, the icon slides to the left and an input appears with a &#34;To&#34; label and a &#34;Send&#34; button. The user simply enters the recipients address and presses send. An AJAX progress spinner appears briefly, then a confirmation message, and the form collapses back to the icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons, Revised</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons-revised/</guid>
      <description>We covered Shelfari&#39;s hybrid button in their list views of bookshelf items. That example showed a single push button with an attached icon for drop down menu. The single button allowed for the use of a default behavior, while the drop down arrow allowed for the display of other options for the item. The drop down menu allowed users to make multiple selections, i.e. using checkbox behaviors, rather than just select one value in the drop down list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTunes Ratings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-ratings/</guid>
      <description>The iTunes Store allows customers to rate items and displays the average rating and total ratings below the product image. They use a disclosure arrow to allow customers to view a breakdown of ratings by number of stars.
1. Customers&#39; average rating, and form select to add your own rating.2. Expanded ratings break down after clicking the disclosure triangle. http://www.apple.com/itunes/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aardvark Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aardvark-registration/</guid>
      <description>The registration process on Aardvark provides a modal dialog that uses some nice content previews, content filtering, and progressive disclosure to guide the new user through the form. 1. Clicking sign up button from an invitation opens modal dialog with basic information form. A preview area updates your info as you fill out the form.2. The birthday input filters and corrects date format. City/State shows suggestions. (The one in yellow is a browser auto-completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Undo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-undo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-undo/</guid>
      <description>Netflix offers an undo function in their Queue that allows users to undo a remove action. Users click an X icon to remove a movie from their queue, and the row is grayed out, showing an undo text link replacing the remove icon. The row persists until the user moves to a different page, so several removed rows may be visible if the user does repeated removes in one session. Upon return visits to the queue, the removed movies will be gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post/Evri Related Content Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/washington-postevri-related-content-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/washington-postevri-related-content-module/</guid>
      <description>The Washington Post uses a related content widget created by Evri that indexes content using person, place, and thing (subject) facets and allows the Post to display a list of related content beneath news. The widget, which is actually a bit of SVG/VML and JavaScript, provides a small visualization of topics in the article, and allows the user to do some filtering of the related content. Navigating to topic pages provides a complete filtering view for exploring and narrowing related content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zappos Search Results Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/zappos-search-results-filtering/</guid>
      <description>The Zappos&#39; search engine provides a nice results filtering interfaces that presents the user with facets for refining their search. The user can click on the terms at the top of the search results page to narrow the set, and a breadcrumb trail shows the selections they&#39;ve made. Each term in the breadcrumb provides a checkbox to remove any one of those selections and broaden their search.
1. Users run a search using the site&#39;s global search box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thesixtyone alerts</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thesixtyone-alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thesixtyone-alerts/</guid>
      <description>Music community site thesixtyone uses unobtrusive growl-like panels in the bottom right corner of the page for system alerts and messaging. Like growl or iminlikewithyou, these messages appear briefly and fade out. The effect is subtle and might be easily missed, but the addition of an ambient &#34;pop&#34; earcon (alert sound) tells you to look for the message. Nicely done.
1. System alerts appear in the bottom right corner, with accompanying alert sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huffduffer Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/huffduffer-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/huffduffer-registration/</guid>
      <description>Huffduffer, a hybrid bookmarking/podcast service features a whimsical inline registration form that&#39;s formatted in sentences with blank areas that the user fills out with their name, password, etc. Kind of a fun, unexpected way to format the form. Reminds me of the kinds of forms you&#39;d fill out by hand in days of old, which goes with the retro style of the site.
Via SwissMiss.
 http://huffduffer.com/signup/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Move and Label Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-move-and-label-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-move-and-label-menus/</guid>
      <description>Google modified the labeling (tagging) menus in Gmail to add a Move option to co-exist with the prior Label drop down menu. The Move menu allows the user to move an email to a single label and then archives it, removing it from the Inbox. The Label menu allows the user to add multiple labels to the email, but does not archive it. Both menus offer a label search input with auto-completion, as well as options to create new or manage existing labels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIKEFOOTBALL Search Box</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nikefootball-search-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nikefootball-search-box/</guid>
      <description>The Nike Football site uses a deceptively simple trick to draw attention to its unobtrusive search box. The narrow sidebar navigation menu features what looks like a search box that is a bit too small to be usable. Clicking what you think is the search box expands a real search input adjacent to the sidebar in the body.
It&#39;s a clever method, but as you can see from the comments, it&#39;s not without problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelfari Hybrid Buttons</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/shelfari-hybrid-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Shelfari has a clever hybrid button/drop down menu to display actions on books. The button label shows the current status of the item, e.g. on my shelf, add to my shelf. When the user hovers over a button of a book that&#39;s not in your shelf, the label changes to &#34;Add to I&#39;ve Read&#34;. Clicking the drop down arrow shows other options for the book with shelf actions in the top half (I plan to read, I&#39;m reading now, I&#39;ve read), and the bottom half shows other attributes of your book (Favorite, I own, Wish list).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autoblog Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/autoblog-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/autoblog-pagination/</guid>
      <description>Autoblog&#39;s photo galleries feature beautiful, large automobile photos. Each gallery shows large beveled previous/next buttons above and below the photo, with a [current photo]/[total photos] indicator above. Below, a strip of thumbnails shows the full list of images in the gallery. An indicator of the current photo in that strip, e.g. with a special border treatment would ice the cake.
 http://www.autoblog.com/gallery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EffectiveUI Accordion Stacks</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/effectiveui-accordion-stacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/effectiveui-accordion-stacks/</guid>
      <description>Effective UI has an interesting Flash UI for presenting menus on their home page using a stacked accordion. Upon landing on the home page, a series of stacked boxes are displayed with both a large descriptive heading of that section and shows the first mini-slide in that deck/stack to help you see what that section is about. Mousing over the first slide in the stack expands the stack to show the headings for the other nodes of content within it, and the user may now hover over the other items to view their descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Spectra Visual Newsreader Carousel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/msnbc-spectra-visual-newsreader-carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/msnbc-spectra-visual-newsreader-carousel/</guid>
      <description>MSNBC.com&#39;s Spectra Visual Newsreader provides an interesting way of visually presenting channels of content from the massive news site. Adding channels drops media cards into the screen and rotates them in a 3D carousel. Below the vortext of cards, a hybrid pagination scrollbar, which bests Apple&#39;s concept, allows the user to select cards to view one at a time. Previous/Next arrows allow linear progression. A helpful [current card]/[total cards] indicator is shown on the scroll bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTunes Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/itunes-pagination/</guid>
      <description>The iTunes Store has 3 different pagination controls it uses in different places. The most common method for paging through a series of items is to show a carousel on the main pages, with prev/next arrow icons to shuffle through sets of 3-4. On special featured modules with larger poster image thumbnails they use coverflow with their hybrid scrollbar which has arrows that increment one item at a time, or allow you to scroll to move through larger increments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wikipedia Roll Clusters and Wheel Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wikipedia-roll-clusters-and-wheel-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wikipedia-roll-clusters-and-wheel-menus/</guid>
      <description>Wikipedia Roll, a Flash-based Wikipedia browsing application attempts to help provide better exploration of Wikipedia entries by doing some content/link analysis and clustering topics and sub-topics related to the retrieved entry. The screen above shows the entry for &#34;interaction design.&#34; You can see that the links occurring in the article, and presumably, other related topics are grouped into clusters that can be further explored. Each cluster provides a wheel tool for spinning through the group&#39;s available terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wowhead Breadcrumbs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wowhead-breadcrumbs/</guid>
      <description>Wowhead is a database of World of Warcraft information. The database provides a hierarchical subject taxonomy to describe items, and presents that hierarchy in the breadcrumbs for the item. When the user hovers ofer a branch in the breadcrumb trail, a drop down menu is displayed to show the node siblings and drill down to children. 1. Single entry view (database record).2. Hovering over the current entry&#39;s parent category (Daggers) to view siblings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-pagination/</guid>
      <description>Pagination is often overlooked as a minor detail. Good pagination gives the user a sense of how many pages of content, e.g. search results or gallery pages, are available to view and makes it obvious how to navigate those pages. It indicates the current page, provides link targets to advance or go backward, provides a shortcuts to jump to the start of the list, and indicates how many pages are left in the list, and possibly how many items are found in the pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickSnapper Toggle Control</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicksnapper-toggle-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicksnapper-toggle-control/</guid>
      <description>The toggle control in QuickSnapper&#39;s account settings panel allows users to toggle a setting on or off. Toggles like this that mimick the appearance of a physical switch make it obvious what the current state is. Clicking the control slides it into the alternate state.
 http://www.quicksnapper.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickSnapper Vertical Carousel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicksnapper-vertical-carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quicksnapper-vertical-carousel/</guid>
      <description>The vertical carousel on Quicksnapper shows a preview of recently snapped screenshots. Unlike most carousels, however, this one auto-scrolls vertically, and provides controls at the top and bottom rather than at the sides. It displays 4 items at a time.
1. Carousel of recent websnaps with scroll buttons at top and bottom.2. Carousel shown in page. http://www.quicksnapper.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Text Editor Task Creation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/evernote-text-editor-task-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/evernote-text-editor-task-creation/</guid>
      <description>Evernote, the unique note keeping desktop, mobile, and web-based application allows users to upload notes from images or PDFs or create them right in the software as one would any publishing system. The note creation editor features a simple rich text editor with one feature that is uncommon for web-based editors--a task checkbox. All this does is insert a checkbox wherever the insertion mark (cursor) is located, and while in edit mode, allows you the user to toggle between checked (done) and unchecked (to do).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issuu Pagination</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/issuu-pagination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/issuu-pagination/</guid>
      <description>Issuu is an online self-publishing service that allows users to create e-magazines and books that are displayed in their slick Flash reader. The service also provides social features around the content. One of the nicest things about the reader is the usable pagination. The reader features the typical next/previous and jump to page features you&#39;d find in an ebook or PDF reader. They also provide some features that are similar to the browsing experience with Preview, the Dock, and QuickLook in the Mac, utilizing miniature thumbnails of pages to scroll through pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engadget Comment Voting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/engadget-comment-voting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/engadget-comment-voting/</guid>
      <description>Engadget&#39;s comment rating and karma system uses +1/-1 voting, so users can vote comments up or down. Votes below a certain threshold get dimmed out rather than hidden. When a vote is applied, the user&#39;s vote is registered, a message appears, and the voting controls are hidden. To the right, there&#39;s an exclamation mark to flag inappropriate comments, which are then immediately collapsed from view.
 http://www.engadget.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sling Welcome Message</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sling-welcome-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sling-welcome-message/</guid>
      <description>Sling.com&#39;s welcome message position&#39;s a 3 column intro to the site for first time users, which it positions between the main promo marquee and the body of the page. Dismiss the message as a logged in user and it shouldn&#39;t come back again.
 http://beta.sling.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Layout Customization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wordpress-layout-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/wordpress-layout-customization/</guid>
      <description>WordPress added some excellent layout customization options on administration screens in version 2.7. The most obvious change comes in the form of the Screen Options tab, which expands a settings panel that let&#39;s the admin hide or show parts of the UI being viewed, and saves those settings for the user immediately. The UI also provides a drag and drop behavior to re-arrange modules. When hovering over a module heading, the icon turns into a full hand and lets the user move modules up or down in the column, or between columns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Comment Rating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-comment-rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-comment-rating/</guid>
      <description>YouTube&#39;s comment rating controls allow users to vote a comment up or down. When user enters a down vote, the comment is collapsed from view. There is a link to the left of rating controls to report a comment as spam.
 http://www.youtube.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gifting Feature at Nintendo</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gifting-feature-nintendo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gifting-feature-nintendo/</guid>
      <description>Nintendo provides excellent illustrations to describe the gifting process on the Wii, using storyboards. The gifting page shows a table of contents at the top, for each use case: sending, receiving, confirmation, and faq. Clicking one of the use cases jumps the user down to the storyboard illustrating steps to complete each case. It&#39;s a simple, very clear, and visual. I wish every support site worked that way. Thanks to Boon Sheridan for the tip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pano Logic Expanding Call to Action</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pano-logic-expanding-call-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pano-logic-expanding-call-action/</guid>
      <description>Pano Logic sells a simple network PC. Their product site features a large graphic of the product, and 3 simple informational modules at the bottom to find out more about the product, read reviews and press, and watch a demo webinar. The modules expand when the user hovers over each box. There isn&#39;t much information added, except for a call to action that tells the user a little more about what they&#39;ll see if they click the link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daylife Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>Daylife&#39;s drop down menu in global navigation that provides a wide ribbon to show both navigation to secondary levels and to show teaser content, e.g. the Latest News menu shows top level news categories as well as recent articles in each category. News sites like Daylife and NewsVine have been coming up with interesting ways of changing user&#39;s expectations of what can exist in global navigation. In some cases, the labels and categories for what appear in global navigation suggest a shifting information architecture that is based on what&#39;s interesting now or what people have been reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics Date Selector</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-date-selector/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-date-selector/</guid>
      <description>Google Analytics offers one of the most sophisticated date selectors for data filtering that I&#39;ve seen. The interface allows you to filter reports to a single day by clicking one square in a 3 month range. To select a date range, you click the start input, click a day, and do the same for the end date range. Or you can enter dates in the text inputs.
The timeline control allows you to visualize the volume of visitor activity as vertical bars, and adjust the date range by pulling slider handles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics Drop Down Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-drop-down-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-analytics-drop-down-menus/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a fan of the drop down menus that span a wide area, e.g. the main body or full page, in order to show a wider range of options rather showing fewer in a vertical drop down and forcing navigation through a fly-out tree. This convention is showing up mostly in global navigation, and with the introduction of Microsoft&#39;s Ribbon, we can expect to see more of it.
Google shows buttons with down arrows to indicate that clicking one of those controls will show expanded options in-screen, a la the drop down menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Mouseover Info</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-mouseover-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-mouseover-info/</guid>
      <description>The video details shown on mouseover in Netflix is one of those behaviors I just take for granted now. They&#39;ve used their quick-loading, shadowed mouseover call outs for years now and they&#39;ve always felt very useful to me and effortless to deal with. They&#39;re always available, and even work in areas you might not expect to see them, like in a recommendation list within a lightbox dialog. The mouseovers even make up for some things that I feel are design shortcomings, like the lack of a feature to show a gallery of poster images or sort by genre in the instant play queue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Quick Add</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-quick-add/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-quick-add/</guid>
      <description>The video queue on Netflix offers a &#34;Quick Add&#34; functionality at the bottom of the queue that lets users search for a particular title and add it to their queue without having to view the video page. It&#39;s a single input with an auto-completion behavior to suggest videos based on what you type. Clicking a title from the suggestion list or hitting return on an exact match adds the video and shows a confirmation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Rate for Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-rate-recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-rate-recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Netflix shows a module to signed in users at the top of their home page asking the user to rate recent returns. The module promises to give 2 recommendations immediately after they&#39;ve rated. On sites like Flickr, the recommendation engine is perhaps one of the single best incentives for adding ratings. On a lot of sites, ratings give you nothing back. This is a good example to illustrate quickly why you&#39;d want to add a rating, and would be particularly useful to demonstrate the value to new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Buzz Index Charts</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-buzz-index-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-buzz-index-charts/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Buzz Index presents the day&#39;s top 20 searches overall, and in a number of categories, e.g. actors. A subject&#39;s buzz score is the percentage of Yahoo! users searching for that subject on a given day, multiplied by a constant to make the number easier to read. Weekly leaders are the subjects with the greatest average buzz score for a given week.
The chart shows current rank, icons for the change in rank over previous day, previous rank position, number of days on chart, score, and score change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Ninjas Cost Estimate Slider</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/css-ninjas-cost-estimate-slider/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/css-ninjas-cost-estimate-slider/</guid>
      <description>CSS Ninjas provide a service for converting designs into XHTML/CSS. Their site features a nice cost estimate tool that allows prospective clients to see how much it will cost by specifying the number of pages that need to be converted. A slider allows you to estimate the cost of 1 to 20 pages. Clicking the &#34;proceed to checkout&#34; link opens the request for quote, and you can enter a number above 20 if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Breadcrumb Tab</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-breadcrumb-tab/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo&#39;s hybrid tab/breadcrumb navigation is one of my favorite approaches to global and local navigation. This navigation interface answers a few nagging questions that an interface designer might ask. &#34;How do I present the user with an interface that provides focus on the area they&#39;ve navigated to, while providing a path back or to other main areas of interest?&#34;
What&#39;s interesting here is that they provide a row of primary navigation tabs at the top level, and replace that with a hybrid tab/breadcrumb once the user makes the decision to drill down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domainr</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/domainr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/domainr/</guid>
      <description>Domai.nr is a simple single serving site that lets you find a domain using all the top level domain extensions to complete your name.
1. The search form.2. Enter a word and view suggestions.3. Green boxes indicate available domains. Click one to purchase. http://domai.nr/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Quotes</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/quotes/</guid>
      <description>The &#34;In Quotes&#34; project in Google Labs is an interesting attempt to leverage information from Google News to try to help people understand where public figures stand on topics and issues by extracting quotes. Google says &#34;Much of the published reporting about people is based on the interpretation of a journalist. Direct quotes, on the other hand, are concrete units of information that describe how newsmakers represent themselves.&#34;
The interface is pretty simple to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/msnbc-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/msnbc-video-player/</guid>
      <description>MSNBC&#39;s video player loads in a pop up window with the video player on the right, and a left sidebar showing navigation options to browse by playlist, category, or show. The video player itself provide a barebones set of controls for pause/play, previous/next, volume, mailto link, and embed code. A square ad unit hides the left sidebar pre-roll and is replaced by a small persistent ad unit sitting below the player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FanSnap Search Results Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fansnap-search-results-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fansnap-search-results-filtering/</guid>
      <description>FanSnap is an event ticket search site that provides faceted results filtering. Users simply enter an upcoming event, and FanSnap returns a list of available tickets from vendors like StubHub, provides filtering by price, seating area, and ticket vendor. If a venue diagram is available seats are overlaid over the venue&#39;s seating chart. Users can sort and star/favorite available tickets in their &#34;short list&#34;, and then click a link to purchase the tickets at the ticket vendor&#39;s site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Accordions</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-accordions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-accordions/</guid>
      <description>Apple&#39;s accordion module provides a method for displaying a good deal of informational and promotional content without overwhelming the interface. The types of things that are displayed in these are accordions are usually supporting content, so the desire to use a design pattern that hides and shows these panels of content is useful. Only one panel is visible at a time, and hovering over or clicking a panel heading brings its content into view with a smooth slide transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Carousels</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-carousels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-carousels/</guid>
      <description>Apple&#39;s Coverflow-like carousels are used on interior pages of Apple.com to provide visual navigation of products using product images. A set of images is displayed in a wide panel with a horizontal scrollbar. Carousels are used primarily for promotion when most sites place a set of images in this upper area of the screen below the navigation. Apple utilizes this space to provide better findability of products within each section of the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu 3 Up Carousel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-3-carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-3-carousel/</guid>
      <description>Hulu&#39;s new 3-up carousel is being utilized in the site&#39;s channels sections to offer a promotional space that takes up less screen height than their 1 up carousel, allowing the display of 3 promo items. This is very similar to the horizontal scrolling Cover Flow module in use on Apple.com interior pages.
1. First set of channels. Scroll bar below allows the user to view more.2. Second set of channels. Hovering over a channel reveals it&#39;s name and an &amp;quot;explore&amp;quot; button to jump to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Channel Drop Down Menu</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-channel-drop-down-menu/</guid>
      <description>Hulu&#39;s drop down menu for channels stretches to the width of the design and provides a multi-column grid of channels. This method of running a drop down or flyout menu left-to-right rather than top-to-bottom allows interface designers to present longer lists of options without worrying about what appears in relation to the fold, and forcing scroll on longer lists.
 http://www.hulu.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnSugar Site Publishing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/onsugar-site-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/onsugar-site-publishing/</guid>
      <description>Sugar Inc. releases the OnSugar Blogging platform to let Sugar community members start their own sites. Based on the Drupal platform, OnSugar provides some very nice modifications to clean up and simplify the posting and content management interfaces provided by the popular open source CMS. What I like most about what they&#39;ve done with Drupal is the clean tabbed UI for content creation, the media embedding options for inserting images from Getty, ShopStyle, and Fashion week photos, and the excellent spread editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Umbrella Today Weather Forecasts</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/umbrella-today-weather-forecasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/umbrella-today-weather-forecasts/</guid>
      <description>Umbrella Today is a dead simple single serving site that delivers your weather forecast with a twist. Enter your zip code and it tells you if you need an umbrella#38212;if it&#39;s raining of course. Give the service your phone number, and they&#39;ll SMS you whenever the forecast calls for rain.
1. Enter your zip code.2. The confirmation screen tells you if you need an umbrella today. Enter your phone number to get SMS notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everymoment Now News Visualization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/everymoment-now-news-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/everymoment-now-news-visualization/</guid>
      <description>everymomentnow is a beautiful news visualization site designed and developed by Craig Mod. The idea is to provide a sense of volume and correlation between keywords within a given subject area. The current incarnation focuses on Obama/McCain in the news. The clean, minimalist interface allows the user to visualize spikes in news article occurrences for each keyword a the highest level. You choose a single focal point using a keyword (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancast Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-video-player/</guid>
      <description>The Fancast has a simple video player interface with typical features. No advanced features like clipping (although it does allow sharing scenes) and the features it does have are not available in full screen mode. Additionally, accessing any of those features, e.g. sharing and embedding, pauses playback. I like the simplicity of the design, but the video player could reach some parity in terms of functionality with what video users are becoming accustomed to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yammer Microblogging</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yammer-microblogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yammer-microblogging/</guid>
      <description>Yammer is a Twitter clone for companies. The service works for users under a single company domain, and provides a combination of microblogging and presence/status information following in the footsteps of ervices like Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn.
1. Sign Up.2. Home page and content entry screen.3. Updates are shown immediately in the page.4. Clicking a hashtag displays only entries with that tag applied.5. Member listing.6. Tag listing. https://www.yammer.com/home</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Localization</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-localization/</guid>
      <description>YouTube&#39;s localization options limit content to submissions from a particular country, and the language selection options allow users to change the interface language. This is one of those interfaces that becomes clear when you&#39;ve clicked the links, because the option are hidden until you click the &#34;Worldwide&#34; link. Qualifying labels like &#34;Content: World | Lang: En (US)&#34; might make these very obvious. It&#39;s nice that YouTube gives you that content selector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolspotters User Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/coolspotters-user-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/coolspotters-user-registration/</guid>
      <description>Coolspotters user registration form does input validation and shows an icon in the right side of the input for valid or invalid values, and displays error message text to the right of the input. Simple.
1. Checking user name and displaying error.2. Validated input. http://coolspotters.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBS Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cbs-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cbs-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The CBS site features a drop down menu that spans the entire width of the layout when the user hovers over shows. Wide drop downs are not unusual, and for a time appeared on the Amazon.com site when they experiencing the growth of their departments. On CBS, this type of interface is used to display as many of the network&#39;s shows as it can, segmenting them by airing time and format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IKEA Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ikea-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ikea-navigation/</guid>
      <description>IKEA&#39;s navigation menus feature a simple navigation bar on the top of the layout. The most important entry points are shown as is a button for new items. A drop down menu at right for the rest of the top level entry points. Within each section, tree navigation interfaces are provided for browsing more deeply within the section.
1. Home page.2. &amp;quot;Living Room&amp;quot; selected in the global navigation. Local navigation appears in the left sidebar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rofo Search Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/rofo-search-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/rofo-search-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Rofo provides a faceted search engine for commercial real estate properties. The beta provides a search interface at the top of the home and results pages to set parameters including location, size, type of space, and budget. Slider controls are used to narrow size and budget. At present, changes in these settings require a manual page submission to update results. The top location shows some limitations on the number of visible values that can be displayed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNET TV Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnet-tv-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnet-tv-video-player/</guid>
      <description>CNET TV provides a video player that showcases their large library of content including product reviews, news coverage, and special reports. The main page of CNET TV features the video player in the center stage, with a short list of featured (hot) content flanking the left side, and a playlist on the right showing the currently playing video. The player controls are simple and easy to use, but at full screen, the controls a little soft and blurry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TheWB.com Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thewb-com-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thewb-com-video-player/</guid>
      <description>The WB brings its video site to the masses of OC and Friends fans and adds another network portal into the mix with Hulu. In terms of visual appearances and the high level navigation (IA), TheWB.com feels like the polar opposite in sensibility to Hulu&#39;s pared down appearances and very usable directory structure and show pages. On Hulu, once you arrive at a show page, everything you can watch whether it be a full episode or clip, is neatly organized and presented on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MobileMe Calendar Date Selector</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mobileme-calendar-date-selector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/mobileme-calendar-date-selector/</guid>
      <description>The date selection controls in MobileMe Calendar mimic the date selection segmented control in iCal. However, the control bar adds an additional drop-down menu for actions like creating events, and jumping to a specific date. The interface is simple. The addition of the action menu makes the functions from the iCal menu bar accessible without having to add to the web-based calendar interface.
1. The full calendar interface.2. The action menu expanded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoEgg Tabs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/videoegg-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/videoegg-tabs/</guid>
      <description>The VideoEgg Advertising Network site uses vertical tabs along the right of the page with labels properly oriented in the north-south direction. While doing tabs this way requires that they be handled as images or Flash, the metaphor is recognizable and its use makes sense immediately. Local navigation is handled inside the banner area. 1. Vertical tabs along right side of page.2. Navigation detail. Local navigation seen in the large banner area to the left of the tabs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Buzz Voting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-buzz-voting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-buzz-voting/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Buzz pulls actively viewed and shared pages from its portal and puts them in a Digg-like interface with vote-to-promote buttons so users may actively push stories up and down the Buzz list. The digg/bury interface is simple. Stories are categorized by several main topic areas, and users may view the stories with the highest vote count, over several time slices, or sorted by recency.
1. When the user visits the site the first time, a guided tour jumps the user around the page to introduce them to the site&#39;s features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ed Lives Here Glossary</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ed-lives-here-glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ed-lives-here-glossary/</guid>
      <description>Paper manufacturer NewPage provides the Ed Lives Here site, a useful resource with information about paper, printing, and design. One of the features of this site is a glossary of printing terms. The glossary provides categorized sub-glossaries, as well as the typical a-z index of terms, and a search input. Browsing through the glossary is facilitated by the A-Z links, which use a fish eye lens to bring focus to a section of the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr Edit In Place Fields</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-edit-place-fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-edit-place-fields/</guid>
      <description>Flickr&#39;s edit in place behaviors make it easy to change data on records without requiring the round trip to a full page editor form. They provided one of the earliest examples of this behavior, using AJAX to quickly update fields in place, and has remained the model to emulate for some time.
1. Flickr entry in user&#39;s photos page.2. Hovering over the title field highlights it with background color to provide a subtl alert the user that it can be edited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panic Tabs and Carousel Panel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/panic-tabs-and-carousel-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/panic-tabs-and-carousel-panel/</guid>
      <description>Panic&#39;s product page for Coda provides a hybrid interface utilizing both tabs along the top of the information panel, and arrows on the sides to slide through all of the pages in a carousel.
1. The product information panel in the full page.2. Clicking the next arrow slides to the next panel in the carousel.3. Clicking a tab further to the right, slides all panels off to the left until the target page is reached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Autos Carousel and Accordion Panel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-autos-carousel-and-accordion-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-autos-carousel-and-accordion-panel/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Autos has uses a nice hybrid design pattern for promoting the different categories of top cars selected by users. Situated in the right hand column, the arrows at the upper right allow the user to slide through the different lists. The details for the top car are shown in an exposed panel of the accordion, and the titles of the remaining 4 are displayed as well with large number to indicate order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNN.com Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnn-com-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/cnn-com-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The CNN News portal provides a very dense global navigation header that&#39;s got quite a bit going on, but succeeds in drawing out the main entry points for news, featured or promoted points of interest, language/edition preference setting, search, and even a sticky alert area for late breaking news. It even borrows the idea of hot topics navigation per section from Newsvine, which allows for a more variable set of local navigation based on what&#39;s happening now, rather than on a rigid top-down IA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/delicious-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/delicious-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The redesigned del.icio.us site provides drop down navigation to signed in users. Clicking the navigation label jumps to that section, or click the arrow to drill down in that section. They provide separators in the drop-down to chunk up the navigation options. There&#39;s some inconsistency in the treatment of selected sections. The blue background of the nav link on Home implies selected color. But if you click the links in the global nav, the blue background on Home remains on Home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delicious Tag Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/delicious-tag-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/delicious-tag-filtering/</guid>
      <description>del.icio.us&#39; tag filtering provides an excellent interface design for filtering tags without having to scan your tag list or tag bundles, which can turn out quite long over time. In a control area that looks and behaves like a hybrid breadcrumb trail, you enter a tag into an input. Tag suggestions are provided as you type. Build up that filter by adding tags, and each tag in your crumb path can be removed independent of the path you took by clicking the tag&#39;s adjacent X icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise 2.0 Conference Inline Login Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/enterprise-2-0-conference-inline-login-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/enterprise-2-0-conference-inline-login-form/</guid>
      <description>The Enterprise 2.0 Conference site, which is run on Jive Clearspace, provides an inline form for logging into the site. Clicking the Login link in the header replaces the header content with a form where inputs and labels are displayed in a single row.
1. Header global navigation with login link.2. Clicking login link replaces the navigation bar with the inline login form. http://community.e2conf.com/index.jspa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Konigi Inline Login Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/konigi-inline-login-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/konigi-inline-login-form/</guid>
      <description>Seems strange to feature this site here, but I&#39;m building up a set of this inline form design convention. Konigi provides an unobtrusive control for logging in via the user&#39;s site login/password or Open ID login in a utility navigation area. Clicking one of these log in links allows the user to enter their credentials without navigating to a form on a separate page.
1. Header with login options in utility nav on the right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pappelina Language Selection</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pappelina-language-selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pappelina-language-selection/</guid>
      <description>Pappelina, an interior design product company, provides a fun language selection page when you arrive at the site. Pick the hand with the ribbons in flag colors for Sweden for Swedish or UK/US for English. I know this is just a Flash splash page, but it&#39;s functional and a pretty entry page.
 http://www.pappelina.com/site.htm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Unbox Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-unbox-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-unbox-video-player/</guid>
      <description>Unbox is Amazon.com&#39;s Movie and TV Show store, which offers downloadable videos that may be played on a user&#39;s PC, TiVo, or portable media player. The Unbox video player provides a &#34;Shop&#34; browser, a carousel of poster images for viewing top selling and renting movies and TV shows. Sadly, you have to make your purchase via the Amazon.com web site, and can&#39;t purchase directly from the player. You also cannot browse videos by genre in the player&#39;s Shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Times Article Clipping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-times-article-clipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/new-york-times-article-clipping/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times&#39; Times File Service allows users to save news items for reading later. Users click an Folder icon in the article tools adjacent to the article. When they navigate to their Times File, they see their list of shaved articles, with options for tagging, describing, and sharing the article via email. A nice feature of the Tiles File can be found under the Most Popular tab, where the most saved articles can be copied into your own library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pattern Tap Guided Tour</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pattern-tap-guided-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pattern-tap-guided-tour/</guid>
      <description>Pattern Tap positions some instructional copy at the top of their site for first time visitors. It displays information about what is on the page and how to use it. A right arrow navigation button allows the user to take a guided tour of the site. The user may dismiss the messages when they&#39;re done with the tour.
 http://patterntap.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thsrs Synonym Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thsrs-synonym-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/thsrs-synonym-search/</guid>
      <description>Ironic Sans provides Thsrs, a single-serving site that provides shorter synonyms for long words. Simple idea that&#39;s well executed. If you&#39;re Firefox user, this is even more useful as a search add on. 1. User enters a long word.2. Shorter synonyms are returned if possible.3. Would be even better if it caught spelling errors. http://www.ironicsans.com/thsrs/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bit.ly url shortener</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/bit-ly-url-shortener/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/bit-ly-url-shortener/</guid>
      <description>Bitly is a simple url shortening service aimed at web professionals. The service provides a simply shortened URL and friendly urls based on keywords you specify. This is an example of a single-serving site that provides a simplified interface, but offers much more functionality following that initial interaction with the service. Attention is paid to making default behaviors easy, but gives expert users much more below the surface. bit.ly also offer referring tracking, an API for web apps, mirrored URL on Amazon Web Services, and thumbnail images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon.com TV Show Episode Details</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-com-tv-show-episode-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-com-tv-show-episode-details/</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#39;s Unbox service displays episodes of a TV show&#39;s season in a table listing. Each episode name is listed by title and air date, with a synopsis teaser, pricing information and a checkbox. On the left of each row is a plus (+) icon so the user can view the episode details. The row expands to show an image and the complete synopsis.
1. Episode listing table.2. Single episode expanded to show details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RYZ Rating and Favoriting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ryz-rating-and-favoriting/</guid>
      <description>RYZ is a sneaker manufacturer that crowdsources the design of their product and shares the revenue with winners. Users download a template to create design and upload to their profile. Participants vote on the designs by giving ratings and winners receive $1000 and $1 for every pair sold. The site provides simple interfaces for both favoriting and rating entries.
1. The voting page.2. Clicking the star badge in the corner of the image adds to favorites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System One Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/system-one-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/system-one-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>System One is an enterprise content management platform that combines functionality of a wiki and CMS in a rich internet application environment. The article editor provides some interesting features and AJAX functionality, including a block/paragraph-level editor, drag and drop moving within an article, and related internal/external content suggestions.
1. The journal&#39;s multi-entry view.2. Clicking the link to create a new page displays an input to provide the page name, and shows suggestions for pages that are similarly named.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AideRSS Table Row Expansion</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aiderss-table-row-expansion/</guid>
      <description>AideRSS is a service that scores and filters RSS feeds so that users can view the most active posts for a web site. Activity is based on number of comments, and posts to digg or del.icio.us. The feeds are displayed in a table, with hot or most active entries indicated by a higher rank and warmer color in the postrank column. A &#34;+ more&#34; icon allows the user to expand entry information within a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.fm Tabs</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-tabs/</guid>
      <description>In Last.fm&#39;s redesign, the site started combining vertical tabs along the left hand side of the content area, and horizontal tabs in the main content area for sub-navigation. This is not something I would recommend. There is something rather unnatural feeling to me when vertical tabs along a Y axis are laid out with text in the West-East orientation. I think for the metaphor to make sense, the South-North orientation has to be respected, as though you were stacking real manila folders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-calendar/</guid>
      <description>Where Google Search gave us syntax for doing all kinds of advanced searching, Google Calendar goes a more natural route. When Calendar was released, it introduced a lot of people to the idea of the natural language command line for the web via the &#34;Quick Add&#34; feature. Via a simple form input, you enter basic event info, e.g. &#34;Lunch with Judy on Thusday at 1pm.&#34; The event is quickly added, and you click the event title in the calendar to edit the details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presdo Calendaring</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/presdo-calendaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/presdo-calendaring/</guid>
      <description>Presdo is a calendaring service that uses a simple form input as the command line for entering natural language commands for events. To use, enter event statements as with Google Calendar. It is always assumed that you are the subject&amp;#8212;the WHO. You just have to fill in the rest of the WHAT, WITH WHOM, and WHERE parts of the statement, e.g. &#34;Have lunch with Judy on Thursday at 1pm.&#34; Once you&#39;ve submitted the basic event info, you&#39;re presented with a more complete UI for entering event details, and this is where the service far surpasses Google&#39;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/twitter-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/twitter-search/</guid>
      <description>With Twitter&#39;s acquisition of Summize, the social messaging service now provides a very nice, and simple to use interface to see what people are twitting about. Enter a topic or keyword and click search. The options in the sidebar of the results screen are substantial too: Feeds, translations, trends, interesting queries, e.g. hashtags. Advanced search and using search operators adds a powerful, Google-like experience to your search.
1. Simple search screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>goosh.org Cmmand Line Interface</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/goosh-org-cmmand-line-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/goosh-org-cmmand-line-interface/</guid>
      <description>Goosh, which dubs itself &#34;the unofficial google shell&#34; interprets the idea of presenting a command line interface via a web site literally. The site uses AJAX to present a terminal shell interface to Google. For simple searches, just enter keywords and click Enter. Type h for help with other commands. It even provides history functionality using keyboard up/down arrows.
1. The default screen is literally a command line interface.2. Help shows available commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogger Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/blogger-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/blogger-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>The new Blogger Draft text editor shares some of the behaviors of the rich text editor in Gmail, and as commenter points out, uses the same icons used in Google Pages. Blogger and Pages use beveled buttons rather than using the more minimalist style of the borderless icons in Gmail. One might argue that these controls are actually more usable because the states of toggles and the affordances supplied by buttons and dropped down menus should be obvious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gmail-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google have been doing some work getting some of their interfaces to be consistent with each other. GMail and Blogger now provide similar interface behaviors and controls, with slight differences. Other applications like Google Sites and Docs continue to have different controls.
Gmail and Blogger are among the simplest of these text editor interfaces, for good reason. In blogs and email, rich text formatting should be bare bones and out of the way as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Mail Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-mail-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-mail-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! Mail&#39;s rich text editor in the composition form is clean and provides the core set of formatting options you&#39;d need. The implementation is simple and intuitive. A few things they do differently include: rolling some commonly visible controls into drop down menus, e.g. text alignment and list style blocks.
1. Font face selection and font size are in HTML form selects. 2. Font color selection. Highlight or background color uses the same color selection control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performancing Metrics Data Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/performancing-metrics-data-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/performancing-metrics-data-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Performancing Metrics is a web analytics product that is focussed on Blog Systems. Their reporting views provide an highly scalable solution for data filtering that takes up very little screen real estate, yet provides a powerful mechanism for adding criteria to do granular reports. This example shows an ad-hoc filtering of the Visitors data on their demo server.
This solution, showing an inline set of filter criteria on a single row contrasts with several typical filtering techniques that can be used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Filter Embedding Media in Comments</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-embedding-media-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-embedding-media-comments/</guid>
      <description>The Wall feature of user profiles in The Filter allows users to create entries with recommendations as embedded content. Users enter their comment and search for anything from an artist to a track to find content to recommend. The selected content is embedded in the comment to be played in the media player.
The interface is similar to those provided in the MTV recommendations app on Facebook and the Video embedding control in Gawker Media comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Filter Rating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/filter-rating/</guid>
      <description>The rating controls in The Filter provide a slider control with a 10 point scale. Each rating is accompanied by an English language equivalent, e.g. 0% on the negative side is &#34;Never show me this again!&#34; and 100% on the positive side is &#34;A new kind of awesome.&#34; Middling ratings are &#34;Not for me&#34;, &#34;Average&#34;, and &#34;This is good.&#34;
1. Ratings slider control.2. The Ratings module in the video player. More related items in carousel below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.fm Feedback</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-feedback/</guid>
      <description>The feedback and bug reporting interface that Last.fm is using during its beta for the redesigned site provides a simple way to report problems and tell the company what you like. During the beta, a temporary, persistent yellow navigation bar is placed at the top of the page with links to info about the beta program, notices for known issues, and an option to leave feedback. Clicking leave feedback expands the yellow bar to show feedback options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.fm Top Content Charts Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-top-content-charts-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-top-content-charts-module/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm&#39;s top artists and top songs content module appears on user profiles. The module shows a list of top content, with options in tabs to change time slice. The content module also provides options to modify settings and embed the content on an external blog or social network site.
1. Default tab, showing last 7 days of top artists with Last.fm&#39;s signature bar chart for number of plays. 2. Last 6 months tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIRB Feedback and Bug Reporting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virb-feedback-and-bug-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/virb-feedback-and-bug-reporting/</guid>
      <description>VIRB&#39;s bug reporting link in the page footer allows signed in users to report bugs or send other feedback quickly and simply. Clicking the &#34;Report a bug&#34; expands the footer to display feedback options.
1. &amp;quot;Report a Bug&amp;quot; link in footer.2. Expanded bug reporting and suggestion interface form expands in the footer. http://virb.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OfficeMax A-Z Index</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-z-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-z-index/</guid>
      <description>OfficeMax displays an a-z index of the store directory in the global navigation. When users hover over any of the letters, a page-wide flyout menu appears to display entries. Clicking on one of the letters, displays the same listing of entries in full page view.
1. A-Z index displayed in global navigation. Hovering over letter shows wide flyout menu of directory entries.2. Directory display for B&#39;s. http://www.officemax.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OfficeMax Faceted Search Results</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-faceted-search-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/officemax-faceted-search-results/</guid>
      <description>OfficeMax search provides faceted filtering of results using controls in a left sidebar. Facets such as category, brand, and price show 5 terms per facet, allow the user to expand to see more terms if any, add and remove facet selections in any order. A breadcrumb trail is also provided to show the selections made, and can be used to clear all selections at once by clicking on the first term in the trail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Media Annotation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-media-annotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-media-annotation/</guid>
      <description>YouTube have added media annotation controls that allow users to add comment bubbles, note boxes, and links (within YouTube only) to their own videos. YouTube is not the first to add media annotations or commenting features like this, but the addition of this feature may mean we&#39;ll see more if it on video portals. The feature is similar to the video annotation that Bubbleply does. Viewers are not allowed to add annotations to other users&#39; media as is done on Flickr and iminlikewithyou.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SensibleUnits.com Conversion Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sensibleunits-com-conversion-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sensibleunits-com-conversion-form/</guid>
      <description>SensibleUnits is a fun single purpose site that converts boring units to real objects as you type.
 http://www.sensibleunits.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conservation International Global Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/conservation-international-global-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/conservation-international-global-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Conservation International site provides an interesting take on the flyout or drop down global navigation bar. The site uses single, short action words set in very large type to indicate what you can do and name the sections of the site: Discover, Learn, Explore, Act, Give. These are nice pathfinder-type labels. When the user hovers over a links, the label expands to provide a phrase. For example, Learn becomes &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickr Sharing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/flickr-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Flickr have added a sharing interface for their photos and videos. Presumably this is because of the introduction of videos into the ecosystem. The interface is provided via an unobtrusive link that uses AJAX to display contextual menus when clicked.
Prior to the introduction of this interface, users had to go to click the &#34;All Sizes&#34; link to find URLs for the item.
1. &amp;quot;Share This&amp;quot; button appears to the right of photo or video title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SugarSync Creating and Moving Items</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-creating-and-moving-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-creating-and-moving-items/</guid>
      <description>SugarSync&#39;s web-based document management application allows users to manage files that are kept on their computers. The interactions for creating and moving folders use an identical design pattern for placing items in a directory on the file system. This is similar to the Save As behavior in operating systems such as the Mac Finder and Windows Explorer, which will let users navigate to a disk drive, and then drill down deeply into a directory location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SugarSync Uploading Files</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-uploading-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sugarsync-uploading-files/</guid>
      <description>SugarSync&#39;s upload file behavior uses a customized interface that is not typical. Instead of using the browser behavior for handling file uploads using &amp;lt;input type=&#34;file&#34;&amp;gt;, which typically provides an input and browse button in Firefox and Internet Explorer, SugarSync uses a single button to invoke the file browsing window, and then displays the file&#39;s name in HTML. To be fair, Safari provides a slicker interface for file uploads, which doesn&#39;t display an input, but only a button, and then shows the file name next to the button when a file is found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nivea Download Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nivea-download-wizard/</guid>
      <description>The Nivea brand advertising site features a very wizard for determining the type of logo file you should download depending on how the logo will be used. The visitor will answer questions about the purpose, application, and size needed. At the end of the process, a file is given to download. The questions are very easy to answer, and stepping the user through this process eliminates having to sift through a longer list of file types to determine the logo that would best suit the user&#39;s application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tork Revolution Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tork-revolution-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tork-revolution-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Tork Revolution site features a Flash global/local navigation system that appears conventional on the surface, but positions the navigation elements in unconventional places on the page, using size, position, and color to indicate hierarchy.
1. The home page.2. Clicking, Foodservice, one of the main entry points in the global nav pulls that word out of the nav and re-positions it at the top of the page.3. Following a link to a sub-page, we are now viewing &amp;quot;Foodservice &amp; Kitchen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Form Auto-completion</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/facebook-form-auto-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/facebook-form-auto-completion/</guid>
      <description>Facebook&#39;s address auto-completion in the compose message form is one of the best examples of auto-completion behavior in a form. The interaction very closely mimics what you would expect to happen in the To field of email applications like Apple Mail and Outlook.
1. Cursor is in the To: field. Contextual help displayed below input.2. Typing characters in the input invokes person/recipient auto-completion suggestions. 3. Selecting a person from auto-completion suggestions, entering a comma, or clicking enter displays the selected recipient in a block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last.fm Tagging</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-tagging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/last-fm-tagging/</guid>
      <description>Last.fm provides a simple interface for tagging artists or tracks that mimics the email address entry design pattern provided in applications like Apple Mail and Facebook Messaging. Their redesign (beta site accessed May 2008) cleans up their tagging interface by providing auto-completion, and the ability delete tags by clicking the item in the input.
1. Clicking the More menu displays the Add Tags link. Presumably, there will be more than just an add tags item in the future, otherwise Add Tags should simple be visible without this extra link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apture Text Editing</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apture-text-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apture-text-editing/</guid>
      <description>The Apture service allows web site publishers to easily find and incorporate multimedia content from the web into their site. Apture requires one line of javascript code to work. The service embeds dynamic links in the page that allow users to preview content from the outside sites in AJAX layers over the page content. Publishers can choose to automatically generate links from certain sites, e.g. YouTube and Wikipedia. They can also create links by selecting text on the page and finding the content they want to embed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inquisitor Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/inquisitor-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/inquisitor-search/</guid>
      <description>Inquisitor calls itself Spotlight for the web. The free search plugin is installed in Safari and provides better search results using Safari&#39;s built in search box. When a user enters text into the input, Inquisitor displays a drop down menu with results suggestions and search term auto-completion. The first section of the drop down shows matching results pages in Google, and in the second section shows auto-completion suggestions for other terms that match the entered text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is Good</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/when-good/</guid>
      <description>When Is Good is a tool that does one thing&amp;#8212;helps a group of people choose the time for their next meeting or event. One person starts by clicking (or clicking and dragging down) all the times that they are available on a calendar grid that shows 2 1/2 weeks of time slots. When Is Good then provides a link to circulate to participants, who see the proposed times and click on when they are free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn Museum Click! Rating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/brooklyn-museum-click-rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/brooklyn-museum-click-rating/</guid>
      <description>The Brooklyn Museum&#39;s Click! show is a crowd-curated exhibition that accepted user submissions for photographs that reflect the theme, &#34;The changing face of Brooklyn.&#34; Following the submission period, visitors are asked to help curate the photography show by evaluation submissions on their effectiveness at demonstrating the theme. The interface for evaluating photos steps the user through each entry and provides a slider control to rate the photo on a scle from most effective to least effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QUEEKY Ratings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/queeky-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/queeky-ratings/</guid>
      <description>QUEEKY is a drawing community that allows users to draw pictures in their browsers using the site&#39;s flash application. Users can rate the drawings using a rating scale ranging from 1 (Hmmm) to 10 (A masterpiece!). Scores on the low side are color coded to a cool violet color and on the high side towards a hotter pink/fuschia.
1. Low rating2. High rating3. Full page http://www.queeky.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Sites Rich Text Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-rich-text-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-rich-text-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google Sites, the new wiki application that is now part of Google Apps is a content management tool based on the JotSpot service acquired by Google. Sites retains the excellent rich text editor tools that JotSpot had. The formatting bar allows users to do the simple things you would expect from a word processor, such as making font changes and adding styles such as headings to text, insert lists, links, images, and table of contents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Sites Theme Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-theme-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-sites-theme-editor/</guid>
      <description>Google released the technology acquired by JotSpot as the new Sites tool in the Google Apps suite. The Sites tools provides the interface you see here for modifying the appearance of your site, using pre-defined themes as a starting place, allowing you to modify the layout of content modules in the left column, and the colors used in the layout.
1. Selecting a theme.2. Modifying page elements.3. Configuring a module.4. Setting colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pattern Tap Tag Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pattern-tap-tag-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/pattern-tap-tag-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Pattern Tap, an interface and visual design gallery, provides a UI for filtering using tags. Best case scenario would get rid of the filter button and also updates the set of available tags to indicate those that can be combined with the current selection (e.g. dim or hide tags that can&#39;t be combined with my selection &#34;black AND white&#34; AND simiple.&#34; Often times in interfaces that provide filtering based on all available tags or index terms, if the filtering UI doesn&#39;t update to reflect those terms that may successfully combined, the user is led down a path to an empty set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indeed Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/indeed-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/indeed-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Job search engine Indeed offers faceted search filtering in their results. Facets include useful filtering criteria such as job title, salary range estimate, company, location, and job type. Filters beneath any facet may be selected at any point while viewing the results, and removed in an ad-hoc manner regardless of the order selected. Users may also remove all filtering to return to original results.
1. Search interface.2. Search results with filters on left column which can be hidden/collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Site Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-site-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/apple-site-search/</guid>
      <description>Apple provides an excellent site search design, which includes an AJAX auto-completion drop down menu showing categorized matches against your query, and thumbnail images of matching items. The categories carry over in the search results page, which displays your results in collapsible sets, much as you would see with the Mac OS Spotlight search. Some result sets are even rendered as a carousel (look at iTunes results).
1. Auto-completion drop down shown for query on &amp;quot;iph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down for everyone or just me? Submission Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/down-everyone-or-just-me-submission-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/down-everyone-or-just-me-submission-form/</guid>
      <description>This is a dead simple service to check server status. It consists of 1 input to enter a domain name, and a link to submit. If the server is up, and you still can&#39;t get to it, then you know connection problems you are experiencing are due to issues at your end.
1. Enter domain and click link to submit.2. Result and link to try another site. http://downforeveryoneorjustme.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TeamSnap Terms of Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/teamsnap-terms-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/teamsnap-terms-service/</guid>
      <description>TeamSnap uses funny copy to accept their terms of service. There&#39;s no way a lawyer every looked at this.
 http://go.teamsnap.com/signup</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capzles Captcha</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/capzles-captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/capzles-captcha/</guid>
      <description>Capzles, a photo management and sharing services uses animated text in a Flash captcha to trick the robots. This is the most sophisticated attempt I&#39;ve seen to make captchas unreadable. It still can&#39;t beat the spam sweatshops, but it seems to me like a very good option for defeating OCR.
 http://capzles.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop Express Captcha</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photoshop-express-captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photoshop-express-captcha/</guid>
      <description>Adobe&#39;s new online service, Photoshop Express, uses handwritten fonts for Captcha forms.
 https://www.photoshop.com/express/landing.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ibeatyou rating</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ibeatyou-rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ibeatyou-rating/</guid>
      <description>ibeatyou is a video portal that allows people to create challenges to compete on anything. Users either upload a video, record from webcam, or import from YouTube.
The rating system is a whimsical little widget for allowing a score from 1 to 5. The vote is indicated by a little blue man holding up a scrore card. They also provide a qualitative award, allowing users to give an award to the entry and name it anything they like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publicis &amp; Hal Riney Webcam Gesture Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/publicis-hal-riney-webcam-gesture-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/publicis-hal-riney-webcam-gesture-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Publicis and Hal Riney site attempts to innovate navigation by replacing mouse input by detecting gestures the user makes against their webcam. Once the Flash file embeds your webcam video into the lower right corner of the page, a body outline is superimposed, and hot spots in the North-South-East-West quandrants are ghosted on the screen to show where you should hold or swipe your hand to navigate. Unfortunately the video ended up eating up resources on my machine to the point that the load times were painfully slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchme Visual Search</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/searchme-visual-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/searchme-visual-search/</guid>
      <description>Searchme provides a search interface that provides screenshots of search results. The user interface is a flash application that mimics Apple&#39;s new coverflow display in the Leopard finder. The search options provide category filters, and relevant categories are displayed once you&#39;ve typed search terms that match a category. The example here shows categories that are relevant to the search for &#34;new york city.&#34;
Search results provide more information about the site when the user hovers over the screenshot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IHT Top Stories Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iht-top-stories-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iht-top-stories-module/</guid>
      <description>The International Herald Tribune site has, in my opinion, been the site that set the bar for clean, minimalist newspaper web sites since John Weir worked on the design circa 2000/2001. The evolution of the site has continued to stick to Weir&#39;s minimalist visual style, although his innovative DHTML column and clipping behaviors are gone.
The top stories content module is an interface element that is a common feature in news sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hulu Carousel</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-carousel/</guid>
      <description>Hulu provides an interesting carousel for the promotion of content on their home page. They use a large stage that spans the entire width of the browser window and shows one promoted piece of content at a time. Left/Right arrows allow the user to page through the promos, and a representation of the promos as mini-screens (small multiples) at the bottom of the stage allows the user to see what number they&#39;re looking at, among the total promos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songza Radial Menus</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/songza-radial-menus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/songza-radial-menus/</guid>
      <description>You rarely see radial menus implemented on the web. Radial menus provide a branching interface from a single starting point. Songza uses this interface convention to provide a very interesting way of selecting from 4 categories of actions that can be performed on a single song: play, share, rate, playlist. These are categories of actions you typically get with audio and video media on web sites. The radial menu allows the designer to keep the display simple, so the user can focus on the lists of titles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digg Contact</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-contact/</guid>
      <description>This is perhaps more about information architecture than interface or interaction design. One thing I like about Digg&#39;s About section is the transparency of the company that&#39;s suggested here. They only provide email addresses for contacting the company, rather than providing a form. They provide 4 types of contact: feedback, abuse, press, and partners, each type of gets sent to an email address. This exposes you, the sender, as it doesn&#39;t allow the sending of anonymous email, and gives them a way to respond to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daylife Favoriting</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-favoriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/daylife-favoriting/</guid>
      <description>Daylife provides an excellent mechanism for favoriting. The news portal, which is published to demonstrate the company&#39;s news delivery product, provides a simple method for saving favorites that uses a star icon. The site classifies articles into topics which are simply terms describing a subject matter, person, or company/organization. Users see star icons when they hover over a link to a topic or a story. Starring the link adds the topic or story to their &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gawker Media Video Comments</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gawker-media-video-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/gawker-media-video-comments/</guid>
      <description>Gawker Media&#39;s weblogs provide a simple method for including YouTube videos in comments. The example shown here is from the Consumerist blog. Users find a video in YouTube, copy and paste the permalink URL into their comment on the blog, and the video is embedded into their published comment. This method of transcluding content is popular in wikis, but the implementation usually involves using a special syntax. Gawker&#39;s method of using translating the permalink is dead simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsweek Top 10 Module</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/newsweek-top-10-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/newsweek-top-10-module/</guid>
      <description>Newsweek uses Clearspring&#39;s Flash widgets to display top read and emailed stories as a content delivery module in a sidebar. This module is like most top story modules provided on news sites, e.g. NY Times, but the interesting features are the ability to adjust the range of stories by time (notice the nice slider control) and to embed the module as a widget. While this module is implemented as Flash, there is no reason it can&#39;t be done as XHTML and Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i&#39;minlikewithyou Comments</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iminlikewithyou-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/iminlikewithyou-comments/</guid>
      <description>i&#39;minlikewithyou&#39;s full Flash interface pushes the boundaries of what can be done with user interfaces in terms of social interaction. The comment feature on the site&#39;s news articles and videos allows users to place comments (including a drawing) over the media. In the case of video, the comments appear briefly on top of the video at the points where people have placed them. Because of the volume of commenting on these videos, tons of comments will roll by in a frenzied flash, so it&#39;s hard to read them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howcast Video Player</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/howcast-video-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/howcast-video-player/</guid>
      <description>Howcast is a web video site founded by veterans of Google and YouTube, to &#34;bring together the personality of user-generated content with the quality of a professional video studio.&#34; The videos produced by the site bring a higher standard of quality than Google and YouTube, and offer interesting features such as chapter markers and time-marked notes called &#34;steps&#34; in Howcast parlance. The content is targetted at information seekers of how to, tutorial, and DIY instructional video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal Captcha</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/drupal-captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/drupal-captcha/</guid>
      <description>Drupal&#39;s captcha module offers some creative alternatives to the typical distorted text of image captchas. These are a few of the examples that are much more readable, and arguably less frustrating. 1. ASCII art captcha2. Math captcha3. Text captcha4. Lost character captcha5. Phrase captcha6. Riddler captcha http://drupal.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MotionBox Video Player Clipping</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/motionbox-video-player-clipping/</guid>
      <description>Motionbox provides a nice interface for creating clips of videos they host. Along with Hulu, Motionbox is among the first to introduce the idea of clipping portions of web video. However, Motionbox outshines Hulu in terms of usability. Clipping is a simple operation that mimics the video selection paradigm users have become comfortable with on video editing software. And unlike Hulu, Motionbox provides instant feedback about where the start and end markers lie, by moving the video playhead with the position of the markers as you adjust the clip size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radar Comments</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/radar-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/radar-comments/</guid>
      <description>Radar&#39;s comment feature allows users to post a public comment on a person&#39;s photo, or post a special comment called a whisper that only the owner will see. The owner may click the small X icons next to the comments to delete. The whisper feature is a nice idea, and the execution is dead simple. Allowing comments when viewing a set of photos in list view is very thoughtful and feels right, since these are small-sized cell phone pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vote Chooser Wizard</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/vote-chooser-wizard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/vote-chooser-wizard/</guid>
      <description>A friend sent me the link to VoteChooser to remind people before the primary to vote. The site consists of a single page wizard that asks you 10 questions about where you stand on political issues. The results page shows how your position aligns with those of presidential candidates in an attempt to help the undecided discover who might be the best person to vote for.
I hesitated at posting this with my results, because I don&#39;t want to make a political statement, but its useful to see how this simple questionnaire is very effective at helping to do a simple research task like figuring out what candidates stand for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AOL Music Desktop Video Widget</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aol-music-desktop-video-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/aol-music-desktop-video-widget/</guid>
      <description>AOL&#39;s Desktop Widget is standalone video player (Adobe AIR application) that runs on the user&#39;s computer. The video player allows users to browse and watch the top 100 AOL Music Videos without having to access their web site. The player provides typical functions including playlisting, favoriting, sending to friend, embedding.
1. Video player on the left. On the right are mosaic of headshots to browse artists and search box.2. Playlist mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oranges Contact Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/oranges-contact-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/oranges-contact-form/</guid>
      <description>Edward Pistachio is a writer pulping fine short stories. Consistent with the lighthearted tone of this site, he provides a contact form that is also all about words. Getting his email address requires solving a few jumbles, and then decoding the address from letters found in the jumbles. Sure it may be frustrating if you can&#39;t figure out the jumbles, and is one of the cleverest ways I&#39;ve ever seen to gain access to a bit of info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kayak Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kayak-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kayak-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Kayak provided one of the earliest examples of using AJAX to provide data filtering controls and live refinement or filtering of results. Their slider controls remain one of the best examples of how AJAX can be used to make filtering visual and intuitive. Sliders allow users to narrow down search criteria including flight duration, takeoff/landing time, and price. 1. Default filtering controls.2. Search results page.3. Search results after adjusting search filters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roost Filtering</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/roost-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/roost-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Roost is a real estate search engine that provides full MLS listings. Their AJAX search refining filters are very similar to those provided by Kayak&#39;s travel search. The slider controls provide a visual method for narrowing down search criteria and results are updated immediately.
1. Default filtering controls.2. Search results page.3. Search results after adjusting search filters. http://roost.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moody Tags</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moody-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/moody-tags/</guid>
      <description>Moody provides a visual tagging interface for music played on iTunes. A 4 x 4 grid of colored squares provides the clickable UI for describing the mood of music tracks along the vertical axis as calm to intense, and along the horizontal axis as sad to happy. Great concept and quite easy to get after a few tries. With tracks tagged by mood, you can later play them back by selecting clicking the listen tab, and selecting as few or many moods as you would like, and finally click play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nike Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/nike-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>The Nike Store provides an excellent faceted navigation for narrowing product listings by sensible facets including gender, product type, sport, color, and price. The site skins the faceted classification tool provided by Endeca, which allows the user to select a product attribute of interest under any facet, and continually provides feedback about the attributes in other facets that can be used to narrow your choice of products down. Nike&#39;s Flash-based implementation is appropriate and useful, and ranks among the best examples of faceted navigation you will find on either commercial or academic databases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaltura Video Editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kaltura-video-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/kaltura-video-editor/</guid>
      <description>Kaltura&#39;s Flash / Flex video editor mimicks a full-featured video editor like iMovie. The company&#39;s product allows its users to add video to a collaboratively created work. The editor features nearly all of the features you would expect from a video editor, but delivers the entire interface via the web. Features include organizing clips from a media library, adding titles, transitions, and special effects, and adding and controlling soundtrack and volume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancast Rating (Hulu Player)</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/fancast-rating-hulu-player/</guid>
      <description>The Fancast experience for the Hulu video player provides a customized rating widget that differs from the straight-forward star rating on Hulu. Users select a text value that gets converted to stars.
1. Button in lower right prompts user to rate the video2. Clicking the button displays scale as text values3. Value selected by user is converted to star rating scale http://fancast.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TED Ratings</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ted-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/ted-ratings/</guid>
      <description>I was a bit confused the first time I saw this rating interface, and have to admit that I ignored it for months. The thing that threw me was the multiple checkboxes offered for each value. But I came back and realized that what this was doing was giving you a pre-defined set of tags which it was then using to create a filtering mechanism for the site. I appreciate that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tubetorial Form Labels</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tubetorial-form-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/tubetorial-form-labels/</guid>
      <description>By flipping the convention of labels on top or to the left of the inputs, Tubetorial provides a nicely aligned solution. We&#39;re accustomed to reading top to bottom and left to right, so it&#39;s a bit strange to have the label and input reversed this way. This works mainly because there are few inputs in a compressed area, but this might not be as efficient on large forms. 1. Comment form input with labels on right http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WEB2RSS Form Labels</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/web2rss-form-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/web2rss-form-labels/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s interesting placing the label inside the input. The form fields align nicely, but I imagine the alignment of the actual text you enter wouldn&#39;t work as well with multiple inputs. Since there is only one text input here, this works to some degree.
1. Label is shown inside form input http://baekdal.com/web2rss</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Explore Related Videos</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-explore-related-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/youtube-explore-related-videos/</guid>
      <description>YouTube&#39;s exploring functionality in the full-screen video player allows users to directed exploration of related videos.
1) Clicking the explore button in the lower left brings up related videos visualization, which is sort of like a digraph that looks like a constellation of stars. 2) Circles in the center are videos. Hover over one circle expands to show you other videos related to that one, forming a cluster. Click a circle to watch a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iStockPhoto Tags</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/istockphoto-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/istockphoto-tags/</guid>
      <description>iStockPhoto provides an interesting way of mapping keywords or tags to the controlled vocabulary the site uses. This makes a lot of sense in a site that wants people to be able to browse for concepts, themes, and subject matter with a high degree of relevancy. Curiously, they refer to the keywords as tags on the review screen when the term &#34;tag&#34; isn&#39;t used on the site as of this writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Faceted Navigation</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-faceted-navigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-faceted-navigation/</guid>
      <description>Hulu provides a nice faceted approach for browsing clips and episodes.
1. Filtering navigation in left sidebar2. All facets exposed; &amp;quot;Clip&amp;quot; selected under Type facet3. &amp;quot;Comedy&amp;quot; selected under genre facet; Selecting &amp;quot;show more&amp;quot; expands to show other choices under facet4. &amp;quot;NBC&amp;quot; selected under Source facet http://hulu.com/videos/views/thumbs/all/clip/all/all/today/1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Hour Work Week Login Screen</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/4-hour-work-week-login-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/4-hour-work-week-login-screen/</guid>
      <description>The clever login screen for Tim Ferris&#39; book site uses words from the book or audiobook as the password for entering restricted areas of its resources section.
 http://fourhourworkweek.com/wms/login/login.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Registration and Login</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-registration-and-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/amazon-registration-and-login/</guid>
      <description>Amazon&#39;s login and registration screen is the standard by which other login screens are measured. The simple flow consists of: 1) entering your email address, and 2) entering your password. If you are a new customer, simply select the new customer radio and the follow up screens provide the registration flow.
1. Enter your email address, if you&#39;re not registered, select &amp;quot;New customer,&amp;quot; otherwise log in2. Enter registration info https://amazon.com/gp/sign-in.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/basecamp-registration/</guid>
      <description>Starting off from Basecamp&#39;s sign up page, you pick your plan option, then fill out their form. The form is clean and simple. Inputs and labels are aligned well and there is a logical chunking of sections of the form. I like the simple hairlines between chunks in the top area.
One of the nicest things about this entire experience is the starting point where you select your plan. The user may return to this page at any point to upgrade, downgrade or cancel their plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digg Captcha</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-captcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/digg-captcha/</guid>
      <description>Digg&#39;s captcha input has nice conversational labels. Sadly they&#39;ve redesigned the registration form so that the nicely chunked form areas all flow into one block.
 http://digg.com/register/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/google-registration/</guid>
      <description>A quick and simple registration form that&#39;s compressed into a small area. The labels could be right-aligned for better readability in that 2 column format and the submit button could be aligned left with the inputs to really clean this up.
 https://google.com/accounts/NewAccount?service=mail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hulu Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/hulu-registration/</guid>
      <description>Simple registration form. No captcha in this form, although that could change when they get out of private beta. Having to click the check button seems unnecessary. A javascript check on blur would be better. This form might benefit from a little chunking, e.g. simple hairlines between some fields.  http://hulu.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/netflix-registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration at Netflix is a multi-page funnel. Form fields are laid out very well, and the flow is pretty simple considering the huge amount of text that surrounds the form. After entering your info, you can begin entering your genre preferences or search for videos to start adding to your queue. 1. Enter email address and password2. Select plan option3. Enter name and shipping info4. Enter payment info http://netflix.com/Register</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photobucket Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photobucket-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/photobucket-registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration couldn&#39;t be simpler. 3 fields: enter a username and password twice and you&#39;re done. No captchas. Oops, is that screenname unavailable, well let&#39;s get alerted right away before you go on. Nice.
1. Enter username, AJAX error check and suggestions if username unavailable2. Enter password http://photobucket.com/register.php</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sidebar Creative Contact Form</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sidebar-creative-contact-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/sidebar-creative-contact-form/</guid>
      <description>The contact page for this design agency features a clever use of an AJAX slider to allow potential clients to for entering their budget in the range of 10K to 500K. Interesting that the slider increments in 25K&#39;s up to 100K, then increments in 100K&#39;s. Once you get them on the phone, I suppose you can give them your real budget. Maybe that helps eliminate small jobs?
 http://sidebarcreative.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! Registration</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/interfaces/yahoo-registration/</guid>
      <description>We happened to catch the Yahoo! registration pages when they were being redesigned in 2007. The first version was captured in November 2007 and the second is the prior version. The redesigned version is subtle, but really improves the user&#39;s flow through the form. It compresses the vertical height of the form and uses more conversational labels.
1. Registration screen2. Old registration screen prior to Fall 2007 https://edit.yahoo.com/registration</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>