<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>services on Konigi</title>
    <link>http://konigi.com/tags/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in services on Konigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notable: Website design feedback </title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/notable-website-design-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/notable-website-design-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Notable is a commercial service that allows teams to screen capture web pages, and gather feedback by placing annotations and markers on the screens.
http://www.notableapp.com/home</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typekit: Foundry-Approved Font Embedding</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/typekit-foundry-approved-font-embedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/typekit-foundry-approved-font-embedding/</guid>
      <description>Jeff Veen announces Typekit, a solution for providing foundry-approved font embedding on the web. More info below from the Typkekit blog.
We’ve been working with foundries to develop a consistent web-only font linking license. We’ve built a technology platform that lets us to host both free and commercial fonts in a way that is incredibly fast, smoothes out differences in how browsers handle type, and offers the level of protection that type designers need without resorting to annoying and ineffective DRM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Whiteboarding with Twiddla</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/team-whiteboarding-twiddla/</guid>
      <description>Twiddla is an easy to use collaborative whiteboard service, but it&#39;s really got the potential to be much more. The whiteboard lets you mark up websites and graphics, and even use a drag-drop library of interface elements for working on interface concepts collaboratively. You communicate with others in the meeting with the chat window, and you can also use built in audio-conferencing capabilities. Very impressive, and free. Would make sense for there to be options for private meetings as well as embedding the whiteboard into your CMS or intranet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feng-GUI:  Feng Shui for Graphic User Interfaces?</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/feng-gui-feng-shui-graphic-user-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/feng-gui-feng-shui-graphic-user-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>This is an interesting idea in principle. Feng-GUI helps you find out how people see your website, photo or ad and which areas are getting most of the attention. Feng-GUI simulates human vision during the first 5 seconds of exposure to visuals,
and creates heatmaps based on an algorithm that predicts what a real human would be most likely to look at.
This offers designers, advertisers and creatives, a Pre-testing technology that predicts performance of an image, by analyzing levels of attention, brand effectiveness and placement, as well as breaking down the Flow of Attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prezi: The zooming presentation editor</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/prezi-zooming-presentation-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/prezi-zooming-presentation-editor/</guid>
      <description>Prezi is an interesting web app that allows users to create Flash-based Zoomable/Pannable presentations. The interface brings up a presentation editor with a keyboard command, and displays a radial menu for placing media objects, drawing paths for prev/next animation, etc. The finished presentation allows users to step through the &#34;slides&#34; as the canvas zooms and pans. It really might be a nice service for doing things like simple product screencasts, for instance, and hopefully the finished product will allow you to export your work for embedding on your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPlotz Wireframing Service</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/iplotz-wireframing-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/iplotz-wireframing-service/</guid>
      <description>iPlotz is another new product offering web-based services for wireframing, mockup, and prototyping of websites and applications. This service allows users to create multiple projects, wireframe them with sketch-style editable components, generate images or PDFs of the wireframes, manage tasks associated with screens, and solicit comments from team members.
http://www.iplotz.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tabbloid Delivers Your RSS Feeds as a Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/tabbloid-delivers-your-rss-feeds-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/tabbloid-delivers-your-rss-feeds-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Tabbloid sat in my tabs for a little while, because really, how interesting can yet another RSS reader be? But now that I&#39;ve tried it, I have to say that I&#39;m pretty happy with the idea of having this pushed to me for those times when I&#39;d rather read blog updates without my Google Reader. Tablloid turns your feeds into a cleanly designed personal magazine, and delivers a PDF to you, with links intact, at an interval you set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Action Method Online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/action-method-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/action-method-online/</guid>
      <description>Behance introduces Action Method Online, a web-based sister to the Action Method paper products that help creatives track and hit action items, and stay productive. Nice.
http://www.actionmethod.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>280 Slides - Create &amp; Share Presentations Online</title>
      <link>http://konigi.com/blog/280-slides-create-share-presentations-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://konigi.com/blog/280-slides-create-share-presentations-online/</guid>
      <description>280 Slides is a service that lets you create presentations online in a Keynote-like interface, and then share them, download them to PowerPoint, and present them online.
http://280slides.com/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
