<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>design critique on Konigi</title><link>http://konigi.com/tags/design-critique/</link><description>Recent content in design critique on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:48:16 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://konigi.com/tags/design-critique/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Design Critique on a Remote Team</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/design-critique-remote-team/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:48:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/design-critique-remote-team/</guid><description>Tips for running remote design critique.</description></item><item><title>Relay.io Design Sharing via Slack</title><link>http://konigi.com/links/relay-io-design-sharing-via-slack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/links/relay-io-design-sharing-via-slack/</guid><description>Relay looks like it&amp;rsquo;ll be a nice design communication tool for teams using Slack. Capture screens directly from Adobe CC, Sketch, Chrome, or anything else on your screen and it&amp;rsquo;ll be ready for critique in Slack, with comments and annotation.
(Hatip Leon)</description></item><item><title>How to give constructive design feedback over email</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/how-give-constructive-design-feedback-over-email/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/how-give-constructive-design-feedback-over-email/</guid><description>I can't imagine email ever being the right way to critique design, or give feedback as a client, but nevertheless it happens, and Julius Tarng, who works on the Branch app, came up with some good advice for those about to give email, and those about to receive it. I think the advice applies for any feedback that's not face to face to face including chat and in comments.</description></item><item><title>Dear Designer, You Suck</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/dear-designer-you-suck/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/dear-designer-you-suck/</guid><description>Khoi Vinh wrote an entry on taking the need for criticism inside the studio, and extending that openness in engaging in critical dialogue to discussion with peers outside of your working groups.
Like it or not, you can’t have a serious discourse about an art form until you have people whose sole involvement in that art form is criticism. You need, in effect, an independent press. Actually, to be clear, what you need is an economic model that can support a corps of passionate, clear-thinking individuals who are dedicated to vigilantly watching over the progression of the medium.</description></item><item><title>What Goes into a Well-Done Critique</title><link>http://konigi.com/blog/what-goes-well-done-critique/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://konigi.com/blog/what-goes-well-done-critique/</guid><description>Jared Spool writes an excellent article describing how to give a good design critique. A well-done critique is a way to step away from the specifics of the design process and better understand how to create great designs. We do this by starting with the current design and asking "What is it we're really trying to do here?" and "How close are we to doing it?"
The design crit is one of the most valuable parts of the design process to me.</description></item></channel></rss>