<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>templates on Konigi</title><link>https://konigi.com/tags/templates/</link><description>Recent content in templates on Konigi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://konigi.com/tags/templates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Form design guidelines crib sheet</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/form-design-guidelines-crib-sheet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/form-design-guidelines-crib-sheet/</guid><description>These form design crib sheets provide examples for laying out forms to get users through the process efficiently. Created by Joe Leech at cxpartners, and available for OmniGraffle, Photoshop, or in PDF vector format.
Via @theresaneil
http://www.cxpartners.co.uk/cxinsights/form_design_guidelines_crib_sheet_free.htm</description></item><item><title>Android Interaction Design Patterns</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/android-interaction-design-patterns/</guid><description>Android Patterns is a community-contributed site with interaction patterns for Android app design. The site is created by the folks at Dutch interaction design firm, UNITiD, who also provide an mobile wireframe templates for Android and Blackberry devices.
http://www.androidpatterns.com/wiki</description></item><item><title>960 grid template for OmniGraffle</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/960-grid-template-omnigraffle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/960-grid-template-omnigraffle/</guid><description>I’m a big fan of increasing efficiency and consistency from conceptual design to implementation. This OmniGraffle template has helped me quite a bit in that regard, and I decided to share it with others.
http://briancray.com/2009/11/30/omnigraffle-wireframing-960-grid-template/</description></item><item><title>Content Templates to the Rescue</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/content-templates-rescue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/content-templates-rescue/</guid><description>Erin Kissane writes about using content templates "... to help speed up the information-collection process, improve consistency across the website, and make the editing process easier and more orderly" in A List Apart.
The ideal situation is to have a content strategist, perhaps a technical writer, who can provide the guidance for auditing and organizing information, and add some rigor to the writing process. The absence of a content strategist on a project necessitates at least dedicating one person to this task.</description></item><item><title>EightShapes Unify</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/eightshapes-unify/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/eightshapes-unify/</guid><description>EightShapes Unify is a collection of templates, libraries, and other assets that enable user experience designers to create more consistent, effective deliverables faster. The system utilizes the Adobe Creative Suite of products; primarily, Adobe InDesign is the key authoring tool.
http://unify.eightshapes.com/</description></item><item><title>Resume Template</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/resume-template/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/resume-template/</guid><description>Matt Brown of thingsthatarebrown.com offers a free, simple, well-designed HTML resume template for those in need.
http://sampleresumetemplate.net/</description></item><item><title>Handbook of Usability Testing: Templates and Forms</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/handbook-usability-testing-templates-and-forms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/handbook-usability-testing-templates-and-forms/</guid><description>The Handbook of Usability Testing, by Jeffrey Rubin and Dana Chisnell, describes how to plan, design, and conduct effective tests. The books site includes a downloads page with templates and examples of usability test plans, questionairres, test scripts, and consent forms.
http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/WileyTitle/productCd-0470185481,descCd-DOWNLOAD.html</description></item><item><title>Usability.gov Templates &amp; Examples</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/usabilitygov-templates-examples/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/usabilitygov-templates-examples/</guid><description>Usability.gov has a very comprehensive set of templates, forms, and examples that are organized by steps in the usability process: Plan, Analyze, Design, Test and Refine. They can be customized for your organization's usability needs. All of these are in the public domain and can be freely downloaded.
Among the most useful of the files you'll find in this collection are commonly used usability test plan templates, waivers and consent forms.</description></item><item><title>zef[a]media UX Templates</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/zefamedia-ux-templates/</guid><description>zef[a]media's UX Template package contains sample paper prototypes/wireframes, personas, sitemaps, and user flow diagrams. Requires MS Visio, Word, and Excel.
http://www.zefamedia.com/websites/free-ux-templates/</description></item><item><title>Web Browser Templates (Photoshop)</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/web-browser-templates-photoshop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/web-browser-templates-photoshop/</guid><description>An Adobe Photoshop .PSD template with Internet Explorer, Firefox for Mac, and Firefox for Windows browser chrome. Provides a layered PSD of browser windows at the following resolutions: 800×600 pixels, 1024×768 pixels, and 1280×1024 pixels.
http://www.junglejar.com/2009/02/01/browser-templates-webdesign-webapplications/</description></item><item><title>Schedule and Cost Summary Calculator</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/schedule-and-cost-summary-calculator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/schedule-and-cost-summary-calculator/</guid><description>About this template This Cost Estimate and Scheduling spreadsheet provides a lightweight method for learning to estimate time to complete a web design project, and calculating cost for completion. The intended audience is individual freelancers or contractors who need to prepare proposals for potential clients. This may not be an ideal format for the calculation of project team estimates. The purpose of the document is to teach you to get acquainted with spreadsheets as tools for cost estimation, with the hopes that you will learn to use and modify it to suit your needs.</description></item><item><title>Todd Warfel's Persona Templates</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/todd-warfels-persona-templates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/todd-warfels-persona-templates/</guid><description>Todd Warfel has posted templates for his data-driven personas. The main file is an InDesign (INDD) file and the visual chart is in Illustrator file. Both are made with CS4.
http://zakiwarfel.com/archives/persona-templates/</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils</title><link>https://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/blog/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</guid><description>About This is a set of shapes for making wireframe in OmniGraffle 5 Pro or OmniGraffle 6 (Mac OS X). It consists of most of the basic elements you'll need to create user interface specifications. No Installation! The stencils ship with OmniGraffle! Find them in the Software category. To download them anyway, get the file and open it, when it appears click the Install button.
Download Download Version 3.</description></item><item><title>OmniGraffle Wireframe Stencils [Archived]</title><link>https://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/tools/omnigraffle-wireframe-stencils/</guid><description>About This is a set of shapes for making wireframe in OmniGraffle 5 Pro or OmniGraffle 6 (Mac OS X). It consists of most of the basic elements you'll need to create user interface specifications. No Installation Required! The stencils ship with OmniGraffle! Find them in the Software category. To download them anyway, get the file and open it, when it appears click the Install button.
Download Download Version 3.</description></item><item><title>STC Usability Toolkit</title><link>https://konigi.com/links/stc-usability-toolkit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://konigi.com/links/stc-usability-toolkit/</guid><description>The STC Usability Toolkit is a resource I've borrowed from over the years and continue to find myself back at fro time to time. The toolkit is a collection of forms, checklists and other useful documents for conducting usability tests and user interviews. http://www.stcsig.org/usability/resources/toolkit/toolkit.html</description></item></channel></rss>